1. My Martial Arts Can Cultivate Themselves!

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, after observing the Moonlit Giant Whale painting, has comprehended the essence of the giant whale, accelerating your cultivation speed by 50%."

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, after one day of arduous cultivation, has achieved 100% progress, automatically breaking through to the fourth level of Body Refining!"

Upon awakening, Lin Fei heard the voice in his mind. As the voice faded, Lin Fei's body crackled and popped. He felt his entire body's vitality expand considerably.

His strength had increased by a significant margin. These were clear signs of reaching the fourth level of Body Refining.

Lin Fei was overjoyed.

Three days ago, Lin Fei acquired this system. Unexpectedly, the system could let his martial arts cultivate themselves automatically. This was unheard of!

"System panel."

Lin Fei immediately summoned the system panel to check.

Host: Lin Fei

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fourth Level (1% Progress)

The system panel was quite simple. It was because that Lin Fei's martial arts were limited to just this technique.

This was the rule of the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei was an outer disciple of the Nine Profound Sect.

According to the sect's rules, before reaching the fourth level of Body Refining, those who entered the Nine Profound Sect could only practice one Body Refining martial art.

Previously, Lin Fei had only been at the third level of Body Refining. Therefore, he could not practice other martial arts.

According to the Nine Profound Sect's rules, within three years as a beginner, one must reach the fourth level of Body Refining. Otherwise, they would be expelled from the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei had only one month left before the three-year deadline. Fortunately, he got the system. Otherwise, in just one month, he definitely would not have been able to reach the fourth level of Body Refining. The ultimate consequence would be expulsion from the Nine Profound Sect, bringing shame to his family.

Upon reaching the fourth level of Body Refining, Lin Fei naturally wanted to learn other martial arts.

After all, the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique could only enhance his physical prowess. It was not a combat martial art.

He still needed to learn some combat martial arts to protect himself.

Luckily, the Nine Profound Sect had a rule that after reaching the fourth level of Body Refining, one could select three martial arts from the Martial Arts Pavilion for free.

Thus, Lin Fei headed out directly. He first went to the Transmission Hall.

Having reached the fourth level of Body Refining, he needed to get certified at the Transmission Hall.

Only after obtaining the certification from the Transmission Hall could he obtain three free martial arts from the Martial Arts Pavilion.

At the Transmission Hall, not many disciples came for certification.

In the Nine Profound Sect, only those at the fourth level of Body Refining, the seventh level of Body Refining, and the acquired realm would come for certification.

The fourth level of Body Refining was the foundation for staying in the Nine Profound Sect. Only those who had reached this level could remain in the sect without worrying about being expelled.

The seventh level of Body Refining was also crucial. If one reached the seventh level of Body Refining before the age of twenty, they could become an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect.

After all, reaching the seventh level of Body Refining before twenty meant that one had the potential to become an acquired realm expert.

If the disciples reached the acquired realm, their status in the Nine Profound Sect would rise dramatically, and they could even participate in many important matters of the sect.

"Elder, outer disciple Lin Fei has reached the fourth level of Body Refining today and has come for certification," Lin Fei respectfully said to the Transmission Elder.

"Stretch out your hand."

Lin Fei respectfully extended his hand. The Transmission Elder then sent his inner power into Lin Fei. A warm current swiftly entered Lin Fei's body, circulating throughout his entire body.

This was inner power! The hallmark of an acquired realm expert.

Acquired realm experts were called acquired because they had cultivated inner power.

Lin Fei was envious.

Before, his greatest dream was to become an acquired realm expert and bring glory to his ancestors.

The Transmission Elder opened his eyes and nodded, "Not bad, your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has indeed reached the fourth level. Your foundation is quite solid, and there is hope for reaching the seventh level of Body Refining in the future."

"Thank you, Elder."

"Alright, bring out your token, and I will give you a new one. With this token, you can go to the Martial Arts Pavilion and claim three free martial arts."

"Disciple understands."

Lin Fei received his new token, overjoyed. So, Lin Fei took his token and left the Transmission Hall directly.

The Nine Profound Sect was vast. The Martial Arts Pavilion and the Transmission Hall were quite far apart.

Lin Fei briskly walked for a long time before reaching the Martial Arts Pavilion.

The Martial Arts Pavilion was much livelier. Many disciples were present. After all, the Martial Arts Pavilion housed many martial arts. It was one of the most popular places in the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei entered the Martial Arts Pavilion and showed his token to the Martial Arts Pavilion Elder.

The Martial Arts Pavilion Elder was an old man with a wine gourd hanging from his waist and white hair and beard, who looked like a wise and experienced expert.

Lin Fei tried asking, "Elder, what kind of wine do you like? I can find some for you."

The Martial Arts Pavilion Elder didn't even raise his eyes, speaking in a hoarse voice, "The first floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion houses Body Refining martial arts, the second floor houses acquired martial arts, and the third floor houses innate martial arts.

You're only at the fourth level of Body Refining, so you can only choose martial arts from the first floor. Once you've made your selection, come back to me, and I'll provide you with the martial arts content. You can only practice in the corresponding training rooms for a maximum of one hour.

Beyond one hour, you'll have to pay. At the fourth level of Body Refining, you can choose three martial arts for free.

By the way, don't try to get on my good side. This old man is at the third level of the acquired realm, with no potential left. I'm neither a hidden expert nor do I possess any peerless martial arts manuals. There's no need for you to waste your time trying to please me."

"Uh... thank you, Elder."

Lin Fei felt a bit embarrassed.

According to rumors, those who guarded places like the library pavilion were either venerable elders of the sect or experts possessing hidden, peerless martial arts manuals.

It seemed this old man was neither. He was just an ordinary acquired realm elder. Moreover, most likely, other disciples were just like Lin Fei, trying to please this Martial Arts Pavilion Elder.

After paying his respects, Lin Fei directly entered the first floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion.

2. Selecting Martial Arts

The first floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion was quite crowded with disciples.

They were all Body Refining disciples. Some were just beginners with a basic understanding of martial arts. Others, like Lin Fei, had broken through to the fourth level of Body Refining.

There were also disciples above the seventh level of Body Refining, likewise choosing martial arts in the Martial Arts Pavilion.

After all, sometimes while practicing martial arts, one might feel that something is off. It might be necessary to make a change.

Body Refining martial arts, in the end, were meant to temper the body. So, they could be changed at any time.

But once one reached the acquired realm and practiced acquired martial arts, which could cultivate inner power, that would be different. Martial arts would not be changed so easily.

But during the Body Refining stage, there was no such worry, and one could change as desired. The only trouble might be all previous efforts were in vain after changing Body Refining martial arts.

Lin Fei did not intend to change his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique. This Body Refining martial art had quite a good refining effect.

What Lin Fei sought was combat martial arts.

"In the Body Refining stage, weapons can play a significant role. So, it's best to choose a martial art that uses weapons."

With a clear goal in mind, Lin Fei began selecting from the martial arts available in the Martial Arts Pavilion.

According to Lin Fei's thinking, he had a system, martial arts could practice on their own. So naturally, he would choose the most powerful martial arts.

As for whether the martial arts were difficult to practice, what did that have to do with him? A mature martial art should be able to cultivate on its own.

Among a bunch of weapon techniques, Lin Fei chose a saber technique called Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

The reason for specifically choosing a saber technique was because among the many options, the Nine Shadow Saber Technique was the only weapon technique which had the fastest speed.

The Nine Shadow Saber Technique had no other fancy features. It only pursued speed. The ultimate speed!

In Lin Fei's memory, there was the saying, "In the world of martial arts, only speed is unbeatable."

Therefore, seeing the Nine Shadow Saber Technique's pursuit of ultimate speed, He naturally chose it.

Of course, Lin Fei had only chosen this saber technique. The specific content of the saber technique was still in the hands of the Martial Arts Pavilion Elder.

Lin Fei was not in a hurry. Since he could choose three martial arts, He wanted to make full use of them.

He couldn't waste the opportunity.

"The Nine Shadow Saber Technique is already formidable enough; choosing another weapon skill would be meaningless. But in the world of martial arts, anything can happen. What if one day, I don't have a weapon? Hand-to-hand combat becomes crucial. So, I must choose a hand-to-hand martial art."

Lin Fei found himself in front of the bookshelf containing hand-to-hand martial arts. The sheer number of hand-to-hand martial arts was overwhelming. With a dazzling array of choices, it was challenging to decide.

Finally, Lin Fei spotted the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist. The name itself sounded powerful.

Lin Fei chose this martial art because of its distinct characteristics. Moreover, it was a martial art that could grow.

The Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist required immense strength to unleash its full power. The greater the strength, the more powerful the fist technique.

If wielded by someone with innate divine strength, it could even kill an acquired expert! Of course, if one lacked strength, the technique would be useless.

Lin Fei's body refining method, the Giant Whale Technique, focused on cultivating blood and qi. His vast blood and qi granted him significant strength.

Practicing the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was fitting.

"Wait, the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique emphasizes blood and qi. But the body isn't just about blood and qi. There's also the skin membrane and muscles and bones. My martial arts can be self-cultivated. So why not train the skin membrane, muscles, and bones together? Doing so would make me even stronger!"

Lin Fei's eyes lit up. He thought of his advantage. That was not fearing how difficult a martial art could be but fearing that the martial art was not comprehensive enough.

Typical body refining martial arts have a focus. For instance, some emphasize blood and qi, while others focus on the skin membrane or muscles and bones.

In reality, they were all the same. Focusing on one aspect allowed faster progress to the ninth level of body refining. This then led to breaking through to the acquired realm and cultivating acquired martial arts to harness inner power. Therefore, being well-rounded during the body refining stage is not crucial.

Of course, the main reason is that most people have limited energy. If cultivated together, progress would be slowed. Breaking through to the acquired realm would become a luxury.

Lin Fei promptly chose a martial art for refining the skin membrane and another for training muscles and bones.

These were the Vajra Iron Cloth and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique.

The Vajra Iron Cloth differed from ordinary Iron Cloth techniques in its extremity.

An ordinary Iron Cloth technique would make the skin membrane tough like cowhide but with vulnerable points. But after mastering Vajra Iron Cloth, there would be no weaknesses.

The only difference was its difficulty.

The Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique was the most potent martial art for training muscles and bones. And it had no equal.

However, this martial art was said to incorporate certain theories from Daoism and Buddhism. Without a deep understanding of both Daoist and Buddhist principles, even beginners would struggle.

Lin Fei chose these martial arts and approached the elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion.

"Nine Shadow Saber Technique, Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist, Vajra Iron Cloth, and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique. Four martial arts in total, but you can only choose three for free. You'll have to leave one martial art behind."

The Martial Arts Pavilion elder shook his head.

Lin Fei couldn't help but ask, "Elder, is there any way I can have all four?"

"Of course, just pay more! All martial arts can be exchanged with contribution points. These four martial arts each cost a thousand contribution points."

"But I don't have any contribution points."

Before, Lin Fei wasn't even at the fourth level of Body Refining, so he couldn't go out and earn contribution points.

"That makes it even simpler; if you don't have contribution points, just pay money. One tael of silver can be exchanged for one contribution point. A thousand contribution points would be a thousand taels of silver."

"Uh..."

The price seemed a bit steep. But Lin Fei thought about it. He was born into a merchant family, and his monthly allowance was substantial. A thousand taels—he could afford it.

"Fine, I'll pay the extra. Here's a silver bill for a thousand taels."

Lin Fei gritted his teeth and chose to pay.

3. Martial Arts With Personality

"Not bad, the youngster is teachable!" The Martial Arts Pavilion elder collected the banknote with a satisfied expression on his face.

Lin Fei received a token for a training room. He chose four martial arts, so he could stay in the training room for up to four hours. After all, the martial arts manuals couldn't be taken away.

"The martial arts manuals must be returned in their original state after a maximum of four hours. Moreover, you must not divulge our sect's martial arts without permission. Otherwise, the Nine Profound Sect's pursuit order will show no mercy."

"Yes, elder, I understand."

Lin Fei took the four martial arts manuals and entered the training room. Inside the training room, Lin Fei lined up the manuals.

The four hours were not meant for actual training. After all, the time was too short. Even with training, how far could one progress?

These four hours were for memorizing the manuals. However, Lin Fei was different. He didn't need to memorize them at all. He only needed to get started with these martial arts.

Once he did, the martial arts would cultivate themselves. So, Lin Fei began practicing Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist. Following the moves in the manual, he performed the technique once.

"Your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist is dissatisfied with your weak aura. The cultivation effect is reduced by 50%, and the progress reaches 1%."

"Uh..."

This was the first time Lin Fei encountered such a situation. It seemed that the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had quite a personality.

"System."

Lin Fei checked the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fourth Level (1% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Beginner (1% Progress)

Lin Fei saw that the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had appeared in the system panel. This meant that Lin Fei didn't have to worry about this martial art anymore.

Although martial art seemed to have quite a personality, Lin Fei would slowly explore how it would be in the future.

Now there were three more martial arts waiting for him to cultivate. So, Lin Fei continued practicing the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

"Using your palm instead of a saber has displeased the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. The cultivation effect is reduced by 80%, and the progress reaches 1%."

Lin Fei could only smile bitterly. It seemed that the Nine Shadow Saber Technique was as temperamental as the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

Lin Fei continued to practice Vajra Iron Cloth and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique.

"Your Vajra Iron Cloth is very satisfied with the host. The cultivation effect is increased by 50%, and the progress reaches 3%."

"Your Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique is very satisfied with the host. The cultivation effect is increased by 50%, and the progress reaches 5%."

Lin Fei received consecutive prompts. His Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique and Vajra Iron Cloth seemed to be progressing well.

Lin Fei thought about it. It was probably related to his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

His Giant Whale Body Refining Technique had reached the fourth level. With powerful Qi and blood, cultivating other Body Refining martial arts would have some beneficial effects to some extent. That's why these two Body Refining martial arts were cultivated so smoothly.

Lin Fei checked the time. Just two hours had passed. So, he left the training room directly and returned the four martial arts manuals to the Martial Arts Pavilion elder.

The Martial Arts Pavilion elder was surprised, "It's only been two hours. Have you memorized everything?"

"I've memorized them all. Thank you, elder."

"Heh, I didn't expect you to be quite clever. Alright, go ahead and leave."

After paying his respects, Lin Fei left the Martial Arts Pavilion directly.

That night, Lin Fei was a bit excited. With five martial arts at his side that could cultivate themselves, perhaps it wouldn't take long for him to reach the fifth level of Body Refining!

The next day, Lin Fei woke up early. Without the need to train hard, he felt refreshed naturally.

As soon as he woke up, he heard a series of voices in his ear.

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has made great progress after a day of hard work, and the progress has increased by 5%."

Lin Fei's eyes brightened. His mood instantly improved.

His Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was currently at the fourth level.

A 5% increase in one day meant that it would only take twenty days to reach 100% and advance to the fifth level.

Such speed was simply astonishing.

Of course, Lin Fei was well aware that this was because his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique had comprehended the profound meaning of the giant whale, otherwise, it wouldn't have cultivated so quickly.

"Your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was in high spirits last night. After a day of hard work, the cultivation progress has increased by 10%."

This was another piece of good news.

The Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was quite competitive.

Although it seemed a bit lackluster at the beginning yesterday, after a night had passed, the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had proven itself as a mature martial art. It could adjust its state on its own.

"Not bad, not bad. Keep it up." A smile appeared on Lin Fei's face.

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique, due to the lack of a saber, is in a low mood and has decided to take a day off. There is no progress in cultivation."

"Uh..."

The smile on Lin Fei's face froze. The Nine Shadow Saber Technique was not living up to expectations.

It hadn't cultivated at all last night!?

However, Lin Fei was also to blame. The Nine Shadow Saber Technique required a weapon, but he didn't have one. So, it made sense that the Nine Shadow Saber Technique hadn't cultivated.

It seemed that he needed to find a saber as soon as possible.

"Your Vajra Iron Cloth, due to not having soaked in a medicinal bath, is in a low mood and there is no progress in cultivation."

"Your Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique, due to not having listened to Buddhist or Taoist scriptures, is in a low mood and there is no progress in cultivation."

Three consecutive pieces of bad news left Lin Fei dumbfounded.

4. Saber Skill Improved

"System."

Lin Fei accessed the system panel to check the progress of each martial art.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Fourth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fourth Level (6% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Beginner (11% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Beginner (1% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: First Level (3% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: First Level (5% Progress)

Lin Fei looked at the martial arts progress on the system panel. He was currently only at the fourth level of Body Refining. But he had as many as five martial arts. Three of them were Body Refining martial arts, and two were combat martial arts.

Lin Fei discovered a problem. Indeed, his martial arts could cultivate themselves. However, the key was that these martial arts had their own personalities.

If their requirements were not met, they could "strike" and refuse to work. They could be lazy and not cultivate.

The Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was currently the most obedient, steadily cultivating almost every day. Like a model student, it was neither arrogant nor impatient, making steady progress.

The Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist's performance was also satisfactory for now. But how it would fare in the long run remained to be seen.

The Nine Shadow Saber Technique, Vajra Iron Cloth, and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique were a bit more problematic.

The Nine Shadow Saber Technique could be easily solved. Just buying a saber should be enough.

As for Vajra Iron Cloth, it required a medicinal bath?

Upon careful consideration, Lin Fei realized that it indeed needed a medicinal bath.

After all, this Vajra Iron Cloth was a type of horizontal hard martial art training. Without a medicinal bath to heal the body, it would break down due to practice.

This problem could also be solved, as long as he had money to afford the medicinal bath.

As for the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique, this was quite interesting.

It required listening to Buddhist and Taoist scriptures?

It sounded intriguing, but in order to make the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique cultivate properly, Lin Fei had no choice but to give it a try.

"Let's go buy a saber first."

Lin Fei got up and left the room. As soon as he stepped outside, he saw two familiar figures.

"Zhang Yuan, Liu Hu, what are you doing here?"

Lin Fei remembered these two people. Both were outer disciples of the Nine Profound Sect, just like Lin Fei. And they were good friends.

"Lin Fei."

Zhang Yuan said with a bitter smile, "Liu Hu and I are here to say goodbye to you."

"Goodbye?"

"Yes, we've been in the Nine Profound Sect for three years and have been stuck at the third level of Body Refining. Now that our three-year term is up, we've been expelled from the sect. So, we came to say goodbye."

Lin Fei was silent. He didn't know what to say.

"Brother Lin, I heard that you broke through to the fourth level of Body Refining yesterday. Congratulations, you can stay in the Nine Profound Sect."

"It was just a fluke. Zhang Yuan, Liu Hu, what are your plans after leaving the sect?" Lin Fei asked.

"I'm going back to inherit my family's business. As for Liu Hu, he's planning to go down the mountain and help me."

Zhang Yuan's family was in business. Liu Hu knew him very well and the two got along well. With Liu Hu's help, Zhang Yuan would have an extra pair of hands after leaving the mountain.

"Then I wish you both smooth sailing. If you need anything in the future, feel free to send me a letter."

Lin Fei considered it for a moment and made the promise. In his memory, both Zhang Yuan and Liu Hu had helped him a lot. They were his best friends in the entire Nine Profound Sect.

Now that his friends were leaving the sect, Lin Fei didn't mind helping them if he had the power to do so in the future.

"Thank you, Brother Lin."

Zhang Yuan was overjoyed. He and Liu Hu came to say goodbye just to wait for Lin Fei's promise.

After all, Lin Fei was still in the Nine Profound Sect.

In the future, he might reach the fifth, sixth, or even higher levels of Body Refining. By then, he could be a powerful ally.

With this promise, they were satisfied.

Looking at the desolate and forlorn figures of Zhang Yuan and Liu Hu, Lin Fei couldn't help but feel a little emotional.

In this world, power was supreme. Whether in business or anything else, without power, it was difficult to make progress.

Zhang Yuan and Liu Hu's departure from the mountain meant that they wouldn't achieve much in martial arts. Not to mention breaking through to the acquired realm, even reaching the seventh level of Body Refining was almost impossible.

Lin Fei felt a sense of urgency. He was relatively lucky. At a critical moment, he broke through to the fourth level of Body Refining and could stay in the Nine Profound Sect.

But the fourth level of Body Refining was nothing. He still needed to continue to improve.

Lin Fei entered the weapon hall directly. The weapons of the Nine Profound Sect could be purchased with contribution points. But Lin Fei had no contribution points.

Of course, silver could be used as well. However, it would be much more expensive that way. But Lin Fei had no choice at the moment.

Among the various weapons, Lin Fei chose a high-quality fine steel saber. Although it couldn't be considered a treasure saber, it was still very good.

This saber cost Lin Fei twenty taels of silver.

Lin Fei still needed some Buddhist scriptures and Taoist scriptures.

There was no other way, he had to go down the mountain to buy them.

And the medicinal bath. The medicinal bath required for Vajra Iron Cloth was extremely expensive.

Lin Fei used the remaining silver to purchase ten portions at once. Almost all of his silver was spent.

"Let's go back."

Lin Fei returned to his courtyard.

"Let's try the Nine Shadow Saber Technique."

Lin Fei took a deep breath. He began to perform the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Although Lin Fei's martial skills could be practiced autonomously, after practicing, Lin Fei could feel it as if he had experienced it himself. It was as if Lin Fei had painstakingly practiced the skill himself.

Lin Fei's Nine Shadow Saber Technique was at the beginner level. Thus, he could barely perform it.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei swung his saber.

Only a single white light flashed.

This was the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, pursuing the ultimate speed.

When one saber swing produced two shadows, it meant that the saber technique was proficient.

If one could swing the saber and produce three shadows, it would be mastery.

Producing six shadows meant transcendence.

To achieve perfection, one had to swing the saber and produce nine shadows.

But now, Lin Fei could only produce one shadow. He was merely a beginner.

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique has just acquired a treasure saber, its mood is excited, and its comprehension greatly increases. The progress of your Nine Shadow Saber Technique practice has increased by 100%, reaching the proficient realm."

A voice suddenly came into Lin Fei's mind.

"Already proficient?"

Lin Fei widened his eyes as if he couldn't believe it. But in the next moment, Lin Fei's mind was filled with various insights. It was as if his hands had the muscle memory of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Then, he swung his saber again.

"Shoo."

Two white lights flashed.

Two shadows!

This was indeed the characteristic of the proficient Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

General combat martial arts are divided into beginner, proficient, mastery, transcendence, perfection, and the realm of the divine.

For an ordinary martial artist, reaching mastery is already very good. Reaching transcendence is almost the limit.

As for perfection?

Basically, only special geniuses or the creators of martial art can achieve perfection.

And the realm of the divine?

That's another level.

Martial arts like the Nine Shadow Saber Technique place great emphasis on comprehension.

Reaching proficiency in one month is already very impressive.

But Lin Fei?

Just one day...

He didn't expect that the autonomous practice of these martial arts was so terrifying when he meet the conditions of them.

"Right, there's also Vajra Iron Cloth. Let's soak in the medicinal bath first and test its effects."

Seeing the rapid progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, Lin Fei naturally held high expectations for Vajra Iron Cloth as well.

5. Pick Up The Task

Lin Fei had a courtyard of his own. The reason why outer disciples were able to have courtyards was simple: wealth.

In Lin Fei's memory, his family should be considered wealthy merchants. Therefore, he was able to buy a courtyard at the Nine Profound Sect.

In the courtyard, Lin Fei heated water by himself. He poured the purchased medicinal herbs into the wooden barrel.

Lin Fei jumped directly into the barrel.

Immediately, Lin Fei felt as if all the pores in his body had opened. Warm currents flowed throughout his body, making him feel extremely comfortable.

"Your Vajra Iron Cloth has detected the nourishing medicinal bath and has begun to practice."

Lin Fei also felt that his skin was itchy and painful, and sometimes red spots would appear. This was due to the practice of Vajra Iron Cloth.

"Your Vajra Iron Cloth is in a great mood, and the practice speed is doubled."

"Your Vajra Iron Cloth has reached the second level."

"Splash."

Lin Fei stood up from the hot water barrel. He looked at the skin on his arm. It felt rough to the touch. But it was very tough.

"Vajra Iron Cloth has reached the second level just like that?"

Lin Fei couldn't help but smile. He had practiced the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique before. He knew very well how difficult it was to practice Body Refining martial arts. It took him two years to step into the second level of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

And now?

In just one day, his Vajra Iron Cloth had reached the second level.

Of course, this must be related to the abundant qi and blood of the Giant Whale Technique. But Vajra Iron Cloth itself was also quite impressive. The more unique the martial art, the more impressive it actually is.

It all depends on whether Lin Fei can satisfy all these martial arts. Only then will these martial arts "practice hard."

So, in the following days, Lin Fei worked hard to find ways to make the martial arts in his body "satisfied."

Lin Fei found that the most stable martial arts were the Giant Whale Technique and Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist. They could practice autonomously every day without doing anything else. Although they couldn't make huge progress all at once, their practice steadily improved.

Nine Shadow Saber Technique and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique were the quirkiest.

Without Buddhist scriptures or Taoist scriptures, Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique had almost no improvement.

Nine Shadow Saber Technique had improved to proficient since acquiring a saber.

But then it stopped again. It didn't improve any further. It seemed that this Nine Shadow Saber Technique valued "enlightenment" very much.

It was necessary to let the Nine Shadow Saber Technique gain more "enlightenment."

The Nine Profound Sect had some senior masters. They could impart some martial arts experience. However, this required contribution points.

If the contribution points were sufficient, one could even specifically ask a certain master for guidance.

Lin Fei felt that if he could invite a master of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique to give him guidance, his Nine Shadow Saber Technique would definitely make rapid progress.

Unfortunately, he didn't have any contribution points.

As for using silver?

Lin Fei didn't have enough silver now. He had almost used it all to practice martial arts and buy medicinal baths. A few days later, Lin Fei's medicinal baths were all consumed.

"System."

Lin Fei brought up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Fourth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fourth Level (31% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Beginner (61% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Proficient (1% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Third Level (16% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: First Level (5% Progress)

Among all of Lin Fei's martial arts, the most significant progress was made by Vajra Iron Cloth. It was served with a large number of medicinal baths every day, making it very comfortable. In just a few days, it had already reached the third layer.

However, after reaching the third layer, the progress slowed down. Most importantly, Lin Fei didn't have any more medicinal baths.

"No contribution points, no silver, no medicinal baths. If I continue to stay in the mountain, my martial arts progress will be slow in the future."

After weighing the situation for a moment, Lin Fei decided to leave the mountain. Staying in the mountain, his daily progress was limited. But if he went down the mountain, he could earn contribution points and even go home for silver. With resources, he could soar to new heights.

"So, should I go home for silver or go down the mountain to do missions and earn contribution points?"

Lin Fei preferred going down the mountain to take silver. Although it would be expensive to buy things within the sect with silver, doing missions would entail certain risks.

Lin Fei was still very weak now. There was no need to rush to take on missions and risk his life.

However, Lin Fei still went to the Mission Hall.

Lin Fei looked at the dazzling array of missions in the mission hall, his eyes shining slightly.

Most of the missions in the mission hall were to support certain places. Actually, these represented the power of the Nine Profound Sect.

The Nine Profound Sect was a martial arts sect, not a charitable organization. The sect occupied a vast territory and had branches and sub-divisions in various places to conduct business and other activities, thus obtaining numerous resources.

But where there were people, there were disputes. With disputes, fighting and killing would follow. These support missions could earn a large number of contribution points.

However, they were too dangerous.

Lin Fei felt that it was better for him to prioritize safety at his current stage.

"If there are no suitable missions, I'll go down the mountain first and get some silver. Using silver to exchange for contribution points is a loss, but at least it's safe. However, disciples below the seventh level of Body Refining are not allowed to go down the mountain easily unless they have a mission..."

Lin Fei felt a headache. He still needed to accept a mission.

Otherwise, even going down the mountain would be a luxury.

"Lu Mountain: Collect ten Black-Backed Centipedes. Time limit: two months."

When Lin Fei saw this mission, his eyes lit up.

"Isn't Lu Mountain the mountain range where Lu Mountain County is located? My Lin family's old home is in Lu Mountain County. Although we moved to the Zhou Mountain Mansion City after becoming wealthy, the city is not far from Lu Mountain.

Besides, this mission is just a collection mission, not a support mission, so it shouldn't be dangerous. However, these mere one hundred contribution points are really too few, but better than nothing."

After thinking for a moment, Lin Fei directly accepted the mission. To be more precise, he was going home to get some silver and complete this mission along the way.

6. Second Young Master Is Back

"Finally, I'm off the mountain."

Lin Fei wore the Nine Profound Sect disciple's attire, rode a swift horse, and carried a thick-backed great saber on his back. He looked like a typical martial artist.

The swift horse was rented from the Nine Profound Sect, and Lin Fei needed to return it once he was back.

Wearing the Nine Profound Sect disciple's attire also had its advantages. Within a few hundred miles around, the Nine Profound Sect was the undisputed dominant force. Neither the underworld nor the legitimate world would dare to provoke the Nine Profound Sect easily. Thus, dressed this way, Lin Fei could avoid many troubles.

Following the route from his memory, Lin Fei traveled along the official roads. Even if it meant taking more time, he preferred the main roads over shortcuts. The world was not too peaceful these days, and taking shortcuts could lead to encounters with bandits.

As it was Lin Fei's first time leaving the mountain, it was better to be cautious. During the day, he traveled on the official roads, and at night, he rested in inns located in large towns. Consequently, with such a cautious approach, nothing unexpected happened along the way.

Lin Fei quickly returned to Zhou Mountain Mansion City, where the Lin family resided as wealthy merchants. Soon, Lin Fei rushed straight to the Lin Mansion.

"Finally, I'm back."

Lin Fei looked at the Lin Mansion before him and finally breathed a sigh of relief. These days on the road, he had been anxious all along. Only upon returning home could he genuinely relax.

"You... Are you the Second Young Master?"

A servant of the Lin Mansion carefully examined Lin Fei and finally recognized him.

"Lin Shi Yi, what, you don't recognize this young master?"

Lin Fei said with a smile. This servant was a family servant who had grown up with Lin Fei. Of course, Lin Fei recognized him.

"Ah? It really is the Second Young Master! You... You're back?"

Lin Shi Yi was overjoyed. The servants of the Lin family immediately ran into the mansion, shouting loudly, "Master, Madam, Eldest Young Master, the Second Young Master has returned!"

"What? Lin Fei is back?"

"Is it Fei?"

In no time, Lin Fei's parents came rushing in after hearing the news.

Lin Fei arrived in the living room and saw his parents. His father looked somewhat plump and white, while his mother was dressed like a noblewoman.

Lin Fei knelt before his parents and respectfully saluted them, "Your unfilial son has returned to see you, father and mother."

Lin Fei's mother was teary-eyed, "It's been three years. Good, good, it's great that you're back."

However, Lin Fei's father seemed worried despite his happiness.

"Fei, you're finally back."

At that moment, a refined-looking young man entered the room, accompanied by a beautiful young woman.

"Big brother!" Lin Fei respectfully greeted him.

This refined young man was Lin Fei's older brother, Lin Wen, who was a few years older than him. Lin Wen helped their father manage the family business in the Lin Mansion.

"Who is this...?" Lin Fei couldn't help but ask about the young woman besides his brother.

"This is your sister-in-law."

"Nice to meet you, sister-in-law."

Lin Fei understood that she was his brother's wife.

"Big brother, when did you get married? Why didn't you send me a letter?"

Lin Fei was surprised, as his brother wasn't much older than him, yet he was already married.

Lin Fei's father cleared his throat, "Fei, you were cultivating diligently at the Nine Profound Sect, and we didn't want to disturb you. That's why we didn't tell you about your brother's wedding. Your brother got married just half a year ago. Your sister-in-law is the legitimate daughter of the Lu family."

Lin Fei nodded. Mr. Lu was a talented scholar who, after failing the imperial exams, turned to business. He was quite wealthy in Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

"Fei, I have a question for you. According to the rules of the Nine Profound Sect, if one does not meet the sect's requirements within three years, they will be expelled from the mountain. Now you have come down the mountain, is it because..."

As Lin Fei's father's voice trailed off, the atmosphere in the entire hall tightened.

This was a big deal!

The Nine Profound Sect was an undisputed powerhouse. In this world, where martial arts were revered, even the Prefecture Lord had to show respect to the Nine Profound Sect. Many matters in Zhou Mountain Mansion City even required the help of the Nine Profound Sect.

Staying in the Nine Profound Sect was of utmost importance to a wealthy merchant like the Lin family.

They had sent Lin Fei to the Nine Profound Sect with high hopes. If he were expelled from the sect, it would not bode well for the Lin family. Even his brother's smile seemed forced.

Only then did Lin Fei notice that in just three years, his brother seemed to have aged considerably. His eyes revealed a hint of fatigue.

"Father, big brother, has something happened to our family?" Instead of answering immediately, Lin Fei asked.

"Nothing major," his brother replied with a smile.

However, Lin Fei's father waved his hand and sat down in his chair with a sigh. He slowly said, "Wen, Fei is your younger brother. It's good that he has come down the mountain this time; he can help you with the family business. Fei, over these three years, my health and energy have declined significantly. As a result, I've gradually handed over the family business to your brother."

Lin Fei remained noncommittal, understanding his father's intention. This was a clear confirmation of his brother Lin Wen's position as the heir to the Lin Mansion.

7. The Dilemma Of The Lin Family

This arrangement had been decided long ago.

Lin Fei would learn martial arts, while Lin Wen would inherit the family business and manage it, providing resources for Lin Fei's cultivation.

"But in recent years, the world has become more chaotic, and bandits and thieves have emerged everywhere. Our Lin family has its own escort agency, but last year, Master Bai of the escort agency has been deteriorating in health and can no longer escort our goods.

Since then, our Lin family's caravan has faced troubles. Almost every time we go out, we suffer losses, sometimes even severe ones. Master Bai was a Body Refining fifth-level expert and had made quite a name for himself in both the underworld and the legitimate world.

Thus, with Master Bai as our escort, our Lin family's caravan usually encountered no issues. But now, there's no one in the escort agency capable of taking on such a responsibility.

As for hiring other Body Refining experts above the fourth level, firstly, we don't trust them, fearing they might seize our goods. Secondly, those unfamiliar fourth-level experts may not be able to deter the bandits along the way.

Over time, our Lin family's business has become increasingly difficult. Fortunately, Mr. Lu allied with our Lin family through marriage, and thanks to your sister-in-law's plea, Mr. Lu 's business now cooperates with ours, allowing the Lin family to barely stay afloat. But if this problem isn't solved, our Lin family will face even greater difficulties in the future."

Lin Fei saw his older brother unknowingly grip his sister-in-law's hand tightly. It was clear that despite their recent marriage, their feelings for each other ran deep. As it turned out, his sister-in-law had helped the Lin family so much.

"Big brother, with the family in such difficulties, why haven't my monthly allowances been reduced?"

Lin Fei received a thousand taels every month at the Nine Profound Sect. This was no small sum. Over the course of three years, it amounted to nearly forty thousand taels!

Given the Lin family's current situation, this money could alleviate their pressing needs.

His brother smiled slightly, "Second brother, your cultivation at the Nine Profound Sect carries the hopes of our entire family. Even if the family is struggling, your allowance won't be reduced!"

Lin Fei felt touched.

"Father, I understand what you're saying. Right now, the world is in chaos, and our Lin family's caravan dares not leave Zhou Mountain Mansion City easily.

In the past, with Master Bai of the escort agency, the situation was better. It might not be because of his strength, but rather because he had connections in both the underworld and the legitimate world after decades of experience. Therefore, some bandits would give face to Master Bai.

But now that Master Bai is unable to escort our goods personally, those bandits won't show us any mercy simply because of the escort agency's banner."

Lin's father nodded, "That's right. A single Body Refining expert at the fourth or fifth level can't achieve what Master Bai did, earning the respect of the bandits."

"Father, let's put this matter aside for now. I'll find a solution."

"You'll find a solution? Fei, you..."

Lin Fei no longer concealed anything and said straightforwardly, "Father, who said I was expelled from the mountain? I came down the mountain on my own to do a mission. Just a few days ago, I officially reached the fourth level of Body Refining and can now stay at the Nine Profound Sect."

"Ah? Is... is this true?"

Lin's father, mother, and older brother Lin Wen all showed a hint of surprise and delight on their faces.

"Of course, it's true. This is my identification plate..."

Lin Fei took out his Nine Profound Sect identification plate. On it was the certification of his Body Refining fourth level.

"Hahaha, Second Brother, I knew you could do it!"

His older brother couldn't help but laugh. During this time, he had been under immense pressure. The entire burden of the Lin family rested on his shoulders.

Now that Lin Fei had become a Body Refining fourth-level expert and an outer disciple of the Nine Profound Sect, Lin Wen felt more confident. No longer like before, when he was always cautious and treading on thin ice in everything he did. That feeling was truly unbearable.

Lin's father was overjoyed and had a feast prepared.

It wasn't until late that Lin Fei returned to his room.

"Phew..."

Lin Fei sighed deeply. Learning about the Lin family's current situation made him feel troubled. He had returned this time to complete a mission as a side task. His real purpose was to come back and get some money. But with the Lin family in such a state, how could he take any money?

"Knock, knock, knock."

Before Lin Fei could lie down, there was a knock at the door.

Lin Fei opened the door.

"Big brother? It's so late, you..."

Lin Fei was surprised.

Outside the door stood his older brother, Lin Wen.

Lin Wen patted Lin Fei's shoulder and handed him a stack of silver bills, "Second brother, here are thirty thousand taels in silver bills. Use them sparingly. With our parents and your sister-in-law present earlier, some things weren't convenient to say. I know that you martial artists consume a lot of resources. This amount may not be much, but it's all the Lin family can currently afford."

"Big brother, thirty thousand taels of silver bills, is the Lin family not doing business anymore?" Lin Fei was shocked.

"Don't be so alarmed. I definitely won't touch the money used for the family business. However, our father had his glorious years, and now that the family's wealth has been handed over to me, I sold some of the treasures he liked when he was young. Don't worry; it won't affect the family business."

"Big brother, this..."

Lin Fei was deeply touched. His older brother had taken care of him since childhood. Even though they had both grown up, their feelings for each other remained unchanged.

"Alright, don't be so sentimental. Go and rest. If you're truly touched, strive to become a Body Refining expert above the seventh level or even a stronger expert!

By then, just showing your reputation, who would dare to bully our Lin family? I, your older brother, will have more confidence in doing business."

After speaking, Lin Wen left.

8. The Enlightenment Of Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique

Back in his room, Lin Fei put the thirty thousand taels of silver bills into his pocket.

He wasn't being pretentious. Right now, he indeed needed this money. Being poor and practicing martial arts would be impossible.

Without this money, Lin Fei would have to take on some sect missions to earn contribution points. But those missions were quite dangerous.

One could lose their life if they weren't careful. He was still weak and didn't want to take such risks.

However, Lin Fei understood that the priority was to solve the Lin family's problems.

Otherwise, if the Lin family fell apart, he wouldn't even have the monthly allowance.

It would be even more difficult! His relationship with the Lin family was one of shared honor and disgrace.

"Old Master Bai could make the bandits show him respect. Of course, it's because of his decades of reputation. But how did that reputation come about? It was also built through fights and battles."

I am an outer disciple of the Nine Profound Sect, and I can use that status. But if I want those bandits to respect me, I still need to prove myself with real battles! However, my current strength is still lacking."

Lin Fei called up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Realm: Body Refining Fourth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fourth Level (51% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Proficient (1% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Proficient (1% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Third Level (16% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: First Level (5% Progress)

Lin Fei took four days to return to the Lin family from the Nine Profound Sect. Only his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique and Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had made some progress.

Among them, Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had reached the proficient level. As for the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, it had also surpassed 50% progress.

According to the daily progress of 5%, it would take at least ten more days for Lin Fei's Giant Whale Technique to reach the fifth level.

In ten days, under normal circumstances, Lin Fei would be able to step into the Body Refining Fifth Level.

"If I want to ensure the safety of the Lin family's business in the future, just having the strength of the Body Refining fifth level might not be enough to deal with all situations. The stronger my strength, the better!"

Lin Fei set a ten-day deadline. First, he would deal with the Lin family's matters. Then, he would go to Lu Mountain to collect Black-Backed Centipedes.

He had two months, which should be enough.

So, early the next morning, Lin Fei asked the Lin family to go to the various pharmacies in the city to purchase the medicinal materials needed for Vajra Iron Cloth.

Spending thirty thousand taels of silver was enough to buy many precious medicinal materials.

Another thing was the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique.

During this period, the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique had not made much progress. It required listening to Buddhist and Taoist scriptures.

Lin Fei asked Lin Shi Yi to take him to a nearby famous temple for a visit.

Lin Fei went to Sanyuan Temple outside the city. Sanyuan Temple was well-known far and wide. The temple was large and had many golden statues of Buddha.

Lin Fei arrived early. As a result, he caught the monks performing their morning rituals.

The sound of wooden fish being struck accompanied the voice of a high monk explaining the scriptures.

"Thus have I heard, at one time, the Buddha was in the Jeta Grove of the city of Shravasti, with a great assembly of twelve hundred and fifty bhiksus..."

Lin Fei heard the scriptures coming from Sanyuan Temple.

"Your Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique has, for the first time, heard the profound Buddhist scripture 'Diamond Sutra', entering a state of enlightenment that lasts for the duration of one incense stick..."

Lin Fei's body stiffened. Immediately after, uncontrollable sounds of "cracking and popping" came from his body. The bones throughout his body seemed to be trembling violently.

During the trembling, Lin Fei could clearly feel that the bones all over his body were improving at a terrifying rate.

"Enlightenment? Can martial arts also achieve enlightenment?"

Lin Fei was shocked in his heart.

This Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique was truly astonishing. It had been silent all along, but now, just by listening to the Buddhist scripture, it had plunged into enlightenment?

The time of one incense stick passed quickly.

Lin Fei heard the system's voice in his mind again.

"Your Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique's enlightenment has ended. It has gained insights from the Buddhist scriptures, causing your bones to resonate. Its training efficiency has doubled, and your training speed has increased tenfold."

"Your Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique has broken through to the third level."

Lin Fei's eyes widened in disbelief. He immediately opened the system panel. His gaze focused only on the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique.

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Third Level (1% Progress)

Lin Fei saw that the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique on the system panel had indeed been upgraded to the third level.

"Amazing! The Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique's enlightenment is worth several years of bitter cultivation for an ordinary person."

Even Vajra Iron Cloth had cost thousands of taels of silver to reach the third level. And it took many days of soaking in medicinal baths.

However, what about the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique?

It was almost like a meteoric rise!

If the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique got enlightenment from time to time, wouldn't it quickly surpass the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique?

As a result, Lin Fei continued to stay in Sanyuan Temple. He stayed until the afternoon.

Lin Fei even found an excuse to visit a senior monk in the temple and sought advice on Buddhist principles.

What was the result?

After several hours, the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique indeed made progress. However, it only increased by 5% in progress.

"It seems that enlightenment is not something that can be easily encountered. Nevertheless, if I want to improve my Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique every day, I still need to rely on Buddhist scriptures."

Lin Fei simply bought a set of many Buddhist scriptures, packed them up, and brought them back to the Lin Mansion.

9. Body Refining Fifth Level

Time passed day by day.

Lin Fei soaked in medicinal baths every day, spending money like water. In the blink of an eye, the thirty thousand taels of silver were almost all spent.

However, the results were quite apparent. Lin Fei's various martial arts skills had made significant progress.

However, the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was still a bit short of reaching the fifth level.

It wasn't until the tenth day.

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has progressed by 5% after a day of hard work yesterday."

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has finally broken through to the fifth level after days of diligent hard work."

"Your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist has reached mastery after days of hard work."

"..."

Lin Fei read through many more notifications.

"System."

Lin Fei directly opened the system panel. Checking with the system panel was more intuitive.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Fifth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fifth Level (1% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Mastery (1% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Proficient (31% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Fourth Level (45% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Third Level (56% Progress)

"I finally reached the Body Refining Fifth Level!"

Lin Fei was overjoyed in his heart. As he predicted, his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique reached the fifth level after ten days.

Moreover, not only the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, Vajra Iron Cloth also reached the fourth level. Even Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique was not far from the fourth level.

What was even more remarkable was the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist. It had improved from "proficient" to "mastery."

Now Lin Fei's strongest combat martial art was the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

The mastery-level Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had immense power in every punch and kick. Combined with the fifth level of Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, the power was tremendous!

The only thing that hadn't made any progress was the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. This saber technique indeed had quite a character. There was no progress during normal times.

Lin Fei didn't know how to improve the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

However, the proficient Nine Shadow Saber Technique was barely enough for Lin Fei at the moment.

"Almost, it's time to deal with the Lin family's affairs."

Lin Fei had been in the Lin family for ten days. According to his plan, he had to deal with the Lin family's affairs. So, he went to the living room and found his parents and elder brother Lin Wen.

"Big brother, Father, I've now broken through to the Body Refining Fifth Level. So, I can try to go on an escort mission and open up our Lin family's business route!" Lin Fei spoke straightforwardly.

"Fei, you've reached the Body Refining Fifth Level?"

Lin's father and elder brother looked at each other. Their eyes revealed a hint of joy.

The Body Refining Fifth Level was considered a strong expert in Zhou Mountain Mansion City

Even the head of the Lin family's escort agency, Old Master Bai, was only at the Body Refining Fifth Level.

"Fei, going on an escort mission is still risky. But now, the Lin family really has no other choice. However, if you want to go on an escort mission, you should visit the escort agency and consult with Old Master Bai. After all, Old Master Bai has decades of experience in escort missions."

Lin Fei nodded and said, "Father, Big Brother, I'm just about to visit Old Master Bai."

"Alright, I'll go with you." Elder brother Lin Wen nodded, and they left the Lin Mansion together.

Bai's escort agency was not far from the Lin Mansion.

Bai's escort agency was originally a small one. Lin's father cooperated with Old Master Bai for the sake of convenience in business and acquired Bai's escort agency.

With the support of the Lin family, Bai's escort agency developed rapidly. It quickly became one of the top escort agencies in Zhou Mountain Mansion City

Soon, the two arrived at Bai's escort agency.

Lin Wen was the owner of Bai's escort agency. Therefore, they could naturally enter the agency directly.

"Young Master Lin."

A young woman with a heroic demeanor walked out of the agency. She was dressed in a tight-fitting outfit. Aside from her slightly rough skin, there were no other flaws.

"Bai Ying, we came to see Old Master Bai."

"Young Master Lin, please come in."

Bai Ying's gaze swept over Lin Fei for a brief moment. She seemed to find him somewhat familiar.

"Bai Ying, this is my younger brother Lin Fei, who just came down from the Nine Profound Sect."

"Disciple of the Nine Profound Sect?"

Bai Ying raised her eyebrows and felt curious. Disciples of a large sect were not common in Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

Several people entered Old Master Bai's room.

Old Master Bai had white hair and a yellowish, emaciated face. He looked seriously ill and was growing weaker day by day.

Seeing Lin Wen come in, Old Master Bai struggled to sit up and said hoarsely, "Young Master, it's all my fault. During this time, the Lin family's business convoy hasn't been escorted, the business route is blocked, and if this continues, I'm afraid..."

Old Master Bai was full of self-blame. He had once received great kindness from the Lin family. Now, he shared the Lin family's fortunes and misfortunes. Naturally, he was deeply concerned about the Lin family's situation.

Lin Wen, however, smiled and said, "Old Master, don't worry. We've decided to go on another escort mission and completely open up the business route."

"Oh? Young Master, have you found any experts to help?"

Old Master Bai's spirit was lifted.

"My younger brother Lin Fei, who just came down from the Nine Profound Sect, will lead the escort mission. What do you think, Old Master Bai?"

As Lin Wen's words fell, everyone's eyes in the room focused on Lin Fei.

10. Martial Arts Sparring

"Greetings, Old Master Bai!"

Lin Fei saluted Old Master Bai with a fist.

"Is this the Second Young Master?"

Old Master Bai also came to his senses.

He, of course, knew Lin Fei, who had been practicing martial arts in the Nine Profound Sect.

"Since the Second Young Master is a disciple of a large sect, his martial arts skills must be extraordinary, and he should be able to take on the escort mission.

However, times have changed. Our Bai family's escort agency flag may not be recognized by the bandits in the Green Forest. If we encounter danger..."

Old Master Bai's meaning was clear. Once they embarked on the escort mission, there would be life-threatening dangers.

"Old Master, why don't you find someone to spar with my younger brother? With your keen eyes, you can naturally determine whether he can lead the escort mission."

Lin Wen suddenly spoke, offering a suggestion.

"That's a good idea. Tie Shan, you go and spar with the Second Young Master."

Old Master Bai's eyes flashed with a brilliant light. He immediately called a burly man standing beside him, who was as tall and strong as an iron tower.

"Brother, are you okay with this?" Lin Wen asked.

"No problem, let's go outside and try."

Lin Fei nodded. He was even somewhat eager to try. After all, he had reached the Body Refining Fifth Level but had little experience in actual combat. This was an opportunity.

So, the group of people left the room and went to the outdoor martial arts training ground.

Many people gathered around. They knew that Lin Fei was a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect.

Tie Shan was Old Master Bai's direct disciple and the future successor of the escort agency.

Lin Wen stood next to Old Master Bai. In fact, Lin Wen also wanted to see Lin Fei's true strength.

After all, seeing is believing and hearing is not. He didn't understand martial arts. But Old Master Bai did. He would naturally be able to see Lin Fei's true strength.

Moreover, Lin Wen knew Tie Shan. Body Refining Fourth Level! This was definitely Old Master Bai's proud disciple.

"Swords have no eyes, since this is a friendly spar, let's not use weapons. How about unarmed combat?" Lin Fei looked at the burly Tie Shan and said.

"Then, please enlighten me, Second Young Master!"

After finishing his words, Tie Shan took a big step forward.

With one stride, he covered a distance of more than three meters.

In an instant, he closed in on Lin Fei.

Tie Shan was burly and had immense strength. As a result, his punch was also very powerful and fierce. And it came very suddenly.

Under normal circumstances, Lin Fei would have to dodge first. However, he showed no intention of dodging.

Seeing Tie Shan's powerful punch, Lin Fei didn't hesitate. He raised his hand and threw a punch as well.

"Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist!"

Lin Fei shouted in a low voice.

"Boom!"

Instantly, the masterful fist technique was unleashed. It automatically mobilized all the power in his body. Blood, qi, and bones all erupted.

The power of the Body Refining Fifth Level was not to be underestimated. As he threw the punch, the air was filled with the sound of a shockwave.

"Bang!"

Finally, the two of them collided with a punch. Tie Shan's face changed drastically at the moment of the clash.

An overwhelming force was transmitted directly from Lin Fei's fist. And it came with momentum like the pressure of a mountain, overwhelming and crushing.

"Crack!"

Tie Shan retreated several steps in a row.

Under his feet, the hard bluestone bricks on the ground cracked like a spider's web. This showed how terrifying the power of Lin Fei's punch just now was.

Tie Shan's body was filled with fluctuating qi and blood. He felt so uncomfortable that he wanted to vomit blood.

He didn't make another move.

In just one strike, the difference in their abilities was clear. Moreover, he noticed that Lin Fei had held back. Otherwise, with that punch alone, his arm would have been disabled.

"Thank you, Second Young Master, for showing mercy."

Tie Shan was an honest man. Lin Fei's strength was greater than his, and he had shown mercy, not making Tie Shan lose face. He naturally felt grateful.

"Hahaha, Tie Shan, you must be at the Body Refining Fourth Level, right? Your strength is really impressive."

Lin Fei also clasped his fists and said with a smile.

In fact, Lin Fei was truly happy in his heart. He didn't use much force just now and it seemed that he had easily defeated Tie Shan.

Tie Shan was certainly not weak. This could only mean that Lin Fei's current strength was indeed very strong.

Moreover, the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist combined with the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was indeed very powerful.

"Your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist has just been tested in a real battle, and it has understood the essence of the fist technique in combat, increasing its progress by 60%."

Lin Fei's eyes brightened. He didn't expect that sparring would bring such benefits.

His Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had made significant progress. It seemed that it wouldn't be long before it advanced from mastery to transcendence.

"How about trying saber techniques?"

Lin Fei couldn't help but itch to try. He wanted to spar with Tie Shan using saber techniques. He wanted to improve his Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

"I haven't practiced saber techniques much, but Bai Ying, my junior sister, is skilled in saber techniques..." Tie Shan said honestly.

"Alright, Lin Fei, that's enough."

Lin Wen turned his head and asked Old Master Bai, "What do you think of Lin Fei?"

"He is qualified to escort the shipment! If I'm not mistaken, the Second Young Master should be at the Body Refining Fifth Level, right? As expected of a disciple from a major sect, truly extraordinary.

However, even with the Body Refining Fifth Level, it won't be easy to deter all the bandits along the way. Tie Shan, Bai Ying, this time you'll lead the team and escort the shipment with the Second Young Master. Do your best to help him succeed!"

Old Master Bai immediately made a decision.

11. Escorting Goods

Early in the morning, a large number of carriages gathered outside the Lin residence. Each carriage was filled with goods. This was the Lin family's caravan.

Many burly escorts were responsible for transporting the goods.

This time, the convoy was led by Lin Fei. Additionally, Bai Ying and Tie Shan, two powerful Body Refining fourth-level experts, were in the group.

The lineup was actually not weaker than when Old Master Bai was in charge. In fact, it was even stronger!

However, no one was certain of success. After all, Old Master Bai had relied on his reputation built over decades, not just his strength.

"Second Brother, if anything goes wrong during this journey, prioritize your life. As long as we're still alive, our Lin family has hope. Don't risk your life for the goods," Lin Wen, the eldest brother, said with a heavy heart.

"Don't worry, Big Brother. I understand," Lin Fei nodded.

That was what he said. But in reality? This trip was almost the Lin family's last resort.

The goods in the caravan were worth a hundred thousand taels. They were to be transported to Su City, the most prosperous city three hundred miles away.

If anything went wrong during this trip, it would be more than just a major blow to the Lin family. They could almost declare bankruptcy. Thus, Lin Fei was more aware than anyone of the importance of this trip.

Moreover, his main goal was not just to deliver the goods. He also wanted to establish a trade route. So that the Lin family's caravan could travel unimpeded in the future. That was the most important thing.

"Set off!" Lin Fei mounted his horse.

And so, the convoy, with the escort flag raised, slowly left Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

With the Lin family causing such a commotion, other families and powers in Zhou Mountain Mansion City were also watching closely in secret.

Lin Fei being a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect was no secret. But they didn't hold high hopes for him.

Just a single outer disciple of the Nine Profound Sect, wanting to clear the path and establish a trade route, seemed to be underestimating the bandits.

Lin Fei, leading the caravan, had already left Zhou Mountain Mansion City. He was still thinking about the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Yesterday, he had sparred with Bai Ying, but there was still no progress with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. Not even a little improvement.

It was different from the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist. Sparring couldn't enhance his progress either.

Lin Fei even hesitated. Should he switch to another saber technique after returning to the Nine Profound Sect? This Nine Shadow Saber Technique was just too strange and difficult to master.

After traveling for half a day, the caravan arrived at the foot of a mountain.

Bai Ying spurred her horse forward and whispered, "Young Master, that mountain ahead is called Nine Rings Mountain. It consists of nine connected mountains. There are nine mountains and eighteen strongholds, with countless bandits. With such a large caravan, we might encounter trouble if we pass below Nine Rings Mountain."

Lin Fei raised an eyebrow, "How did Old Master Bai manage to pass when he escorted the caravan before?"

"In his early years, my father saved the life of a bandit leader on Nine Rings Mountain. As a result, as long as my father escorted the caravan through here, we could pass by paying a small toll.

But since my father fell ill and couldn't escort the caravan anymore, the bandits of Nine Rings Mountain no longer gave us face. They either demanded several times the toll or outright robbed us."

Lin Fei understood. These bandits on Nine Rings Mountain were the first hurdle the Lin family caravan had to overcome.

The caravan slowly approached the foot of Nine Rings Mountain.

With a rustle, a large number of ragged bandits emerged from the dense bushes at the foot of the mountain.

These bandits were thin and pale. It was more accurate to call them refugees than bandits.

In fact, most of these bandits were indeed refugees. They were forced to become bandits out of desperation. However, among them were a few burly, fierce-looking true bandits.

One brawny man with iron rings in his ears stepped forward, sneering, "If the caravan wants to pass through Nine Rings Mountain, leave a toll."

"We are from the Bai family's escort agency. Could the leader perhaps show some leniency?"

Bai Ying stepped forward and introduced herself.

"Hahaha, we can show some leniency. Pretty lady, if you stay behind and give us ten thousand taels of silver, you can go."

"Shameless!"

Bai Ying's face turned cold.

The other bandits burst into laughter.

"Ten thousand taels..."

Lin Fei's eyes turned cold. There were a hundred thousand taels worth of goods this time. But the profit wouldn't be a hundred thousand taels.

Now they wanted ten thousand taels right away. And this was just the first stop. There were countless other bandits ahead.

How could they afford it?

Lin Fei had thought of countless possibilities before. He wanted to consider the bigger picture. Or negotiate with the bandits and leave some silver behind.

However, it seemed now that it was useless. The Bai family's banner no longer had any deterrent effect.

"Since this is a matter of the martial world, let's follow its rules! If you can win against my saber, you can have whatever you want."

Lin Fei dismounted and stepped forward, standing in front of Bai Ying.

"You arrogant kid, I'll grant your wish!"

The burly bandit wielded a large saber, looking strong and powerful. With a whoosh, the bandit charged directly at Lin Fei.

His momentum was not weak. Judging by his appearance, he should have the strength of around the third level of Body Refining.

In the next moment, two white streaks of light flashed from Lin Fei.

These were two shadows.

No one could even see how Lin Fei had drawn his saber.

With a heavy thud, Lin Fei's powerful saber strike landed on the bandit's saber.

And with that, both the man and his saber were cut in half.

With a thud, the burly bandit fell to the ground.

His body was now in two pieces.

12. Nine Shadow Blade Technique Broke Through To Mastery

"Dead?"

Lin Fei was somewhat surprised. This was his first time using the Nine Shadow Saber Technique without holding back. During his practice with Bai Ying, it was just a friendly spar and he had only used about 20-30% of his strength.

But now, with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique at full power, its might was incredibly terrifying. One saber strike killed a bandit at the third level of Body Refining.

"I killed someone?"

Lin Fei's eyes narrowed slightly. He knew that as a martial artist, he would eventually have to kill. But he hadn't expected it to be this easy.

Yes, easy.

It was as simple as killing a chicken.

Too easy.

Were these bandits really this weak?

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique has killed for the first time, stirring excitement within the technique. It comprehended the secret of the fast saber."

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique has broken through to mastery."

Lin Fei was slightly taken aback. Suddenly, his mind was filled with insights into the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. The mastery-level Nine Shadow Saber Technique was even more terrifying.

At this moment, Lin Fei finally understood why the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had been progressing so slowly before, like a tortoise's pace.

It turned out that the Nine Shadow Saber Technique was a purely murderous saber art. It needed to be practiced through killing in order to advance rapidly.

Seeing their leader dead, the other bandits were stunned. However, Lin Fei had come back to his senses. Since he had already killed someone, he naturally had to clean up the rest of the bandits.

"Kill!"

Lin Fei charged into the group of bandits like a ferocious tiger descending the mountain. With one swing of his saber, three streaks of white light appeared.

One swing produced three saber shadows. This meant that Lin Fei's Nine Shadow Saber Technique had reached mastery.

Such a saber art was purely for killing. Especially in group fights, it was practically unstoppable.

These bandits were quickly killed one by one. Only a few emaciated refugees remained, now kneeling on the ground and surrendering. The real bandits had basically all been killed.

Lin Fei was covered in blood and looked like a god of death.

At this time, Bai Ying and Tie Shan approached.

"Young Master, this is just one group of bandits. There are countless others behind them," Bai Ying said softly.

"I know. I was just establishing my authority. I believe the other bandits in the Nine Rings Mountain will now know the consequences of targeting the Lin family's caravan. We can't possibly kill all the bandits in Nine Rings Mountain. Moreover, if we kill them, other bandits will take their place.

But according to the rules of the martial world, I can challenge all the bandit lairs. When the time comes, as long as our Lin family's banner is displayed, they won't dare to stop us!"

Lin Fei's eyes sparkled with determination. He had already thought of a solution.

However, Lin Fei's words left Bai Ying and Tie Shan astonished.

"Young Master, you want to challenge all the bandit lairs in Nine Rings Mountain?"

"Is that not possible?"

"It's theoretically feasible, but it's too dangerous. If there's even a slight mistake, I'm afraid..."

Challenging all the bandit lairs in Nine Rings Mountain was something even the old master Bai couldn't accomplish.

"Without such a method, the Lin family's caravan will never be able to trade normally. So, let's do it this way."

Lin Fei had already made up his mind.

Bai Ying and Tie Shan exchanged glances. They both nodded silently.

"Bai Ying, Tie Shan, you two retreat a little. Wait for me to defeat all the bandit lairs on the mountain, and then we'll meet up. If I haven't returned by tomorrow, don't worry about me, and retreat back to Zhou Mountain Mansion City."

Lin Fei said solemnly.

"Yes, Young Master."

Bai Ying and Tie Shan understood Lin Fei's intention. So, without further delay, Lin Fei grabbed a bandit and strode towards Nine Rings Mountain.

"System."

Lin Fei activated the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Fifth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fifth Level (1% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Mastery (61% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Mastery (96% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Fourth Level (45% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Third level (56% Progress )

Lin Fei took a look. Not only had the Nine Shadow Saber Technique broken through to mastery, but its progress had also reached 96%.

In other words, Lin Fei's killing spree just now had actually improved the Nine Shadow Saber Technique so much.

"If I kill another person with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, will it break through to transcendence?"

A thought crossed Lin Fei's mind. Once a martial skill reached transcendence, it was vastly different from mastery.

For example, once the Nine Shadow Saber Technique reached transcendence, one saber strike could produce six saber shadows. Its power would be increased by several times.

Although there were no experts at the sixth level of Body Refining in the bandit lairs of Nine Rings Mountain, it couldn't be guaranteed that there wouldn't be some strong fighters.

The stronger he was, the better.

"Young Master, the bandit lair is right ahead. As you instructed, I'll listen to your commands. Will you let me go?" the captured bandit cautiously asked.

"Let you go?"

Lin Fei sneered. This bandit was a genuine ruthless criminal, not a refugee. His hands were stained with countless lives.

"Perfect. I'll use your blood to consecrate my saber and help my saber art reach new heights!"

Lin Fei's saber fell swiftly.

"Ptui."

With one saber strike, the bandit's head was severed.

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique's progress has reached 100%, breaking through to transcendence!"

"Finally, transcendence."

Lin Fei was overjoyed. His saber was still stained with blood.

With a gentle swing, six saber shadows appeared, fast as lightning, too quick for the naked eye to discern.

Lin Fei's Nine Shadow Saber Technique had reached transcendence. Now, Lin Fei could truly be considered a saber expert!

"With my saber art at transcendence, it's time to strike while the iron is hot and challenge all the bandit lairs in Nine Rings Mountain!"

Lin Fei looked up to the sky and howled, "Lin Fei from Zhou Mountain Mansion City has come to challenge all the masters in Nine Rings Mountains!"

With a howl, Lin Fei ran towards the mountain stronghold in front of him.

13. No One Can Stop Me

Nine Rings Mountain consisted of endless interlocking mountain ranges, making it a challenging place to eliminate bandits.

Lin Fei moved quickly and arrived at the bandit lair in no time. However, the gates of the lair were tightly shut, and the bandits inside were extremely nervous upon hearing Lin Fei's voice. They hid within the lair, refusing to come out.

"Not coming out?" Lin Fei's eyes turned cold.

Just because others couldn't deal with these bandits didn't mean he couldn't. Lin Fei looked around and spotted several huge boulders at the foot of the mountain, which were most likely left over from the construction of the lair. Some of the boulders had sunk into the ground.

Lin Fei approached one of the boulders, which weighed at least several hundred pounds. He took a deep breath and grabbed the boulder with both hands, lifting it with a powerful heave.

"Up!"

With the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique and the third level of the Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique, Lin Fei's blood, tendons, and bones were incredibly strong.

Naturally, his strength became terrifying, comparable to those with innate divine strength. Thus, Lin Fei was able to lift the massive boulder. Without hesitation, he threw it at the bandit lair's gate.

"Boom!"

The boulder smashed heavily into the gate, which was made of wooden fences and couldn't withstand such a force. The gate was instantly shattered.

Laughing, Lin Fei leaped through the broken gate and entered the lair.

"Who are you? How dare you break into our lair?" the bandits asked as they rushed out to confront Lin Fei.

Several bandit leaders stared at Lin Fei with grave expressions, especially after witnessing him lifting and throwing the boulder to break the gate. The bandits were all apprehensive, fearing Lin Fei's power.

"I am Lin Fei from Zhou Mountain Mansion City!" he announced. "My Lin family's caravan wants to pass through Nine Rings Mountain, and I heard that the leaders here want to collect tolls.

We, the Lin family, do not wish to pay. So, I took the liberty of coming to Nine Rings Mountain. You can inform all the bandit lairs in Nine Rings Mountain. If any leader wants to collect our toll, they can try to challenge me.

If I lose, you can do whatever you want with me. If the bandit leader loses, from then on, whenever the Lin family's caravan passes through Nine Rings Mountain, no one shall obstruct us!"

"The Lin family..."

The bandits in the lair understood. This was the wealthy merchant Lin family from Zhou Mountain Mansion City. And from what Lin Fei said, it seemed like he wanted to challenge the entire Nine Rings Mountain alone. How arrogant!

"Alright, Lin Fei, wait for a few hours. The leaders of the various lairs will come," said a bandit with a deep voice.

So, Lin Fei found a cool spot in the lair, sat down cross-legged, and closed his eyes to rest.

"Big leader, we have so many people. We could just swarm him and hack him to death with our sabers!" whispered some of the bandits.

Lin Fei was just one person, while their lair had one to two hundred people. They were beaten to their own lair and their entrance was blocked. This was outrageous!

"You want to die? Go ahead, but don't drag us down with you," said the one-eyed bandit leader coldly. He continued, "Once one reaches the fourth level of Body Refining, its strength becomes terrifying.

What's the point of having more people? If it comes down to a fight, he could kill us one by one. Moreover, Lin Fei is challenging the entire Nine Rings Mountain bandits, not just our lair. Why cause unnecessary trouble? Once the experts from other lairs arrive, they will deal with him.

The bandits weren't stupid. There was no need to be the first to confront Lin Fei.

An hour passed, and suddenly, there were footsteps approaching from outside the lair.

"Whoosh."

A sharp arrow flew through the air, reaching Lin Fei in the blink of an eye.

"Clang!"

Lin Fei didn't even open his eyes. He quickly drew his saber from behind and slashed down.

"Crack."

The arrow was cut into two pieces by Lin Fei's saber.

"Swish."

Lin Fei opened his eyes, and he saw many figures outside the lair. These people all exuded a fierce aura to varying degrees. At least all of them were at the fourth level of Body Refining, and there were quite a few of them.

The one who had just fired the arrow was a bandit with tattoos all over his face.

"Was it you who shot that arrow just now?" Lin Fei asked coldly.

"Yes, it was me. Zhou Mountain Mansion City's Lin family? Heh, last time I robbed quite a bit of silver from you. What can you do about it?" The tattooed man replied with a smug expression.

"You want to be the first to act? Then go die!"

A cold glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei instantly stood up, like a fierce beast, charging straight toward the tattooed man.

The tattooed man was taken aback, not expecting Lin Fei to dare to attack him directly in front of so many people.

"Big brother!" The tattooed man shouted.

A cloaked man beside him, with a solemn expression, roared, "Kill!"

The cloaked man wielded a pair of hammers, which indicated his formidable strength.

Meanwhile, the tattooed man also nocked another arrow, aiming at Lin Fei.

One close, one far - their combined attack was extremely powerful.

"I said I'm going to kill you, and you won't be able to stop me!" Lin Fei knew that among these bandits, not all of them were on the same side. These two were from the same lair, which was why they joined forces. However, in this situation, Lin Fei had no choice but to press forward.

In order to intimidate these bandits, he needed to demonstrate an overwhelmingly powerful and domineering strength.

Therefore, these two had to die!

14. Deterring Bandits

"Slash!"

Lin Fei swung his saber.

Six flashes of white light streaked past, creating six saber shadows.

At this moment, the transcendent realm's Nine Shadow Saber Technique displayed its terrifying power.

The most significant feature of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique was its speed.

Speed pushed to the extreme. So fast that a single slash left multiple saber shadows.

It seemed as if Lin Fei only swung his saber once.

But in reality?

He had swung it six times!

The cloaked man, wielding his two hammers, couldn't even get close to Lin Fei.

His body suddenly stiffened and came to a halt.

"Pfft."

The next moment, blood gushed from the cloaked man's body.

On his neck, chest, and abdomen, deep wounds that exposed the bone appeared.

"Thump."

The cloaked man fell to the ground with his eyes still wide open.

There was no breath left in his body.

Dead!

The cloaked man seemed strong and powerful, wielding his enormous hammers, looked like someone not to be messed with. Among the many bandits in Nine Rings Mountain, the cloaked man was a true expert.

But now?

He couldn't even withstand a single slash from Lin Fei.

"Big brother!" The tattooed man's face changed drastically, a hint of grief and anger in his voice.

Just as Lin Fei was dealing with the cloaked man, he had also drawn his bow and shot an arrow at Lin Fei.

The arrow flew at incredible speed.

Almost at the same moment Lin Fei killed the cloaked man, the arrow had already reached his face.

Moreover, this arrow was aimed directly at Lin Fei's face, a vicious move.

At this moment, it was too late for Lin Fei to dodge.

However, Lin Fei didn't even bother dodging.

With lightning speed, his left hand reached out.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei grabbed the arrow with his bare hand.

The power behind this arrow was terrifying.

Yet, Lin Fei caught the arrow without a single tremor in his hand.

Not only was his hand speed fast, but his strength was also incredibly formidable.

"Here, take it back!" Lin Fei coldly glanced at the tattooed man and then threw the arrow back at him.

"Pft."

The arrow plunged into the tattooed man's throat, blood gushing out.

The tattooed man fell to the ground with a "thump," his body convulsing.

After a few breaths, he lay completely motionless.

Dead!

Two Body Refining Fourth Level experts from the Nine Rings Mountain bandit groups joined forces.

Yet, they couldn't withstand even a single move from Lin Fei. Both were killed directly by him.

For a moment, all the bandits' eyes narrowed. Their gazes were fixed on Lin Fei. Their faces filled with a hint of wariness.

Lin Fei held his large saber. His eyes swept over the many bandits, coldly saying, "Who else?"

The numerous bandits present remained silent.

"Lin Fei, your strength is indeed formidable. But no matter how strong you are, can you annihilate all the bandit groups in Nine Rings Mountain? It's impossible for the Lin Family's caravan to not pay the toll. We, the bandit groups of Nine Rings Mountain, will not allow it!"

As everyone remained silent and wary, a voice rang out from the crowd.

"Hmm?"

Lin Fei fixed his gaze. It was a thin bandit, hiding among the crowd, not daring to come out.

"Yes, I can't annihilate all the bandit groups in Nine Rings Mountain. But whoever targets the Lin Family's caravan, I can annihilate their bandit group! If you don't believe me, you can try.

Besides, I am an outer disciple of the Nine Profound Sect, and I have a great chance of becoming an inner disciple in the future. If I can't annihilate all the bandit groups in Nine Rings Mountain now, it doesn't mean I won't be able to in the future!"

Lin Fei's large saber was still dripping with blood. It was a threat.

For a moment, many bandits' faces turned ugly.

A single Lin Fei might not be worth fearing. But an outer disciple of the Nine Profound Sect was a different story.

If he really became an inner disciple, at least he would have to be at the Body Refining Seventh Level.

With connections and the help of fellow disciples. by that time, even pushing across the entire Nine Rings Mountain wouldn't be a difficult task.

In the martial world, strength is essential. But so is having a background.

Lin Fei's backing was the Nine Profound Sect. This was a leg as thick as they came!

leg: background. Chinese slang

"Very well, Lin Fei! Our Clear Wind Mountain bandit group will no longer collect tolls from the Lin Family."

Finally, a bandit from a mountain stronghold spoke up.

Lin Fei killed two Body Refining Fourth Level experts from the bandit groups with one move. This had already proven his strength.

Even a Body Refining Fifth Level expert might not be a match for Lin Fei. So, whether to take action or not was no longer important.

Since they couldn't defeat him, eliminate the threat completely, and Lin Fei had the backing of the Nine Profound Sect, what else was there to say?

Naturally, they could only agree to Lin Fei's demands.

Once the first one agreed, others followed. Thus, the many bandit groups of Nine Rings Mountain all agreed to Lin Fei's request.

From then on, the Lin Family's caravan would no longer be troubled by the Nine Rings Mountain bandits.

"Good, I hope you all keep your word, so I don't have to make another trip up the mountain."

With that, Lin Fei put away his large saber.

With a leap, he jumped into the air.

In a few bounds, he had already left the bandit stronghold and disappeared from everyone's sight.

15. Deserted Temple And Old Taoist

"Nine Shadow Saber Technique hasn't improved much."

Lin Fei glanced at the system panel. He had just used the Nine Shadow Saber Technique to kill the cloaked man, who was a Body Refining Fourth Level expert.

However, the progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had barely improved. This indicated that after reaching transcendence with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, further improvement would be very difficult.

This was normal.

For any martial art, Once it reaches transcendence, to go a step further and reach perfection couldn't be achieved simply through hard work. It also relied on opportunities, good fortune, and other factors.

At this moment, Bai Ying and Tie Shan were anxiously waiting. They didn't know Lin Fei's situation.

"He's back!"

Suddenly, Bai Ying's sharp eyes noticed a familiar figure on the road ahead.

It was Lin Fei returning!

"Young Master, are you alright?"

Bai Ying and Tie Shan hurriedly approached, examining Lin Fei up and down.

Lin Fei smiled and said, "It's done. I've dealt with Nine Rings Mountain. From now on, the Lin Family's caravan can pass through Nine Rings Mountain without paying any silver or being obstructed."

"What? Really? That's like challenging the entire Nine Rings Mountain!"

Bai Ying's eyes revealed a look of astonishment. Others might not know the difficulty of dealing with Nine Rings Mountain, but Bai Ying was well aware.

Even when Bai Ying's grandfather escorted caravans, he had to pay silver to the Nine Rings Mountain bandit groups, only then could they pass through safely.

And now?

Lin Fei went up the mountain and accomplished the feat that the Lin Family's caravan wouldn't even need to pay silver from now on.

"Alright, let's go. Su City is still far away, and there are other bandits to clear along the way..."

Lin Fei didn't become complacent. He was very clear that Nine Rings Mountain was just the first stop.

Days passed by.

The caravan had been on the road for four consecutive days. They were getting closer to Su City.

Along the way, Lin Fei was almost invincible. All the bandits were dealt with by Lin Fei. Moreover, Lin Fei had obtained the bandits' promises that they would never trouble the Lin Family's caravan again.

Furthermore, Lin Fei even gained a title. It was called Fast Saber Asura!

The title Asura actually referred to the fact that Lin Fei had killed many people. His saber was always bloodthirsty!

This was also a characteristic of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. The saber was just too fast. If one couldn't block it, death was inevitable.

Gaining a reputation in the world of martial arts was, in fact, a kind of honor for martial artists.

Many Nine Profound Sect disciples ventured out into the world. If they didn't have any reputation, they were probably not very strong.

On this day, the sky was gradually darkening. However, they wouldn't be able to make it to Su City in time.

"Up ahead is an abandoned temple. Let's spend the night there and head to Su City tomorrow."

Lin Fei now had absolute prestige within the caravan. When he spoke, everyone naturally complied. So, the caravan members came to rest in the abandoned temple.

Surprisingly, there were people inside the temple. An old man in a gray Taoist robe. And a fifteen or sixteen-year-old child who looked quite clever.

But what was strange was that behind the old man were five burly men wearing black cloaks, with their faces obscured and an ominous aura about them.

They seemed like guards but didn't quite look like it. There was a faint scent of sandalwood in the temple.

Lin Fei was about to speak. At this moment, Bai Ying's face changed drastically, and he shouted, "Quick, hold your breath! The sandalwood is problematic, retreat!"

As soon as Bai Ying's words fell, Lin Fei almost instantly withdrew without any hesitation.

The others who were slow to retreat collapsed to the ground. They were completely powerless, finding it difficult to even move.

Lin Fei was shocked and immediately asked, "What's going on?"

Bai Ying, still somewhat shaken, said solemnly, "My father once warned us to be cautious and careful when encountering monks and Taoists in the world of martial arts. If there is an unusual fragrance, immediately hold your breath and keep your distance. I didn't expect that the sandalwood would actually be poisonous..."

Lin Fei's face darkened. This was the experience of Old Master Bai, who had ventured out into the world. Obviously, the person who poisoned the sandalwood was the old Taoist in the temple.

"Archers."

Lin Fei called for the archers in the caravan. Arrows were aimed at the old Taoist and others inside the temple.

"Where did you wild Taoists come from, daring to poison people in the temple?" Lin Fei shouted loudly at the people inside the temple.

"Swish."

The old Taoist in the temple suddenly opened his eyes. There was a faint trace of blood in his eyes.

"Heh heh, you guys are cautious. However, since you've come, you might as well all stay."

The old Taoist waved his hand. Immediately, four burly figures rushed out from behind him.

"Whoosh."

These four burly figures walked out of the temple with big strides and charged toward Lin Fei and the others.

"Fire!"

At Lin Fei's command. Arrows rained down on the four men like a downpour.

"Clang clang clang."

However, when the arrows hit the four men there was actually the sound of metal clashing as if they were shooting at a sheet of iron.

The arrows fell to the ground from the four men's bodies. These arrows had no effect on the four of them.

"Hard martial arts?"

Lin Fei was slightly surprised in his heart. Hard martial arts were difficult to master. But now, four hard martial arts masters appeared all of a sudden.

It was strange.

The escorts also drew their sabers and rushed forward to block the four men.

These four men were not fast. They even seemed somewhat stiff. But each punch and kick had immense power.

"Boom."

A moment of carelessness and someone's chest was crushed, and it seemed like he wouldn't survive.

"Clang."

When the escorts' sabers struck these men's bodies, it was like cutting a wall. They couldn't cut through or hurt these people at all.

"Whoosh."

Without any hesitation, Lin Fei suddenly pulled out his saber from his back.

16. Zombies

"Nine Shadow Saber Technique!"

Lin Fei slashed out with his saber. Six saber shadows as fast as lightning.

"Boom."

Lin Fei's saber struck one of the black-cloaked men, but he encountered great resistance. It was like slashing at a rock. At most, it only cut a bit of skin.

"This kind of hard martial arts..."

Lin Fei's heart was shaken. However, he reacted very quickly.

After the first strike missed, he pulled out his saber again and slashed it down toward his opponent's head.

He didn't believe that the opponent's hard martial arts could make their head just as hard.

"Swish."

As Lin Fei slashed down with his saber, the black cloak shattered with a hard sound, revealing the true face of the enemy.

In front of Lin Fei, the opponent's face was dark and purplish. Their pupils were white, and there was a faint smell of decay all over their bodies.

This was obviously not a living person. It was a dead person!

"A... corpse?"

Lin Fei was shocked.

"Retreat."

Lin Fei retreated frantically. Bai Ying and Tie Shan also saw the true faces of their opponents at this moment.

Indeed, they were all the same. All dead people. Or rather, zombie!

"Second Young Master, these people are corpses. To be able to control corpses, it must be a demonic technique. The old Taoist in the ruined temple must be a demon Taoist!"

Bai Ying's voice was trembling. Demonic techniques were occasionally rumored in the martial arts world.

However, they didn't expect to encounter one today.

"Zombies. That's it, this must be the most malicious evil technique rumored in the martial arts world, the zombie demonic technique!" Lin Fei said solemnly.

In his mind, he had some memories. They were some martial arts trivia from the Nine Profound Sect.

Among them, he had heard there were some Taoists who specialized in refining corpses into zombies impervious to sabers and spears, extremely powerful.

Such zombies had almost no weaknesses or vulnerabilities, which was very terrifying.

Perhaps their only drawback was that they were not very agile. But even so, the four zombies were closing in step by step.

At such a close distance, it was difficult for them to escape.

"These zombies have immense strength, and their bodies are impervious to sabers and spears. They are difficult to deal with. To solve these zombies, we need to deal with the demon Taoist first. I'll go into the temple and take care of that demon Taoist!"

Lin Fei came up with a plan. To catch the thief, first catch the king.

These zombies had no consciousness. There must be someone controlling them. Undoubtedly, the main culprit was the demon Taoist in the temple.

Therefore, as long as Lin Fei killed the demon Taoist, the zombies would naturally lose their threat.

So, Lin Fei bypassed the four zombies and headed straight for the temple.

There was poisonous sandalwood smoke inside the temple, but this couldn't stop Lin Fei. He just had to hold his breath.

However, just as he held his breath and was about to enter the temple, a tall and burly man suddenly strode out of the temple.

A zombie!

This was another zombie.

Behind the demon Taoist, there were a total of five zombies. Previously, only four had appeared. This fifth zombie should be for the protection of the demon Taoist.

Without dealing with this zombie, Lin Fei couldn't enter the temple.

"Nine Shadow Saber Technique!"

Lin Fei's large saber in his hand furiously slashed at the zombie. Each slash was extremely fast and almost all of them landed solidly on the zombie's body.

However, it was useless. It didn't hurt the zombie at all.

Instead, the zombie grabbed Lin Fei's large saber and Lin Fei could only let go.

"Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist!"

Lin Fei didn't hesitate. He punched out.

He was not only skilled in saber techniques but also in boxing.

Moreover, his boxing style was powerful and heavy.

"Boom."

The zombie made a muffled sound and was actually pushed back by Lin Fei's punch.

Lin Fei's eyes lit up. He immediately closed in on the zombie.

"Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom."

Lin Fei landed a series of over ten punches on the zombie's body, each blow could break through solid rock.

But when it landed on the zombie, it was like punching cowhide. It had no effect at all.

It could only push the zombie back.

"Your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist has met an evenly matched opponent. In the heat of battle, it has comprehended the Shock Technique, your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist has reached transcendence!"

In the midst of the battle with the zombie, a voice suddenly appeared in Lin Fei's mind.

"Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist has transcended? And what does the Shock Technique mean?"

Lin Fei was somewhat puzzled. But in the next moment, a memory suddenly surfaced in his mind.

It was the memory of the transcended Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

At the same time, Lin Fei naturally understood the meaning of the Shock Technique.

It turned out that one must comprehend a certain trick to achieve transcendence with the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist. That was the Shock Technique.

The Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was indeed known for its powerful and heavy force. But its more advanced aspect was the power of shock.

It could deliver the force into the enemy's body. This was the true power of the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

Without comprehending the Shock Technique, the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist would never be able to reach transcendence. Just like the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

The Nine Shadow Saber Technique also required the comprehension of the "fast saber" realm, only then could it achieve transcendence.

The Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was already close to transcendence after a few days of hard training. It was just a little bit short.

Now, Lin Fei was fighting against the zombie. Breaking through in battle was normal.

"Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist!"

Lin Fei's eyes sparkled with brilliance. The next moment, the transcended Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist struck the zombie's body once again.

17. The Transcendence Realm Of Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist

A note from RighteousEgg

Do you like this story? Please don't forget to review/comment/rate it! I'm now posting one chapter a day, I'll post an extra chapter for every review and two for every advanced review. Any suggestions are welcome.

"Boom."

The transcended Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist punched down, making a sound like a real dragon's roar.

In fact, this was not a dragon's roar. It was the sound of the tremendous force, impacting the zombie's body.

"Splash."

Lin Fei could clearly see that The zombie's body trembled. Inside, there was a sound of "crackling."

The transcended Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist could produce a shockwave. It shattered the zombie's internal organs and bones in an instant. So even the zombie was affected to some extent. However, the zombie still didn't fall.

"Zombies are originally corpses, so even if their internal organs are pulverized, they still won't die. But the zombie will definitely be affected. Moreover, zombies also have weak points. Since it's not in the chest or abdomen, it must be in the head."

Lin Fei observed carefully. The current zombie, although not falling, its actions were still somewhat affected.

For example, its ribs were broken. So its movements became slower.

Lin Fei approached the zombie again and punched the zombie's head.

"Boom."

The zombie's head was extremely hard. It could even be called the hardest part of its body. Therefore, no one would choose to attack a zombie's head.

However, Lin Fei's Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist utilized the power of shock, hitting the zombie's head. It instantly shattered the Blood Core within the zombie's skull.

The zombie relied on the Blood Core in its skull. Once the Blood Core were shattered, the zombie would be useless.

"Thump."

With one blow from Lin Fei, the zombie fell to the ground with a loud noise, motionless.

"Success!"

A hint of joy appeared on Lin Fei's face.

However, seeing the zombie fall, the old Taoist's face changed drastically.

"How is it possible? How could you, a mere Body Refining martial artist, defeat the iron corpse that I refined?"

The old Taoist was obviously caught off guard. He never thought that a mere Body Refining martial artist could defeat his zombie.

His zombie was extremely strong, and immune to sword and spear attacks. Only an Acquired martial artist using inner power to attack the zombie's body would have a chance to destroy the zombie.

As for a Body Refining martial artist?

Even if they could repel the zombie, killing it was absolutely impossible. But Lin Fei made the impossible possible.

"Evil Taoist, die!"

Lin Fei didn't want to miss this once-in-a-lifetime opportunity. He held his breath and instantly rushed into the temple.

At this moment, there was only the old Taoist and the fifteen or sixteen-year-old little Taoist behind him in the temple.

The old Taoist was panicked. Seeing Lin Fei come in, he shouted, "How dare you, a mere Body Refining martial artist, be so presumptuous in front of me?"

The old Taoist took out a pill from his pocket and swallowed it.

Immediately, the old Taoist's body was covered with bulging veins, and his body swelled to a terrifying height of about two meters.

"Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist!"

Lin Fei punched out without any hesitation.

"Boom."

The old Taoist's body trembled.

"Ah..."

Following that, the old Taoist spat out blood. His entire body deflated like a punctured ball, instantly returning to his original appearance and the entire person was sent flying by Lin Fei, falling heavily to the ground.

"Slap."

Lin Fei immediately went forward to extinguish the sandalwood. Gradually, the sandalwood poison in the temple disappeared.

"Is he dead?"

Lin Fei waited for a while, but he didn't see any movement from the old Taoist. However, Lin Fei didn't approach. Instead, from a distance, he directly threw the large saber in his hand.

"Thud."

The saber penetrated the body, directly cutting off the old Taoist's head. Even so, the old Taoist still didn't make any movement.

Lin Fei was finally at ease.

Without the protection of the zombie, old Taoist was actually useless and unable to withstand even a single blow.

With the old Taoist dead, the four zombies outside the temple also stopped moving.

Lin Fei approached, using the power of shock, shattering the Blood Core within the skulls of the four zombies one by one to prevent them from going berserk and causing any accidents.

At this moment, there was only the fifteen or sixteen-year-old little Taoist left in the temple.

The old Taoist was already dead. The little Taoist's face was somewhat pale. Seeing Lin Fei and the others coming in with sabers, looking murderous, the little Taoist was terrified.

He immediately knelt down and said, "Hero, spare my life. All of this was done by the old Taoist, it has nothing to do with me, spare me, please!"

The little Taoist kept kowtowing and his forehead was already bleeding.

"What are you to the evil Taoist?"

Lin Fei asked.

"I... I am just someone who was captured by the old Taoist to serve him."

"Serve? I don't think so, you're the old Taoist's disciple!"

A glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

The little Taoist's body trembled, and he quickly said, "Hero, I never wanted to be the old Taoist's disciple, he forced me. I'm just a servant, a child in his eyes."

The little Taoist's desire to survive was strong.

Lin Fei looked at the old Taoist's corpse and then looked at the zombies outside.

A thought crossed his mind. So, he took the little Taoist aside for interrogation.

"I'll ask, you answer. Tell the truth, and I can spare your life. If you're dishonest, you'll join your master in death."

"Yes, ask away, hero. I will be honest and answer every question."

A glimmer of joy appeared on the little Taoist's face. As long as Lin Fei didn't kill him, everything was negotiable.

18. Zombie-refining Technique

Lin Fei learned the origins of the old Taoist from the little Taoist.

It turned out that the old Taoist was a Qi cultivator. He accidentally obtained a technique for refining zombies.

In order to create powerful zombies, the old Taoist tried various methods to kill some Body Refining martial artists.

Especially those who practice hard martial arts, using them to refine zombies would double the effect.

The reason they were in this abandoned temple was because the area around the temple was desolate. And it was some distance from Su City.

Many travelers would choose to rest in the temple for a night. So, the old Taoist waited here like a hunter waiting for prey.

Of the five zombies, three were created by killing martial artists who sought shelter in the temple. And thus, they were transformed into powerful zombies.

"Cultivator..."

A thought crossed Lin Fei's mind. He hadn't expected that in addition to martial artists, there were cultivators. Moreover, the methods of these cultivators were truly mysterious and unpredictable.

According to the little Taoist, the old Taoist was only at the second level of the Qi Condensation realm. But with just the second level of the Qi Condensation, he could control five terrifying zombies.

If there weren't martial artists like Lin Fei who mastered the Shock Technique, body Refining martial artists basically stood no chance against these iron corpses.

This was truly horrifying.

"By the way, where is the Zombie-refining Technique?" Lin Fei asked.

"It's in the old Taoist's pocket."

Lin Fei hurriedly searched and found a palm-sized object that looked like a turtle shell, made of neither gold, jade, nor paper. It was densely covered with text.

This was the Zombie-refining Technique.

Lin Fei's heart was filled with joy. If he could cultivate the Zombie-refining Technique, wouldn't he become a cultivator too?

"How do I cultivate the Zombie-refining Technique?" Lin Fei asked.

"Well... the old Taoist said that it requires aptitude. And the aptitude for becoming a cultivator is one in ten thousand."

"Aptitude?" Lin Fei furrowed his brow.

"This treasure jade is what the old Taoist said could identify whether one has aptitude or not. Put the treasure jade in your hand. If it glows, it means you have aptitude. If it doesn't glow, it means you don't have the aptitude."

Lin Fei held the treasure jade in his hand and quietly waited. However, after waiting for a long time, the treasure jade did not emit any light. It seemed that Lin Fei did not have any aptitude.

"Do you have aptitude?" Lin Fei looked at the little Taoist and asked.

"I... I have aptitude. But cultivating the Zombie-refining Technique is extremely difficult. I... I have just begun to sense Qi and am just a beginner. I haven't even reached the first level of Qi Condensation. According to the old Taoist, under normal circumstances, it would take me three years to reach the first level of Qi Condensation," The little Taoist cautiously said.

Lin Fei remained silent. He glanced at the Zombie-refining Technique on the turtle shell again. A thought crossed his mind.

With the system, maybe he could give it a try. So, he silently memorized the incantation of the Zombie-refining Technique.

"The Zombie-refining Technique rejects you for not having cultivator aptitude, refusing to cultivate."

Suddenly, the voice of the system sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

"Uh..." Lin Fei's face stiffened.

"R-Refusing to cultivate..."

This was the first time Lin Fei had encountered such a situation. Even the system said he had no aptitude to be a cultivator. It seemed that the Zombie-refining Technique was destined to have nothing to do with Lin Fei.

"Hmph, so what if you're a cultivator? You were still killed by me, a Body Refining martial artist! Once a martial artist becomes powerful, reaching the Acquired or even Innate level, they are also extremely powerful!"

Lin Fei didn't care much about not being able to become a cultivator. However, the methods of cultivators were indeed weird. Sometimes, they were even difficult to guard against.

This little Taoist was a bit troublesome.

"Little Taoist, what do you think I should do with you? If I let you go, who knows if you'll want to avenge the old Taoist? You, a cultivator with countless tricks, could hide in the shadows and cause me trouble. The best way is to remove the roots, completely eliminate future troubles, don't you think?"

Lin Fei's words made the little Taoist's soul tremble with fear.

The little Taoist was clever. He, of course, understood Lin Fei's meaning.

"I... I have a way to ensure that you can trust me completely. There's a Heart Pulse Technique mentioned in the Zombie-refining Technique. Once you use the Heart Pulse Technique, you'll be able to sense me at any time, even detecting any ill intentions I might have, and with a single thought, I would die.

Also, even though I haven't reached the first level of Qi Condensation, I can cultivate, I'm still young, and I have potential. Even the elder Taoist said my aptitude is acceptable.

If I can reach the first level of Qi Condensation or higher in the future, I can be of great help to you. Yes, martial arts. Since you are a martial artist, you will need external assistance and elixirs to reach the acquired or innate realm. If I become a cultivator, I can help you refine the pills needed for your martial arts training."

Lin Fei's eyes lit up.

Pills!

These were valuable items.

Martial artists also needed pills. Even Body Refining martial artists were no exception. However, the price of elixirs within the Nine Profound Sect was too high. It was not something Lin Fei could afford.

But with the young Taoist, especially one with aptitude, if he becomes a cultivator capable of refining pills in the future, it would be of great significance to Lin Fei.

"Heart Pulse Technique, huh?"

Lin Fei carefully examined the Zombie-refining Technique.

Indeed, it contained a secret method called the Heart Pulse Technique. This was just a little trick that even mortals can perform.

Once the Heart Pulse Technique was used to control the other's essence blood, unless the other party could break through the realm above Qi Condensation, otherwise, they would be unable to break free from the Heart Pulse Technique.

As for the realm above Qi Condensation, the Zombie-refining Technique did not provide any information. But reaching a level beyond Qi Condensation would definitely be very difficult.

"Fine, young Taoist, use the Heart Pulse Technique, offer your essence blood, and your life will be spared."

Lin Fei spoke slowly, making his decision.

19. Tool For Refining Pills

The caravan continued on its journey, but this time with an extra person. The young Taoist also joined the caravan on its way to Su City.

He had already used the Heart Pulse Technique to let Lin Fei control his blood essence, and the feeling was quite wonderful. It was as if Lin Fei could sense the Taoist's every move.

Moreover, Lin Fei couldn't sense even a hint of malice in the Taoist. That was why he was so at ease, letting the Taoist follow along.

After entering Su City, the caravan rested for a day to handle the goods before heading back to Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

The return journey was quite peaceful because Lin Fei had already cleared the way for the caravan. The Lin family's caravan would no longer encounter any troubles. Therefore, it only took a few days for them to return to Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

"Big brother, father, mother, I have cleared the way for the caravan on this escort mission. From now on, the Lin family's caravan can leave anytime and head to Su City. Along the way, as long as we raise the flag of the Lin family, no one will dare to trouble the caravan."

Upon hearing this, the elder brother was overjoyed. "That's great! Hahaha, our Lin family is saved!"

Lin Wen was also pleasantly surprised. Sending Lin Fei on this escort mission was actually a last resort, and they didn't have much hope for it.

But unexpectedly, Lin Fei not only successfully delivered the goods to Su City but also cleared the way for the caravan. This was simply incredible.

"It seems that my decision to send Lin Fei to Nine Profound Sect despite objections was the right one!" said Lin's father, feeling proud and satisfied.

The disciple from a major sect was indeed different. Just look at the old man, Bai, who had practiced martial arts his whole life but only relied on his reputation to travel the Jianghu.

But Lin Fei was different. It had only been a few years, three years at most, and he had already subdued so many bandits on his last trip.

Lin Fei was the pride of the Lin family.

After lunch, Lin Fei arranged for the little Taoist to stay in a separate courtyard. The Taoist was nameless and had been a beggar until he was taken in by an old Taoist.

Lin Fei thought for a moment and said, "You can't reveal your identity, so I'll give you a name that won't stand out in the Lin family. From now on, you will be called Lin Miao."

"Thank you, Young Master, for giving me a name," said Lin Miao, the Taoist, who didn't care much about his name as long as he could survive.

"Stay in this courtyard and don't leave unless it's necessary. As for the zombies, I brought them back for you, but you must not harm anyone without my orders. Remember, your top priority is to cultivate and strive to reach the Qi Condensation Period and be able to refine pills. I'll find time to bring you some books and materials on pill refining."

Lin Fei's positioning of Lin Miao was simple. He was just a tool for refining pills.

After arranging Lin Miao, Lin Fei returned to his room.

He hadn't soaked in a medicinal bath for many days, so he had someone prepare one for him.

"System."

While soaking in the medicinal bath, Lin Fei opened the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Cultivation Level: Body Refining Fifth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fifth Level (16% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Transcendence (1% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Transcendence (1% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Fourth Level (45% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Third Level (91% Progress)

Lin Fei took a look.

Only the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique could still be improved.

The Giant Whale Body Refining Technique diligently increased by 5% every day, which was indeed very diligent.

As for the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique, it was even simpler.

Lin Fei carried Buddhist sutras and Taoist scriptures with him. All he needed to do was recite a section every day to improve it.

As for the Vajra Iron Cloth, there would be no improvement without a medicinal bath.

The most troublesome ones were the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist and Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Since the two martial arts reached transcendence, it was as if their practicing progress had stopped.

It seemed that there was a hurdle from transcendence to perfection in martial arts practice.

It was extremely difficult and required some opportunities to achieve perfection.

"Body Refining martial arts are the foundation! Combat martial arts can be put aside for now."

Lin Fei was very clear.

Body Refining was the key and his foundation. He needed to reach the Body Refining Seventh Level as soon as possible so that he could become an Inner Sect disciple of the Nine Profound Sect and obtain more benefits and resources.

However, whether it was the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, Vajra Iron Cloth, or Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique, the cultivation progress was not particularly fast.

This was still due to Lin Fei's lack of resources.

He knew that there were some pills in the sect that could increase his blood and strengthen his bones.

Eating one would be like having divine help during the Body Refining stage.

However, the contribution points required for those pills were too terrifying, and only Inner Sect disciples were eligible to exchange for them.

"It seems that I have to find a way to get the pill recipe and let Lin Miao try to refine it."

Lin Fei had many thoughts in his mind.

However, he could think about it after returning to the Nine Profound Sect. The top priority was to complete the mission first before returning to the sect. After all, he had been away for a long time.

20. Back To The Nine Profound Sect

A note from RighteousEgg

Each chapter is a bit short. This is because the more often I update, the more readers I can attract. As a newbie, I have to do this.

Lin Fei's mission was to collect ten black-backed centipedes in Lu Mountain.

Initially, Lin Fei planned to go to Lu Mountain himself, but he realized that it would be a waste for him to go there. Why catch the black-backed centipedes in the depths of the mountains himself? That would be a waste of time.

Lin's family was a wealthy merchant in Zhou Mauntian Mansion City, and all they needed to do was offer a bounty. There were plenty of people willing to go to Lu Mountain to catch black-backed centipedes.

Lin Wen bought black-backed centipedes at a sky-high price of 100 taels of silver per centipede. Twenty of them cost only 2,000 taels of silver, which was nothing for the Lin family. However, it was enough to entice many people to take the risk and venture into the deep of Lu Mountain.

"Your Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique has reached the fourth level."

"Your Vajra Iron Cloth has reached the fifth level."

Lin Fei only needed to wait quietly. Days passed, and he stayed at home, which allowed him to focus on practicing his Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique and Vajra Iron Cloth. Both of them had broken through, but the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique had yet to reach the sixth level.

"Bro, the ten black-backed centipedes you wanted have been collected," Lin Wen's voice came from outside the door.

Lin Fei went out to take a look and saw that his elder brother had ten porcelain bottles, each containing a black-backed centipede. There were small holes in the bottle caps to ensure that the centipedes did not suffocate.

Lin Fei took the centipedes.

"Big bro, now that the ten Black-Backed Centipedes have been collected, I have to set off and return to Nine Profound Sect," said Lin Fei to his elder brother.

Lin Wen nodded and said, "That's good. After all, you are a disciple of the sect, and now an outer sect disciple. You should return to Nine Profound Sect. I'll wait for your good news and hope you can become an inner sect disciple as soon as possible. When that happens, our Lin family will have an inner sect disciple in Nine Profound Sect. Just the reputation alone will make others think twice before messing with us."

Lin Wen knew that for the Lin family to become prestigious, they would need Lin Fei to excel in Nine Profound Sect and become an inner sect disciple. Only then would the family's reputation truly soar.

Lin Fei personally said goodbye to his parents and gave Lin Miao instructions before setting off alone towards Nine Profound Sect on a fast horse.

Before leaving, his elder brother gave him another 50,000 taels of silver bills, completely depleting the family's fortune.

Lin Fei did not refuse, as the Lin family's caravan could finally leave Zhou Mountain Mansion City. They would make back the money sooner or later. And Lin Fei needed a lot of silver to exchange for contribution points in Nine Profound Sect.

Along the way, he encountered no trouble and safely returned to Nine Profound Sect.

"Submit the task," said Lin Fei as he went straight to the task hall and handed in the task, receiving 100 contribution points.

These contribution points were not worth mentioning, so Lin Fei exchanged all 50,000 taels of silver notes for contribution points, receiving a total of 50,000 contribution points!

With this, Lin Fei became rich again. However, Lin Fei needed to plan carefully for these 50,000 contribution points.

He must use them in need, which would maximize his strength.

"System."

Lin Fei called up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Fifth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fifth Level (71% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Transcendence (1% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Transcendence (1% progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Fifth Level (1% progress)

Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique: Fourth Level (51% progress)

Lin Fei carefully reviewed his martial arts.

The Giant Whale Body Refining Technique and Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique practiced themselves diligently every day, which were two very hard-working martial arts.

So, even if Lin Fei did nothing, his Body Refining progress would still improve. Therefore, Lin Fei doesn't need to spend any contribution points on Body Refining martial arts.

At most, he would buy some medicinal materials to practice Vajra Iron Cloth. So, if Lin Fei wanted to increase his strength, there was only one way to do it: combat martial arts!

When his Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist and Nine Shadow Saber Technique reach transcendence, they could no longer improve.

Lin Fei felt like a fishbone was stuck in his throat. He must find a solution.

Moreover, combat martial arts were the greatest for increasing one's strength.

Once the Nine Shadow Saber Technique reaches perfection, he could create nine saber shadows with one strike. The increase in strength would be enormous.

"Perhaps there is a way. My martial arts can understand, right? Isn't it like a person, who can quickly improve with the guidance and instruction of a master?"

Lin Fei thought of a way. Not only could martial arts practice itself, but it could also gain insights.

It was no different from a person. It might be effective if someone guided and instructed it.

Of course, it would cost money! That meant he had to give contribution points.

Lin Fei needed guidance, but his saber technique and fist technique had already reached transcendence.

Therefore, he had to find people who had reached perfection to give him guidance.

But how easy was it to achieve perfection in Nine Shadow Saber Technique and Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist?

At least, in Lin Fei's three years as an outer disciple, he had not heard of anyone achieving perfection.

Of course, this could also be because he was an outer disciple. The information was blocked, and he did not know about the inner sect.

"Go to the task hall."

Lin Fei made a quick decision. He would spend money on this matter at all costs.

As long as he had enough contribution points, he would not be afraid of not getting guidance.

A note from RighteousEgg

Hope you guys enjoy the chapter. All suggestions are welcome. Don't forget to rate/review/comment.

21. Post Tasks

A note from RighteousEgg

Thank you for the review, malinizgeldi. Here are three chapters.

I believe that the protagonist did not indiscriminately kill innocent people, but rather those who deserved to be killed. I want to portray the protagonist as someone who values family and friends and is fiercely opposed to evil.

As for the MC growing too fast to be found and so on...I will explain later.

The task hall was still crowded with people. Most of them were there to see if there were any suitable tasks to take on. But Lin Fei was there to post tasks.

He went straight to the task hall elder and respectfully saluted, "Elder, I want to post a task."

"Post tasks?" The elder looked at Lin Fei.

Lin Fei was just an outer disciple. It was rare for outer disciples to come and post tasks.

"Okay. The minimum contribution value for a task is one hundred."The elder said calmly.

"I understand."

Lin Fei knew the rules of the task hall. They didn't charge for posting tasks, but they set a minimum contribution value to prevent people from posting random tasks. One hundred contribution points outside the hall were equivalent to one hundred taels of silver, which was not affordable for everyone.

"What tasks do you need to post?"The elder asked.

"I am posting two guiding tasks. If there are senior members of the sect, or fellow disciples, who have mastered the Nine Shadow Saber Technique or Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist to the perfection level, they can guide me for an hour. The reward for the task is one thousand contribution points!"

Lin Fei gritted his teeth and offered a thousand contribution points directly. This was a big loss.

"One mastery in saber technique or fist technique to perfection level?"

The elder was slightly surprised. But then he looked at Lin Fei with meaningful eyes and said, "You don't understand what it means to master a martial art to the perfection level.

Whether it's the elder or the inner disciples, they won't be interested in your mere thousand contribution points if they have mastered a martial art to the perfection level.

You could wait for ten or fifteen days, but I doubt anyone will pay attention to your tasks."

Lin Fei was taken aback and respectfully said, "Please enlighten me, elder."

"It's simple. You need at least five thousand contribution points to attract the attention of those elders or inner disciples who have mastered their martial arts to the perfection level."

"Um..."Lin Fei hesitated.

One task required five thousand contribution points. If he was going to post two tasks, it would be ten thousand contribution points.

That's a lot of money!

"Okay, then it's 5,000 contribution points. Elder, please help the disciple put on these two tasks," said Lin Fei, gritting his teeth.

Finally, he made up his mind. As long as he could improve his strength, the contribution points spent would be worth it!

"Okay, the tasks are posted, you can go back and wait quietly. Only those who have taken on the tasks can know your information, and they will naturally come to you," said the elder.

"Thank you, Elder," Lin Fei said respectfully, bowing.

Although it was a bit painful, he had no choice.

Lin Fei left the task hall.

About half an hour later, a cold-faced, stunningly beautiful woman arrived at the task hall.

Although she looked beautiful, she exuded a cold aura from head to toe. Like a sharp saber.

No one dared to approach her. And her attire proved that she was an inner disciple.

"Isn't that Senior Sister Ling Yao?"

"I heard that Senior Sister Ling Yao recently broke through to the fourth level of Acquired Realm. With such talent, she has the potential to reach Innate Realm in the future."

"She is one of the most outstanding disciples in our Nine Profound Sect in terms of talent."

This black-clad woman was well-known in the Nine Profound Sect. She was one of the prominent figures in the sect.

Ling Yao ignored the discussion of others.

Her beautiful eyes were scanning the task wall for any easy and high-contribution-point tasks that were not too far from the sect.

She rarely did tasks. But she wanted a pill recently, and she needed contribution points. Therefore, she had to come and look for it. However, such tasks were not easy to find.

Tasks were ranked according to the amount of contribution points rewarded. Ling Yao checked the task list from top to bottom. She wasn't very satisfied with most of the tasks.

"Hmm? Nine Shadow Saber Technique perfection state, teach for an hour, 5,000 contribution points?"

Ling Yao's eyes lit up.

How generous!

Teaching for an hour and getting 5,000 contribution points was not common.

After all, teaching tasks were usually posted by outer disciples. Many senior members of the sect would take on these tasks.

However, this task had specific requirements. Only someone who had reached perfection in Nine Shadow Saber Technique could teach it.

Ling Yao had just reached perfection in this saber technique.

Moreover, in the entire Nine Profound Sect, there were only a few who could reach perfection in Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Ling Yao went directly to the elder in charge of the task hall and respectfully said, "Elder, I'll take the task of teaching the Nine Shadow Saber Technique."

The elder certainly knew Ling Yao.

She was the star of hope in the Nine Profound Sect. She was expected to become an innate and top talent at the core of the Nine Profound Sect in the future.

But he still had to follow the rules of the task hall.

"Ling Yao, if you want to take on this task, you must first demonstrate your Nine Shadow Saber Technique and show that you have reached perfection."

"Of course, Elder, please watch carefully."

Ling Yao drew her long saber and gently made a cut in the air.

"Swish."

Nine saber shadows appeared in the air.

"One saber, nine shadows, not bad. It has indeed reached perfection. You can take on this task!" The elder's eyes also showed a hint of surprise.

To reach perfection in martial arts, one must be an exceptional genius.

Many elders, even if their strength was stronger than Ling Yao's, cannot reach perfection in martial arts.

Ling Yao took the task information handed to her by the elder.

"Lin Fei, an outer disciple?"Ling Yao was slightly surprised.

She originally thought that only inner disciples would post this teaching task. But she didn't expect it to be an outer disciple.

Moreover, the nameplate showed that Lin Fei was only at the fourth level of Body Refining.

For a moment, Ling Yao was also curious. So she turned around and left the task hall, heading towards the outer disciple area.

22. I Have A Strike, Please Advise

"I wonder if anyone would take the task?"

Lin Fei had returned to his courtyard and couldn't help but feel pained at the thought of losing 10,000 contribution points.

Suddenly, he saw a figure in black appearing in his courtyard, emanating a cold and distant aura.

Lin Fei was taken aback but quickly realized that this was Nine Profound Sect, and it should be safe. He asked, "Who are you?"

"Ling Yao, an inner disciple. I accepted your task to teach you the Nine Shadow Saber Technique for one hour," Ling Yao said coldly.

"Senior Sister Ling Yao?" Lin Fei was surprised, having heard of her name even as an outer disciple. Ling Yao was one of the most outstanding talents in Nine Profound Sect and an expert in the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. It was hard to believe that someone of her caliber would take on a task like this.

"Cut the crap, I will only instruct you for an hour, and the clock starts from now.

Since you issued the mission, you must have great attainment in Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Use all your strength, don't have any scruples, and strike at me."

Ling Yao was decisive in both speech and action.

Lin Fei did not hesitate either and whispered, "Sorry, Senior Sister Ling, I have to offend you!"

In the next moment, Lin Fei drew out his big saber.

"Swish!"

Lin Fei made a saber strike without any reservation, using all his strength and accompanied by six saber shadows. The speed was astonishingly fast.

"Dang..."

Ling Yao also made a move, but she did not even use inner power. Lin Fei could not even see Ling Yao's saber speed clearly, but Ling Yao's saber firmly blocked Lin Fei's strike.

"One saber and six shadows, the transcendence level!

No wonder you need someone who has achieved perfection in Nine Shadow Saber Technique to guide you. It seems that your saber technique has reached its limit and cannot be improved any further.

Your saber technique had a great killing aura, while Nine Shadow Saber Technique is purely focused on speed. Its only purpose is to be faster..."

Ling Yao began to guide him. Anyway, she only needed to guide him for one hour. How much Lin Fei could comprehend depended on himself.

Of course, she would not keep anything hidden. Otherwise, if it were to be known by the elder in charge of the task hall, it would not be good for everyone.

Whether or not she was hiding anything, everyone present was a martial artist and naturally knew it.

Ling Yao did not hide anything. She even demonstrated it to Lin Fei personally.

Lin Fei was amazed. Ling Yao's Nine Shadow Saber Technique was devoid of anything extraneous.

For example, Lin Fei's Nine Shadow Saber Technique carried a lot of killing intent.

Of course, this had nothing to do with Lin Fei.

It was the Nine Shadow Saber Technique's own "enlightenment."

What about Ling Yao's saber technique?

It was simply fast! Purely fast!

There was no other attachment.

No killing intent, anger, and so on.

All that existed was the purest of speed.

It was as if it had returned to its original state.

With just a gentle swing of her saber, nine saber shadows instantly appeared.

With such speed, it would be useless even if Lin Fei were stronger and faster.

By the time he reacted, his head would have already rolled off.

"So this is the power of perfection-level martial arts? It's truly terrifying..."Lin Fei was shocked.

Body refining was indeed fundamental. But combat skills and techniques were equally important.

Otherwise, even with great physical strength, a lightly swung saber from the opponent could take off your head.

Ling Yao explained patiently.

In the blink of an eye, it had been nearly an hour.

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique has received guidance from a perfection-level expert and has understood its own mistakes. It had eliminated all impurities and returned to the basics, your Saber technique has reached a deeper level and has achieved the realm of perfection!"

"Boom!"

As the words fell, Lin Fei felt as if he had gained a new memory.

This memory seemed to have been born with him.

It was as if Lin Fei had practiced saber techniques countless times.

He had gained a complete understanding and thoroughly grasped the secrets of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Ling Yao saw that the time was up. So, she coldly said, "The hour is up, I have given you meticulous guidance. The task is considered completed. If you're not satisfied, you can go appeal at the task hall."

For this type of guidance task, if the disciple who issued the task felt that it was not worth it or felt that the other party did not give their all, they could go to the task hall and appeal to the elders.

An hour of guidance seemed to would not give Lin Fei much improvement.

"No need."Lin Fei suddenly spoke up and smiled, "Senior Sister Ling, I have a strike, please advise."

"Whoosh."

In the next moment, Lin Fei struck with his saber.

This saber strike had no signs. It seemed to have suddenly appeared.

In Ling Yao's eyes, it was as if nine clusters of white light had suddenly appeared.

Nine blades were attacking her from all directions.

"Whoosh."

Ling Yao's figure shook slightly.

She even retreated one step, as if a phantom, and avoided Lin Fei's saber edges by a hair's breadth.

Ling Yao's eyes narrowed slightly, and she said in a deep voice, "One saber and nine shadows? Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique reached perfection? Your comprehension is astonishing!"

"Senior Sister Ling is too kind. Besides, even if my saber technique has reached perfection, I cannot even touch your clothes."

Lin Fei also sheathed his saber.

There was also some surprise in his eyes.

Ling Yao had just used footwork, which Lin Fei had not yet trained in.

This footwork was like a ghostly phantom.

Even with one saber and nine shadows, he could not touch Ling Yao in the slightest.

23. Fused SaberTechnique

"Your saber technique aptitude is strong. Perhaps you may comprehend the legendary saber intent in the future.”

"Saber intent? May I ask, Senior Sister Ling, what does saber intent mean?"Lin Fei asked curiously.

Ling Yao was not a talkative person, but Lin Fei's talent in saber technique was truly amazing, and he was not an ordinary person. Therefore, she did not mind befriending him.

So Ling Yao replied, "It is already very difficult to reach transcendence in ordinary martial arts. As for perfection, unless you have extraordinary talent and comprehension, it is impossible to achieve it.

And above perfection, there is actually another realm called 'the realm of the divine.'

If you can reach the realm of the divine through saber technique perfection, then perhaps you can comprehend the saber intent. This saber intent is the realm of the divine."

Lin Fei listened carefully, "May I ask how to practice saber intent, Senior Sister Ling?"

Ling Yao shook her head, "If I knew, I would have already practiced it."

"I only know that once you have grasped saber intent, others will have no chance of drawing their saber in front of you."

"That powerful?" Lin Fei was shocked.

This saber intent was simply amazing, a completely different realm.

"Saber intent is even more difficult than achieving innate. So, you don't have to worry too much about it.

Although I don't know how to achieve saber intent, I have heard that those who have achieved saber intent are masters of various saber techniques.

So, if you want to achieve saber intent, you can practice other saber techniques more, and perhaps you can find a way."

After speaking, Ling Yao turned around and left the courtyard.

"Thank you, Sister Ling."

Lin Fei thanked her and looked up again.

Ling Yao had disappeared without a trace.

"Saber intent is even more difficult than innate..."

Lin Fei shook his head and looked at the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial arts realm: Body Refining Fifth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Fifth Level (71% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Transcendence (1% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (0% progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Fifth Level (1% progress)

Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique: Fourth Level (51% progress)

His Nine Shadow Saber Technique had already reached perfection.

But the progress of the cultivation behind perfection was directly 0.

It was estimated that it would be difficult to make any progress in the future.

The Nine Shadow Saber Technique had reached the level of "one saber, nine shadows," and had already reached its limit.

"The method that Ling Yao mentioned might be worth a try."

Lin Fei made a calculation in his mind.

Wasn't it just practicing more saber techniques? This was nothing for Lin Fei.

His martial arts could practice themselves.

"Let's try a few more saber techniques first and see if it works."

So Lin Fei went straight to the martial arts pavilion.

The elder of the martial arts pavilion was still the same old man with white hair.

This time, the old man didn't say much.

Lin Fei went straight to the first floor and chose some basic saber techniques.

Each of these saber techniques only required 100 contribution points, and ten of them added up to only 1,000 contribution points.

Lin Fei exchanged for all of them, took some time to memorize them, and then returned to his yard.

Now, he just needed to wait quietly.

One day, two days, three days, four days...

In the blink of an eye, six days had passed.

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, the cultivation progress has increased to 101% after a day of hard cultivation."

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has broken through to the sixth level!"

After six days, a voice rang in Lin Fei's mind.

Immediately, Lin Fei's blood and qi roared inside his body like a great river, surging continuously. A powerful momentum emanated from Lin Fei's body.

Body Refining sixth level!

Lin Fei finally broke through, and the seventh level was just a step away.

Moreover, given Lin Fei's age, once he reached the Body Refining seventh level, he would have a hundred percent chance of becoming an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect.

Although there was only one word difference between inner and outer disciples, the treatment was vastly different.

Lin Fei's Body Refining martial arts had been steadily improving. But no one had yet taken the task of instructing him in the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

Lin Fei even suspected that no one in the Nine Profound Sect had perfected the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

Lin Fei checked the ten basic saber techniques again.

These saber techniques were very simple.

In just a few days, he had already reached the transcended level.

Of course, this was because these saber techniques were all fast and had some similarities to the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Lin Fei continued to wait.

In the blink of an eye, another ten days had passed.

"After many days of hard work, your Thirty-Six Fast Saber Technique has reached perfection."

"After a fierce battle with your Nine Shadow Saber Technique, your Thirty-Six Fast Saber Technique was defeated and willingly merged into the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, increasing its foundation."

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique has increased by 1% in practice progress."

These were the series of voices that suddenly rang in Lin Fei's mind.

24. Body Refining Seventh Level

A note from RighteousEgg

Hope you enjoy the chapter. All suggestions are welcome. Don't forget to rate/review/comment.

"Nine Shadow Saber Technique's progress has reached 1%?"

Lin Fei was shocked.

Since reaching perfection in the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, the practice progress had been stuck at 0, with almost no improvement.

But now it has actually reached 1%.

And, it seemed to be because the Thirty-Six Fast Saber had reached perfection and was "absorbed" by the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, adding to its foundation.

So that was why it increased by 1%.

"That means the Nine Shadow Saber Technique can still improve even after reaching perfection.

Just by practicing other saber techniques to perfection, they can be absorbed by the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Doesn't that mean I have a chance to learn saber intent?"

Lin Fei felt his heart burn with passion.

Saber intent! Drawing a saber before it was a luxury. How powerful would it be?!

Even comprehending saber intent was harder than becoming innate.

It showed how extraordinary the saber intent was.

For ordinary people, it was very difficult to practice their martial arts to perfection, even for basic martial arts.

Lin Fei had practiced ten saber techniques.

Fortunately, they were just basic saber techniques and did not require much insight to reach perfection.

However, even if he merged all ten basic saber techniques into the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, the progress would only be increased to 10%.

Lin Fei continued to wait patiently.

As time passed, he achieved perfection in all the other nine basic saber techniques, and each one was absorbed by the Nine Shadow Saber Technique without exception.

However, the progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had only increased to 8%.

This indicated that some of the basic saber techniques might not be able to improve the progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique at all.

Therefore, Lin Fei's idea of searching for countless basic saber techniques and piling up the progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique to 100% in order to comprehend saber intent was almost impossible to achieve.

Perhaps, as the progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique continued to increase, no matter how many basic saber techniques he practiced, they might not be able to improve the progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique any further.

So, Lin Fei went to the Martial Arts Pavilion again and selected some saber techniques that were stronger than the basic ones, such as the Swift Wind Saber Technique, Shadow Saber Technique, and so on.

However, these saber techniques took a longer time to practice, and achieving perfection was not easy either.

Lin Fei's idea of comprehending saber intent in a short period of time was shattered.

Days passed one by one.

Lin Fei's attention once again focused on the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, because the progress of the technique was approaching 100% again.

This meant that the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was about to break through, and this breakthrough was different from previous ones and held significant meaning.

Once the breakthrough happened, he would be at the seventh level of Body Refining and could become an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei was filled with excitement as he waited for this day to come. He did not have to wait long before he received the news.

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has reached 101% after yesterday's intense practice."

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has broken through to the seventh level."

Many memories flooded Lin Fei's mind, and his blood and qi once again grew stronger. His body underwent an earth-shattering transformation.

"System," Lin Fei muttered to himself as he prepared to check his condition.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Art Realm: Body Refining Seventh Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Seventh Level (1% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Transcendence (1% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (8% progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Sixth Level (31% progress)

Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique: Fifth Level (81% progress)

He noticed that while many of his martial arts had progressed, his Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist remained at "transcendence" and had not shown any progress.

His task to guide the technique seemed to have been ignored, and it appeared that no one in the Nine Profound Sect was capable of perfecting the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

Nevertheless, Lin Fei was happy as he finally achieved the seventh level of Body Refining at the age of 18, which meant he was now qualified to become an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect.

Having reached the seventh level of Body Refining at the age of eighteen, he was already considered a genuine genius within Nine Profound Sect. Of course, there was still a considerable distance to be covered before reaching the level of the top talents.

There were some who had reached the seventh level of Body Refining at the age of twelve, setting a record within Nine Profound Sect.

The inner sect disciples of Nine Profound Sect were the true backbone of the sect, and as such, many resources were allocated to them. Any Nine Profound Sect inner sect disciple was considered a big shot in their local area.

For example, if Lin Fei were to return to the Zhou Mountain Mansion City as an inner sect disciple, everything would be different. Some officials in the city would even treat him with a special kind of respect.

"Okay. Go to the Transmission Hall first to confirm my martial arts level, and then join the inner sect!" Lin Fei couldn't wait any longer. He had spent enough time in the outer sect and it was time for a change of scenery.

With that, Lin Fei got up and headed straight for the Transmission Hall.

25. Promotion to the Inner Sect

A note from RighteousEgg

Usually one chapter a day, sometimes two. Don't forget to rate/review/comment.

The Transmission Hall was empty with only a few people present when Lin Fei arrived. They were undergoing martial arts certification.

Lin Fei waited for his turn and then stepped forward.

"Respectful greetings to all the elders," Lin Fei bowed.

"Why have you come to the Transmission Hall?" the elder asked.

"I came to certify my Body Refining at the seventh level," Lin Fei replied.

"Show me your badge," the elder demanded.

Lin Fei took out his badge, and the elder got his information immediately.

The elder was surprised after checking Lin Fei's information. "Lin Fei, eighteen years old. You were only at the fourth level of Body Refining before. Are you sure you're here to certify at the seventh level?"

"Yes, I am here to certify at the seventh level. Please, elder," Lin Fei replied and immediately activated the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

A massive surge of blood energy hit them.

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was best known for its blood energy, so it was terrifying when fully activated.

The elder had extensive experience and could tell Lin Fei's current state with a glance.

"The seventh level of the Whale Technique, not bad. You have indeed reached the seventh level of Body Refining.

Moreover, you're only eighteen years old and have reached the seventh level of Body Refining, making you an inner disciple.

Those who reach the seventh level of Body Refining before twenty years of age and become inner disciples will be rewarded ten thousand contribution points by the sect."The elder smiled.

"Thank you, elder," Lin Fei was also very happy.

The task of teaching the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had cost him five thousand contribution points before. Now, he had gained ten thousand contribution points in one go. Overall, he had profited.

"This is your new badge."

Lin Fei received the new badge, which was red and represented the status of an inner disciple.

"Junior Brother Liu, take Lin Fei to the Inner Sect to handle the procedures."

"Yes, Senior Brother," Liu replied.

The elder waved his hand, and Liu led Lin Fei out of the Transmission Hall.

"I'll take you to the Inner Sect first. As for your belongings in the Outer Sect, you can handle them after you join the Inner Sect."

"Yes, Elder Liu," Lin Fei nodded.

He knew that the Inner and Outer Sects were two different areas.

Inner disciples could go to the outer door, but outer disciples cannot enter the inner door. Soon, Lin Fei followed Elder Liu to the inner door.

Upon seeing the inner door, Lin Fei noticed that there were fewer people and many separate courtyards.

"Lin Fei, inner disciples have their own courtyards. Over there is an empty one, you can choose whichever one you like," said Elder Liu.

Lin Fei scanned the courtyards and realized that they were all pretty similar. "This one will do," he said.

"Okay, I'll make a note of it," Elder Liu quickly jotted it down. "Now that you are officially an inner disciple, there are some things you need to know.

Inner disciples can earn a thousand contribution points every month. Most of the items that can be exchanged within the sect using contribution points can be purchased at a fifty percent discount by inner disciples.

Inner disciples can also obtain three acquired-level martial arts skills for free from the Martial Arts Pavilion.

However, these are all benefits that inner disciples enjoy. Naturally, there are corresponding obligations.

Inner disciples must obey the sect's orders and go to various places to support or defend the sect.

The support missions you see are pretty much the same thing."

Lin Fei felt a shiver down his spine. Inner disciples enjoyed many benefits that were incomparable to outer disciples.

Inner disciples were the true disciples of the Nine Profound Sect, as most of them were acquired-level martial artists, who were considered real experts.

The Nine Profound Sect had seized so much territory that they needed disciples to defend it, and they might even come into conflict with other forces. This required experts and acquired-level martial artists were just for that.

The Nine Profound Sect relied on its numerous inner disciples to maintain its current power and even expand it further.

This was also why Nine Profound Sect was not stingy at all towards its inner disciples, the real reason why.

The outer disciples might not have much experience in fighting and killing, but what about the inner disciples?

Each of them had been through countless battles. They were no longer fragile flowers raised in a greenhouse.

"By the way, inner disciples can choose to have a master or not," Elder Liu reminded.

"Usually, it is the innate level experts who take disciples as their students.

Whether or not an innate level expert will accept you as a student depends on your fate."

"Thank you for reminding me, Elder Liu," Lin Fei said respectfully and bowed.

"Haha, I have high hopes for you. If you become an innate expert someday, who knows, I might even come to you for guidance," Elder Liu said, then left.

Lin Fei walked into his yard.

Although it was empty, it was clean, indicating that someone had been taking care of it.

"Not bad, but the outer yard needs to be sold," Lin Fei thought and left the inner gate, returning to his outer yard.

He had bought his outer yard with a considerable amount of money, and now that he was leaving, he naturally wanted to recoup his investment.

So, Lin Fei spread the word that he was selling this yard.

The news had only been out for a day when someone came to his door.

And it was a woman.

26. Clan Patronage

A note from RighteousEgg

Hope you enjoy the chapter. Do not forget to comment/rate/review!

"Who are you?" Lin Fei looked at the woman in front of him.

She had a somewhat charming appearance. Her gaze was always sizing up Lin Fei.

"My name is Chen Lian. I heard that Senior Brother Lin was going to sell this courtyard, so I came to take a look."

"Buying the courtyard? One thousand taels of silver, no bargaining, can be paid with contribution points." Lin Fei stated the price.

He had bought the courtyard for one thousand taels of silver in the first place. As long as he didn't lose money selling it, it was fine.

Moreover, there were many outer disciples. There were also many wealthy disciples. Buying a comfortable courtyard for one thousand silver was nothing.

"Deal!"

Chen Lian was very straightforward and directly gave Lin Fei a silver ticket worth one thousand taels of silver.

"I won't take away some of the commonly used things in the house, leave them all to you."

Lin Fei stood up and prepared to leave.

"Senior Brother Lin, wait."

"Is there something else?"

Lin Fei looked at Chen Lian with a puzzled gaze.

Chen Lian took a deep breath and said in a deep voice, "I heard that Senior Brother Lin has just entered the inner door?"

"You are very well informed," Lin Fei nodded.

It was not a secret, but the fact that she was so well-informed meant that Chen Lian must have some connections in the inner door.

"Senior Brother Lin, I do have one more thing to ask you about. I represent the Chen family and invite Senior Brother Lin to accept our family's patronage.

Once you become a patron, our Chen family will provide you with one thousand taels of silver every month. If Senior Brother Lin becomes an acquired martial artist in the future, we will provide you with five thousand taels of silver every month."

"Patronage?" Lin Fei heard of this for the first time.

Chen Lian smiled and said, "It's normal that Senior Lin hasn't heard of it. In fact, almost every inner disciple becomes a patron of some family or force.

After all, martial artists need various resources. Without money or contribution points, how much can be achieved with just completing tasks and the monthly allowance given by the Nine Profound Sect? So, some wealthy merchants or forces need to provide support.

We provide money, and in return, inner disciples become patrons. We can also take advantage of the name of inner disciples to act. It's a mutually beneficial arrangement."

Lin Fei pondered for a moment and asked meaningfully, "It's not that simple, is it? You can't just take money for nothing. Besides the name of the inner disciple, if something happens, I have to step in, right?"

Chen Lian nodded and said, "Naturally. Since we have sponsored Senior Brother Lin, if the Chen family encounters any trouble, we will naturally ask you for help.

But if the enemy is too formidable, Senior Brother Lin can also refuse to help. It's not mandatory, and we cannot force you.

Even every time Senior Brother Lin helps, we will offer compensation to ensure that Senior Lin is satisfied.

Our Chen family is a family of good deeds, and we usually don't encounter significant trouble. For general troubles, we can handle it ourselves.

Senior Brother Lin can consider it carefully and compare the prices offered by other forces. Our sincerity is undoubtedly the most abundant!"

Chen Lian seemed very confident.

Lin Fei returned to the inner door.

Regarding Chen Lian's proposal of "clan patronage," Lin Fei also considered it carefully.

The conditions were indeed quite good. However, he wanted to wait a little longer to see if other forces were offering higher prices.

Days passed one by one. In a blink of an eye, six days had passed.

Lin Fei had almost understood the inner door.

"System."

Lin Fei checked the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Seventh level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Seventh level (7% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Transcendence (1% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (8% progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Sixth level (61% progress)

Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique: Sixth level (11% progress)

During this period, the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique had the most significant improvement, reaching the sixth level, making Lin Fei's bones and muscles stronger and increasing his strength.

However, what made Lin Fei uneasy was the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

In six days, his progress in cultivation had only increased by 6%, reaching a total of 7% when combined with its previous progress.

In other words, he was making average daily progress of only 1%.

At this rate, it would take him at least one hundred days to break through to the eighth level. That was almost three and a half months.

Actually, this cultivation speed was already considered fast. But compared to Lin Fei's previous cultivation speed, it was simply too slow.

After all, Lin Fei's goal was not just to reach the acquired or innate levels, but to go beyond innate! He had lofty ambitions.

If the Body Refining stage was progressing so slowly, what about the acquired or even innate levels? Wouldn't they be even slower?

"It seems that I have to find a way to speed up my cultivation of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

The main focus of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique is to cultivate qi and blood.

So, as long as I can quickly increase my blood and qi, then my cultivation will definitely improve.

Within the Nine Profound Sect, there is a type of blood-increasing pill that can enhance one's blood, but it's very expensive. One pill requires one thousand contribution points."

Lin Fei stood up.

He decided to exchange for one blood-increasing pill to test its effectiveness.

So, Lin Fei got up and went to the Treasure Pavilion of the Nine Profound Sect.

27. Blood-Increasing Pill

The Treasure Pavilion was a crucial place in the Nine Profound Sect.

It was said that the guards at the entrance were all strong practitioners above the seventh level of the acquired realm. And within the Treasure Pavilion, there were innate-realm experts guarding it at all times.

The reason why it was so highly valued was that almost all of Nine Profound Sect's cultivation resources were stored there. This included precious medicinal herbs, weapons, pills, and more, almost everything you could ask for. Of course, the prerequisite was that you must have contribution points.

"Elder, I want to exchange for a blood-increasing pill."

Lin Fei spent a thousand contribution points to exchange for a blood-increasing pill.

Soon, Lin Fei returned to his room. He sat cross-legged and took out the blood-increase pill. The pill was blood-red in color and emitted a strange fragrance.

"Gulp."

Lin Fei swallowed the blood-increase pill in one gulp. Suddenly, his body began to feel hot, and the blood and qi in his body accelerated their flow. Even his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique automatically started to operate.

As time passed, about an hour later, Lin Fei heard a voice from the system in his mind.

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has absorbed the power of the blood-increase pill, and your blood and qi have gained significant growth. Your cultivation progress has increased by 5%."

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei opened his eyes, a hint of brilliance in them.

"One blood-increase pill can increase my Giant Whale Body Refining Technique's cultivation progress by 5%.

Then, with twenty blood-increase pills, I can break through to the eighth layer of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

Twenty blood-increase pills require a cost of twenty thousand contribution points."

Lin Fei carefully calculated it. It was worth it!

Lin Fei's current contribution points were still around 40,000.

After all, he needed to buy the medicinal materials for Vajra Iron Cloth every day. Otherwise, his hard body technique cannot be improved.

And this was only the seventh level.

If he reached the eighth level, the blood-increasing pill might not be as effective. At that time, the consumption will be even greater.

All of these required contribution points, which were money. Lin Fei needed a lot of money.

"It seems like I should go find Chen Lian."

Lin Fei decided in his heart.

During this period, some families and forces did approach him proactively after Lin Fei entered the inner door.

Their only purpose was to offer patronage! However, the conditions provided by these forces did not surpass those offered by Chen Lian.

Even most of them were worse than Chen Lian's conditions.

Lin Fei personally went to find Chen Lian.

Chen Lian lived in the courtyard where Lin Fei used to stay in the outer door.

"Senior Brother Lin, have you made a decision?"

Chen Lian didn't seem surprised to see Lin Fei come to find her. However, she was still very enthusiastic.

"Chen Lian, 15,000 taels of silver per year, and it must be paid in advance and in full. If the Chen family agrees, I can be their patron."

Lin Fei went straight to the point and directly stated his conditions.

"Fifteen thousand taels of silver, and it must be paid in advance and in full. This..."

Chen Lian was a little hesitant.

"Within two years, I will reach the acquired realm!" Lin Fei said coldly.

"Is that true?"

"Of course. If I don't reach acquired within two years, I will return everything I received from the Chen family." Lin Fei's tone was full of confidence.

Chen Lian pondered for a while.

Reaching acquire-realm within two years... At that time, Lin Fei would only be twenty years old.

For a twenty-year-old acquire realm martial artist, that was already considered an outstanding talent.

After a long while, Chen Lian looked up and said, "Senior Brother Lin, I personally lean towards agreeing with you. However, I cannot make the decision myself. I have to report back to the Chen family."

"I can't wait for too long." Lin Fei frowned.

"Within ten days, we will definitely give Senior Brother Lin a reply."

"Okay, let's set it for ten days." After speaking, Lin Fei turned and left the outer sect area.

In Lin Fei's opinion, the Chen family would most likely agree. It was only extra 3,000 silver taels a year. But in exchange, they would have a potential acquire realm martial artist as their patron.

This transaction was definitely not a loss!

After leaving the outer sect area, Lin Fei went straight to the Treasure Pavilion.

"Elder, I want to exchange for twenty Blood-Increasing Pills," Lin Fei said directly.

"Twenty Blood-Increasing Pills?" The Elder of the Treasure Pavilion furrowed his brows and said, "Blood-Increasing Pills can indeed enhance one's blood and qi, but absorbing them requires a long time and a huge amount of energy.

Moreover, if you take too many Blood-Increasing Pills, it will cause your blood and qi to become unstable and affect the foundation for developing inner power in the future. Are you sure you want to exchange for twenty Blood-Increasing Pills?"

"Yes, please. Elder," Lin Fei said without hesitation.

Lin Fei had known about these drawbacks that the elder had mentioned a long time ago. But none of these was a problem for him.

His Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was very diligent. It practiced almost day and night, like a model worker.

With such diligent cultivation, how could it cause his blood and qi to become unstable and affect his foundation?

Instead, his foundation would be incredibly solid.

"These are twenty Blood-Increasing Pills, and you can only take one pill per day."

"Thank you, Elder."

Lin Fei's contribution points were reduced by 20,000, but he obtained twenty Blood-Increasing Pills.

He did not go out of the courtyard again and instead took Blood-Increasing Pills every day to cultivate.

Most people could only take one Blood-Increasing Pill per day at most.

Taking more than that would waste the medicine's efficacy and make it difficult to absorb.

But Lin Fei was different. He could easily absorb two Blood-Increasing Pills every day.

Taking two Blood-Increasing Pills allowed Lin Fei's progress in the Giant Whale Technique to increase by 10% every day, and the speed of its progress was very fast.

28. Body Refining Eighth Level

A note from RighteousEgg

Hope you guys enjoy the chapter.

In the blink of an eye, nine days had passed.

On this day, Lin Fei's blood and qi trembled.

Immediately, he heard the voice of the system in his mind.

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has broken through to the eighth level after many days of hard training."

Lin Fei opened his eyes wide.

"Body Refining eight levels!"

Lin Fei immediately checked the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Eighth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: eighth level (2% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: transcendence (1% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: perfection (8% progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: seventh level (6% progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: sixth level (56% progress)

Sure enough, Lin Fei had now reached the eighth level of Body Refining. And Vajra Iron Cloth had finally reached the seventh level.

Lin Fei reached out his hand. His skin looked a bit rough. But it was as tough as cowhide.

Even ordinary sabers might not be able to cut his skin.

Vajra Iron Cloth had an unparalleled defense against some force attacks.

Now, even if Lin Fei stood still and let those below the seventh level of Body Refining attack him, he wouldn't be hurt much.

This was hard martial arts! Training hard martial arts was very slow. But if one reached a high level, it would be terrifying.

However, at this point, the effect of some of the Vajra Iron Cloth's medicine baths had already diminished.

Similarly, Lin Fei could clearly feel that the Blood-Increasing Pill's effect had also weakened a lot.

Although it had not completely lost its effect, if he wanted to rely on herbal baths and Blood-Increasing Pills to improve his training progress again, he would inevitably consume more quantities.

That meant silver. A huge amount of silver!

Lin Fei now had just over ten thousand contribution points on him.

For Lin Fei, it was not enough.

"It's been nine days... how Chen Lian's side is doing?"

Lin Fei thought for a moment, got up directly, and left the inner door.

Soon, Lin Fei arrived at Chen Lian's courtyard.

"Chen Lian, what is your Chen family's decision?"

Lin Fei saw Chen Lian in the courtyard and asked directly.

"Senior Brother Lin, I was just about to find you."

"Yesterday, someone from the Chen family came. They also brought silver bills and said that a genius like Senior Brother Lin needs at least 20,000 taels of silver a year." Chen Lian immediately took out the silver bills.

"20,000 taels?" Lin Fei took the silver bills.

He remembered very clearly that his request was only 15,000 taels of silver a year.

But the Chen family's attitude was very strange. They gave an extra 5,000 taels of silver.

"Interesting. I feel your sincerity." Lin Fei nodded.

His goodwill towards the Chen family immediately increased a lot.

After all, he was really short of silver now. And the Chen family just right sent it over.

"As long as you are satisfied, Senior Brother Lin." Chen Lian smiled.

Lin Fei returned to the inner door.

He now had more than 30,000 contribution points. So he directly bought thirty Blood-Increasing Pills.

Lin Fei now only hoped to reach the ninth level of Body Refining as soon as possible.

Because, only when he reached the ninth level of Body Refining, could he try to give birth to the inner power.

Once inner power was born, he would become an Acquired martial artist.

There was a fundamental difference between an Acquired martial artist and a Body Refining martial artist.

Now Lin Fei didn't have many contribution points left. His cultivation speed in the future would inevitably slow down.

Lin Fei thought about it, but he didn't have a good solution.

After advancing to the eighth level of Body Refining, Lin Fei used the Blood-Increasing Pills again.

He could absorb three pills every day.

Therefore, in just ten days, Lin Fei's Blood-Increasing Pills were consumed.

And Lin Fei's progress in the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was only 40%.

In other words, three Blood-Increasing Pills could only increase Lin Fei's progress in the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique by 4% each day.

However, even so, the Blood-Increasing Pill was also gone.

It was increasingly difficult for Lin Fei to maintain a 4% daily speed increase.

However, there was also some good news. Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique had reached the seventh level.

The progress of the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique had always been steady. It only needed to listen to Buddhist and Taoist scriptures.

However, after reaching the seventh level, just listening to Buddhist and Taoist scriptures was no longer enough. Its progress had also slowed down.

During this time, Lin Fei was hesitant because his Body Refining progress was very slow.

He went to the Martial Arts Pavilion and practiced some saber techniques. However, each of them barely reached transcendence. All of them had hit a bottleneck.

By now, almost all of Lin Fei's martial arts skills had hit a bottleneck and could no longer be improved.

"I need to come up with a plan... and the most important thing is to earn contribution points!"

A thousand contribution points per month were clearly not enough to support Lin Fei's cultivation.

"Let's go to the task hall and see."

Lin Fei was also helpless and could only go to the task hall to see if there were any suitable missions for him.

He now understood why most of the disciples who accepted missions were inner disciples, while outer disciples were rare.

Inner disciples consumed resources at a terrifying rate, and without doing missions, they couldn't sustain the cost of practicing martial arts.

Lin Fei went to the task hall. It always seemed crowded here.

The task wall was covered with various missions.

"Lin Fei."

Suddenly, a clear and cold female voice came from behind Lin Fei.

29. Flowing Clothes Skill

Lin Fei turned his head and saw a familiar figure.

"Senior Sister Ling, are you here to pick up a mission too?" Lin Fei looked at Ling Yao.

Ling Yao was an inner disciple, now Lin Fei was also an inner disciple, so their identities were equal.

Ling Yao narrowed her eyes slightly. It seemed that she saw Lin Fei's badge. "So, you have become an inner disciple. It seems that you have reached the seventh level of Body Refining?"

"I just recently advanced to the seventh level of Body Refining," Lin Fei replied politely.

Ling Yao looked Lin Fei up and down before speaking directly, "You came to the task hall to pick up a mission, right? Being an inner disciple consumes too many resources compared to being an outer disciple. I have a mission here. Well, it's my personal request. I don't know if you will take it or not?"

"What mission?" Lin Fei asked.

"I have a distant cousin in Yi Mountain Mansion City who has had some trouble at home recently.

There has been a flower-snatching thief in Yi Mountain Mansion City recently, suspected to be above the seventh level of Body Refining.

My cousin's family sent me a letter asking me to go to Yi Mountain Mansion City to protect my cousin for a period of time.

But I have had a crucial task recently and can't spare the time, so I entrust you to go to Yi Mountain Mansion City.

The deadline is one month. I will give you ten thousand contribution points separately. After the deadline, my cousin's family will give you another twenty thousand silver.

If you can catch or kill that flower-stealing thief, not only can you get my cousin's family's silver, but also the official reward from the government."

Lin Fei's eyes lit up. However, after considering for a moment, he asked in doubt, "This condition is too good. Even an acquired strong person could be hired with this. Why would you entrust such a mission to a mere Body Refining martial artist like me?"

Ling Yao laughed, "You are not an ordinary Body Refining martial artist. With the Nine Shadow Saber Technique at the perfection realm, it is rare for anyone in the Body Refining stage to withstand your one saber."

Moreover, although three thousand silver can hire acquired martial artists, they will not be too grateful to you. For you, it is like giving you charcoal in the snow, and the significance is different. Well, will you take this mission or not?"

Lin Fei looked at Ling Yao meaningfully.

Ling Yao was straightforward, even saying "giving you charcoal in the snow." It was clear that she was trying to win over Lin Fei.

Anyway, entrusting the mission to anyone was the same. Lin Fei had enough strength.

"Okay, I'll take on this task. Thank you, Senior Sister Ling, for your kindness!" Lin Fei saluted with clasped hands.

Ling Yao took the initiative to show kindness, so of course he had to accept.

"Okay, I'll transfer ten thousand contribution points to you first. I'll also write a letter for you to take directly to the Liu Family in Yi Mountain Mansion City."

So, Ling Yao transferred the contribution points to Lin Fei and gave him a letter.

"The Flower Thief must have outstanding speed and agility. Guarding for a month would be too time-consuming. The best way is to catch or kill him.

However, to catch the Flower Thief, I must have martial arts skills in speed and agility."

So, Lin Fei went to the Martial Arts Pavilion again.

He had just received ten thousand contribution points from Ling Yao. Plus, he had several thousand contribution points from before. Therefore, choosing a lightness skill was naturally not a problem.

There were also many lightness skills in the Martial Arts Pavilion. After all, speed and agility were also important in combat.

Like Ling Yao, she had good lightness skills that even if Lin Fei had the Nine Shadow Saber Technique at perfection level, he wouldn't be able to touch her at all.

However, what Lin Fei wanted was a lightness skill that combined speed and agility.

This was a bit difficult to find. After all, Body Refining martial artists did not have inner power.

Their agility relied solely on physical movements.

As for speed? That had to rely on brute force.

After searching for a long time, Lin Fei finally found a martial art skill that was barely satisfactory.

"Flowing Clothes Skill."

"Agility and light, allowing one to move quickly and nimbly within a small space."

Lin Fei glanced at the introduction of this martial art skill. He was still relatively satisfied.

As for speed, Lin Fei had already given up.

Without inner power, what talk of speed? It would be better to compete in endurance.

Anyway, for Body Refining cultivators, whoever ran faster relied on endurance and strength.

Lin Fei exchanged for this lightness skill.

It took him half an hour to memorize the Flowing Clothes Skill.

"Your Flowing Clothes Skill has been Beginner-level after half an hour of hard training."

Lin Fei was moved.

"Swoosh, swoosh, swoosh."

In the training room, Lin Fei began to move and dodge.

The training room was very narrow. But Lin Fei moved like a light swallow, agile and nimble.

"The agility is indeed not bad. Hope it can be as diligent as the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist."

Lin Fei was very satisfied with this martial art. But he still didn't know the nature of this martial art.

Lin Fei preferred diligent martial arts that he didn't need to worry about them.

Lin Fei had already gained lightness skills, so he didn't want to delay any longer.

He packed his luggage and carried the big saber on his back.

This was Lin Fei's second time leaving the mountain. But this time, he didn't need to take on a task. Inner disciples could leave the Nine Profound Sect freely.

Lin Fei rented a fast horse.

Riding on the fast horse, he left a trail of dust and quickly left Nine Profound Sect.

30. Martial World People In Lin Family

A note from RighteousEgg

I wanted to take a moment to recommend a great book that I recently had the pleasure of reading. The book is called The Fusionist, written by my friend JBrooks, and I truly believe that it is a must-read for any fan of the fantasy genre.

JBrooks has crafted a rich and intricate world full of magic, adventure, and fascinating characters. The writing is engaging and vivid, making it easy to get lost in the story.

If you're looking for a thrilling fantasy read, I highly recommend checking out The Fusionist by JBrooks. You won't be disappointed!

The Fusionist:

A young man and his axe… along with a whole bunch of magic he doesn’t want

Larek Holsten is different from most people, but as long as it helps him become the best Logger he can be, he doesn’t really care all that much.  He and his best friend, an axe with a powerful fusion on it causing it to become sharper and stronger than a normal tool, are feared by the trees in the magical forest north of his home, as he can fell them faster than anyone else in the community.

Unfortunately, his abnormal physical appearance has a bit more of an influence over the population of the Kingdom than he figured, which ends up causing some problems when he visits the nearby village of Rushwood.  After a deliberate misunderstanding lands him in trouble, Larek is taken away from his family and the only home he’s ever known.  Along the way, a magical “potential” inside of him is discovered by those more knowledgeable than him in the ways of magic, and he is ordered to attend some sort of school for Mages.

The problem?  Contrary to many who would jump at the chance of wielding powerful magic to fight monsters, Larek has absolutely no desire to become a Mage.  All he wants is to go back home and chop down more trees with his best friend.

Contains LitRPG elements such as character progression and statistics.  No explicit sexual content or harems.

Liu Family, Yi Mountain Mansion City.

In the Liu Family hall, gathered many people from the martial world were dressed in strange clothes.

Mr. Liu was a slick and cunning businessman, looking very friendly.

He said to the martial artists, "Thank you, heroes, for coming to help me in the Liu Family. However, we cannot underestimate the Wind Chasing Fragrance, we have to wait a little longer."

At this point, a burly man carrying a large hammer became unhappy and shouted, "Mr. Liu, we have so many martial arts experts here, even if the Wind Chasing Fragrance is an acquired martial artist, he dare not come to the Liu Family and cause trouble. Why are we still waiting?"

"Yes, who are we waiting for?"

"We'll be in trouble if we don't make a plan now and the Wind Chasing Fragrance arrives."

For a while, these martial artists were all a little dissatisfied.

Mr. Liu continued to smile and said, "Dear heroes, we still have to wait for my niece. My niece is not an ordinary person, she is an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect. She has already reached the acquired fourth level. I have written to her and invited her to come to the Liu Family to help us. She should be arriving in the next few days."

Mr. Liu's words quieted the many martial artists in the hall.

An inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect. And even reached acquired fourth level.

Such a strong person was not someone these mere and wandering martial artists could compare to.

"Mr. Liu, someone outside claims to be a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect and says was invited to the Liu Family." At this time, a servant hurried over to report.

Mr. Liu's face lit up and he said with a smile, "It should be my niece, please bring her in quickly."

The martial artists in the hall also brightened up.

The inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect. They also wanted to see what she was capable of.

After a while, a strong-looking man was led by the Liu Family servant to the hall.

"Lin Fei from the Nine Profound Sect, greet Mr. Liu."

The man was Lin Fei, who had traveled all the way to the Yi Mountain Mansion City as quickly as possible.

"Hero Lin, where is my niece?"

"Niece?"

Lin Fei quickly realized that the other party was referring to Ling Yao.

Therefore, Lin Fei said directly, "Senior Sister Ling has some important matters to attend to, so she couldn't come. Therefore, she entrusted me to come and protect the safety of the Liu Family. This is Senior Sister Ling's letter."

Lin Fei handed the letter to Mr. Liu.

Mr. Liu quickly opened and read the letter.

His brows furrowed slightly, and he glanced at Lin Fei.

Then, Mr. Liu put away the letter and smiled, "According to what Ling Yao said in the letter, Hero Lin, you are also an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect?"

"Yes, I was promoted to the inner sect not long ago." Lin Fei answered truthfully.

"That's good. An inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect should be a talent like my niece..." Mr. Liu was quite satisfied.

"Hehe, I heard that according to the rules of the Nine Profound Sect, as long as you reach the seventh level of Body Refining before the age of twenty, you can be promoted to the inner sect. You were just promoted to the inner sect not long ago... you are still in Body Refining?"

Lin Fei raised his head.

The person who spoke was a cold-eyed bald man.

"Hero Lin, aren't you an Acquired Martial Artist?" Mr. Liu was also a bit anxious.

"I haven't advanced to Acquired-realm yet." Lin Fei said calmly.

Suddenly, Mr. Liu's face became a bit unpleasant.

In the hall, many martial arts people whispered and laughed, looking at Lin Fei, a bit meaningful.

"Mr. Liu, since everyone is here, let's discuss how to catch the flower thief the Wind Chasing Fragrance?"

"Right, I heard that the government offices have a bounty of three thousand taels of silver. This is not a small amount."

"I think that the Wind Chasing Fragrance is probably afraid to come to the Liu Mansion now..."

For a time, all the martial arts people in the hall began to discuss loudly.

It seemed that they had completely ignored Lin Fei's presence.

"Hero Lin, I'm sorry for this. You came from afar and must be tired. Let me arrange for you to rest first."

It was evident that Mr. Liu was somewhat disappointed with Lin Fei.

But after all, he was entrusted by Ling Yao, so Mr. Liu could not lose his manners.

"Thank you."

Lin Fei was indeed a bit tired. Then, led by Liu's servants, he was arranged to rest in a guest room.

In the room, Lin Fei thought in his mind.

"System."

Immediately, the system panel appeared in front of Lin Fei.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Eighth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Eighth Level (42% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Transcendence (1% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (8% progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Seventh Level (6% progress)

Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique: Seventh Level (11% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Mastery (42% progress)

Lin Fei looked at the mastery level achieved in the Flowing Clothes Skill and felt quite satisfied. In the past few days of rushing on the road, Lin Fei had encountered some bandits and used the Flowing Clothes Skill a few times. Flowing Clothes Skill did not disappoint him and it reached the mastery level in just a few days.

With the Flowing Clothes Skill, as long as the flower thief the Wind Chasing Fragrance appeared, Lin Fei would have the confidence to catch or kill the opponent.

As for those mocking and ridiculing him, Lin Fei did not care. Those wandering martial artists who could achieve the acquired realm would already be lucky enough. How could Lin Fei bother about them?

Lin Fei closed his eyes to rest and didn't know how long had passed when he heard a knock on the door.

"Click."

Lin Fei opened the door and saw a beautiful and graceful young woman standing outside, accompanied by two maidservants.

31. The Wind Chasing Fragrance

"May I know who you are?"

Lin Fei didn't recognize this woman.

At this moment, one of the woman's maidservants said, "Young Master Lin, this is our Miss."

"So it's Miss Liu!"

Lin Fei immediately understood. This young woman must be Ling Yao's distant cousin and the person he needed to protect.

Miss Liu looked graceful and said, "Thank you for coming all the way, Young Master Lin. Please forgive my father's neglect earlier."

"It's nothing. The Liu family didn't mistreat me." Pausing for a moment, Lin Fei asked, "Miss Liu, what brings you to see me?"

Lin Fei knew that Miss Liu was a young lady from a wealthy family and not someone who would casually meet strangers. Since she came to find him, there must be a reason.

Miss Liu smiled slightly and said, "I heard that Young Master Lin had arrived, so I came to see you. My father may not know my cousin's character, but how could I not? My cousin is always cold on the outside but warm at heart, and very perceptive.

If she promised to come to the Liu family but couldn't make it due to other matters, then the person she sent to replace her must be no ordinary person. Even if Young Master Lin is not an acquired martial artist, I believe you have other means that are not inferior to those of one.

I'm afraid my father's neglect may have caused some displeasure in your heart. So I came to apologize."

Lin Fei found it amusing. This Miss Liu was much smarter than Mr. Liu.

"Miss Liu, don't worry. Since I've promised to protect you, I will do my best to keep you safe." Lin Fei also made a promise.

Only then did Miss Liu feel relieved, so she bowed and left.

"This Lin Fei... seems to be just an acquired martial artist at most, does Miss really value him so much? You even went to see him specifically." Miss Liu's maid seemed to have doubts.

"What do you know? My cousin is proud, and even if someone is also an acquired martial artist, she won't look at them if they are not exceptionally talented.

But Lin Fei, a mere Body Refining martial artist, can make my cousin specially commission him to protect me. It shows that Lin Fei definitely has extraordinary abilities.

I'm afraid it depends on Lin Fei in the end whether I can get through this ordeal safely."

After speaking, Liu's expression also revealed a hint of worry.

The flower thief the Wind Chasing Fragrance had never failed in Yi Mountain Mansion City recently.

Even if she was clever, she was ultimately a weak woman with no ability to defend herself. She still had some worries in her heart.

Three days passed in a flash.

The Liu Mansion was very quiet, and nothing happened.

Not only did the Wind Chasing Fragrance not come, but there was also even no trace of the Wind Chasing Fragrance in Yi Mountian Mansion City.

However, the people in the Liu Mansion did not relax their vigilance.

As long as the Wind Chasing Fragrance was not eliminated, they would not be at ease.

After all, who didn't know the most beautiful person in Yi Mountian Mansion City was the daughter of the Liu Mansion?

Lin Fei was in the hall. He, like other guests, was guarding near the hall.

At this moment, a man with a long sword walked in from outside.

He was Shen Changsheng, known for his reputation in the martial arts community.

"Wait."

A short monk suddenly stood in front of Shen Changsheng.

"What's the matter?" Shen Changsheng's face turned cold, and his tone was somewhat unfriendly. After all, anyone would be unhappy when blocked.

The short monk was ugly and his mouth curved into a slight smile that looked somewhat sinister.

"You're not Shen Changsheng," the monk said coldly.

"Hmm?" At this point, everyone's gaze turned to him.

Lin Fei also frowned. He had met Shen Changsheng several times. If this wasn't Shen Changsheng, then who was?

Seeing that everyone was staring at him, the monk sneered and said, "I have a very sensitive nose. I remember the scent of everyone's body very clearly. There isn't as much fragrance on Shen Changsheng as there is on you. And some of the fragrances are aphrodisiacs. Being able to carry aphrodisiacs with you and being in the Liu Mansion... hehe, Wind Chasing Fragrance, I didn't expect you to infiltrate the Liu Mansion in this way."

Upon hearing the monk's words, everyone's expression changed drastically, and they all raised their weapons to surround "Shen Changsheng".

"Shen Changsheng" looked around, but was not panicked. Instead, a strange smile appeared on the corner of his mouth. "Didn't expect my disguise to be discovered by your dog nose. Now that you've seen through my disguise, you can be the first to die!"

In an instant, "Shen Changsheng" drew his sword and attacked.

"Swish!"

The sword light flashed, and a hole appeared in the monk's throat.

"You..." The monk stared at "Shen Changsheng" in disbelief and died, seemingly unable to believe that he had died so easily.

"Thump!"

The monk's body fell to the ground.

At this point, "Shen Changsheng" had already taken off his face mask, revealing a slightly old face.

"It really is the Wind Chasing Fragrance!"

"Pity the monk was killed by him'."

"Didn't expect the Wind Chasing Fragrance's disguise to be so lifelike."

The martial artists present did not ask where the real Shen Changsheng had gone.

Since the Wind Chasing Fragrance could disguise himself as Shen Changsheng, there was no need to ask.

Shen Changsheng was probably dead.

32. Beheading An Acquired Martial Artist

A note from RighteousEgg

Hey guys, I recently stumbled upon an interesting web novel on the Royal Road website called "I Suck at Titles" by Ellen Taylor.

I highly recommend giving "I Suck at Titles" a read if you're a fan of fantasy and adventure novels. It's a fun and entertaining story that's sure to keep you hooked until the very end.

I Suck at Titles:

It was supposed to be the best story I’d ever created, my love letter to the fantasy genre. It had heroes gathering mythical artifacts, an epic fight with a dragon, and adventure! But instead, due to a faulty narration device, this story now had me, in the flesh.

Which means I, the creator of this world, now have God-like powers to do whatever I want, and when someone has unlimited abilities, it starts to corrupt even the best of individuals. An unlucky guy like me becoming God is a recipe for disaster.

Everything is now ruined. There is no epic journey. There are no forging friendships. There’s not even a fight with a dragon anymore. There is no skill to gain, no progress to be made, because I am literally God. The only thing I needed to focus on is finding a way out of my story. Oh, and to not go insane with power and destroy everything I created.

Ugh, this is going to suck.

"Don't waste your breath with him, kill!"

One of the swordsmen wielding a sword shouted and charged directly toward the Wind Chasing Fragrance.

"Shhho!"

But the next moment, the Wind Chasing Fragrance struck back with a sword.

The crowd didn't even see the sword swinging, yet the man was already dead.

"What?"

"The Wind Chasing Fragrance is known for his swift body movements, but how can his martial arts be so strong?"

"The monk only at the Body Refining 6th level. However, the man he just killed was Zhao Jiu the Mad Saber, a Body Refining 8th level expert. How could he not block a single move?"

"Could it be that the Wind Chasing Fragrance is an acquired martial artist? Otherwise, Zhao Jiu couldn't have been defeated so easily."

For a moment, everyone stared at the Wind Chasing Fragrance in awe and fear.

They only knew him for the Wind Chasing Fragrance's agility, and subconsciously thought that his martial arts were only average.

But now, after witnessing his skills, they realized how wrong they were.

Terribly wrong!

"Hahaha! Dare to block my path, you bunch of worthless fools? Die!"

The Wind Chasing Fragrance dashed into the crowd of swordsmen, brandishing his sword.

"Swish, swish, swish!"

His sword was flashing with each move and was stained with blood.

With every swing of his sword, one swordsman after another fell dead.

In just a few breaths, more than ten martial world masters had been killed.

At this moment, the crowd was filled with horror.

"Inner power! The Wind Chasing Fragrance has inner power! He is an acquired martial artist!" cried out one of the swordsmen who had survived his attack.

Inner power was the symbol of an acquired martial artist.

It had been confirmed that the Wind Chasing Fragrance was an acquired martial artist.

At this moment, all the martial world heroes were shocked. They dared not approach and surround the Wind Chasing Fragrance anymore.

"Hmph, a bunch of weaklings." The Wind Chasing Fragrance stood with his sword, which was still dripping with blood.

He gave a cold glance and then prepared to move to the back hall.

"Swish."

Just then, a figure moved.

Lin Fei, who had been silent all this time, finally made a move.

In fact, Lin Fei had been observing all along.

He found out that the Wind Chasing Fragrance was indeed an acquired martial artist. He had inner power.

But he didn't always use his inner power. Instead, he tried his best to avoid using it.

Most of the time, he used his swordsmanship to kill those martial artists.

Lin Fei immediately understood.

The Wind Chasing Fragrance should only be at the first or second level of acquired.

His inner power was very limited. He couldn't just squander it at will.

And after killing so many martial artists, The Wind Chasing Fragrance had already consumed a lot of his inner power.

At this moment, He was at his weakest. And that was when Lin Fei made his move!

"Nine Shadow Saber Technique!"

Lin Fei didn't hesitate. He went all out from the start.

Facing an acquired martial artist with inner power, Lin Fei wouldn't dare to take it lightly.

"Swish."

Lin Fei swung his saber. Nine saber shadows appeared.

The sharp saber edges seemed to envelop the Wind Chasing Fragrance from all directions.

There was no escape for the Wind Chasing Fragrance.

"Hmm? This saber technique..."

The Wind Chasing Fragrance's expression changed slightly.

But in the next moment, he actually thrust his long sword forward.

"Clang..."

The tip of his sword accurately pierced the tip of Lin Fei's saber.

"Good swordsmanship!" Lin Fei's saber was blocked, so he didn't hesitate to lunge forward and throw a fierce punch with his left hand.

"Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist!"

Lin Fei not only had saber techniques but also fist techniques.

Moreover, his Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had even reached the level of transcendence, and his punch was extremely powerful combined with the qi from Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique and Gaint Whale Body Refining Technique.

Once it hit the opponent, even an acquired martial artist would be killed without a doubt!

"How dare you!" The Wind Chasing Fragrance also threw a punch.

"Bang!"

The fists of the two collided fiercely.

Lin Fei immediately felt a tingling pain in his hand, making his arm feel weak and powerless.

Inner power!

Obviously, The Wind Chasing Fragrance had used his inner power.

This inner power was extremely destructive to those without inner power.

However, Lin Fei's Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was not easy to take either.

"Crack."

The Wind Chasing Fragrance's face changed drastically, even letting out a scream. This punch was powerful. It directly broke his arm.

The Wind Chasing Fragrance's punches and kicks were obviously weak. Caught off guard, he was caught by Lin Fei.

Seize the opportunity!

Lin Fei gritted his teeth and endured the pain and weakness in his left hand.

He held the saber in his right hand and swung it again.

"Splurt."

This saber strike was impossible for the Wind Chasing Fragrance to avoid. Lin Fei cut off his head with one swing.

For a moment, blood splattered. The whole hall was filled with a strong smell of blood.

"Thump."

The headless body of the Wind Chasing Fragrance fell to the ground. The whole hall was in chaos.

The previous noisy and unruly martial artists all looked at each other in disbelief.

It seemed that they could not believe what they saw.

The Wind Chasing Fragrance was an acquired martial artist. He had already killed more than ten people.

But Lin Fei, who they had ridiculed before, actually clashed head-on with the Wind Chasing Fragrance with his Body Refining martial artist body and killed him.

This was truly shocking for them.

"Is this the strength of a disciple from a major sect?"

Some martial artists whispered to each other, unable to conceal the shock on their faces.

33. The Secret Of Inner Power

A note from RighteousEgg

Hi there! I wanted to recommend a fantastic novel. It's called "The Swordwing Saga" and it's by GeorgieD.

GeorgieD's writing is excellent, and he does a great job of building up the characters and the world they inhabit.

If you're a fan of LitRPG and cultivation novels, then I highly recommend checking out "The Swordwing Saga".

The Swordwing Saga:

Restarting the apocalypse was a good way to die, according to Rieren, even if she’s made too many enemies along the way. Especially since she would be reborn in the process.

Unfortunately, when she goes back to the past, she isn't the only one who remembers the previous timeline. Everyone else does too.

Now, half the world already hates Rieren’s guts, while the other half is searching for who’s forcing them to go through the monstrous apocalypse again.

The only saving grace—Rieren is reborn where the world doesn’t know her. Yet. With her identity one misstep away from a fatal revelation, Rieren must use her experience to forge the quickest path through a maze of rival sects, warring factions, and hidden threats, all to attain and surpass her former power before her greatest enemies close in.

Lin Fei, a body-refining martial artist, slew the Wind Chasing Fragrance. This made the group of martial artists in the hall realize the difference between a wandering martial artist and a disciple of a major sect.

Lin Fei rested for a while but found that his left hand was still sore and powerless, almost as if it were useless. This caused him to worry.

"I must have suffered internal injuries. Inner power injuries are not easy to recover from. Seems that I must hurry back to the sect to receive treatment."

Lin Fei's left arm was now immobilized, but he was not too worried. Once he returned to the sect, his arm would definitely be healed. He just needed to do so as soon as possible. Otherwise, his arm would be disabled.

Lin Fei looked at the body of the Wind Chasing Fragrance on the ground. He thought about how, as an acquired martial artist, the Wind Chasing Fragrance must have been skilled in acquired martial arts.

So, Lin Fei struggled to stand up and went to search his body of him. He took everything from the body, which included three secret manuals for sword techniques, body techniques, and acquired-level martial arts, as well as some silver bills.

Lin Fei counted the silver bills and found that there were over fifty thousand taels. This was a pleasant surprise, but it was also expected.

The Wind Chasing Fragrance had been wreaking havoc for such a long time, disappearing without a trace after stealing valuable items, so it was not surprising that he had managed to accumulate so much money along the way.

Besides the martial arts manuals and silver tickets, Lin Fei also found some porcelain bottles with various types of powders inside, including some aphrodisiacs and other types of drugs.

Mr. Liu also returned to the hall, accompanied by his daughter.

Mr. Liu was also aware of everything that happened in the hall.

He came in front of Lin Fei and hurriedly saluted, "Thank you, Hero Lin, for killing the evil thief."

Mr. Liu saw the blood in the hall and was very uncomfortable, his face turned white.

But at this moment, he also held back nausea in his heart and saluted towards Lin Fei, "Hero Lin, thank you so much. Without you, I'm afraid no one would be able to restrain this evil thief today, then the consequences would be unthinkable."

Lin Fei graciously accepted the salute from Liu's father and daughter. It was indeed he who saved Miss Liu.

"Mr. Liu, Miss Liu, I'm a little unwell now, so I'm going back to my room to rest."

"Quickly help Hero Lin to go back to his room to rest."

Thus, the two maids hurriedly went forward and helped Lin Fei leave the hall.

Looking at Lin Fei's back as he left, Mr. Liu sighed a little and said, "It's still my daughter's wise eyes that know people to have recognized this Lin Fei's uncommonness. But sigh, my old eyes are dimming and I was actually a little disappointed with Hero Lin.

Fortunately, you remedied the situation in time and didn't let Lin Fei chill, otherwise, it would be me who harmed you and the Liu Family."

Mr. Liu couldn't help but be afraid afterward.

If his attitude was a little worse at the beginning, Lin Fei could have "Slacked off" and let the Wind Chasing Fragrance do whatever he wanted.

At that time, the Liu family would have been finished.

"Dad, don't you know cousin's character? She personally entrusted the person, how can it be bad?"

Miss Liu looked at Lin Fei's back, and her eyes were also shining.

Although she was not a martial artist, she knew that Body Refining martial artists killing acquired martial artists who were stronger than them was not an easy task!

Even though she was sure of Lin Fei's extraordinary talent, she didn't expect him to be so powerful.

"Well, well. I was wrong. My eyes deceived me and my daughter is clever." Mr. Liu laughed heartily.

Lin Fei was helped back into the room, and he took out three secret manuals he had obtained from the Wind Chasing Fragrance. One was a sword technique, one was a body technique, and the other was an acquired martial art.

Lin Fei glanced at the sword and body techniques and found that they were not particularly advanced. The sword technique was not even as good as the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. As for the body technique, it was acquired level. It required inner power to practice, which was useless for Lin Fei.

"The acquired martial art!"

What Lin Fei valued most was the acquired martial art. At Nine Profound Sect, he could obtain three acquired-level martial arts for free, but he didn't go to the martial arts pavilion to get them because he hadn't reached the ninth level of Body Refining yet. However, it was okay to take a look at the acquired martial art for now.

So, Lin Fei opened the acquired martial art manual.

This martial art was called Flowing Cloud Force. Finally, Lin Fei understood some of the mysteries of acquired martial artists after checking it.

It turned out that the inner power of acquired martial artists was not cultivated but produced naturally. When a Body Refining martial artist's body reached its limit, it would produce a trace of inner power, and then they could choose some acquired martial arts to gradually strengthen their inner power.

The birth of inner power was actually divided into three types: Qi and blood, tendons and bones, and skin and membranes.

It's very difficult to reach the limit of the tendons and bones as well as skin and membranes, especially the skin and membranes. Any technique that practice the skin and membranes are considered to be hard martial arts, and it is extremely difficult to produce inner power through it. Therefore, it is relatively easy for Qi and blood to produce inner power.

Thus, most martial artists in the Nine Profound Sect chose to strengthen their Qi and blood when they were Body Refining. The Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was a martial art that could strengthen Qi and blood.

The foundation of the acquired martial artists was very important. Once inner power was born, it was related to the strength or weakness of the inner power and the speed of future practice.

If Qi and blood were strong, the inner power produced would naturally be strong. If Qi and blood were weak, the inner power produced would be weak.

Lin Fei also saw a description that if someone could produce inner power from Qi and blood, tendons and bones, and skin and membrane, and then combine the three inner powers and practice acquired martial arts, their foundation would be extremely strong, surpassing most other acquired martial artists. Only then would they have a greater chance of becoming an innate strong martial artist than most ordinary ones.

"It seems that I should continue to practice my Vajra Iron Cloth and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique and practice them to the limit until I can produce inner power. When I combine the three inner powers and practice acquired martial arts, my foundation will be extremely strong, surpassing most other martial artists!" Lin Fei's eyes sparkled with a hint of brilliance. He already knew how to enter the acquired level.

34. The Big Purchase In Treasure Pavilion

A note from RighteousEgg

Thanks for your review! Here are three chapters! Hope you enjoy them!

Yi Mountain Mansion City was shaken by the news that the Liu family had killed the notorious thief the Wind Chasing Fragrance.

The thief's body was sent to the government office, and the reward money from the government naturally fell into Lin Fei's hands, as well as the silver from the Liu family.

Originally, Ling Yao had promised 20,000 taels of silver, but this time, Mr. Liu unexpectedly gave him 30,000 taels of silver, saying that the extra 10,000 taels were compensation for their previous neglect of Lin Fei. Naturally, Lin Fei did not refuse the extra money and accepted it.

This trip was quite rewarding for Lin Fei. With the silver from the Liu family, the government's reward money, and the silver he found on the Wind Chasing Fragrance, he received almost 90,000 taels of silver, which was a significant sum. Lin Fei was naturally satisfied.

However, Lin Fei's left hand showed no signs of improvement after a day of rest, and the situation even worsened. So he didn't delay any further and went to Mr. Liu and Liu's residence to bid farewell, saying, "Mr. Liu, Miss Liu, My arm was injured, and the condition hasn't improved. I need to return to the Nine Profound Sect for treatment as soon as possible, so I've come to say goodbye."

"Young Master Lin, the Liu family is extremely grateful. When you come to Yi Mountian Mansion City in the future, you must come to the Liu family as a guest." Mr. Liu didn't insist any further.

"Definitely." After saying that, Lin Fei turned around and left.

A few days later, Lin Fei returned to the Nine Profound Sect. He immediately went to find Ling Yao.

"Are you injured?" Ling Yao looked at Lin Fei's left arm hanging down, and her expression changed slightly.

"That flower thief was an acquired martial artist. I was injured by his inner power. He has been killed by me, and Miss Liu is safe." Lin Fei briefly explained the situation.

"Acquired martial artist... you were injured by his inner power. If you have inner power, it's easy to deal with it. But if you don't, you need someone else to expel the inner power in your arm." Ling Yao approached and placed her hand on Lin Fei's left arm.

Immediately, Lin Fei felt a hot stream of energy flowing into his body from Ling Yao's hand.

Ling Yao was very close to Lin Fei. A faint fragrance entered Lin Fei's nose.

Lin Fei calmed his mind and quietly experienced Ling Yao's inner power as it flowed through his arm's tendons and meridians.

As time passed, about half an hour later, Ling Yao withdrew her hand. Sweat appeared on her forehead, and she looked a bit tired.

"Okay, I have expelled the inner power in your arm. Try it out."

Lin Fei slowly lifted his arm. It could move now. However, it was still a little sore and weak.

"Eat some blood-activating and stasis-dissolving medicine and rest for a few days, and you'll be fine.

Lin Fei, I didn't expect the Wind Chasing Fragrance to be an acquired martial artist, putting you in danger.

This time, I owe you a favor. If you need any help in the future, you can find me."

Ling Yao said solemnly.

She was indeed at fault this time.

She asked Lin Fei to protect Miss Liu, but she didn't expect the opponent to be an acquired martial artist.

Lin Fei was only a Body Refining martial artist.

If it weren't for Lin Fei's strength, the consequences would have been death.

She felt guilty in her heart and owed Lin Fei a favor, which was only reasonable.

"Okay, then I won't be polite. If anything happens in the future, I will definitely ask Senior Sister Ling for help." Lin Fei was also not polite.

Ling Yao's favor was hard to come by, and he wouldn't waste it. Not to mention, this time he did take a risk.

After Ling Yao left, Lin Fei immediately got up and went to the Treasure Pavilion.

Inside the Treasure Pavilion, Lin Fei exchanged all the silver bills for contribution points.

Ninety thousand silver notes were equivalent to ninety thousand contribution points.

Combined with the ten thousand plus contribution points he had previously, Lin Fei's contribution points finally exceeded the one hundred thousand mark.

Inside the Treasure Pavilion, Lin Fei purchased some medicines for promoting blood circulation and removing blood stasis to treat his arm injury.

However, Lin Fei still wanted to continue buying some Blood-Increasing Pills.

But, the effect of the Blood-Increasing Pills in cultivating was not good anymore.

At least, Lin Fei felt that it was too slow.

So, he asked the elder of the Treasure Pavilion, "Elder, do you know of any other elixirs that can increase one's qi and blood, besides the Blood-Increasing Pill?"

"Blood-Increasing Pill is already the best elixir for increasing qi and blood in our Nine Profound Sect," the elder replied.

Lin Fei pondered for a moment.

The effect of the Blood-Increasing Pill was still there, but it was too slow.

Now Lin Fei was at the eighth level of Body Refining.

Taking one Blood-Increasing Pill could only increase his cultivation progress by about 1%.

If it were other martial artists, this speed would be quite amazing.

After all, many martial artists took several years to make a breakthrough.

Now Lin Fei's Gaint Whale Body Refining Technique had a cultivation progress of 42%.

He needed at least sixty Blood-Increasing Pills to break through to the ninth level.

Thinking of this, Lin Fei raised his head and said to the elder, "I want to exchange for sixty Blood-Increasing Pills."

"Sixty pills, are you sure?" The elder was somewhat surprised.

"Sure."

The elder did not say anything and directly took out sixty Blood-Increasing Pills, a total of sixty thousand contribution points.

"Also, some medicinal materials to cultivate the Vajra Iron Cloth."

Lin Fei purchased some medicinal materials to use for medicinal baths.

Otherwise, the progress of the Vajra Iron Cloth would hardly improve.

After some purchases, Lin Fei had just over ten thousand contribution points left.

"No amount of contribution points would be enough to spend...."

Lin Fei shook his head and quickly left the Treasure Pavilion with the purchased medicinal materials and Blood-Increasing Pills.

A note from RighteousEgg

Now my Ko-fi provides more chapters.

35. Unexpected Surprise

Time passed day by day.

After a few days of rest, the injury on Lin Fei's arm had fully recovered.

Thanks to the Blood-Increasing Pill, his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was steadily improving.

The Vajra Iron Cloth was also improving. However, his Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique hit a bottleneck.

Despite listening to Buddhist and Taoist scriptures every day, its progress in cultivation had been almost stagnant.

Lin Fei knew he had not found the right method.

If he found the right method, his Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique would also continue to improve.

His Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist and Nine Shadow Saber Technique had hardly improved either.

Especially the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

After Lin Fei fused ten basic saber techniques and reached 8% progress, the Nine Shadow Saber Technique did not improve anymore.

The problem was the other saber techniques he practiced.

For example, the Gale Saber Technique and Shadow Saber Technique had only reached the transcendence level, not perfection.

Therefore, they cannot be integrated into the Nine Shadow Saber Technique to enhance its foundation and progress.

"Perfection..."

Lin Fei murmured. He hoped to cultivate saber intent.

If he could cultivate saber intent, his strength would certainly advance by leaps and bounds.

During this period, the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique had been steadily improving due to the Blood-Increasing Pill. However, Lin Fei could not afford to be idle. He must find a way to continue improving the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

"Oh, I can still issue tasks. Let those who have practiced the Shadow Saber Technique and Gale Saber Technique to perfection guide me. By then, my Nine Shadow Saber Technique will continue to improve with these saber techniques perfected."

Lin Fei's eyes lit up. He thought it was a good idea.

The Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist and Nine Shadow Saber Technique were considered superior martial arts in the body refining realm.

However, the Gale Saber Technique and Shadow Saber Technique were different.

They could only be considered slightly stronger than basic saber techniques.

It was much easier to reach perfection in these techniques than in the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist and Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

He might find someone who had reached the perfection level of these saber techniques in the Nine Profound Sect.

So Lin Fei went to the task hall.

"Elder, I am issuing a task."

"What task?"

"I need to be guided by those who have reached perfection in five saber techniques, including the Gale Saber Technique, Shadow Saber Technique, Falling Leaves Saber Technique, etc., for one hour. The task reward is 3,000 contribution points!"

Lin Fei had previously practiced a total of five saber techniques, all of which had reached the transcendence level.

Therefore, he issued five tasks at once. Each guidance task offered a reward of 3,000 contribution points.

After all, these saber techniques were much inferior to the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. Three thousand contribution points were already a generous reward.

However, this meant that he would need 15,000 contribution points in total. It would almost drain all of Lin Fei's remaining contribution points.

After issuing the tasks, Lin Fei returned to his courtyard and waited patiently.

Sure enough, just an hour later, a man in white martial attire arrived at Lin Fei's courtyard.

"Are you Lin Fei who issued the guidance tasks?"

"How should I address you, senior brother?" Lin Fei bowed and saluted.

"I'm Bai Wei."

"So it's Senior Brother Bai. May I know which saber technique you have taken the task for?"

"It's the Falling Leaves Saber Technique. I will not withhold anything during the hour, but how much you can comprehend depends on your talent."

Then, Bai Wei began to demonstrate the Falling Leaves Saber Technique to Lin Fei.

The Falling Leaves Saber Technique emphasized lightness and agility. Although it was also fast, being light and elusive was the essence of the Falling Leaves Saber Technique.

"Your Falling Leaves Saber Technique has received the careful guidance of a perfection-level expert, and it had understood the ultimate essence of the Falling Leaves Saber Technique, breaking through to the perfection level!"

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique had a fierce battle with the Falling Leaves Saber Technique and won, and the Falling Leaves Saber Technique was automatically integrated into the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, enhancing its foundation."

"Your progress in the Nine Shadow Saber Technique has increased by 2%."

A series of voices echoed in Lin Fei's mind.

"Thank you, Senior Brother Bai," said Lin Fei.

Bai Wei was skeptical. Did he really earn 3,000 contribution points just like that?

He didn't think that Lin Fei could learn much in just an hour.

But anyway, his task was completed. Whether or not Lin Fei learned anything was none of his concern. So Bai Wei turned and left.

Lin Fei returned to his room.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately pulled up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Eighth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Eighth Level (51% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Transcendence (1% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (10% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Seventh Level (21% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Seventh Level (12% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Mastery (56% Progress)

Lin Fei had many martial arts. Although their progress was slow, it was still gradually improving.

The only martial art that had not made any progress at all was the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

No one had taken on the task that Lin Fei had posted.

Lin Fei wondered if he should withdraw the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist task?

But even if he withdrew it. He could only recover 5,000 contribution points. It wouldn't make much of a difference.

"The progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique is also very slow. Fusing with the perfection-level Falling Leaves Saber Technique only increased the progress by 2%. It's only at 10%, still far from cultivating saber intent." Lin Fei shook his head.

He felt that investing his energy and resources into the Nine Shadow Saber Technique might have been a wrong decision.

The slight improvement in the Nine Shadow Saber Technique wouldn't make much of a difference.

"The Nine Shadows Saber Technique seems to have changed a little after fusing with the Falling Leaves Saber technique." Lin Fei directly slashed the Saber in the air.

"Swish."

The sharp saber suddenly erupted.

"Hmm? This is..."

Lin Fei's eyes lit up slightly. He found some unexpected surprises.

36. One Slash, Ten Shadows

"Swoosh!"

Lin Fei noticed that when he swung his saber, it wasn't just the usual nine saber shadows that appeared, but ten.

This was terrifying. Despite only adding one saber shadow, it was on the basis of the nine saber shadows, which significantly increased the power of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

"I wonder what level this one saber with ten shadows is considered now?" Lin Fei was curious. After all, even the founder of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had only been able to master nine shadows.

However, Lin Fei had not forgotten his task of perfecting four other saber techniques. Most likely, others had already mastered them and it was only a matter of time before they take on the tasks.

True enough, over the next ten days, people came to instruct him for an hour on different saber techniques, which greatly improved Lin Fei's progress in the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, reaching 18%.

With the Nine Shadow Saber Technique advancing by leaps and bounds, the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique also progressed rapidly. Lin Fei ate one Blood-Increasing Pill after another and was able to refine three or even four pills each day. As a result, he was approaching a breakthrough in his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

"Boom!" Suddenly, one morning, Lin Fei's body trembled and his blood and qi surged, even radiating outside of his body. His terrifying blood enveloped his entire body, making him look like a bloody figure.

"After enduring numerous hardships, your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has finally broken through to the ninth level."

"After many days of hard work, your Vajra Iron Cloth has broken through to the eighth level."

A series of voices suddenly sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

"They both broke through together?"

Lin Fei was pleasantly surprised. He didn't expect to receive good news so early in the morning. And it was two pieces of good news.

"System."

Lin Fei directly brought up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Ninth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Ninth Level (1% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Transcendence (1% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (18% progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Eighth Level (1% progress)

Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique: Seventh Level (44% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

Lin Fei saw the system panel.

His martial arts realm had reached the Body Refining ninth level. This also meant that he was finally close to acquiring inner power. And he was just one step away from being able to give birth to the inner power.

Of course, this step was very difficult to cross. In fact, there were many martial artists at the Body Refining ninth level. But not many of them were able to give birth to the inner power.

The proportion was probably only about fifty percent. Almost half of them remained at the Body Refining ninth level, unable to give birth to inner power and become acquired martial artists.

Lin Fei had the system panel, which was very intuitive. He knew that only when the progress of his Giant Whale Technique in the ninth level reached 100%, would he be able to give birth to the inner power.

But the speed of cultivation from the eighth to the ninth level was already very slow. It would probably be even slower to reach the limit of the ninth level and give birth to the inner power.

Lin Fei's Nine Shadow Saber Technique had reached 18%.

In terms of saber techniques, Lin Fei had surpassed many people in the Nine Profound Sect. Even many senior brothers and even acquired experts in the sect cannot compare to Lin Fei in saber techniques. He estimated that his saber techniques could rank among the top three in the Nine Profound Sect.

"My current strength is Body Refining ninth level. And I'm stronger than the average perfection realm in saber techniques. Maybe, if I encounter a criminal like the Wind Chasing Fragrance again, I won't need to waste so much time. I can just defeat him with one strike!" Lin Fei's eyes flashed with a hint of radiance. He now had absolute confidence.

Although he had not yet acquired inner power and was not an acquired martial artist, his strength was already comparable to that of an ordinary acquired martial artist.

"Saber techniques can actually be improved. I just need to practice other saber techniques and then release guidance tasks. But I have no contribution points at the moment.

Moreover, the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique can still be enhanced with Blood-Increasing Pills. It's not completely ineffective, just weakened a lot. If I want to reach the limit of Body Refining, don't know how many Blood-Increasing Pills I need to take. It's impossible to exchange them with contribution points alone."

"If I could refine Blood-Increasing Pills myself..." Lin Fei thought of a solution. He had long thought about alchemy, and he had also inquired about it.

Generally speaking, people could not refine pills, not even acquired martial artists. The reason was simple: the inner power of acquired martial artists cannot leave their bodies. Only innate martial artists, who had innate inner power in their bodies that never depletes, could refine pills.

The sect's pills were mostly refined by innate martial artists. But Lin Fei knew how valuable the time of an innate martial artist was. They would not spare time to refine pills for him.

Occasionally, some other people could also refine pills, such as immortal masters, but they were extremely rare and had to have special qualifications.

Nine Profound Sect did not have any immortal masters, but Lin Fei knew that Lin Miao was actually an immortal master, although a mediocre one who had not yet reached the first layer of Qi Condensation and could not refine pills.

"Wait a minute, does he need to reach the first level of Qi Condensation to refine pills?" Lin Fei wondered. As long as he had spiritual power, Lin Miao should be able to refine pills.

"Maybe I can have Lin Miao try," he thought. "But I need to figure out the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pills first..."

37. The Recipe Of Blood-Increasing Pill

A note from RighteousEgg

I wanted to take a moment to recommend a book that I think you all will enjoy. My dear friend has published a novel called "A Countess' Magic".

It's a captivating and imaginative story. The characters are well-developed, the world-building is rich, and the plot is full of twists and turns.

A Countess' Magic [A Transmigrated into a Villainess LitRPG with Xianxia, Kingdom Building and politics]

A girl escaping from a marriage. An ancient family. A power long forgotten.

Althea wished she could transmigrate into a different world. Even a book would do. And one day she did. But there was a teensy tiny problem.

The character she transmigrated into was the cannon fodder fiance of the male lead. The misunderstood girl that ends up sacrificing herself in the final battle after spending her last days in jail, accused of murder.

So she does the thing her books taught her. Tear the engagement and let the lovebirds deal with each other. That is about when things began to change.

Lin Fei pondered for a long time, and a figure came to mind - Ling Yao! Among the people he knew in the inner sect, perhaps only Ling Yao could help.

After all, Ling Yao had an extraordinary background and was a key disciple cultivated by the Nine Profound Sect. With this in mind, Lin Fei went straight to Ling Yao's courtyard.

"Senior Sister Ling," Lin Fei said as he arrived at Ling Yao's courtyard, where he found other female disciples who seemed to be inner sect disciples.

These female disciples looked at Lin Fei curiously, and he greeted them respectfully, "Greetings, senior sisters."

"Senior Sister Ling, it seems that this junior brother is looking for you for something, then we are gonna leave first."

"Senior Sister Ling, we will come back tomorrow."

"Hee hee, Senior Sister Ling, think about that matter yo~"

Thus, all three female martial artists got up and left the courtyard.

As the three female warriors rose to leave, Ling Yao raised her head and looked at Lin Fei, "You usually keep to yourself, and this is your first time coming to me. What do you need my help with?"

Knowing Lin Fei's character, Ling Yao was sure that he had something important to discuss. Lin Fei hesitated for a moment before asking, "Do you happen to have the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill?"

"The recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill?" Ling Yao frowned and asked, "Only innate masters or mysterious Qi cultivators can make pills. I don't know why you need the recipe, but if you really need it, I'll try to get it for you. But are you sure you want to waste the favor I owe you on the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill?"

Lin Fei could tell what was going on. Ling Yao could obtain the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill. And it didn't seem to be too difficult for her.

"I am sure, please help me, senior sister." Lin Fei replied firmly.

A favor in exchange for the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill. As long as Lin Fei needed it, he did not feel like he was losing out.

"Okay, I will give you the recipe tomorrow."

Lin Fei nodded, naturally trusting her.

He left, and Ling Yao watched his figure disappear, her gaze becoming sharp.

"The recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill. Seems that this junior brother Lin also has secrets..." Ling Yao shook her head and did not think about it any further.

After all, she also had her own secrets. Anyway, she had already befriended Lin Fei, and that was enough.

The next day, Ling Yao personally came to Lin Fei's courtyard.

"This is the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill you wanted."

Ling Yao handed a recipe to Lin Fei directly.

"Thank you, senior sister!"

Lin Fei looked at Ling Yao meaningfully and breathed a sigh of relief.

It was obvious that she was not a simple disciple to be able to obtain the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill so easily.

"In fact, the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill is not as difficult as you think. This is not a unique elixir of the Nine Profound Sect, many other sects have it too.

So, as long as you pay a certain price, you can still get the recipe. After all, the recipe is not the key. The most crucial thing is the ability to refine the pill."

Lin Fei naturally understood what Ling Yao meant.

The recipe could be obtained easily, but it was not so easy to have innate experts or Qi cultivators.

However, Lin Fei also knew that Ling Yao made it sound easy, but she must have paid some price to obtain the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill. It was definitely not easy.

"Anyway, thank you, Senior Sister Ling."

After receiving the recipe for the Blood-Increasing Pill from Ling Yao, Lin Fei packed his luggage and was ready to leave.

He took a look at the various medicinal materials on the Blood-Increasing Pill. They were not particularly precious, and even on the mountain below, they could be purchased.

So Lin Fei rented a fast horse and left the Nine Profound Sect once again. However, this time Lin Fei wasn't in a hurry to travel.

"I need silver."

At the Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei only had contribution points. But purchasing the raw materials needed for alchemy off the mountain would require silver.

Of course, maybe Lin's family could provide the silver, but refining alchemy was a very expensive process. Especially since Lin Miao might not succeed in refining the pill, and it would require practice, which would cost even more.

Therefore, if he could get some silver, he would try to get as much as possible. Lin Fei's method was also very simple, even crude.

He didn't take the official road, but instead took some smaller roads, preferably in the mountains and rugged terrain. He wanted to encounter some bandits on his own initiative. By killing the bandits, he would naturally be able to get silver.

There was also a reason why Lin Fei had the confidence to do this. The last time Lin Fei went down the mountain, he was only at the fourth level of Body Refining, so he had to be cautious.

But now, Lin Fei had reached the ninth level of Body Refining, and his Nine Shadow Saber Technique had reached perfection, even reaching the level of one slash with ten shadows.

Lin Fei's comprehensive strength was comparable to some acquired martial artists. Therefore, he didn't have to be as cautious as last time.

However, Lin Fei didn't know if his luck was too good or too bad. Even though he took the smaller roads, he didn't encounter a single bandit.

Just as Lin Fei was about to return to the official road, he suddenly smelled the scent of blood.

"Is something happening?" Lin Fei's eyes lit up. Finally, he encountered something. He hoped it was a group of bandits blocking the road so he could kill them and get some silver.

Lin Fei got off the horse and quietly headed toward the direction where the smell of blood was coming from.

38. The Perfection Of Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist

A note from RighteousEgg

Shoutout: A Corrupted Legacy [Villain Xianxia LitRPG System Progression Fantasy]

"Finally, I've done it!" Li Wuchen exclaimed.

With a thud, the body of the Foundation Establishment cultivator fell to the ground, marking the completion of the final requirement.

[System Activated]

[System: Demonic God Vessel]

[Criteria Met:]

- Activate Amulet: Complete

- Activate Partial Demonic Transformation x3: Complete

- Kill Higher-Ranked Cultivator: Complete

[Congratulations! You Are The New Demonic God Vessel]

"What's going on? A vessel?" Li Wuchen muttered, panic creeping into his voice as he stared at the floating screen before him. The very idea of serving as a vessel for such a dark and malevolent being filled him with dread, and he wondered what he had gotten himself into in his pursuit of power.

In the woods by the official road, a group of bandits surrounded a sedan chair. There were also a dozen or so guards nearby, but they were already corpses lying on the ground.

"S-So many bandits...What should we do?" the steward trembled as he spoke.

A young and beautiful woman, supported by her maidservant, also looked pale at the moment. This was also the first time she had encountered such a situation.

However, she was now the backbone of the group and had to summon up the courage to shout at the bandits on the opposite side, "Which mountain do you come from? Blocking the road can only be for the sake of money. But as long as you let us go, we will give you silver as much as you want! We have fifty thousand taels of silver bills on us right now. We will give you all of them."

The bandits on the opposite side lit up at the words. Fifty thousand taels of silver notes were not a small sum. However, they were bandits and silver bills were useless to them. They needed cash.

"Miss Zhang, everyone loves silver. But this time, we not only want silver but also your lives! It's just a pity for a beauty like Miss Zhang. I really can't bear to kill you like this. If it weren't for the order from the boss, I might even want to take you up the mountain to play for a few days."

The people of the Zhang family turned pale at these words. This meant that they were inescapably killed today. These bandits were going to kill them all.

"Leave no one alive!" The leader of the bandits' eyes flashed with a hint of ferocity.

"Dad, your daughter will come down and accompany you."

Miss Zhang shed tears as she pulled out a dagger, ready to commit suicide to avoid being dishonored by the bandits.

"In broad daylight, how dare you bandits to do this? You deserve to die!" Suddenly, a cold voice echoed in everyone's ears.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei took a step forward and charged into the circle of bandits.

"How dare you interfere in our business? Kill him!"

Although the bandits were somewhat surprised, they did not care about Lin Fei since he was just one person.

"Swish." Lin Fei swung his saber.

Suddenly, a white saber light flashed, and several bandits felt a coldness on their necks. Their heads had been separated from their bodies.

Blood spurted out, and the air was filled with a strong smell of blood.

"Bang, bang, bang."

With his nimble footwork and transcendent Flowing Clothes Skill, Lin Fei was like a fish in water in the midst of the group attack.

The bandits couldn't even touch the corner of his clothes.

Meanwhile, Lin Fei continued to decapitate them with his saber and knocked them out with his Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

"Great!"

Lin Fei felt a sense of excitement in his heart.

He had been practicing martial arts for such a long time, always "enduring" and constantly improving his strength through cultivation.

However, the number of times he had fought in a real battle was few, let alone being so invincible like now, fighting alone against dozens of fierce bandits.

Lin Fei had always suppressed himself, perhaps without even realizing it. But now, facing these bandits, Lin Fei had no mercy.

After all, these bandits were all stained with blood on their hands. They deserved to die! So, Lin Fei killed them without hesitation and with great pleasure.

He even got some unexpected surprises.

"Your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist has become more powerful as you fight, and you have thoroughly comprehended the concept of ferocity during the battles."

"Your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist has reached perfection through days of accumulation and one moment of enlightenment!"

A voice rang in Lin Fei's mind.

"Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist has reached perfection?" Lin Fei was pleasantly surprised.

It had been a long time since his Nine Shadow Saber Technique had reached perfection, but his Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had not improved at all. Even the guidance task for Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had not been removed from the mission hall.

But now, killing these bandits had unexpectedly led to the perfection of the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

"Ferocity concept?" Lin Fei received a memory.

Then, he instinctively used Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

"Boom!"

The fist struck out, and the air seemed to vibrate. In the ears of many, there was a deafening roar, as if a real dragon and elephant were roaring. This fist was truly ferocious to the extreme.

"Crack!"

Lin Fei's fist hit the saber of a bandit. The saber was made of high-quality steel, but it was still shattered by Lin Fei's fist. The bandit, along with his saber, flew out and his chest caved in. He was dead.

The power of Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist at the perfection level was so terrifying.

"Run!" The bandit leader was terrified and fled.

But Lin Fei was also fast, and his Flowing Clothes Skill allowed him to catch up to the leader in just a few steps.

Then, he slashed with his saber.

"Splurt!"

The bandit leader's head flew high into the air and fell to the ground with a thud.

The leader's body lay motionless on the ground, and the remaining bandits were too afraid to run anymore. They threw down their weapons and knelt on the ground.

39. Miss Zhang's Request

A note from RighteousEgg

Thanks for your review. Two chapter's here. Hope you enjoy them.

"Ah..." Lin Fei let out a sigh of relief.

He was covered in blood now, which looked quite terrifying. Of course, it was all the blood of those bandits. Lin Fei himself wasn't injured at all.

There were a lot of bodies lying on the ground. Even Lin Fei couldn't help but slightly tense up at the sight of so many bandits, all killed by him alone.

"Young hero." At this moment, a woman's voice came from behind Lin Fei. "Thank you for saving us, young hero."

The other people from the Zhang family also expressed their gratitude. Other members of the Zhang family also saluted him.

"It's just a matter of justice." Lin Fei didn't say much but began to search through the bodies of the bandits on the ground. However, apart from some cash, there wasn't even a single silver bill.

Lin Fei then realized that these bandits usually only accepted cash and wouldn't even bother with silver bills. Even if they got them, they wouldn't dare to exchange them at a bank.

Seeing Lin Fei searching through the dead bodies, the Zhang family members looked at each other in confusion.

At this point, the steward and his guards began interrogating the bandits.

"Which mountain bandit group are you from?"

"W-We're from the Black Cloud Fort."

"Black Cloud Fort? That's far from here, even from Luo City. How did you end up intercepting our Zhang family's team here?"

"We were sent on orders from our boss to intercept the Zhang family's team... Our boss and the second young master of the Zhang family in Luo City were conspiring on something."

As soon as the steward heard this, his face changed drastically. He quickly informed Miss Zhang about the information he had gained from interrogating the bandits.

Miss Zhang widened her eyes and trembled all over.

"Is... Is it Second Uncle? How could he dare to do this? Conspiring with bandits to intercept me."

Miss Zhang's eyes were lifeless as if she had suffered a great blow.

The butler couldn't help but say, "Master suddenly passed away, and you have been living in the old mansion in the countryside. The Zhang family's business in Luo City is naturally managed by Second Master. But these properties belong to the Master after all, always. Only after his death, can Second Master rightfully and completely obtain these properties."

In fact, without the butler's reminder, Miss Zhang already understood.

"Your boss has also come to Luo City?"

"Yes, our boss has also arrived."

The butler's face sank.

He whispered to Miss Zhang, "We're in trouble. The head of the Black Cloud Gang is said to be an acquired martial artist. And Second Master has conspired with the Black Cloud Gang. Even if we enter the city, I'm afraid we will fall into a trap.

As for reporting to the officials, it is useless. I'm afraid Second Master has already bought off the government. But if we return to the old mansion in the countryside, we won't be able to regain Master's property. And we have to be on guard against Second Master's men..."

The butler's face was full of worries. This was a dead end! The situation was very unfavorable for Miss Zhang.

"There may be a way. As long as Second Uncle dies, Father's property can naturally be recovered." Miss Zhang gritted her teeth and rallied.

"But Second Master is now in his prime, surrounded by many skilled people. How can we deal with him?" The butler was worried.

Miss Zhang's gaze fell on Lin Fei, who was still searching the corpses on the ground.

Just now, Lin Fei had single-handedly killed so many bandits. It was like a god descending to earth. It gave Miss Zhang a great shock!

So Miss Zhang walked straight toward Lin Fei.

"Young hero, we have a request." Miss Zhang approached Lin Fei from behind and said softly.

Lin Fei stood up and asked calmly, "What's the matter?"

"Young hero, my Second Uncle conspired with the Black Cloud Gang to intercept me in order to seize my father's property.

Now Second Uncle is in front of Luo City. I intend to take back the property, but I am weak and alone. I hope you can help me.

If we succeed, the Zhang family will offer 100,000 taels of silver. Here are 50,000 taels of silver bills as a deposit."

Miss Zhang gritted her teeth and spoke. After speaking, she looked at Lin Fei with a hint of expectation in her eyes.

The reason why they directly talked about silver was because of Lin Fei's performance. After these bandits died, Lin Fei was eager to search their bodies, which must have meant he was short on silver.

That was why Miss Zhang offered a sky-high price of 100,000 taels of silver. This amount would definitely make Lin Fei tempted, as it was an astronomical number.

Lin Fei was currently in dire need of money. But there was also a risk involved in this matter, so he didn't immediately agree.

Instead, he asked, "Miss Zhang, are there any strong men around your second uncle?"

"Yes, my second uncle colluded with the Black Cloud Gang bandits. And the big leader of the Black Cloud Gang is said to be an Acquired martial artist."

"Acquired... what level?"

Miss Zhang was a little hesitant.

The butler hurriedly spoke, "We do not know the specific levels. It is said that the boss of Black Cloud Gang only broke through to become an Acquired martial artist three years ago."

"Three years? That should not be more than Acquired three levels, or even, possibly just Acquired one or two levels." Lin Fei was also weighing on his heart.

The boss of Black Cloud Gang was a bandit after all. Cultivation speed would certainly not be much faster.

Although Lin Fei could be comparable to Acquired martial artists, and even be able to kill some of them. But he was not an Acquired martial artist after all.

Lin Fei would definitely take some risks once he agreed.

However, that was one hundred thousand taels of silver, equal to one hundred thousand contribution points.

This was not a small amount of money.

40. I'm Expensive

My Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist, vigorous and fierce, has just reached the realm of perfection. Moreover, my Nine Shadow Saber Technique could produce ten shadows with a single slash, even surpassing the realm of perfection.

In addition, my hard martial arts, Vajra Iron Cloth and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique make my strength and defense far superior to that of an ordinary Body Refining martial artist at the ninth level.

Even if it is an acquired martial artist at the first or second level, I can defeat them with a single slash!

Many thoughts flashed through Lin Fei's mind regarding his current strength. He was not completely unaware of it. On the contrary, he was very clear about it. His strength was sufficient to challenge acquired martial artists of higher levels.

There was even one acquired martial artist, the Wind Chasing Fragrance, who died in his hands. This risk was not a big deal for the sake of a hundred thousand taels of silver.

"Miss Zhang, I can promise you, but this is your internal matter in the Zhang family, and I, as an outsider, shouldn't interfere rashly. So, I have a win-win solution," Lin Fei said, considering his words carefully.

"What is the solution?" Miss Zhang asked.

"It's simple. You can offer me as a clan patron in the name of the Zhang family," Lin Fei said.

"Patron?" Miss Zhang's eyes lit up. "Our Zhang family originally had a patron. However, the patron was an inner disciple of Autumn Haze Mountain. But that inner disciple is no longer in Luo City. Also, he is the Zhang family's patron, and the second uncle is also a member of the Zhang family. If he intervenes, who knows whom he will help? So, if that's the case, I will offer you as clan patron in the name of the Zhang family!"

Miss Zhang made a decisive decision without any hesitation. After all, Lin Fei was the only person who could help her turn the tide.

"Wait, my conditions are not over yet. My patronage is expensive. One hundred thousand taels of silver per year. Will you accept it?" Lin Fei continued.

"One hundred thousand taels of silver per year?" Miss Zhang was slightly surprised. Although she had just promised to give Lin Fei one hundred thousand taels of silver, it was a one-time payment.

It included Lin Fei's gratitude for saving her life and helping her regain her estate. But Lin Fei's request for a patron was an annual payment. It was equivalent to the patronage of an acquired martial artist at the fourth level or above, and it also required the disciples from a famous sect with significant influence.

"I wonder about the identity of the young hero..." Miss Zhang asked cautiously, "After all, annual patronage of one hundred thousand taels of silver was not a small matter. Even with the financial resources of the Zhang family, we must be cautious."

"I am Lin Fei, a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect's inner sect, at the ninth level of Body Refining," Lin Fei did not hide his identity.

"Hmm? Ninth level of Body Refining?" Miss Zhang widened her eyes as if to have discovered something remarkable.

Just now, Lin Fei alone had killed dozens of bandits, including those at the seventh level or higher of Body Refining, and even the leader who was at the ninth level.

Lin Fei had crushed them like cutting vegetables. Even an acquired martial artist could not have done that.

Miss Zhang had always thought that Lin Fei was an acquired martial artist, but she didn't expect that he was at the ninth level of Body Refining, and also a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect's inner sect.

The Nine Profound Sect was a large sect, not inferior to the Autumn Haze Mountain. In fact, the Nine Profound Sect's influence had surpassed that of the Autumn Haze Mountain in recent years.

Miss Zhang was smart and naturally understood that with Lin Fei's ninth level of Body Refining, he dared to assist her in dealing with acquired warriors, which meant that he must have had some backing.

A Body Refining martial artist that was comparable to an acquired martial artist! Lin Fei's potential was unimaginable.

"Alright, we will offer a patronage of one hundred thousand taels of silver per year to Young Hero Lin!" Miss Zhang readily agreed.

As for the disciple of Autumn Haze Mountain that they had been offering patronage to, Miss Zhang had already decided that once they reclaimed their property, they would no longer offer patronage to that disciple. They would focus all their efforts on offering patronage to Lin Fei.

Lin Fei nodded in satisfaction. As long as he helped Miss Zhang regain her property, the combined annual offerings from the Zhang family and the Chen family would amount to 160,000 silver once he reached the acquired realm in the future.

This was a sum that many acquired realm disciples of the Nine Profound Sect couldn't even dream of receiving. Perhaps only those above the acquired realm seven level could get such a large amount of offerings.

Of course, the premise was that Lin Fei could help Miss Zhang regain her property. If he failed to do so, everything would be in vain.

"All right, Miss Zhang, we can't delay any longer. Let's set off now. We need to catch them off guard before Black Cloud Gang and your uncle respond!"

"Okay, let's go immediately!" Miss Zhang made a prompt decision. She had staked everything she had, almost all her wealth and even her life, on Lin Fei. If they failed this time, she would have no way out.

It was not easy to make such a tough decision for her.

So, the Zhang family and the entourage rushed toward Luo City at the fastest speed possible. Even Miss Zhang rode a horse.

Finally, after several hours, they managed to enter Luo City before the city gates closed.

41. The Power Of Ten Shadows With A Single Slash

Zhang Mansion, Luo City.

Second Master Zhang and the Black Cloud Gang leader were waiting quietly in the hall.

The Black Cloud Gang leader, Zhao Yihu, dressed in black, was able to remain calm. But Second Master Zhang was a bit restless.

He stood up and paced back and forth in the hall. A hint of impatience appeared on his face.

"It's getting late, and the city gates are about to close. Why haven't your men returned yet? Has something happened?" Second Master Zhang asked Zhao Yihu.

Zhao Yihu raised his head. There was a bold scar from the corner of his eye to his left cheek.

"Don't worry, Second Master. It's just a girl and some guards. All of the guards did not even have one Body Refining seventh level. What could go wrong? Let's just wait."

After thinking it over, Second Master Zhang agreed.

The situation was basically under control since he had taken care of the government, business partners, and even some family relationships.

Only his niece, who was still in her teens, remained. She almost had no experience and could not pose a threat to him.

Suddenly, a cry came from outside the door. Several servants rushed back in a panic.

"Second Master, they've broken in!"

Second Master Zhang stood up abruptly.

Even Zhao Yihu's eyes flashed with surprise.

"Did Second and Third Brothers fail?" Zhao Yihu frowned.

He had sent his second and third-in-command, the strongest in the gang besides himself.

The second-in-command was even a ninth-level Body Refiner. How could they fail against a Miss Zhang?

Soon, a group of people came into the Zhang family living room from outside. The leader was disheveled and haggard-looking Miss Zhang.

"You..."

Second Master Zhang's face gradually turned dark as soon as he saw Miss Zhang.

Miss Zhang stared at Second Master Zhang with cold eyes, "Uncle, surprised to see me back? This weak woman who traveled from a remote village didn't die on the way, disappointing you."

Her eyes were icy and her tone was quite impolite.

"Well, since it has come to this, I have nothing to hide anymore. The Zhang family's assets were built up by your father and me through hard work. But when your father died, you, a little girl, suddenly want to inherit the business. How could it be?

I advised your father to leave you a small stake and let me take care of the business, but your father refused. He even wanted to drive me out of the Zhang family.

Since that's the case, then don't blame me for being ruthless and sending your father on his way."

Second Master Zhang's expression twisted and his appearance was very terrifying.

"What? My father was killed by you?"

Zhang's face turned pale, staring at Second Master Zhang as if she couldn't believe it.

"Hahaha, so what if it was me? Not only your father but also you will die today!" Second Master Zhang waved his hand.

Suddenly, many martial artists surrounded the hall, making it impossible to escape.

"Miss Zhang, there's no point in saying more." Lin Fei glanced at Miss Zhang.

This woman was very strong. But being strong was not enough in this situation. Power was the most important.

"I'm curious, how did you escape from the hands of my Second and Third Brother's men and return to Luo City?"

At this moment, Zhao Yihu, the leader of the Black Cloud Gang, slowly spoke up. And his gaze was fixed on Lin Fei.

"Acquired martial artist!" Lin Fei calmly said, "It seems that you are Zhao Yihu, the leader of the Black Cloud Gang. I'll send you to meet other bandits!"

Lin Fei took a step forward, his Flowing Clothes Skill's agile body technique allowing him to cross a distance of more than ten feet in an instant. In an instant, he arrived in front of Zhao Yihu.

"You're looking for death!" Zhao Yihu didn't dodge or evade and punched out.

With a loud "bang," the two fists collided, causing a muffled sound to reverberate throughout the hall. Lin Fei's arm went numb, but it didn't become as limp as it did last time.

This time, Lin Fei's inner power, including his blood, muscles, and skin, had all been greatly enhanced compared to last time, and he was certain that the Black Cloud Gang Leader Zhao Yihu probably only got to acquired second level, which wasn't much stronger than the Wind Chasing Fragrance.

But even with Lin Fei's greatly improved physical abilities, he still couldn't withstand the full force of Zhao Yihu's inner power. Another blow from Zhao Yihu and Lin Fei's arm would have been disabled.

However, Lin Fei had his saber, and he risked getting close to Zhao Yihu in order to wait for the perfect opportunity.

With a swift motion, Lin Fei drew his saber from his right hand and used the Nine Shadow Saber Technique to create ten shadows with a single slash.

Zhao Yihu had only a feeling.

Fast. Ultimate fast!

He could not even barely keep up with Lin Fei's saber shadow. He only felt a cold sensation around his neck and then his eyes widened as he couldn't say a word.

"Chop!"

Zhao Yihu's head fell to the ground, and blood spurted out, filling the hall with a pungent smell of blood.

42. Leave

With a thud, Zhao Yihu's head fell to the ground and even rolled a bit.

Everyone was stunned, even Miss Zhang was having trouble believing what she had just seen.

Lin Fei had beheaded Zhao Yihu with just one swing of his saber!

Zhao Yihu was a powerful acquired martial artist, even if Miss Zhang had confidence in Lin Fei, this was too fast!

The bandits who were present were the first to panic. They didn't even think about avenging Zhao Yihu. If an acquired martial artist had even been killed, what chance would they have?

Thus, the bandits of the Black Cloud Gang dispersed and fled in all directions.

Only a few martial artists recruited by Second Master Zhang remained, but they were hesitant and didn't dare to approach.

Second Master Zhang's eyes turned red, and he shouted, "Quickly, he's only one! He's now exhausted!"

But as soon as he finished speaking, Lin Fei's figure flashed like a ghost, and he had already arrived in front of him.

With the transcendent Flowing Clothes Skill, Lin Fei's footwork was truly extraordinary, especially in a narrow environment, where he was like a fish in water.

With a swish, Lin Fei swung his saber, and ten saber shadows flashed by.

Second Master Zhang couldn't resist at all, he just stared with wide eyes and a hint of fear on his face.

As death approached, he finally became afraid, but it was too late. His head fell to the ground, just like Zhao Yihu.

After Zhao Yihu and Second Master Zhang were both dead, only a few guards and recruited martial artists remained. Miss Zhang shouted, "The mastermind is dead, quickly put down your weapons and you may be spared!"

Immediately, some people threw down their weapons and surrendered. "I surrender, don't kill me," they said. "I just arrived at Zhang family, what Second Master Zhang did has nothing to do with me..."

In a short time, the situation was settled. Zhang's house was back in Miss Zhang's hands.

"I didn't expect Zhao Yihu to be so vulnerable," someone said. "It seems that Miss Zhang should be safe now."

"As for the remaining matters of taking over Zhang's family, it depends on Miss Zhang's ability," another person said.

Lin Fei put away the saber and went to Miss Zhang's side. Miss Zhang didn't know what to say.

Was Zhao Yihu really that weak? Were acquired martial artists really that vulnerable? No, it was just that Lin Fei was too strong.

"Master Lin, it's not that Zhao Yihu was too weak, it's that you're too strong!" Miss Zhang said excitedly. "The situation of Zhang's family is settled now. Master Lin, you can rest here for a while. Leave the rest to me."

With Lin Fei's cooperation, Miss Zhang managed to control the situation in Zhang's family. She sorted out the accounts and cleared out Second Master Zhang's loyalists. It all went smoothly.

Lin Fei obtained an acquired skill from Zhao Yihu's body, which was just an ordinary acquired skill. He took only one glance and lost interest.

In this world, most high-level martial arts were found in major sects, like the Nine Profound Sect, for example. There were only a handful of secret manuals of martial arts outside of those sects.

It wasn't as if anyone could just happen to come across them. Obviously, Zhao Yihu did not have that kind of luck, or else he wouldn't have lost his life in Lin Fei's hands.

Lin Fei flexed his arm a bit and noticed that it only swelled up a little this time. It would probably recover within a few days, and he wouldn't have to go through the pain he experienced when he fought the Wind Chasing Fragrance. This made him have a hunch about inner power.

"Inner power may be powerful, but it is not omnipotent. When the tendons, fascia, blood, and qi are strong enough, they can withstand inner power. Therefore, no matter how high I advance in acquired skills in the future, physical fitness is still very important." Lin Fei had a moment of clarity.

Days passed, and Lin Fei did not leave Luo City immediately. Instead, he waited for three more days. During that time, Miss Zhang gradually gained control over the Zhang family's businesses and completely took over them.

Lin Fei prepared to say goodbye to Miss Zhang. "Miss Zhang, since you've taken control of the Zhang family's businesses, I should take my leave now."

Miss Zhang looked a little tired, but her eyes still shone. She knew she couldn't keep Lin Fei forever; he would leave sooner or later.

"Thank you for staying at the Zhang Mansion these past few days, Lin Fei. If not for you, I wouldn't have been able to take control of the Zhang family's businesses in such a short time."

During that time, Miss Zhang also spread some information about Lin Fei. Such as Lin Fei was an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect and a patron of the Zhang family and so on.

With Lin Fei's presence, those who coveted the Zhang family and wanted to cause trouble would also fear him and not dare to act easily.

"Bring the silver bills over here."

Soon, the steward brought over the silver ticket. Lin Fei took a look and was surprised, "One hundred fifty thousand taels?"

Miss Zhang replied, "I decided to give you a year's patronage in advance. You've helped me so much. I've also counted the Zhang family's businesses during this time, and there was quite a bit of silver. So, I decided to give it to you all at once."

Lin Fei nodded and put away the silver bills. Miss Zhang had given him fifty thousand taels before, and with this one hundred fifty thousand, he now had two hundred thousand taels.

"I won't refuse then. If anything happens, send a letter to the Nine Profound Sect. Goodbye, Miss Zhang."

With that, Lin Fei turned and left on his horse, quickly disappearing from sight.

Watching Lin Fei's departing figure, Miss Zhang's eyes shone with a mysterious light. "It would be nice if you could stay forever, but you're not one to be satisfied with the mundane. Even if I were to give you everything I have, you still wouldn't stay..."

"Well, with Lin Fei as my patron, I can safeguard the foundation of the Zhang family at least..." Miss Zhang gritted her teeth, and her unrealistic thoughts vanished completely.

43. Return To The Lin Family

"I'm back."

A few days later, Lin Fei finally returned to his family home in Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

"Father, mother."

Lin Fei saw his parents in the hall.

"By the way, where is big brother? Why haven't I seen him?"

"Your older brother is busy with business. Since you opened up the business for our family last time, our family's business has been very busy. Your older brother leaves early and comes home late every day."

Lin Fei nodded.

After chatting with his parents for a while, he left and went to the secluded rooms in the back yard, where Lin Miao lived.

Lin Fei didn't say much to his parents about Lin Miao. He just told them to keep their distance and not to come to this area. This was set as a restricted area, and no one was allowed to enter without permission.

So Lin Fei found it very quiet when he arrived. There wasn't a single servant from the Lin family around.

"Creak."

Lin Fei opened the door.

"Young master?"

Lin Miao was sitting cross-legged in the room, seemingly meditating.

When he saw Lin Fei, Lin Miao's eyes showed a hint of surprise.

"Not bad, are you cultivating?" asked Lin Fei.

"Yes, young master. Why have you come back?" replied Lin Miao.

Lin Fei knew that Lin Miao had been very obedient during this period and had hardly left the Lin family.

Rather than answering directly, Lin Fei continued to ask, "Have you reached the first level of the Zombie-refining Technique?"

"I'm sorry to disappoint you, young master. Although I have made some progress during this time, I still haven't been able to reach the first level," replied Lin Miao, shaking his head.

The first level of the Zombie-refining Technique corresponded to the first level of Qi Condensation. In fact, Qi cultivation was much more difficult than martial arts cultivation.

Each level of improvement was very difficult, so talent was very important. Qi cultivators paid more attention to talent, as it directly determined their achievements.

With Lin Miao's aptitude, if he progressed step by step, he would probably find it very difficult to break through to the fourth level of Qi Condensation. At most, he would only be able to reach the third level.

This showed how difficult Qi condensation was.

"However, you should have spiritual power now, right?" asked Lin Fei suddenly.

The acquired martial artists possess inner power, while the innate martial artists possess innate inner power. As for the Qi Cultivators, they possess spiritual power.

"I do have spiritual power, but not much," Lin Miao said honestly.

"So, you can control zombies now?" Lin Fei's heart skipped a beat.

"Not quite. I need at least get to the first level before I can try to control them," Lin Miao replied.

"How long do you think it will take you to reach the first level of the Zombie-refining Technique?" Lin Fei pondered for a moment and asked.

"Master, this place is not suitable for cultivation. Especially for the Zombie-refining Technique, it is better to cultivate in places with stronger Yin Qi to achieve better results. If I practice here, it will take about three years to reach the first level," Lin Miao said.

"Three years..." Lin Fei fell silent upon hearing this.

"Forget it, let's give it a try anyway," Lin Fei finally decided.

After all, Lin Miao was just a tool for alchemy. It didn't matter how strong he could become through cultivation. What Lin Fei needed was the pill.

"Starting from tomorrow, you will try to refine pills according to this prescription. This is the most basic pill that Body Refining martial artists needs," Lin Fei said. "I will buy all the materials and furnaces for you, and even some books on simple alchemy techniques. Your goal is only one. At all costs, refine the Blood-Increasing Pill for me!"

"Yes, young master. I will try tomorrow," Lin Miao nodded in agreement.

Lin Fei left and returned to his room.

"System," He called up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Art Realm: Body Refining Ninth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Ninth Level (1% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (18% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Eighth Level (1% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Seventh Level (48% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Lin Fei glanced at the panel and realized that the only thing he could still improve was the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique.

However, the Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique could now only increase the practice progress by 1% per day. Once it reached the eighth level, Lin Fei estimated that even 1% progress per day cannot be achieved.

As for the Vajra Iron Cloth, it still required more expensive medicinal baths. Despite having a hundred thousand taels of silver, Lin Fei must prioritize Lin Miao's alchemy and not squander it easily.

"Well, I'd better focus on cultivating the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique to produce the inner power first. Then go and practice the Vajra Iron Cloth and the Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique," Lin Fei made up his mind.

The next day, Lin Fei had a large amount of medicinal materials purchased, all of which were the raw materials for the Blood-Increasing Pill. He would personally supervise Lin Miao and let him try alchemy.

The pill furnace, materials, and everything were all ready. Last night, Lin Miao also read some alchemy books and basically mastered some basic alchemical techniques. He was ready to give it a try.

"Young master, I'm ready," Lin Miao said.

"Okay, let's begin," Lin Fei replied, staring closely at the pill furnace beside Lin Miao.

44. Alchemy

"Fire!"

Lin Miao lit the firewood under the furnace, added some coal to raise the temperature. Gradually, the furnace became extremely hot. Then, he proceeded step by step, throwing some medicinal materials into the furnace according to the proportion of the Blood-Increasing Pill recipe.

As time passed, the inside of the furnace became blazing red, and the raw materials of those medicinal materials gradually turned into a sticky liquid. At this point, it was up to the Qi cultivator or innate expert to take action.

Alchemy required controlling the temperature and the final condensation of the pill, which needed to be manually controlled. Innate martial artists could use their innate inner power to control it because it could be released to external. Likewise, Qi cultivators could also do the same by extending their spiritual power into the furnace.

As for Body Refining martial artists or acquired martial artists, they could only watch. Although acquired warriors had inner power, they could not release it externally, so they could not refine the pill.

Lin Miao urged his own spiritual power to extend into the furnace and began to protect the liquid medicine, even shielding it from the burning heat.

This was the control of temperature, knowing when to heat up and when to cool down, which required the skill of an alchemist.

As time passed, Lin Miao continued to maintain his spiritual power, but it was too weak, and he had not even reached the first level of Qi Condensation.

If he were to refine pills needed by Qi cultivators, it would be impossible. However, just refining the Blood-Increasing Pill was enough for Lin Miao's spiritual power to hold up.

After just a quarter of an hour, a strange fragrance floated out of the furnace.

"Has the pill been formed?" Lin Fei stared at the furnace intently.

"Hoo..." Lin Miao retracted his spiritual power and collapsed to the ground as if he were completely exhausted. "Young master, I... I'm exhausted. My spiritual power has been almost completely depleted and need a whole day to recover. So I can only refine the Blood-Increasing Pill once a day at most."

Lin Miao's voice was trembling, obviously pushed to the limit. Even the last bit of time was forced.

"Lin Miao, you've worked hard today." Lin Fei glanced at Lin Miao, then turned his attention to the furnace.

He had no confidence in whether or not the pill had formed.

"Open!" Lin Fei used a tool to open the lid of the furnace all at once, and the lid fell to the ground. A strong fragrance emanated, but there seemed to be a burnt smell mixed in with it.

Lin Fei approached the furnace and took a look. Inside the furnace was completely paste-like, black, and messy.

"Failed?" Lin Fei was disappointed.

Lin Miao struggled to get up and also looked disappointed when he saw the situation inside the furnace.

"Young master, My fault. I couldn't control the temperature properly, which caused the refining to fail." Lin Miao lowered his head.

"Not necessarily a failure," Lin Fei said as he took out his tools and began searching inside the furnace.

Finally, he found three pills among the black residue.

"You succeeded. Three Blood-Increasing Pills," Lin Fei said with a smile.

"However, I need to test them first," he added and swallowed one of the pills directly.

His massive blood qi quickly began to refine the Blood-Increasing Pill as a hot stream flowed through his body.

"Your Giant Whale Body Refining Technique has absorbed the effect of the Blood-Increasing Pill, and its progress has increased by one-thousandth."

The system's voice sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

"It works!" Lin Fei exclaimed, "But its effect on me is too small. One pill can only increase the progress of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique by one thousandth. To reach the limit of body refining and acquire inner power, I would need to take at least one thousand pills."

Lin Fei calculated the cost. According to the price of the Nine Profound Sect's Blood-Increasing Pills, one pill required one thousand contribution points, and that was already a fifty percent discount for inner disciples. To obtain one thousand pills, he would need one million contribution points, equivalent to one million taels of silver!

This was an astronomical figure.

How many tasks would he need to complete to accumulate so many contribution points? Using Blood-Increasing Pills for the purpose of practicing the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was too extravagant.

Without them, Lin Fei would have to endure the slow progress of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, which might take several days or even a month to improve by one percent.

It would take years, even more than ten years, to reach the acquired realm.

There were many disciples in the inner sect who took years to advance from the ninth level of Body Refining to the acquired realm.

Lin Fei couldn't bear such slow progress.

"The cost of the medicinal materials used in that furnace shouldn't exceed one hundred taels of silver, but Lin Miao still refined three Blood-Increasing Pills," Lin Fei murmured to himself. "At this rate, I could get one thousand Blood-Increasing Pills with no more than forty thousand taels of silver. What a huge profit!"

He was amazed by the incredible profitability of alchemy.

With only forty thousand taels of silver, he could refine one thousand Blood-Increasing Pills, while the Nine Profound Sect sold them for one million taels of silver.

Of course, there was an important reason for this price difference - the alchemist.

Which innate expert would spend all day refining Blood-Increasing Pills?

And which Qi Condensation cultivator would refine pills every day?

It would only hinder their own cultivation.

Only Lin Fei, who controlled Lin Miao, could make him refine Blood-Increasing Pills instead of cultivating himself.

Lin Fei couldn't help but feel grateful for his decision to keep Lin Miao alive.

45. The Marriage Contract

A note from RighteousEgg

Oh, marriage. Clichés?

However, there was one troublesome matter, speed.

The speed of the pills that Lin Miao refined was too slow. He could only refine once a day. And only three pills could be made each time.

How long would it take to refine a thousand pills? At least a year.

One year was too long.

"Lin Miao, you only refine once a day?" Lin Fei frowned and asked.

"Well..." Lin Miao thought for a moment and said in a deep voice, "I can restore my spiritual power quickly in a place with heavy Yin Qi and I will refine more than once a day. I could even refine two, three times, or even more."

Lin Fei nodded.

With more refining times and a proficient technique, the number of pills made each time would also increase.

By then, it wouldn't take so long to refine a thousand Blood-Increasing Pills.

"Where is a place with heavy Yin Qi?" Lin Fei asked again.

"Young master, you don't have to go look for a place specifically. I saw a formation in the zombie-refining technique called the Yin Gathering Formation. The formation is very simple, and I should be able to set it up.

However, the materials needed to set up the formation are a bit special. We need corpses to set up it. There are corpse puppets around, but only five of them. To set up the Yin Gathering Formation, we need at least nine corpses." Lin Miao explained.

Lin Fei fell into deep thought. There were still four corpses.

"I'll get you the remaining four corpses. During this time, focus on studying the refining technique and try to increase the number of pills made each time." Lin Fei said.

"Yes, young master." Lin Miao nodded and Lin Fei left the backyard directly.

Lin Fei was considering the matter of four corpses. Where could he get four corpses from? It would be great if he were in Luo City.

Back when Lin Fei killed the bandits, there were more than just four of them. However, it didn't matter if there were no bandits.

For Lin Fei, getting four corpses was not a difficult task.

Nowadays, it was not peaceful. People die every day.

The mass graves outside the city were piled up with bodies like mountains.

Having the Lin family's servants drag back four corpses was not a difficult task at all.

So, Lin Fei found the steward of the Lin family.

"Steward, find four people and have them go to the mass graves outside the city to drag back four corpses. Just put them in the side courtyards at the back, and someone will take care of them. This is fifty taels of silver. You can give it to the servants as a reward."

"Thank you, Young Master. Please rest assured, I will arrange it right away." The steward took the silver.

Fifty taels. The servants would be eager to do it. It was just transporting corpses, there was no danger.

In the afternoon, a familiar voice sounded outside Lin Fei's door.

"Bro, you're finally back," At this time, Lin Wen, the elder brother, finally finished his busy work and returned to the Lin family.

"Elder Brother, was there any trouble with your business?" Lin Fei asked.

"Hahaha, now everyone knows that our Lin family has an Inner Sect disciple of the Nine Profound Sect. Who dares to make trouble?

Brother, come on, let's go to the hall. Father and I have been worrying about you all this time. There is a good thing."

"A good thing? What good thing?"

"You'll find out when you get there."

Lin Wen was quite mysterious.

So, Lin Fei followed his elder brother to the hall.

In the hall, their parents were also smiling. There was also an old woman who looked to be around fifty years old.

"This must be the Second Young Master, right?" The old woman was also scrutinizing Lin Fei.

And, with a wave of her hand, a middle-aged man dressed as a scholar next to her actually took out a pen and paper and began to draw.

"Father, Mother. What's going on?" Lin Fei's brow furrowed slightly.

"Fei, this is Wang Po."

"We have arranged a marriage for you and I guarantee you will be satisfied. Therefore, we need your portrait to show to the lady. Likewise, the lady also has a portrait for you to see."

"Marriage?" Lin Fei had forgotten about this.

At his age, he should have settled down and started a family in this world. Especially for a wealthy merchant family like the Lin family.

"Father, mother, I just want to focus on martial arts now."

Lin Fei had no intention of getting married at the moment.

"Practicing martial arts and getting married doesn't have to be mutually exclusive. So many inner disciples of the Nine Profound Sect, even the talented ones, have gotten married. Which one of them hasn't married?"

Lin Fei opened his mouth to argue, but couldn't.

Indeed, most of the inner disciples of the Nine Profound Sect had gotten married.

They were just practicing martial arts alone in the Nine Profound Sect.

Only a small portion of the disciples was fully dedicated to practicing martial arts.

"Second brother, I know that people who practice martial arts have their own ideas. So, we talked to your father and decided to find you a suitable match, and you will definitely be satisfied.

In fact, this marriage proposal was not initiated by us. The girl's family approached our Lin family.

She is the daughter of the prefect, and the prefect has one son and three daughters, with only the youngest daughter, Wang Xuan, unmarried.

Wang Xuan, like you, is practicing martial arts in the sect. However, she joined Autumn Haze Mountain and entered the inner sect last year.

Both you and she are practitioners of martial arts, so you will definitely be satisfied with this marriage.

Take a look at the portrait. Her appearance and background are both excellent.

Moreover, this marriage proposal can be considered a high-level match for our Lin family. It is also because the prefect sees your potential and bright future that his daughter is willing to marry into our family."

Lin Fei glanced at the portrait.

The woman in the portrait was indeed quite beautiful. And her temperament was spirited, making her pleasing to anyone's eyes.

46. Yin Gathering Formation

A note from RighteousEgg

Hi everyone, I wanted to recommend a book called "Dark Magus: LitRPG Fantasy Adventure".

I was really captivated by the fast-paced, action-packed story, which combines elements of gaming, fantasy, and adventure to create a truly immersive reading experience.

I highly recommend "Dark Magus" to anyone who enjoys reading LitRPG or fantasy adventure stories. It's a great read, and I think you'll really enjoy it!

Dark Magus (LitRPG Fantasy Adventure)

Dark Magus is a fun and humorous adventure with some LitRPG elements like stat boxes, classes, loot, and a boatload of magic. There will be dungeons, progression, and the occasional murder mystery.

After being cast out of his home, and removed from his office as Arch-Magus of the Queen, Olivander Casumus searches for a new direction to take his life. A chance encounter with a young man failing the most basic of guild contracts leads him to a new adventure, just when he thought he had seen it all.

Gregory of Demering is an aspiring guild member with his sights set on Gold rank. He wants to be a powerful knight, capable and trustworthy. The only problem is that the first Class he earned was "Coward." When he meets Olivander while out on a guild contract, the crutch he has leaned on for years literally burns away, and he's catapulted into a new adventure.

Cooper is a dog who just can't help but find awful places to fall asleep. With a life dedicated to chasing balls, napping, and begging people for food, he's surprised to suddenly be dragged along on an adventure with two humans, who, as far as he can tell, don't realize he's just a dog.

While Lin Fei was still hesitating, his mother spoke up, "Fei, it's not just a matter of whether you want to or not. It depends on whether Wang Xuan is willing or not.

Wang Xuan has returned to Zhou Mountain Mansion recently. Your portrait will also be shown to her. If Wang Xuan is satisfied, there is a possibility for this marriage to continue."

Lin Fei understood. There was a gap between the Lin family and the prefect's family.

After all, the prefect was a high-ranking official. The point was whether Wang Xuan was willing to choose Lin Fei, not the other way around.

"Leave it to mother and father to arrange." Lin Fei did not refuse directly.

Even if he refused, it would be useless. His parents had ways to make him agree.

Wang Xuan might not like him either. So, Lin Fei was not too worried.

"Master Lin, Madam Lin, the portrait of your second young master is done. Can you take a look and see if it's satisfactory?" At this moment, the painter handed Lin Fei's portrait to his parents.

Lin's father and mother were very satisfied and gave some silver to Wang Po with a smile.

Wang Po then left the Lin mansion with the painter.

Lin Fei didn't pay much attention to the matter. He went straight to Lin Miao's residence.

"Oh? The body has been brought back?"

Lin Fei immediately felt a cold and eerie atmosphere had just arrived at the side courtyard.

It wasn't a temperature coldness, but rather the feeling that the whole side courtyard was ominous.

"The body was brought back this afternoon. I have already arranged it into a Yin Gathering Formation."

"How's the effect?"

Lin Fei saw five corpse puppets and four corpses arranged on the ground in a special way.

"The effect is very good. With the Yin Gathering Formation, my spiritual power is recovering very quickly. With this recovery speed, I can restore all of my spiritual power immediately and refine another furnace of pills."

Lin Fei shook his head and said, "There's no need to be in such a hurry. You should first study the techniques of refining elixirs. Can you estimate how many times you can refine the elixir in a day with the Yin Gathering Formation?"

Lin Fei was more concerned about the number of times the pills could be refined.

Lin Miao pondered for a moment and said, "If I recover at this speed and put all my effort into refining, I can refine five times a day!"

"Five times?" Lin Fei calculated silently and seemed very satisfied.

"Good. Rest well tonight and study the technique. Tomorrow, start full force on refining the Blood-Increasing Pill," he said. "Make sure to produce one thousand Blood-Increasing Pills in the shortest possible time."

"Young master, rest assured. I will complete the task of refining one thousand Blood-Increasing Pills as soon as possible," Lin Miao said.

Lin Fei nodded and then returned to his room to rest. He was quite an at ease with Lin Miao. Lin Miao was a smart person who knew that he had to satisfy Lin Fei's needs to the fullest if he wanted to be valuable. Lin Fei wouldn't care about someone who had no value.

Of course, Lin Miao also wanted to show his value, and this alchemy was an opportunity. If he could satisfy Lin Fei, then he wouldn't have to live in fear anymore.

...

In the Zhou Mountain Mansion City prefect's office, the prefect handed a portrait to Wang Xuan and asked with a smile, "Xuan, what do you think of Lin Fei?"

Wang Xuan was dressed in tight armor, holding a long sword, and looked heroic. She took the portrait and shook her head, saying, "Father, I don't like this type. Besides, I heard that he only recently entered the Nine Profound Sect's inner sect and is only at the seventh level of body refining. It's probably difficult for him to advance to the acquired realm in the future. Do you really want your daughter to marry him?"

The prefect waved his hand helplessly and let the matchmaker and others leave. Only he and Wang Xuan were left in the living room.

The prefect sighed and said, "Daughter, you know that your father, as a prefect, is currently facing a lot of difficulties. The court is in turmoil, and there are countless bandits outside. If it weren't for the support of the aristocratic families and wealthy merchants here in Zhou Mountain Mansion City, I wouldn't even be able to stand firm in this place.

This Lin Fei is a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect's inner sect. He recently opened up the Lin family's business route and even defeated the bandits in the Nine Ring Mountains. He should have some skills.

Moreover, the Lin family is the local tyrant in Zhou Mountain Mansion City, with money, grains, and people. This is the best match that I can find for you in the city.

Xuan, you shouldn't be stubborn anymore."

The prefect's decision to marry into the Lin family was not a whim. He had considered multiple factors.

"Father, I understand your difficulties, so I have made connections with some talented people at Autumn Haze Mountain," Wang Xuan said.

"Especially after I entered the inner sect, I met Senior Brother Liu Hao.

Senior Brother Liu Hao has already acquired the third level, and perhaps it won't be long before he reaches the fourth level.

Moreover, his family has close relations with Autumn Haze Mountain and even has an innate powerhouse in his ancestry.

Senior Brother Liu Hao and I are in a relationship. Estimate that he will come to propose in a while. This time I came down the mountain to talk to Father about this.

Senior Brother Liu Hao is stronger than Lin Fei in every aspect. As for the Lin family, they are just a wealthy merchant family. How can they compare to the Liu family?

If Father is worried about bandits near the city, Senior Brother Liu Hao would sweep them away."

There was a look of pride in Wang Xuan's beautiful eyes,

The prefect's eyes also lit up.

It seemed that sending Wang Xuan to Autumn Haze Mountain was the right decision. His daughter did not disappoint his expectations.

Not only had she improved her martial arts skills, but she had also already chosen a suitable husband.

Moreover, both his background and martial arts qualifications were excellent choices.

"What about the Lin family..."

"Father, you can just say that I have seen Lin Fei's portrait and am not interested. Then the Lin family will naturally understand."

"Well...it can only be done this way." The prefect secretly nodded.

47. One Thousand Blood-Increasing Pills

The next day, Lin Fei was summoned to the hall.

"Fei, you need to be mentally prepared for your marriage."

Lin's father weighed the matter for a long time, hesitating as if he wanted to say something but stopped.

Lin Fei's heart moved. It seemed that there was something wrong with his marriage.

"Father, tell me, what's the matter?"

"Lord Prefect has sent a message. After seeing your portrait, Wang Xuan was not very interested, so..."

Lin's father's voice also gradually lowered.

Lin's mother seemed to be complaining, "What's wrong with my son? He is handsome and also an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect. Even if she is the daughter of the prefect, my son is also worthy..."

Lin's mother continued to chatter, showing some dissatisfaction.

However, Lin Fei appeared very calm. He even breathed a sigh of relief in his heart.

"Fei, you..." Lin's parents were still worried.

"Father. Mother. Don't worry, I'm fine. Since Wang Xuan is not interested, we don't need to force it." After speaking, Lin Fei bid farewell and left.

Watching Lin Fei leave, Lin's mother was somewhat reluctant, "Master, Lord Prefect is really overdoing it this time. He was the one who first proposed a marriage alliance with our Lin family. How could he..."

"Okay, stop talking. In fact, this may not be a bad thing. Didn't you see that Fei was already dissatisfied with this marriage? Maybe Fei already has someone in mind."

Lin's father said meaningfully.

"Oh? Fei has someone in mind, most likely a disciple from the Nine Profound Sect. Perhaps it's one of his senior sisters?" Lin's mother's eyes lit up.

"We don't need to bother about who exactly it is. Fei has more independence than us..." Lin's father's expression was calm.

However, there was obviously a hint of dissatisfaction in his eyes. The prefect's actions really showed that he didn't take the Lin family seriously.

But the other party was prefect. For such trivial matters, the Lin family had no choice.

Although Lin Fei had already left the hall. His senses were keen.

Lin Fei could still hear his parents' conversation even from a distance.

"They think I have someone in mind? Well, this is good too. I can have a peaceful time for a while." Lin Fei murmured in a low voice.

He knew he didn't have anyone in mind.

Thinking about it, Lin Fei's mind involuntarily conjured up a figure.

Ling Yao!

He would rather marry Ling Yao if he really had to.

Lin Fei shook his head. It wasn't time to think about these things yet.

He went directly to Lin Miao's sideyard and watched Lin Miao refine the Blood-Increasing Pill.

Lin Miao set up the Yin Gathering Formation, which was indeed effective.

After a whole day, he had successfully refined it five times, and each time, he produced around ten pills.

In one day, he could refine a total of fifty Blood-Increasing Pills.

At this rate, Lin Miao would be able to refine one thousand Blood-Increasing Pills in twenty days.

Moreover, even with the consumption of alchemy furnaces, medicinal materials, and other expenses, it would not exceed forty thousand taels of silver.

Lin Fei was very satisfied. He brought back the fifty Blood-Increasing Pills he had refined on the first day to his room.

He swallowed ten Blood-Increasing Pills at once.

"Buzz."

Suddenly, the qi and blood in Lin Fei's body shook.

The Giant Whale Body Refining Technique was also automatically operated.

Ten Blood-Increasing Pills at once were too easy for Lin Fei now. His huge qi and blood could almost be refined instantly.

Moreover, even ten Blood-Increasing Pills could only improve the cultivation progress of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique by 1% for him now.

Lin Fei could fully absorb all fifty Blood-Increasing Pills in one day.

"Twenty days, and I will be able to give birth to inner power!" Lin Fei murmured in a low voice, a gleam of determination flashing in his eyes.

He had been waiting for this day for a long time and the thought of it made his heart burn with excitement.

As time passed, Lin Fei took Blood-Increasing Pills every day and the progress of his Giant Whale Body Refining Technique improved visibly.

He was getting closer and closer to giving birth to his inner power.

Knowing that there was a constant supply of Blood-Increasing Pills, Lin Fei no longer paid attention to Lin Miao's pill refining work.

Instead, he focused on the medicinal bath for the Vajra Iron Cloth. After studying it for a few days, Lin Fei had a rough idea of its function.

The medicinal bath promoted the recovery of the skin membrane, which was constantly damaged during the practice of Vajra Iron Cloth.

With the improvement of Lin Fei's Vajra Iron Cloth realm, the efficacy of the ordinary medicinal bath became less effective in repairing the damaged skin membrane, resulting in slower progress in his cultivation of Vajra Iron Cloth.

Lin Fei came up with a solution in recent days.

"Young Master, the stuff you wanted has arrived," the butler's voice came from outside the door.

Lin Fei opened the door and saw the butler holding a package. He smiled and ordered, "Continue to buy more, the more the better."

"Yes, Young Master," the butler replied before leaving.

Lin Fei brought the package into his room and placed it on the table.

Inside the package was a box filled with white porcelain bottles.

Lin Fei opened one of the bottles and immediately a strong smell of blood emanated from it.

48. One Step Away

"Golden light snake blood." Lin Fei muttered in a low voice.

The porcelain bottles were filled with the fresh blood of golden light snakes.

Golden light snakes were a type of snake with a very small and short body. They were a specialty of Lu Mountian.

They were highly poisonous. Although it was not a deadly venom, if someone was poisoned by its venom, they would kill quickly if not treated effectively.

Golden light snakes had a special characteristic. Once their blood was applied to the skin, it would gradually make the skin tough.

Even some small scars, when smeared with golden light snake blood, could gradually fade away or even disappear.

If it wasn't for the fact that venom of the golden light snake was incurable and powerful, Lin Fei was afraid that all the golden light snakes in Lu Mountian would have been caught.

Lin Fei suddenly thought of this characteristic of golden light snake blood, wondering if it would be helpful for practicing Vajra Iron Cloth.

So he asked the butler to purchase golden light snake blood for a high price. Despite the venomous nature of golden light snakes, some people still venture to catch them.

"Let's try."

Lin Fei took a deep breath and poured the golden light snake blood from the porcelain bottle and applied it all over his body.

Instantly, Lin Fei's whole body emitted an unpleasant smell of blood.

The snake blood applied to his body quickly had an effect. A tingling and unbearable feeling arose.

Lin Fei knew that Vajra Iron Cloth was actually constantly breaking and refining the skin. And the golden light snake blood was repairing the skin. So this tingling and unbearable feeling occurred.

However, this proved that golden light snake blood was effective.

After using up a bottle of golden light snake blood, Lin Fei heard the system's voice in his mind about an hour later.

"Your Vajra Iron Cloth worked particularly hard today, and its cultivation progress has increased by 2%."

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei opened his eyes, unable to hide his joy.

"Just one bottle increased my cultivation progress by 2%. And this time, I bought dozens of bottles. Plus, the butler is still helping me purchase snake blood, so I'll have even more blood in the future."

Lin Fei's eyes gleamed with excitement. This Golden Light Snake Blood was of great significance to him.

It meant that Lin Fei was confident that he could reach the limit of Vajra Iron Cloth in a short period of time, thus giving birth to inner power. And this inner power was extraordinary, it was part of the hard martial arts that was not to be underestimated.

"Continue."

Lin Fei applied the blood again. Amazingly, it was still effective.

For the next few days, Lin Fei spent almost every day in his room applying golden light snake blood to his Vajra Iron Cloth. And his Vajra Iron Cloth was improving at a speed never seen before.

After a few days, the system's voice rang in Lin Fei's mind.

"Your Vajra Iron Cloth has broken through to the ninth level after days of hard work!"

Lin Fei touched his skin and found that the membrane had become significantly tougher. His whole body was like a layer of "light armor," even more terrifying than ordinary light armor.

Now, the Vajra Iron Cloth could finally show its power.

Lin Fei took out a dagger and lightly drew it across his arm's skin.

"Shhh."

To his surprise, his skin wasn't cut.

Lin Fei applied more force and had to use at least 30% of his strength to barely cut a small wound, which quickly stopped bleeding.

"Untouchable by sword or spear!"

Lin Fei's eyes flashed with a hint of strangeness. When hard martial arts reached their peak, they would exhibit some mystical characteristics. And the mystical characteristic that his Vajra Iron Cloth exhibited was untouchable by sword or spear. Even if he stood in place and let an ordinary person use a saber to hack at him, they probably wouldn't be able to harm him in the slightest.

This was the terrifying aspect of hard martial arts.

"Vajra Iron Cloth has also reached the ninth level, but it still needs to continue. It would be best to cultivate until inner power is born…"

Lin Fei continued to use the golden light snake blood.

He felt it out. The effect seemed to have weakened a bit. But it was only a little weaker.

The progress of Vajra Iron Cloth cultivation was still very fast.

It was only when he ran out of golden light snake blood and had not collected more that Lin Fei could take a temporary break. Otherwise, he would be applying snake blood every day.

In the blink of an eye, twenty days had passed.

"System."

Lin Fei brought up the system to check the progress of his many martial arts.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Body Refining Ninth Level

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Ninth Level (99% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (18% Progress)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Ninth Level (95% Progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Seventh Level (68% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Lin Fei saw the progress of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique. It had reached 99%. And Vajra Iron Cloth was not far behind.

Both were just one step away from giving birth to inner power.

"The Giant Whale Technique is about to give birth to inner power. What kind of inner power it will give birth to?" Lin Fei murmured softly.

Many Body Refining martial artists had different types of inner power. After all, the martial arts they practiced were different.

Lin Fei took a deep breath. He adjusted his state of mind.

"Let's begin."

He directly swallowed ten Blood-Increasing Pills in one gulp.

Ten Blood-Increasing Pills were just enough to increase the cultivation progress of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique by 1%.

Lin Fei's Giant Whale Technique was only 1% away from giving birth to inner power.

49. Limit Of Body Refining

A note from RighteousEgg

Thanks for your review. Four chapters here.

Ten Blood-Increasing Pills were swallowed into his stomach, transforming into a warm current that quickly flowed throughout his body.

Simultaneously, the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique automatically activated, causing Lin Fei's blood and qi to surge continuously inside him.

He could clearly sense that his blood and qi had reached a limit, as if a barrier was pressing down on them, preventing them from increasing any further.

This was the limit of his blood and qi, the limit of his Body Refining. Once a martial artist reached the limit of Body Refining, their inner power would emerge.

"Body Refining limit, inner power is born..." Lin Fei muttered softly. He was feeling the situation inside his body carefully. As his blood and qi continued to surge, he gradually felt a slight warm current appearing inside him. This warm current was like a mist, barely perceptible, but undoubtedly real.

"Inner power!" Lin Fei suddenly realized.

With a slight movement of his mind, his eyes opened, and he extended his hand. In the next moment, a trace of inner power gathered in his palm.

He lightly pressed his hand against the ground, and there was a soft sound as the ground trembled. Lin Fei widened his eyes. His palm seemed to have sunk into a piece of bean curd, leaving a clear palm print on the ground.

"inner power, it really is inner power! But... why is this inner power so terrifying?"

Lin Fei's heart trembled slightly. His inner power was really terrifying.

He had encountered acquired martial artists before and even killed two.

One was the Wind Chasing Fragrance, whom he had killed in Yi Mountian Mansion City. The other was Zhao Yihu, whom he had killed not long ago in Luo City. Both of them were acquired martial artists with inner power.

Lin Fei had also collided head-on with their inner power. However, compared to the trace of inner power he had just produced, their inner power seemed too weak.

"Pff!"

Lin Fei increased his strength. The trace of inner power that had just been generated in his body was instantly depleted. However, a clear handprint appeared on the ground.

"There should also be differences between different types of inner power. The stronger the Body Refining technique, the harder it is to produce inner power. But once inner power is generated, it's stronger than others!"

A glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

He already had a general idea of why his inner power, although small in quantity, was much more powerful than the inner power of the Wind Chasing Fragrance and Zhao Yihu.

The difference lay in the Body Refining martial arts.

Whether it was the Wind Chasing Fragrance or Zhao Yihu, they were all lone martial artists

What kind of Body Refining martial arts could they get? Just very ordinary martial arts.

Therefore, the inner power they produced was naturally very ordinary.

But Lin Fei was different. He had been practicing the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique all along.

Even among all the Body Refining martial arts in the Nine Profound Sect, it belonged to a rather powerful type.

It was precise because of this that Lin Fei had found it so difficult to practice before.

But once inner power was born, it was not something that could be compared to the Wind Chasing Fragrance or Zhao Yihu.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately called up the system panel to check his martial arts situation.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Realm

Giant Whale Body Refining Technique: Limit (Unable to improve)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (Progress 18%)

Vajra Iron Cloth: Ninth Level (95% Progress)

Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique: Seventh Level (68% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

The first thing Lin Fei saw was the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

Sure enough, it had reached its limit. Even the cultivation progress was not displayed, but instead showed "unable to improve."

This was the limit of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique.

Once inner power was born, the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique would be almost at its end.

Martial arts also had limits. It cannot be infinitely improved.

However, Lin Fei's realm had already reached the Acquired.

In other words, from the moment he was born with inner power, he was no longer a Body Refining martial artist but an Acquired!

Lin Fei rested for a while. His inner power slowly recovered bit by bit. However, he only had a little inner power, which was not much.

Moreover, at the moment, Lin Fei could only rely on his huge supply of blood and qi to automatically generate inner power. Therefore, the increase in inner power was very slow.

He needed martial arts in the Acquired realm.

Lin Fei had two Acquired martial arts. They were obtained from the Wind Chasing Fragrance and Zhao Yihu.

However, Lin Fei did not want to practice these two martial arts. Because they were too ordinary.

He could receive three Acquired martial arts for free at the Nine Profound Sect.

However, Lin Fei would not choose to rush to practice Acquired martial arts at the moment.

"Acquired martial artists rely on inner power. The stronger the inner power, the stronger the Acquired martial artists' strength.

To make inner power strong enough, the foundation of martial arts must be strong enough.

Otherwise, even if the same Acquired martial arts are cultivated in the same realm, the difference in inner power will be huge, and the strength will naturally be vastly different.

So, I still need to wait. Wait until the Vajra Iron Cloth gives birth to inner power, and even wait for the Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique to give birth to inner power.

At that time, the three inner powers will merge into an unparalleled huge inner power. With this inner power as a foundation, practicing Acquired martial arts will be twice the result with half the effort!"

Lin Fei's eyes shone with brilliance. He had a plan in his mind.

50. Second Inner Power

Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

Wang Xuan blushed. In front of her were two young men dressed as martial artists.

"Junior Sister Xuan, you said your father almost betrothed you to someone else?"

One of the young men, who held a long sword, seemed arrogant.

"Senior Brother Liu Hao, my father didn't know about me and Senior Brother before...I have already explained everything to him. That man is just a nobody in Zhou Mountain Mansion City, how can he compare to Senior Brother? Besides, my father has agreed to our relationship."

Wang Xuan seemed afraid that Liu Hao would misunderstand, so she explained the whole story.

"Junior Sister Xuan, you don't have to worry. You are also a disciple of our Autumn Haze Mountain's inner sect. How can someone from Zhou Mountain Mansion City be compared to you? Can he match up with you? I heard that he is a disciple of Nine Profound Sect's inner sect?"

Liu Hao obviously knew something about it.

Wang Xuan knew that Liu Hao was proud. Even though this matter had nothing to do with Lin Fei. But since he knew, Liu Hao must have felt uncomfortable.

He might even go looking for trouble with Lin Fei. Wang Xuan didn't want to stir up trouble.

So she took the initiative to hold Liu Hao's hand and said, "Senior Brother, Lin Fei is just a Body Refining martial artist. He has only just been promoted to the inner sect of the Nine Profound Sect after three years. He is nothing compared to you.

Senior Brother doesn't need to bother with such an ordinary person and a trivial matter. Isn't Senior Brother Chen Yuan going to Luo City for something? Senior Brother Chen Yuan's matter is more important."

The other martial artist, also an inner sect disciple of Autumn Haze Mountain, was Chen Yuan.

At this time, he also smiled and said, "Senior Brother Liu Hao, Junior Sister is right. How can a mere Body Refining martial artist be worth your attention? Lin Fei is just an ant on the ground, and he will probably only be a Body Refining martial artist for the rest of his life.

But Senior Brother is a divine dragon in the sky, destined to become an innate expert and dominate the world! How can someone like Lin Fei deserve Senior Brother's attention?"

Liu Hao glanced at Chen Yuan and Wang Xuan.

He couldn't help but smile, "Right, Junior Sister Xuan is right. A mere Lin Fei, still a Body Refining martial artist, is indeed not worth our attention. Okay, let's go say goodbye to the uncle first, then accompany Junior Brother Chen Yuan to Luo City, take care of his matter, and then return to the sect."

"Haha, I am also gonna investigate why the Zhang family suddenly withdrew their patronage for me. It's just a small matter that can be solved in Luo City. It's an honor to have the company of senior brother."

"Anyway, it's on the way. Moreover, Junior Brother Chen Yuan just broke through to the acquired, and your inner power is unstable. If you encounter any small problems in Luo City, I will take care of them for you."

"Thank you, Senior Brother Liu Hao!"

So Wang Xuan, Liu Hao, and Chen Yuan said goodbye to the prefect and quickly left Zhou Mountain Mansion City towards Luo City.

...

Lin Fei sat cross-legged in the room, his whole body covered in the golden light snake blood. His skin turned red, and he felt a tingling sensation, but he remained unmoved.

He was used to it by now. He had just reached the limit of the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique yesterday, and he was about to develop inner power today.

And now, his Vajra Iron Cloth also almost reached its limit, which was about to give birth to inner power! When the two inner powers merged, what kind of power would they bring? Lin Fei was not sure.

Today was crucial for him, and he ordered the servants in the Lin mansion not to disturb him at this time.

As time passed, the effect of the golden light snake blood on Lin Fei's body gradually weakened, but he felt that his Vajra Iron Cloth was still a little short of reaching its body refining limit.

However, Lin Fei was not worried because he had prepared a lot of golden light snake blood. So he applied a large amount of it again.

Lin Fei's skin had become somewhat black and even a bit rough to the touch. After all, it was training the skin to become tougher than cowhide.

Suddenly, Lin Fei's skin began to vibrate slightly, and there seemed to ripple appearing on his slightly black skin, like the ripples on water. Then, the tough skin began to crack with a "crackle."

Lin Fei opened his eyes wide and grabbed the skin on his hand and tore it apart with a "chirp." There was no blood or pain. After the old skin cracked open, a new layer of skin was revealed, which looked very fair and tender.

Lin Fei seemed to have been "reborn" and transformed like a completely different person. Looked like a handsome young gentleman from a distance.

However, these details were inconsequential. What mattered was the new layer of skin on his body.

Lin Fei felt as if an invisible force was covering his entire body, and it was tingling with a slight burning sensation.

"The inner power produced by the skin membrane! The Vajra Iron Cloth has finally reached its limit!"

A flash of enlightenment crossed Lin Fei's mind.

52. The Letter From Miss Zhang

The letter was indeed written by Miss Zhang. The contents of the letter were a plea for help to Lin Fei.

It turned out that not long after Lin Fei had left Luo City, the Zhang family felt burdened by the responsibility of providing for two martial artists.

So they sent a message to Chen Yuan, an inner disciple of Autumn Haze Mountain, to revoke their patronage to him. From then on, the Zhang family only offered incense to Lin Fei alone.

However, the Zhang family received some news from other channels of Autumn Haze Mountain.

Chen Yuan seemed to have left the mountain, and he even broke through to the acquired realm! The main purpose of Chen Yuan's trip down the mountain this time was to seek an explanation from the Zhang family.

Normally, patronage was agreed upon by both parties. But if one party were too dominant, then there would be no room for discussion.

Miss Zhang was afraid that Chen Yuan would harm the Zhang family, so she wrote the letter, hoping Lin Fei would go to Luo City.

After all, Lin Fei was now the only patron worshipped by the Zhang family.

After reading the letter, Lin Fei pondered for a moment and said to the butler, "Prepare my horse, I'm gonna go to Luo City."

"Luo City? Young master, has something happened?" The butler was concerned.

Judging from Lin Fei's demeanor, it was definitely not good news.

Lin Fei shook his head slightly and said, "Nothing major, I just need to take care of some things in Luo City. Tell my parents that I'll be gone for a few days."

"Okay, young master, I'll make the arrangements."

The butler didn't ask any more questions and quickly left to prepare.

"Chen Yuan of Autumn Haze Mountain..." Lin Fei's eyes turned cold.

It was related to the "huge" patronage of one hundred thousand taels of silver per year. Lin Fei would not back down.

If the other party wanted to fight, he would fight back.

Now that Lin Fei had merged his two inner powers, he was also an acquired martial artist. Naturally, he was not afraid.

Soon, the butler prepared a fast horse.

Lin Fei rode the horse and quickly left Zhou Mountain Mansion City, heading towards Luo City.

...

"Is this the Zhang Family's mansion? What a magnificent place. It seems that the Zhang Family is a top-tier wealthy merchant in Luo City."

"Junior Brother Chen, you're lucky to have found a wealthy and powerful patron in the Zhang Family."

Liu Hao looked at the huge Zhang mansion in front of him and smiled.

He and Wang Xuan and Chen Yuan had already arrived in Luo City. Now they were standing in front of the gates of the Zhang mansion.

Chen Yuan smiled and said, "When the Zhang Family first found me, they were not as large as they are now."

"In recent years, thanks to my reputation, the Zhang Family's business has grown and expanded in Luo City, like a snowball getting bigger as it rolls. At first, it was a good thing, and I could also receive patronage from the Zhang Family.

But some time ago, the Zhang Family suddenly terminated our patronage relationship. Hmph, they used my name to expand their business. Now they want to abandon me. What kind of world is this where things are so easy?"

If their response this time doesn't satisfy me, they'll regret offending a disciple of the Autumn Haze Mountain Inner Sect!"

Chen Yuan's eyes flashed with a hint of fierceness. It was obvious that he was really angry.

Otherwise, he wouldn't have just recently broken through the acquired realm and hurriedly come down from the mountain to "settle accounts" with the Zhang Family.

"All right, Junior Brother Chen. It's just the Zhang Family. Since you're here, they will naturally satisfy you. Let's go in."

So the three of them walked towards the gates of the Zhang mansion.

The Zhang Family's servants immediately stopped them and said, "Wait, who are you?"

"Get lost!"

Chen Yuan casually lifted his hand and directly lifted the Zhang Family's servant guarding the gate. Then he threw him inside the gate.

"Tell the master of the Zhang Family that Chen Yuan of the Autumn Haze Mountain has arrived!"

Chen Yuan's eyes were cold, and he was not polite to these Zhang Family servants at all.

The three of them directly broke into the Zhang Family's hall. They sat down in a grandiose manner. Even the Zhang Family's maidservants had to offer good tea with trepidation.

At this moment, Miss Zhang arrived.

Chen Yuan and Liu Hao looked up and saw Zhang. Both of them raised their eyebrows. What a beautiful woman!

Miss Zhang was gentle and graceful, with a soft and watery temperament. In terms of appearance, she was even more beautiful than Wang Xuan.

"Who are you?" Chen Yuan asked.

"I am currently in charge of the affairs of the Zhang Family. Hero Chen, the decision to terminate your patronage was also made by me. Some time ago, the Zhang Family had some internal turmoil. Patron Chen cannot have been completely unaware of it. May I ask Patron Chen, did you come down from the mountain to the Zhang Family at that time and administer justice?"

Miss Zhang's eyes were sharp as she looked directly at Chen Yuan.

At first, Miss Zhang thought that Chen Yuan was unaware of the affairs of the Zhang family.

However, after gaining control of the Zhang family, Miss Zhang realized that things were not as she had thought.

Miss Zhang's second uncle had even written a letter to Chen Yuan, and even sent money, asking him not to interfere in the affairs of the Zhang family.

Of course, Chen Yuan was happy to oblige. After all, it was an internal conflict within the Zhang family, and it didn't concern him who would ultimately become the head of the family, as long as they continued to pay their patronage to him.

But now, the Zhang family was no longer paying patronage to Chen Yuan. Naturally, he was anxious and even went down the mountain himself.

"Miss Zhang, the previous matter was an internal affair of your Zhang family and had nothing to do with me. After all, even a just judge cannot judge family matters.

Besides, I was in a crucial period of martial arts practice at the time when I was breaking through the acquired realm, so naturally, I had no energy to pay attention to the affairs of the Zhang family."

Chen Yuan's tone was calm.

"Yes, it was an internal affair of the Zhang family and had nothing to do with the young hero Chen. Then, is it not okay for my Zhang family to stop paying patronage to you from now on? Does young master Chen plan to force my Zhang family to continue paying patronage?"

Zhang's tone was also aggressive, making even Chen Yuan unable to suppress his anger for a moment.

"Miss Zhang, I don't want to waste any more words on this. Now, I'll ask you one question, is it true that the Zhang family will no longer pay patronage to me from now on?" Chen Yuan's gaze was sharp like a saber, staring fixedly at Miss Zhang.

The atmosphere in the entire hall became tense all of a sudden.

53. Lin Fei Is Here

A strong aura emanated from Chen Yuan's body.

Miss Zhang was just an ordinary woman. Facing this kind of pressure, her face turned somewhat pale.

But she endured it. At least on the surface, she appeared calm.

"Young Hero Chen, I apologize. Zhang family has no intention of continuing to offer our patronage to you." Finally, Miss Zhang slowly spoke. And her tone was decisive.

"Bang!"

Chen Yuan's fist smashed into the armrest of the chair.

"Crack!"

Instantly, the chair was shattered into pieces. Chen Yuan suddenly stood up.

"Swoosh, swoosh, swoosh!"

A large number of Zhang family guards rushed in from outside the door. These guards all drew out their sabers. surrounding Chen Yuan and the others in the middle.

However, these guards seemed quite nervous. After all, they were facing an acquired martial artist from Autumn Haze Mountain!

"Good, very good! It seems that Miss Zhang is determined. Then my and Zhang family's accounts from these years should be settled!" Chen Yuan laughed in anger.

"Wait a minute." At this moment, Liu Hao spoke up. He took a slow sip of tea.

Looking at Miss Zhang with a calm expression, he said, "Miss Zhang, you've probably found a new patron, haven't you? Otherwise, you wouldn't be so anxious to sever the relationship with Junior Brother Chen. You can tell us who it is. Then we can also have an idea, how about it?"

After hearing Liu Hao's words, Miss Zhang fell silent.

She knew Chen Yuan came to "demand justice." The Zhang family could not intimidate Chen Yuan. Perhaps only Lin Fei could.

Moreover, the Zhang family's clan patronage was not a secret. It could be figured out by inquiring in Luo City.

"Lin Fei, an Inner Sect disciple of the Nine Profound Sect!" Miss Zhang slowly spoke.

"What? What did you say?" Wang Xuan widened her eyes. A strange expression appeared on her face.

Lin Fei, an Inner Sect disciple of the Nine Profound Sect.

Same name, same surname, and was even an Inner Sect disciple of the Nine Profound Sect.

Was it a coincidence? But, it didn't seem like it. It wasn't that coincidental!

But Lin Fei had just become an inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect, how could he be a patron by the Zhang family? Moreover, Chen Yuan was removed.

One should know that Chen Yuan was an acquired martial artist, even if he didn't make a breakthrough recently, he was still at the ninth level of Body Refining.

"Miss Zhang, are you talking about Lin Fei from Zhou Mountain Mansion City? Isn't he just at the Body Refining level?" Wang Xuan asked.

"Do you know him?" Miss Zhang was also surprised. These people were all disciples of Autumn Haze Mountain. Could it be that they also knew Lin Fei from Nine Profound Sect?

Wang Xuan widened her eyes. It was indeed Lin Fei from Zhou Mountain Mansion City that she knew, but he was just a mere Body Refining martial artist who had only recently entered the inner sect of Nine Profound Sect and was only at the seventh level of Body Refining. How could he become a patron of the Zhang family?

Chen Yuan and Liu Hao were also surprised. The new patron of the Zhang family was actually just a Body Refining martial artist.

"Hahaha, what a Lin Fei! Miss Zhang, I don't know how he tricked you. But do you think a mere Body Refining martial artist can protect the Zhang family's business and deter the small fry from all sides? Don't destroy the foundation of the Zhang family in your hands." Chen Yuan sneered.

Miss Zhang also realized that these people really knew Lin Fei, but they seemed to look down on him. After all, Lin Fei was a top genius who could kill acquired martial artists above his level. Were these inner disciples of Autumn Haze Mountain too arrogant or self-important?

"If there's nothing else, please leave. Escort them out!" Miss Zhang's tone was not polite at all, giving the order to kick them out.

"Hehe, are you going to kick us out now? But I want to settle accounts with you, Miss Zhang. How many benefits has the Zhang family gained over the years because of my reputation? The Zhang family needs to return everything they earned! Otherwise, these mere Body Refining guards won't be able to stop me!"

Chen Yuan pulled out his long sword with a "clang". The sharp edge of the sword made the surrounding guards feel a chill in their necks and take a step back involuntarily. If they really fought, they would probably be cut by Chen Yuan's sword before they even got close.

This was simply not something they could handle. So, the guards all turned their gaze to Miss Zhang.

Miss Zhang got agitated. She never expected Chen Yuan to be so shameless.

However, she was powerless at the moment. A figure suddenly appeared in her mind. If that person were here, how could Chen Yuan and his followers act so recklessly?

"I have informed Lin Fei, he is the patron of my Zhang family. If you harm my Zhang family, he will not spare you!" Miss Zhang's voice trembled with anger.

"Ridiculous, he's just a Body Refining martial artist. Does he dare to threaten us? If he dares to come, I will kill him with one strike!" Chen Yuan proudly brandished his sword.

"Is that so? Lin Fei is here, and you can draw your sword now."

Suddenly, a cold voice echoed in everyone's ears.

"Whoosh."

Everyone seemed to see only a shadow. Then, a figure appeared in front of Chen Yuan.

"You..." Chen Yuan's eyes narrowed slightly. He was about to draw his sword without thinking, but his sword was motionless when Lin Fei had already unsheathed his saber.

"Swish."

Lin Fei swung his saber. The sharp saber blade seemed to cut through Chen Yuan's neck.

At the same time, ten saber shadows flickered by.

"Crack."

Lin Fei had already sheathed his saber.

Then, Lin Fei stood quietly in front of Chen Yuan. It was as if he hadn't moved at all. It seemed that everything that just happened was an illusion.

54. Powerful Inner Power

At this moment, the hall became very quiet. One could hear a pin drop.

Chen Yuan still held his long sword. But his arm seemed to be trembling. He lowered his head.

A strand of his hair quietly snapped off and fell to the ground. In an instant, Chen Yuan's face turned pale as paper.

"You...you are..."

"I am Lin Fei, the one you can kill with one strike," Lin Fei spoke calmly.

Chen Yuan's expression turned very dark.

Although he did not see Lin Fei's saber movement clearly just now, he truly felt the sharpness of the saber. As if it could cut off his head in an instant.

He did not die, but a strand of his hair was cut off.

He and Lin Fei were clearly not at the same level! He couldn't block Lin Fei's attack. He couldn't even see Lin Fei's move clearly before he was defeated. He was completely defeated!

"I spare your life for being a disciple of Autumn Haze Mountain, and cut off only a strand of your hair." Lin Fei said coldly.

Autumn Haze Mountain and Nine Profound Sect were both major sects.

As neighboring sects, their relationship was not particularly good, but it was not bad either. If Lin Fei rashly killed a disciple of Autumn Haze Mountain, there would still be some trouble.

"What a fast saber! And there were no inner power fluctuations. This is the pure saber technique realm. If I'm not mistaken, your saber technique has already reached the perfection realm!" Liu Hao's pupils slightly shrank.

This was terrifying appearing on Body Refining martial artists.

And with Liu Hao's vision, he could naturally see that the saber technique Lin Fei displayed was definitely not ordinary. It must be a very sophisticated saber technique. It must not be simple to be able to practice to perfection.

"Who are you?" Lin Fei's tone was without any fluctuations.

"Liu Hao, a disciple of Autumn Haze Mountain." Liu Hao said calmly.

"Come to think of it, we actually have some connection. What do you think, Xuan?" Liu Hao has now confirmed Lin Fei's identity.

At this moment, Lin Fei finally noticed the woman next to Liu Hao. He felt that she looked familiar.

Soon, Lin Fei remembered where he had seen her before. After all, he had just seen her portrait a few days ago. He wasn't that forgetful.

"Wang Xuan, in consideration of your father's reputation, I won't pursue this matter. You three can leave." Lin Fei said calmly, seemingly not paying too much attention to Liu Hao.

Wang Xuan's heart skipped a beat. She knew Liu Hao's personality.

Liu Hao appeared gentle and easy to get along with. But in fact, he was arrogant and self-important and cared a lot about his face. Ignoring him in front of so many people, Liu Hao would definitely be angry.

Sure enough, Liu Hao's face turned cold, and he said, "Lin Fei, your saber technique is indeed good, but the foundation of a martial artist is still their realm! Even if your saber is fast, how can you break through my sword net using the third-level inner power of Acquired to activate!?"

As Liu Hao finished speaking, he suddenly drew his long sword.

"Shoo." The long sword made a light sound.

Then, Liu Hao's long sword began to move. It actually formed a huge sword net.

This sword net was powered by inner power. It could both attack and defend and was a very comprehensive martial art.

This was a truly acquired martial art. Even the other people in the hall who were far away felt like they were being pricked by needles all over their bodies.

Those who were a little closer felt like they were about to be cut by the sword net.

"Acquired Third Level..." Lin Fei also felt threatened.

The opponent's inner power erupted and the sword net appeared instantly. The sharp sword blades were aimed directly at Lin Fei.

Although Lin Fei had defeated acquired martial artists before and even killed two, the Wind Chasing Fragrance, Zhao Yihu, and Chen Yuan were all only at the acquired first level. In terms of inner power, they were far inferior to Liu Hao.

And Liu Hao's sword net in his hand was not an ordinary sword technique, but a very profound and exquisite acquired-level sword technique. Liu Hao even trained it to the level of transcendence, so it had such terrifying power.

However, Lin Fei did not back down.

"Inner power? I have it too!"

In the next moment, the big saber on Lin Fei's back was unsheathed with a "swish".

Lin Fei swung his saber, and suddenly, it seemed like there were saber shadows everywhere, ten saber shadows emanating sharp edges.

But that was only the surface.

This strike seemed the same as the one Lin Fei had previously used, but in fact, the powerful inner power in his body had surged into his arm, making the saber's power increase by an unknown number of times.

Finally, Lin Fei's saber struck the sword net in the sky with a "bang".

Liu Hao's originally calm face suddenly changed, and then his whole body trembled uncontrollably. With a "crack", the long sword in his hand suddenly appeared with cracks and shattered instantly.

The sharp saber edge enveloped his whole body as if it were going to cut him in half. Liu Hao felt the threat of death for the first time.

"Ah..."

Liu Hao roared in anger, blood flowing from his eyes, nose, and ears due to the impact of Lin Fei's saber. At this moment, Liu Hao had to extend his right hand and hold it in front of him.

With a "chirp", Lin Fei's saber fell.

A sound of metal clashing was heard.

Liu Hao's sleeve was torn, revealing a wrist guard inside.

Lin Fei's saber strike didn't manage to break through the wrist guard, but the power behind the strike was enough to shatter Liu Hao's arm. It would take at least ten days to half a month for him to recover without resting.

Liu Hao's face fell, and he looked as if he saw a ghost. If he hadn't been given a special wrist guard by his elders just now, his arm would have been severed, and he might have been split in half by the remaining force of the saber.

"The fluctuation of inner power...You have inner power, are you an acquired martial artist?" Liu Hao was terrified.

"You'll never leave if you don't get lost now." Lin Fei's tone was cold, staring at Liu Hao and Chen Yuan.

Liu Hao didn't dare to delay, nor did he say a word. He was afraid that Lin Fei would really go crazy and kill them. He had to save his life first and seek revenge in the future.

56. Hongfa Temple

"Patron Lin, are you talking about Hongfa Temple?" Miss Zhang thought for a moment and spoke.

In Luo City, the most famous temple was Hongfa Temple. Because there was once a great monk in Hongfa Temple.

"Yes, it's Hongfa Temple. I wonder if Miss Zhang knows which true high monks are currently in Hongfa Temple?"

"If you're talking about high monks, Hongfa Temple does have some. Master Fayan and Master Fajue are both venerable monks of the contemporary Hongfa Temple."

Lin Fei nodded and said, "Miss Zhang, I need your help with something. I hope you can use the influence of the Zhang family to introduce me to Masters Fayan and Fajue. I want to discuss Buddhist principles with the two venerable monks."

The Zhang family was a wealthy merchant in Luo City. They were also frequent customers of temples like Hongfa Temple.

Naturally, he could guarantee to see the two high monks of Hongfa Temple with the Zhang family's help.

Miss Zhang did not ask why Lin Fei wanted to meet the high monks. She nodded and said, "This is easy, but Patron Lin will have to stay with the Zhang family for a while. Within three days, I will make sure Patron Lin sees the two high monks."

"Thank you, Miss Zhang."

Lin Fei decided to stay with the Zhang family for a few more days.

Returning to his room, Lin Fei immediately called up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Level

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (18% progress)

Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique: Seventh level (68% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

Lin Fei's Giant Whale Body Refining Technique and Vajra Iron Cloth had reached their limits, giving birth to inner power, and could no longer be improved. Therefore, he deleted them from the system panel to save space. Otherwise, the panel would look too cluttered and confusing.

Lin Fei mainly focused on Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique, which was only at the seventh level. The current progress of its cultivation had reached 68%.

Compared to the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique and Vajra Iron Cloth, the cultivation speed of the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique was simply too slow.

This was not because Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique wasn't working hard. In fact, Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique was also working hard in cultivation.

But the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique required both Taoist scriptures and Buddhist sutras, especially the latter. Lin Fei suspected that it was created by a monk.

This time, Lin Fei stayed in Luo City to search for a high monk from the Hongfa Temple, hoping to listen to his Buddhist teachings and gain insights to enhance his cultivation progress. He aimed to reach his limits as soon as possible and give birth to the third inner power, which would merge the three types of inner power into one.

Then, Lin Fei could enter the Martial Arts Pavilion and select acquired martial arts, officially beginning his training in the acquired realm.

In just three days, the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique only increased the cultivation progress by 3%, which was as slow as a snail. Fortunately, Miss Zhang finally had good news for him.

"Patron Lin, two high monks from the Hongfa Temple have agreed to see you. You can enter the temple with this Buddhist bead as a token."

"Thank you, Miss Zhang. I will leave for the Hongfa Temple immediately. Time is of the essence," Lin Fei replied without hesitation.

He left Zhang Mansion right away and headed to the Hongfa Temple, which was located on the outskirts of the city, it was not isolated since the temple was always bustling with people. Upon arrival, Lin Fei saw a crowd of people and smoke rising from the temple, as well as merchants selling their goods outside the temple.

Knowing it would be difficult to see the high monks with so many people around without Miss Zhang's help, Lin Fei felt thankful. He walked straight to the front of the temple.

"Donor, please queue up for incense," a monk stopped Lin Fei.

"I have come to see Masters Fayuan and Fajue. This is the token," said Lin Fei.

Lin Fei took out a string of Buddhist beads directly.

The novice monk scrutinized Lin Fei carefully and said, "Seems that the Donor is the Lin Fei that the Zhang family mentioned. The two masters are already waiting for you in the meditation room. Donor Lin, please follow me."

Lin Fei followed the novice monk into the Hongfa Temple.

The Hongfa Temple was bustling with incense and activity outside, but inside, it was very peaceful and did not disturb the meditation of the senior monks.

"Ha!"

Suddenly, as they passed through an empty space, Lin Fei saw some young monks practicing martial arts in the open area.

"Hongfa Temple also has monks practicing martial arts?" Lin Fei asked. He remembered that Hongfa Temple was not a sect.

The novice monk replied, "Donor, those are the martial monks of Hongfa Temple. They are only practicing some basic boxing and footwork to protect the safety of many monks in the temple."

"I see," Lin Fei nodded.

With his eyesight, he could naturally see that those martial monks were indeed only practicing basic boxing and footwork, and did not have Acquired realm ones, only Body Refining. It was indeed far inferior to those martial arts sects.

"Donor Lin, the two masters are in the meditation room, please come in," The novice monk stood outside the meditation room and did not intend to go in.

Lin Fei nodded and pushed open the door of the meditation room, walking straight in.

57. Enlightenment

Inside the meditation room, Lin Fei saw two old monks sitting on meditation cushions. Both of them had white beards, and although they looked very old, their spirits were still high.

There was a faint smell of incense in the air that seemed to calm the mind and bring peace.

"Lin Fei greets the two masters," Lin Fei respectfully bowed to the two old monks.

One of the white-bearded old monks smiled and spoke, "Donor Lin, I heard from people of the Zhang family that you also have mastery in Buddhism, so you want to discuss Buddhism with us?"

Lin Fei shook his head slightly and said, "I dare not claim mastery, but I have read the Diamond Sutra and have some doubts. I hope the two masters can enlighten me."

"Oh, the Diamond Sutra? Please speak, donor," the old monk said.

Lin Fei began to recite some verses from the Diamond Sutra. In fact, because of the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique, he read a lot of Buddhist scriptures every day, especially the Diamond Sutra, so he could recite them fluently.

Lin Fei and the two monks began to exchange their understanding of Buddhism and Buddhist doctrine.

The two Zen masters were highly skilled in Buddhism and had a deep understanding of it. Lin Fei also received a long-awaited message from his system.

"Your Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique, hearing the profound Buddhist teachings, has entered into enlightenment, and its cultivation progress has increased by 50%."

"Your Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique has broken through to the eighth level."

As time passed, Lin Fei's Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique benefited greatly from the exchange with the two Zen masters. Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique broke through to the eighth level during its enlightenment.

However, the two Zen masters were already advanced in years, and after two or three hours of talking, they were feeling tired. Lin Fei bid farewell to them, but he did not leave. Instead, he stayed at the temple because his Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique had not yet reached the limit of body refinement.

He did not want to miss the opportunity of exchanging Buddhist teachings with the two Zen masters every day. He knew that it would greatly benefit his cultivation.

So, Lin Fei informed the Zhang family. Then he lived in the Hongfa Temple. He exchanged Buddhist teachings with the two high monks of the Hongfa Temple every day.

The two Zen masters of the Hongfa Temple also enjoyed exchanging Buddhist teachings with Lin Fei.

In the blink of an eye, more than ten days had passed.

During these ten-plus days, Lin Fei's Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique had been improving every day. However, after reaching the ninth layer, the speed of improvement slowed down. But even if it was slower, it was gradually approaching its limit.

One day, after just finishing the exchange with the two Zen masters, Lin Fei couldn't wait to return to his room.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately brought up the system panel to check his martial arts.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired First Level

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (18% progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Ninth level (99% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

Lin Fei saw that the progress of his Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique had reached 99%. It was only 1% away from reaching the limit of Body Refining and giving birth to inner power.

Lin Fei was burning with enthusiasm. Naturally, this couldn't stump him. He immediately took out many Buddhist scriptures and began reciting them.

Gradually, Lin Fei could clearly feel that the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique was improving little by little. Perhaps, he could give birth to inner power today.

...

"Bang, bang, bang."

Outside the meditation room, a novice monk anxiously knocked on the door of the two Zen masters.

"Two masters, something bad happened...Cian has returned..." The novice's voice revealed a hint of panic.

"Don't panic, you're saying that Cian has returned?"

"Yes, Cian has returned. The martial monks have surrounded him, but they can't capture him. Moreover, Cian has even killed several martial monks."

"Namo Amitabha, what has to come will come. Let's go and see. Oh, and..." The Zen master stopped.

"Let a novice monk inform Lin Fei that there is danger in the temple and ask him to leave the Hongfa Temple."

"Yes, master!"

So the novice monk left immediately.

The two Zen masters arrived at the back gate of Hongfa Temple.

In an open space behind the gate lay many corpses of martial monks. The air was filled with a hint of blood.

Many martial monks surrounded a short-haired man holding a curved saber. The saber was stained with blood, and it was evident that the man had killed the martial monks on the ground.

"Amitabha. Cian, since you were expelled from Hongfa Temple, why did you come back to cause more trouble?" shouted Master Fayuan.

The man with the curved saber sneered, "Fayuan, Fajue, you have finally arrived."

"When I came to Hongfa Temple, I only wanted to become a martial monk to avenge myself," he continued.

"You have acquired martial arts skills, but you refused to teach me. You accused me of holding grudges and being unsuitable to become a monk. Eventually, you expelled me from Hongfa Temple," he said with a cold smile. "But what in the end? I still learned martial arts, and I even became an acquired martial artist!"

Fayuan sighed deeply and said, "Since you have achieved what you wanted, you should be happy. Why did you come back to cause trouble again?"

"Hmph, although I learned martial arts, do you know how I have lived these past few years?" Cian asked angrily.

"I have been living on the edge of life and death every day, constantly fighting. If you hadn't expelled me from Hongfa Temple, how could I have lived such a hell-like life?"

"So, I made a silent vow that I would make Hongfa Temple regret it when I became proficient in martial arts," he said, his tone full of hatred.

He hated Hongfa Temple so much that if they had taught him martial arts, he would have avenged himself and not ended up in such a miserable state, enduring inhumane torture.

Therefore, he wanted to take revenge on Hongfa Temple, even to the point of burning it to the ground, to ease his hatred.

58. Three-in-One Inner Power

Lin Fei stayed in the room all the time, reciting Buddhist scriptures. He could feel that the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique was steadily improving. He didn't know how long had passed when he felt a slight tremor in his body, followed by the sound of the system in his mind.

"You recite the Buddhist scriptures with a joyful mood, and the progress of Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique is increased by 1%."

"Your Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique has reached its limit and cannot be improved further."

As the system's voice fell, Lin Fei's whole body began to shake with a "crackling" sound. His bones seemed to be vibrating madly, and a familiar warmth flowed out from the depths of his bones, attaching to his bones and flowing throughout his body.

Lin Fei clearly felt that his bones seemed to be expanding at a terrifying speed. He stretched out his hand, and at that moment, he felt that the bones in his arm were indestructible.

Of course, this was Lin Fei's illusion caused by his bones improving too much all at once.

"Inner power! Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique has finally given birth to inner power!"

Lin Fei opened his eyes with excitement and immediately summoned the system panel to check his martial arts.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired First Level

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (18% progress)

Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique: Body Refining Limit (cannot be improved)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

Lin Fei saw that his Tendon Transformation and Bone Forging Technique had indeed reached its limit and could not be improved further. An inner power had been automatically generated.

This was the third inner power that had been born in Lin Fei's body. The inner powers borning in his bones circulated throughout his body, and the two-in-one inner power seemed to be stimulated and was also restless.

At this point, Lin Fei no longer hesitated.

"Integrate!"

Suddenly, Lin Fei proactively mobilized his two-in-one inner power to integrate into the inner power of the Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique. The two Inner Powers quickly entangled and merged into a completely new Inner Power.

"Boom!"

Lin Fei shook all over.

The two Inner Powers rapidly entangled and merged, gradually transforming into a completely new Inner Power that instantly skyrocketed. The Three-in-One Inner Power!

Lin Fei felt that this new Inner Power was filled with terrifying power, about ten times stronger than the previous Inner Power of the Giant Whale Technique. This was purely a feeling, but he thought this feeling was not wrong.

"Qi and blood, tendons and bones, and skin and membranes, these three Inner Powers have merged into one. This kind of Inner Power should be the best among all martial artists in terms of both quality and quantity! If I return to the Nine Profound Sect, I can choose the acquired level martial arts in the martial arts pavilion and officially step into the acquired level of cultivation!"

Lin Fei's mood was surging. He finally waited for this day! Three Inner Powers merged into one, creating the strongest Inner Power.

It was not that the more Body Refining techniques one practiced, the more Inner Powers one would get. In fact, all Body Refining martial arts could be basically categorized into three types: Qi and blood, tendons and bones, and skin and membranes.

Practicing Vajra Iron Cloth and then hard martial arts like Golden Bell Cover would not have much effect, and ultimately only produces one Inner Power, which was skin and membranes Inner Power.

Therefore, Lin Fei had now merged his three Inner Powers of Qi and blood, tendons and bones, and skin and membranes into one. In a sense, this was the great perfection of the Body Refining level.

"These days, thanks to the two Masters of the Hongfa Temple. It's time to leave the Hongfa Temple. I should say goodbye to the two Masters first!"

Lin Fei was going to get up and bid farewell to the two Masters. During these days, he discussed and debated Buddhist teachings and doctrines with them. Lin Fei admired the character and Buddhist realm of the two abbots very much.

"Screech."

Lin Fei opened the door and find that there was no one outside. Normally, the temple was deserted, but there were often monks passing by. One could even hear the chanting of sutras in the main hall. But now it was empty and very quiet.

Just as Lin Fei frowned, a novice monk ran over from a distance.

When he saw Lin Fei, the novice monk came to him panting and said anxiously, "Donor Lin, there's something going on in our temple today, and we've temporarily closed the temple. So please leave the temple first."

"Hmm? The temple is closed? May I ask what's going on?" Lin Fei was a little surprised.

The Hongfa Temple was a famous temple far and wide, and pilgrims came in large numbers every day. The temple was open almost every day of the year. Why was it closed today for some special reason?

Seeing that Lin Fei refused to leave, the novice monk became anxious and said, "Donor Lin, please follow me and leave quickly. There is a wicked guest who has come to the temple today, and our martial monks may not be able to withstand them. If you stay in the temple, you may be in danger. That's why our abbot has asked me to take you away."

"Wicked guest?" Lin Fei's face changed.

He could faintly smell a hint of blood coming from the direction of the back door.

"Both Masters have shown great kindness to me. I'd like to see what kind of wicked guest dare to kill in this pure land of Buddhism." Lin Fei used his Flowing Clothes Skill and his figure flashed, taking him several yards away.

Even the novice monk was stunned to see this.

"Donor Lin..." The novice monk wanted to call out loudly. But in the blink of an eye, Lin Fei's figure disappeared.

The novice monk was horrified. He had no idea that the person who was discussing Buddhism with the two masters was actually a skilled martial artist.

The little novice monk gritted his teeth and ran towards the direction of the back door as well.

59. Crisis at Hongfa Temple

"Amitabha. Cian, since you are stubborn and refuse to repent, then I have to deal with you. Martial monks, form up!" Master Fayuan gave the command.

Immediately, dozens of martial monks shouted loudly and rushed toward Cian.

"Hmph, you weak chickens, without even an acquired martial artist! You're just dying for nothing!"

Cian's eyes flashed with a sharp light. Then, his figure moved like a ghost, advancing instead of retreating, and suddenly penetrated into the group of martial monks.

"Pff."

Cian raised his curved saber. Suddenly, black lights flashed and disappeared.

Many martial monks clutched their necks suddenly, blood splattered, and they fell to the ground one after another.

Many martial monks widened their eyes, even writhing in pain.

The gap was too big. Cian's footwork was extremely excellent, and these martial monks couldn't even touch him. But the curved saber in Cian's hand was like a ghost. Once the black light flashed, a martial monk would fall.

In a short time, ten more martial monks fell to the ground. The whole open space was almost dyed blood red, shocking to the eye! Even the two abbots couldn't sit still at this moment.

"Stop, Cian, stop! It was us that expelled you from the temple. If you want revenge, take our lives. Amitabha."

The two abbots sat cross-legged on the ground, waiting quietly for Cian to take action.

"Hehe, you two old monks are really pitiful. But, why didn't you pity me back then? Since you want to die, then I will fulfill your wish!"

Cian's eyes were full of killing intent, and even his expression seemed distorted. His figure was like a ghost, and he instantly rushed toward the two abbots.

"Master..."

Some of the novices and monks around them shed tears. They knew that the two Zen masters did not possess any martial arts skills. They were only scholar-monks from the Hongfa Temple.

In the Hongfa Temple, the status of scholar monks was much higher than that of martial monks. However, no matter how high their status was, or how profound their Buddhist teachings were, they were powerless in the face of the current situation. They couldn't stop Cian's curved saber.

Cian's curved saber had already reached the faces of the two Zen masters. It seemed that at the next moment, the curved saber would cut through their necks.

"Amitabha."

The two Zen masters closed their eyes.

"Bang."

Suddenly, there was a muffled sound.

The crowd only saw a blurry figure appear in front of the two Zen masters in an instant.

Cian's curved saber didn't work for the first time.

It was a saber! A seemingly ordinary saber.

But it was this ordinary saber that firmly caught Cian's curved saber, without even trembling in his hand.

"Who are you?"

Cian's eyes widened, and he immediately backed away, seemingly very wary of the stranger who suddenly appeared before him.

The two Zen masters also sensed something was wrong, so they opened their eyes.

After seeing Lin Fei, the two Zen masters shook their heads and sighed, "Donor Lin, you are just a pilgrim. Why involve yourself in these disputes?"

However, Lin Fei shook his head.

He glanced at the dead martial monks lying all around.

There were more than twenty martial monks all killed by the man with the curved saber in front of him.

Moreover, all of them were killed with a single saber strike. The man in front of him, Cian, was definitely not a good person!

"Old Zen masters, right and wrong, I don't want to get involved." During this time, I have disturbed the two masters many times, please forgive me. I don't have any gifts to give either. Since this happened today, I cannot pretend that I didn't see anything. So, I will give this villain's head to the two masters as a gift."

Lin Fei looked at Cian with a cold gaze.

"Whoosh."

At the next moment, Lin Fei displayed the Flowing Clothes Skill.

With a step, he instantly crossed several meters of distance.

"You wanna kill me? No one has been able to kill me for so many years! You're asking for death!"

Cian's killing intent surged in his heart. However, he was cautious and careful by nature. The angrier he was, the calmer he became.

Seeing Lin Fei approaching him, Cian immediately wanted to retreat. But no matter how fast his reaction was, Lin Fei's saber was even faster.

Especially with the boost of his three-in-one inner power, Lin Fei's saber speed was simply incredible.

"Swish."

Lin Fei slashed with his saber. Ten shadows appeared instantly.

They seemed to envelop Cian's entire body.

Ten shadows in every direction.

Saber's sharp blade was firmly locked onto Cian. A sense of danger rose in his heart.

He wanted to retreat, to avoid it, but he found that the saber was too fast, so fast that he didn't have time to use his lightness skill.

"How could Saber be so fast?"

This was Cian's last thought.

"Pfft."

The explosive power of the Triple Inner Power was unleashed, and Lin Fei's saber easily cut off Cian's head. Blood splattered everywhere.

Lin Fei's back was turned towards Cian, but Cian's head had already fallen to the ground.

It was still rolling.

"Thud."

Cian's headless body fell heavily to the ground.

Many novices and monks around saw this scene. Their eyes widened in shock. Their faces showed a trace of disbelief.

Cian, who had just been invincible and seemed to be an unparalleled villain, couldn't even block a move, had already lost his head and died completely.

The once-grand Buddhist temple instantly became silent, and one could hear a pin drop!

60. Mystery Token

"Amitabha." Master Fayuan and Master Fajue recited a Buddhist chant.

Lin Fei went straight to Cian's body. He searched the body for a while but found no martial arts secret manuals. There were only some silver tickets and a black token.

Lin Fei didn't look closely and put everything into his pocket.

"Two masters, thank you for your hospitality. Farewell!" Lin Fei said. He then turned around and left Hongfa Temple with big strides.

Lin Fei quickly returned to his home and was immediately called by his parents.

In the living room of the Lin family, Lin's father and mother looked at Lin Fei with a solemn expressions.

"Fei, you've been gone for more than ten days. I heard from the steward that you went to Luo City?" Lin's father asked.

"Father, the Zhang family in Luo City had requested my help. They encountered some trouble and wrote to me. I naturally had to go and solve their problem." Lin Fei replied.

Lin's father nodded. As a wealthy merchant, he had heard of powerful martial artists who could be employed by others. But he never thought that his own son would one day be employed by others.

"Fei, ten days ago, the Prefect sent some gifts. He said that the Wang family had done us wrong in our past dealings and wanted to apologize." Lin's father continued.

"I've been thinking these days that something seems off. Why would the Wang family suddenly send gifts? Fei, did you do something?" Lin's father and mother looked at Lin Fei with suspicion.

They were not foolish. As a high-ranking official, how could the Prefect easily apologize and send gifts? Moreover, the gifts were indeed sincere.

Lin Fei immediately understood. It seemed that Wang Xuan and Prefect Wang were both smart people. By sending gifts to the Lin family, they were actually expressing their stance - they did not want to be enemies with Lin Fei.

"Mother, Father, you can take the compensation and be at ease. I went to Luo City and unexpectedly ran into Wang Xuan. She seems to be together with an inner disciple of Qiuxia Mountain. The trouble I helped Zhang's family solve was related to them. It's probably because Wang Xuan told the prefect, so he sent the compensation."

Upon hearing this, Lin's parents were shocked.

"Fei, what did you do to make the prefect send compensation?!" Lin's father's voice was trembling.

"Mother, Father, I've already broken through to the acquired realm! From now on, in Zhou Mountian Mansion City, no one can intimidate our Lin family. Nobody, not even the Prefect Wang! From now on, Zhou Mountian Mansion City will listen to our Lin family!"

After finishing speaking, Lin Fei bowed to his parents and left, leaving Lin's parents in a state of shock.

...

Back in his room, Lin Fei took out some miscellaneous items from his pocket. These things were all obtained from Cian. Among them were some silver notes.

Lin Fei took a careful look. There were quite a lot, 160,000 taels of silver.

If added the remaining 140,000 taels of silver bills that Lin Fei still had, he now had a total of 300,000 taels of silver bills on him.

"Who is Cian? Where did he get so many silver bills?" Lin Fei was very curious.

Even for an acquired martial artist, it was not easy to carry around tens of thousands of taels of silver notes so casually. This Cian's identity was probably not simple.

Among the pile of items on the table, besides the silver notes, there was also a black iron token.

Lin Fei picked it up and looked at it. It was a token with four small characters engraved on it.

"What does 'Earth 23' mean?" Lin Fei flipped the black token over and over. He tended to think that it was a token that proved Cian's identity.

Cian should belong to a mysterious organization. Earth 23 represented Cian's identity.

Lin Fei couldn't find any other information about this mysterious organization for now, so he had to put the token away.

This trip back to Lin's family was fruitful for Lin Fei. Not only did he obtain a large number of silver notes, but he also broke through to the acquired realm with the fusion of three inner powers.

Even more importantly, Lin Miao could now refine pills! At least, he could refine some pills for martial artists.

If Lin Miao became stronger and reached the level of qi condensed, he could refine more valuable pills.

Lin Fei went to Lin Miao's side courtyard. The atmosphere here seemed even eviler than before.

Although this area was designated as a forbidden zone in the Lin family, there were still some servants who were curious and wanted to come in and take a look.

But since Lin Miao set up the Yin Gathering Formation, no one dared to come to the side courtyard anymore.

Lin Fei opened the gate of the side courtyard.

Even though he was already an Acquired Martial Artist and had extremely strong physical abilities, having even practiced Vajra Iron Cloth, it seemed to have no effect against the erosion of the Yin Gathering Formation on him. He felt as creepy as everyone else.

"The Qi Cultivation system is completely different from the Martial Arts system. If I encounter a Qi cultivator, I must be careful and cautious. I must take the initiative and not give the opponent any chance to catch their breath, thoroughly killing them!" Lin Fei's heart trembled.

He thought again that although there were few Qi Cultivators in this world, there must be some.

If he encountered one in the future, he must not be careless. He must use his full force to crush or even kill them.

Otherwise, some of the Qi Cultivators' techniques could be mysterious and unpredictable, making it hard to defend against.

"Lin Miao."

"Young Master."

Lin Miao seemed to be in his element in the Yin Gathering Formation. He exuded a special aura that Lin Fei could sense. Lin Miao must have become stronger.

"Lin Miao, I will be leaving tomorrow and returning to Nine Profound Sect. Your first priority in the Lin family from now on is to practice hard and strive to reach the first level of Qi Condensation."

"I will also have you refine some other pills in the future, which may be even more difficult. You must have a stronger spiritual power to support it."

Lin Miao nodded and said, "Young Master, don't worry. I have been cultivating in the Yin Gathering Formation, and the effect is very good. I will work hard to reach the first level of Qi Condensation as soon as possible."

"Good, then I can rest assured."

Lin Fei looked around the room, which had become creepy because of the Yin Gathering Formation, and suddenly had an idea.

He blurted out, "Lin Miao, do you know any methods for people without the talent to cultivate spiritual power and become a cultivator?"

61. Martial Artists Cannot Achieve Longevity

A note from RighteousEgg

Thanks for your review!

Lin Fei had always had a thought in his mind, to become a Qi cultivator.

The reason was simple, lifespan!

It was rumored that Qi cultivator experts could achieve longevity. But what about martial artists? Even innate martial artists could only live for a little over a hundred years.

Of course, low-level Qi cultivators were probably similar to martial artists. But what about high-level ones? There was always hope for longevity.

On the other hand, no matter how powerful a martial artist was, no matter how mysterious their martial arts were, they would still turn into a handful of dirt after a hundred years.

Martial artists couldn't achieve longevity.

"Well..."

Lin Miao smiled bitterly and said, "Second Young Master, you've also read the Zombie-refining Technique. There's no record of how ordinary people become Qi cultivators. So, I don't know how someone without the aptitude for Qi cultivator can become one. Moreover, I remember the young master asked me this question before..."

Lin Fei fell silent. He had indeed asked Lin Miao about it before. But Lin Miao only had a vague understanding of the Qi cultivator before.

"Lin Miao, have you not discovered anything during your time in the Lin Family?" There was a glint in Lin Fei's eyes as he stared at Lin Miao.

Lin Miao was a smart person. He immediately understood what Lin Fei meant.

Lin Miao quickly knelt down and said, "Second Young Master, I've always been loyal to the Lin Family and to you."

"Alright, tell me about your discoveries."

Lin Fei asked calmly, neither agreeing nor disagreeing.

Lin Miao took a deep breath and said in a deep voice, "Second Young Master, I have indeed made some new discoveries during my recent practice. Especially after setting up the Yin Gathering Formation, I vaguely realized that the Zombie-refining Technique is incomplete."

"Hmm? What do you mean?" Lin Fei raised his eyebrows and asked.

"Young Master, martial artists have realms. Body Refining, acquired, innate, and these are all complete realms. So based on my speculation, there must have other realms above Qi Condensation.

After all, just relying on Qi Condensation, it is impossible to have a long lifespan and live for a long time like the legends.

At the Qi Condensation level, one still experiences aging, sickness, and death, and there is not much difference from ordinary people.

But the Zombie-refining Technique does not have the next step. That is to say, if one practices the Zombie-refining Technique, they may never be able to reach the realm above Qi Condensation.

I don't know if this is a limitation of the Zombie-refining Technique itself or if it is incomplete."

Lin Miao's discovery surprised Lin Fei.

Qi Condensation cannot get immortality? Or rather, the Qi Condensation realm cannot achieve immortality. One must reach a realm above Qi Condensation to do so. But what was above Qi Condensation?

Lin Fei did not know.

"Forget it, Lin Miao, focus on your cultivation. I will explore these secrets slowly when I am stronger in the future."

Lin Fei did not stay long and left because there was a Yin Gathering Formation there, which could cause problems for his body if he stayed too long in the secluded courtyard, even if he was an acquired martial artist.

After returning to his room, Lin Fei carefully thought about what Lin Miao had said. It seemed that achieving immortality was not that simple. Not every Qi cultivator could achieve immortality.

"Maybe I will naturally understand some of these secrets when I reach the innate level."

The night passed without any further discussion.

The next day, Lin Fei bid farewell to his parents. He had to return to the Nine Profound Sect.

On his way back, Lin Fei did not encounter any troubles and returned to the Nine Profound Sect smoothly.

Lin Fei first exchanged all his 300,000 silver tickets for contribution points. He suddenly had 300,000 contribution points.

"By the way, let's change the token first."

Lin Fei prepared to go to the transmission hall for certification. He would exchange his token for the acquired realm one.

Although both were for inner disciples, some tasks in the mission hall could only be undertaken by inner disciples with an acquired realm token. This token was the only measuring standard, and so it was very important.

Lin Fei arrived at the transmission hall and respectfully said to the elder there, "Elder, I have just broken through to the acquired realm and have come to be certified and change my token."

The elder in the transmission hall was somewhat surprised. Generally speaking, although inner disciples might not change their tokens with every level breakthrough, almost all of them at the ninth level of Body Refining would definitely come to change their tokens.

But what about Lin Fei?

He had gone directly from the seventh level of Body Refining to the acquired realm and only now had come to change his token. This was quite surprising!

In fact, it was not that Lin Fei was too patient but that he had just broken through to the acquired realm soon after reaching the seventh level of Body Refining and did not have time to go to the transmission hall for certification and to change his token.

The elder in the transmission hall took out an oval-shaped blue stone and said to Lin Fei, "Place your hand on the blue stone. Activate the inner power in your body. If you can leave a mark on the blue stone, the certification will be successful."

"I understand," Lin Fei nodded.

It seemed that this blue stone was quite special. Once inner power was activated, the blue stone would change. This made the certification process quite straightforward.

Otherwise, if each disciple came to be certified and tested each other's inner power, it would be very dangerous! If two martial artists' inner powers conflicted, there would be big trouble.

Therefore, Lin Fei placed his hand on the blue stone.

He activated a small amount of inner power and infused it into his palm, leaving a light imprint on the blue stone.

62. Secret Discovered

Suddenly, a strange change occurred when Lin Fei's palm was imprinted on the bluestone.

"Crack."

The hard bluestone suddenly split into four or five pieces.

Lin Fei was stunned. He really only used a little bit of inner power. He didn't mean to show off his inner power at all. He was even very cautious.

"Elder, this..." Lin Fei didn't know what to say.

"Swish."

However, the elder suddenly stood up, staring at Lin Fei with sharp eyes, "You have combined three types of inner power?"

The elder of the Transmission Hall had seen many talents. But combining three types of inner power was definitely the top talent among the top talents. There was even hope to achieve the innate realm!

"Elder, I didn't mean to..." Lin Fei did not answer directly. Instead, he frowned. He didn't want to reveal the secret of his three-fold inner power.

Upon hearing this, the elder of the Transmission Hall snorted coldly and said, "It is an advantage to practice without arrogance or impetuosity. But don't always think about hiding your strengths.

Young people should have their own edge. The martial arts path is like sailing against the current, you will retreat if you don't advance.

The sect does not lack top talents with three-in-one inner power, although they are rare, they do exist. What are you hiding?

Nowadays, the trend is getting worse and worse. Many young people are obviously talented, but they still insist on hiding their strengths. They don't realize that the sect has various resources tilted toward top talents.

Even top martial artists, and even innate masters, are willing to take disciples and guide the outstanding disciples of the sect so that they can take fewer detours.

Lin Fei, right? Are you still hiding your strengths now?"

The elder of the Transmission Hall sat down again and stared at Lin Fei.

Lin Fei pondered for a moment, then bowed and said sincerely, "Thank you for the elder's guidance. I do possess triple inner power."

"Which martial arts did you practice?" the elder asked.

"I have practiced the Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique, and Vajra Iron Cloth separately." Lin Fei answered honestly.

"Blood and qi, tendons and bones, skin and membranes, three types of inner power merged into one. No wonder the bluestone shattered," muttered the elder of the transmission hall in a low voice.

Seeing that Lin Fei seemed confused, the elder explained with a smile, "The bluestone is used to test the disciples' inner power. Usually, no matter how strong the inner power is, even at the peak of the acquired level, it cannot break the bluestone.

However, its internal structure is very special. Once someone merges the three types of inner power into one, even if it's just a little bit, that kind of inner power can shatter the bluestone.

So, this is also a method the sect uses to identify some top talents, so as to avoid losing them due to concealing their abilities, and neglecting to cultivate them, which leads to these top talents taking many detours.

Remember, the sect is not your enemy, and you don't need to be wary of it everywhere. On the contrary, the sect is your home and your strongest backing. If a disciple encounters danger or even dies, outside the sect, the law enforcement hall of Nine Profound Sect will investigate it thoroughly and give the disciple justice!"

Lin Fei hurriedly saluted and said, "I understand, Elder."

Upon careful consideration, Lin Fei had never heard any rumors about disciples fighting each other in Nine Profound Sect, at most it was just some healthy competition. Only in this way can the sect maintain its cohesion and truly develop and grow.

"Alright, here's your nameplate. However, you should not cultivate any acquired-level martial arts for the time being. But it's okay to practice combat martial arts.

I will inform the Sect Master of your situation. I believe the Sect Master will arrange for an innate-level expert to take you as their disciple. At that time, there will naturally be an innate-level expert to guide you on how to choose acquired-level martial arts and continue to practice martial arts.

Only in this way can you avoid taking detours and advance in one go, reaching the innate level!"

The elder of the transmission hall spoke much more than usual today, all because Nine Profound Sect had produced a good seedling, and he was itching to see how far Lin Fei could go. Unfortunately, he himself was not an innate-level expert.

There was an unwritten rule in the sect. All those who have triple inner powers could only be accepted as disciples by an innate martial master. This was to avoid delaying the progress of top talents.

For a martial arts sect to become strong, innate martial masters were the key factor. The more innate martial master there were, the stronger the sect would be.

Every disciple who has triple inner powers could be considered a potential innate martial master, and the sect would do its best to train them.

"Thank you, Elder."

"Alright, go."

The elder in charge of transmitting techniques waved his hand, and Lin Fei turned around and left.

Watching Lin Fei's figure disappearing into the distance, the elder in charge of transmitting techniques revealed a smile at the corner of his mouth, "Another good potential disciple who has triple inner power. I wonder which Elder will step forward this time to accept him as a disciple?

Last time, the Elders fought fiercely for such a disciple. Whatever, this matter is still something that the Sect Master has to worry about..."

The elder immediately got up and left the hall, he had to report to the Sect Master himself.

Lin Fei had already left the hall. He remembered the warning from the elder in charge of transmitting techniques.

"Since I cannot practice martial arts at the acquired level, I can choose some combat martial arts to practice."

Lin Fei didn't know when he would be accepted as a disciple by the senior members of the sect and be taught martial arts.

He couldn't practice martial arts at the acquired level before the senior members of the sect made a decision, but it was for his own good, so as not to take the wrong path in the future.

However, he couldn't neglect his combat martial arts. His saber skills were still far from producing saber intent. So, he headed straight to the martial arts pavilion.

63. Saber-Drawing Technique

A note from RighteousEgg

Cough, thanks for your review. Two chapters here.

Lin Fei once again met the lazy elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion. He presented the emblem to the elder respectfully and said, "Elder, I have come to choose the acquired martial arts."

The elder glanced at the emblem and narrowed his eyes slightly. "You have become an acquired so quickly? Not bad, not bad. However, I recall that you seemed to have chosen three Body Refining martial arts. Which one gave birth to inner power?"

This elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion seemed to have some impression of Lin Fei. After all, disciples who chose three Body Refining martial arts were still few in number.

Lin Fei looked at the elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion and did not conceal anything. He replied, "Elder, I have given birth to inner power in all three martial arts."

"Three-in-one?"

The elder's muddy eyes seemed to clear up all at once, and a sharp light flickered. "Your inner power indeed is three-in-one."

The elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion looked deeply at Lin Fei, assessing him up and down. Then he sighed deeply and said, "Seems that I underestimated you. When you came to choose martial arts at the Martial Arts Pavilion, I thought you were ordinary and even a bit presumptuous.

But I didn't expect that you would really give birth to three kinds of inner power, and even fuse them into one. If I remember correctly, the three Body Refining martial arts you chose were Giant Whale Body Refining Technique, Vajra Iron Cloth, and Tendon Transformation And Bone Forging Technique.

Qi and blood, skin and membranes, and tendons and bones, all are complete!"

Lin Fei remained silent.

The elder pondered for a while and said, "Alright, go to the second floor. You can still choose three acquired-level martial arts for free. However, don't choose any acquired martial arts that you can practice until after you have a teacher. Your master will teach you."

"The elder of the Transmission Hall has already reminded me of this. Thank you, elder."

"I was talking too much. Go ahead, go ahead..."

Lin Fei bowed to the elder and then went straight to the second floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion.

The second floor was different from the first. All of the martial arts here were acquired-level. Therefore, the number of people was also very few.

After all, the number of disciples at the Acquired level was far less than that of the Body Refining level.

Lin Fei's selection of martial arts was also well-planned.

Weapons, boxing, and lightness skill.

For weapons, Lin Fei chose the saber technique. For boxing, he chose the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist. As for lightness skill, he chose the Flowing Clothes Skill.

Among them, Lin Fei had achieved perfection in both the saber technique and the boxing, but the Flowing Clothes Skill was only at the transcendence level. However, Lin Fei did not care, as long as it was usable. There was no need to waste time and energy on it.

As for the saber technique and boxing, both could be taken to the next level, but Lin Fei had not made any progress in understanding the meaning of the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist. Perhaps practicing other basic boxing techniques could help, and he needed to go to the first floor of the martial arts hall to make his selection.

Lin Fei's primary goal was to select the saber technique, so he went to the bookshelves where the saber techniques were located. The main characteristic of his Nine Shadow Saber Technique was speed, and the saber techniques he acquired now would also follow this direction.

Therefore, Lin Fei naturally chose "fast saber" techniques, such as "Blinking Saber Technique," "Empty Flash Saber Technique," "One-Stroke Kill Saber Technique," "Thunder Flash Saber Technique," and so on. He saw rows of saber techniques on the bookshelf one after another, all of them fast saber types.

Lin Fei felt a bit dazzled by the variety of techniques, each had its own unique features.

Lin Fei didn't want to make any choices. He wanted them all. However, the reality was that he only had three free opportunities to select acquired martial arts, and any additional martial arts would require expensive contribution points.

Moreover, it would be more difficult to reach the perfection level for acquired martial arts, and if he couldn't reach that level, it wouldn't increase his proficiency in the saber technique or help him understand its meaning.

Therefore, Lin Fei ultimately decided to choose only one saber technique after much consideration. This technique was called the "Saber-Drawing Technique" and was described with only a few words: fast, accurate, and ruthless.

Blood would surely be spilled when using this technique. With his decision made, Lin Fei went straight to the elder.

"Elder, I have chosen my martial art, the Saber-Drawing Technique!"

"This is the secret book of the Saber-Drawing Technique. As usual, you have only one hour to study it."

"Yes, elder."

Lin Fei received the secret book of the Saber-Drawing Technique and immediately entered the practice room.

64. One Slash, Thirteen Shadows!

"Saber-Drawing Technique"

Inside the practice room, Lin Fei opened the Saber-Drawing Technique manual. There were very few words written on it.

Saber-Drawing Technique was actually divided into two parts.

The first part was nurturing the saber, and the second part was unsheathing the saber.

The first part was used to nurture the treasured saber with inner power in a special way. The second part was to unsheathe the saber and kill the enemy when it was time to use it. The longer the saber was nurtured, the greater the power when unsheathing it.

Lin Fei realized that Saber-Drawing Technique was just perfect for him.

Other martial artists who practice Saber-Drawing Technique needed to spend time and energy nurturing the saber, but Lin Fei was different.

His martial skills could self-practice. In other words, he could constantly nurture the saber 24 hours a day.

Even if he only had one day, the power of the Saber-Drawing Technique would still be considerable.

The downside of the Saber-Drawing Technique was that it was only one move, but Lin Fei was not concerned.

He still had the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, which was not inferior to any acquired-level saber technique. It was more than enough as a basic move.

If used well, Saber-Drawing Technique would be able to kill with one strike and turn the tide of battle. So, Lin Fei began practicing Saber-Drawing Technique.

He had enough time to become a beginner in Saber-Drawing Technique. This technique was actually very simple.

Both nurturing the saber and unsheathing the saber have a core, which was the way inner power flows through the meridians.

In fact, Saber-Drawing Technique was about making inner power flow through several specific meridians in the hand. Usually, inner power was used to nurture the saber through these meridians.

But when inner power explodes through these meridians in battle, it would be the real Saber-Drawing Technique.

Basically, all acquired combat martial arts were like this.

Compared to Body Refining martial arts, the key of acquired martial arts was to use inner power to enhance explosive power. This applies to all martial arts, including fist, lightness, and sword techniques.

If inner power was not used, it is not much different from Body Refining saber techniques. But if inner power was used, the attack level was completely different.

Lin Fei followed the steps of the Saber-Drawing Technique, slowly flowing inner power through the specific meridians in his hand.

Lin Fei held the saber tightly in his hand. It seemed like he was intimately connected with Saber in an instant. This feeling was very unique.

"Amazing..." murmured Lin Fei in a low voice. He had never felt this way before. It was as if the saber had become a part of his body. Of course, this was just an illusion, a sensation that came from the nurturing saber.

In the early stages of practice, it was necessary to hold a saber in one's hand. But in the later stages, one only needed to keep a saber nearby or carry it on one's back.

After practicing for a while, Lin Fei had a distinct feeling that saber had come to life. Its power seemed to have increased a lot.

Without hesitation, Lin Fei shouted in a low voice, "Saber-Drawing Technique!"

Saber was unsheathed with a "clang" and emitted a sharp aura, directly cutting into the ground and leaving a large hole in the solid stone tiles of the room.

"Terrifying power," thought Lin Fei. "I've only been nurturing Saber for half an hour, and its power had already reached such a level. If I nurture saber for ten days, half a month, or even a year, how much more powerful will it become?"

Lin Fei's eyes brightened. The power of the Saber-Drawing Technique far exceeded his expectations. He had only just started to practice it, and he was still just a beginner.

Line Fei carefully pondered.

The strike from the previous use of the "Saber-Drawing Technique" not only had tremendous power, but it was also incredibly fast. Its speed was even faster than Lin Fei's Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

Of course, the "fast" of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique and the "fast" of the Saber-Drawing Technique was different. The "fast" of the Saber-Drawing Technique was the purest form of speed, a direct and straightforward attack without any twists or changes.

Meanwhile, the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had "saber shadows" that pursued how many times it could stack saber moves in an instant, and it had some techniques.

"Wait, what if I apply some of the techniques of the Saber-Drawing Technique to the Nine Shadow Saber Technique? Would it work?" A thought flashed in Lin Fei's mind.

The Saber-Drawing Technique was indeed very fast, but it was only possible due to the inner power exploding within several special meridians in the hand. What about the Nine Shadow Saber Technique?

Lin Fei had an idea and began to mobilize his inner power to run within the several meridians of his hand. He then tried to perform the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

As time passed, "swish," suddenly, Lin Fei's inner power exploded, and the saber move was exceptionally smooth.

"Your Nine Shadow Saber Technique has taken an unusual path and gained insight into the secret of inner power eruption. Its training progress has increased by 25%."

The system's voice sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

Lin Fei's heart was elated, and he slashed with the techniques of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

"Swish."

Thirteen saber shadows!

As expected, Lin Fei's Nine Shadow Saber Technique had improved once again: one slash, thirteen shadows!

65. Can Martial Arts Bring Immortality?

A note from RighteousEgg

Hello everyone! From the next chapter onwards, I'll be updating only one chapter per day. The reviews will not increase the number, but the word count for each chapter will be increased from 1000 to an average of 1500 words. You can check out more chapters on my Patreon page. The update schedule on Patreon is different from that of Royal Road. You won't have to worry about cliffhangers as I will update an entire plotline to avoid them. In short, Patreon chapters will be updated to more than seven chapters per week. Thank you for your support and attention.

"Thirteen saber shadows with one strike. My saber technique has improved again!"

Lin Fei's heart moved, and he immediately silently recited, "System."

Suddenly, the system panel appeared in front of him.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired First Level

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (43% progress)

Saber-Drawing Technique: Beginner (15% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

Lin Fei saw the system panel and found that Saber-Drawing Technique had just reached the beginner level, which was within his expectations.

The progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had actually increased by 25%, reaching 43% progress, which was a remarkable leap forward.

It must be noted that Lin Fei had incorporated some saber techniques that were slightly weaker than Nine Shadow Saber Technique, and they were all in the perfection realm. But one saber technique only increased the progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique by 2%.

But now, Lin Fei had comprehended the secret of using inner power with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, which resulted in a 25% increase in progress.

As Lin Fei slowly sorted out his memories of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, he gradually understood the reason for this.

The reason why Nine Shadow Saber Technique had such a significant improvement was that Lin Fei had paired it with inner power. By using inner power to execute Nine Shadow Saber Technique, its power could be directly increased.

This was equivalent to elevating Nine Shadow Saber Technique from a Body Refining level martial art to an Acquired level martial art. It was a qualitative leap!

Therefore, the 25% increase in progress for Nine Shadow Saber Technique was normal. Lin Fei was also certain that every time the progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique increased by 10%, one more saber shadow would be added. So, it increased to thirteen saber shadows from ten saber shadows.

Of course, it was not just the number of shadows that increased, but also the power of the saber technique. The power of one strike with ten saber shadows was vastly different from that of thirteen saber shadows.

Lin Fei felt that the time had come, so he got up and left the practice room. He had only selected one Acquired level martial art this time and could still choose two more, but Lin Fei did not intend to choose anymore. He decided to wait until he got a master before selecting any martial arts.

So, he left the second floor and arrived at the first floor. He spent some contribution points and took some basic boxing techniques with him.

These basic boxing techniques would slowly reach perfection with time.

When that time came, he would incorporate them into the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist, which would increase its foundation of it and improve its progress.

Lin Fei returned to his courtyard and waited quietly for news from the sect.

...

"Sect Master."

At this moment, in the main hall of the Nine Profound Sect, an old man with white hair suddenly arrived.

Although the old man had white hair, he had a vigorous spirit and a healthy complexion, with no signs of aging.

The master of the sect wore a gorgeous robe and quickly stood up to greet the old man, saying, "Greetings, Grand Elder Kong Ming."

The white-haired old man was none other than the prestigious Grand Elder Kong Ming of the Nine Profound Sect.

Every Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect was an innate powerhouse, and even the sect master did not dare to neglect them.

"Sect Master, you sent a message a few days ago saying that there was a talented disciple with Triple Inner Power. His name is Lin Fei, right?" Elder Kong Ming asked.

"Yes, his name is Lin Fei," the sect master replied.

"Have you investigated his background thoroughly?" Elder Kong Ming asked again.

"Grand Elder Kong Ming, Lin Fei is a descendant of the Lin family in Zhou Mountain Mansion City. He joined our Nine Profound Sect three years ago and only just broke through to the fourth level of Body Refining, barely qualifying for the outer sect," the sect master explained.

"Then, in just a few months, he made an incredible breakthrough from the fourth layer of Body Refining to the limit of Body Refining, and even birthed an inner power, breaking through to the acquired realm," he continued.

The sect master had investigated Lin Fei's background thoroughly.

Of course, this was not a secret. Someone who was interested and took a little effort could find out.

"Sect Master, don't you find it a bit strange? Lin Fei was silent before, but now he has made a name for himself. Moreover, his cultivation speed is so fast."

The sect master hesitated for a moment and nodded, "I do have some doubts. Please enlighten me, Grand Elder."

"It's simple, Martial Arts Heart!"

"Hmm? What do you mean?" The sect master looked puzzled.

"Some people perform poorly in the early stages. That's because they haven't been under pressure. I think this son must have been under pressure during the three-year period.

So he finally broke through before the three-year period arrived. Then he became unstoppable, probably because he had a firm grasp of his martial arts heart.

To put it bluntly, he must have understood why he practices martial arts. Usually, these things can only be understood after reaching innate. Sect Master, we martial artists are different from Qi cultivators.

For Qi cultivators, talent and aptitude are the most important. Without talent and aptitude, everything is in vain. For us martial artists, the most important thing is intelligence and willpower.

Only with excellent intelligence and a firm heart for martial arts can we overcome all obstacles and eventually reach innate.

Sect Master, you can bring this disciple into the hall and ask him."

The sect master hesitated for a moment.

The heart for martial arts, willpower, and intelligence.

He felt that Grand Elder was not here to accept Lin Fei as a disciple but to give him guidance. He had been stuck at the peak of acquired for many years.

Does he still have a chance to reach innate?

"Grand Elder, please wait a moment. I'm gonna call Lin Fei to the hall immediately!"

The sect master waved his hand.

Immediately, someone went to the inner gate to call Lin Fei.

At this moment, Lin Fei was practicing the saber technique in his own yard.

"Lin Fei, the Sect Master is summoning you. Hurry and follow me to the hall."

"Finally..."

Lin Fei stood up and followed the messenger martial artist.

The sect master's hall was located in the center of the entire Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei demonstrated his lightness skills and followed closely behind the messenger martial artist.

After a while, they arrived at the hall. When he entered the hall, he saw two martial artists sitting at the top.

One was a middle-aged man wearing a luxurious robe, exuding a majestic aura. The other was an elderly man with white hair and a sharp spirit.

"Greetings, Sect Master. Greetings, Grand Elder!" Lin Fei immediately paid his respects.

He had already received a message from the martial artist on the way here, knowing that the Grand Elder Zhao Kongming had personally come today. Most likely it was to accept him as a disciple.

The sect master looked at Lin Fei and examined him up and down. Then he spoke in a deep voice: "Lin Fei, just a few months ago, you were only at the third level of Body Refining.

In just a few months, you have progressed all the way to the Acquired Realm. Grand Elder Zhao Kongming told me that you have a heart for martial arts.

I ask you, what is your heart for martial arts Or, what is the goal you want to achieve in your martial arts practice?"

The sect master's words echoed in the hall. And also echoed in Lin Fei's ears.

Lin Fei's heart trembled. He knew he had progressed quickly in his cultivation, of course. But Elder Zhao Kongming actually said he had the heart for martial arts.

So what was his heart for martial arts? Lin Fei fell into deep thought.

What was his purpose in practicing martial arts?

After a long time, Lin Fei looked up and gazed at Elder Zhao Kongming.

He asked loudly word by word, "May I ask Grand Elder, can martial arts bring immortality?"

66. Three Vitality Technique

A note from RighteousEgg

This is an extra chapter for the review.

"Can martial arts bring immortality?"

Lin Fei's voice echoed throughout the entire hall.

This was Lin Fei's doubt. And also his insistence.

His true purpose in practicing martial arts was to achieve immortality.

Lin Fei's words made the sect master's gaze freeze. He did not answer, but instead looked toward the grand elder.

The grand elder suddenly burst out laughing: "Hahaha, that's a good question. Lin Fei, what if martial arts can grant immortality? What if martial arts cannot grant immortality?"

The grand elder's gaze was also fixed on Lin Fei.

Without hesitation, Lin Fei answered calmly and firmly, "If martial arts can grant immortality, the disciple will do everything in his power to pursue the pinnacle of martial arts! If martial arts cannot grant immortality..."

Lin Fei fell silent.

Back in the Lin family, he had told Lin Miao that martial arts might not grant immortality, so he wanted to become a Qi cultivator.

But if he did not have the talent, no matter what, he could not become a Qi cultivator. What should he do then?

Lin Fei's eyes narrowed slightly. At this moment, he seemed to vaguely understand what the heart for martial arts was.

"Swish."

Lin Fei raised his head, and a hint of determination appeared in his gaze.

"If martial arts cannot grant immortality, then the disciple will strive to make martial arts able to grant immortality!"

Lin Fei's voice was calm, but his tone was decisive.

"Hahaha, sect master, did you hear that? You were asking what the heart for martial arts is. And now, Lin Fei has already told you what the heart for martial arts is! This is the heart for martial arts!"

The sect master stared intently at Lin Fei. His mind was shaken!

Until today, he finally understood what was the heart for martial arts.

"Grand Elder, I understand now, thank you for your guidance!"

The sect master respectfully bowed to the grand elder.

Today, the grand elder's actions seemed to be to recruit Lin Fei as a disciple.

But in fact, he was also "enlightening" the sect master.

After all, the sect master got acquired-realm the peak for many years. He was only one step away from being innate.

But this one step was stuck because the sect master's will was not firm enough. He did not have the heart for martial arts!

The elder nodded satisfactorily, and his gaze turned to Lin Fei again.

"Lin Fei, I can definitely answer your question. Martial arts can grant immortality!"

The grand elder's tone was very firm.

Lin Fei felt a shock in his heart. He stared at the grand elder with a piercing gaze.

"Is it true?"

"Hahaha, of course. However, it's very difficult to achieve. And, that's something that comes after achieving innate. You should focus on achieving innate first before talking about eternal life. Now, I want to take you as my disciple, are you willing?"

Lin Fei understood that this was an opportunity, especially since the grand elder had given him the answer he most desired.

"Disciple pays respect to Master!"

Lin Fei respectfully knelt down and paid his respects to the grand elder.

"Congratulations to Grand Elder for acquiring a good disciple!"

The sect master also congratulated Zhao Kongming with a smile.

"Good, Lin Fei, follow me."

Zhao Kongming's figure flickered and he actually floated in the air. Step by step, he walked out of the main hall.

Lin Fei was also extremely surprised, but he didn't hesitate and immediately displayed his lightness skill, chasing after Zhao Kongming's figure.

Although Zhao Kongming didn't seem to be moving fast with each step, Lin Fei used all his strength but still couldn't catch up.

Fortunately, Zhao Kongming's cave dwelling was not far from the main hall. It was located on a mountain peak in the Nine Profound Sect.

There were many mountain peaks within the Nine Profound Sect, all towering high with cave dwellings on them. It was said that these cave dwellings were the residences of innate powerhouses within the sect.

"Shoo."

Lin Fei came to a stop. He had already arrived at Master Zhao Kongming's cave dwelling.

The cave dwelling looked very simple, with only some basic household items. There were several maids cleaning and tidying up inside the cave dwelling.

"Lin Fei, even though you have only acquired first level, you have the triple inner power and your foundation is extremely solid, so you have the potential to become innate in the future!

However, this is only a possibility. Don't slack off in your training at the acquired realm. If you aspire to immortality, you can't train like an ordinary person.

Your inner power is already strong enough. Therefore, you don't need martial arts that focus on increasing inner power significantly.

You should seek stability and consolidate your foundation. Only in this way can you have a stronger foundation after reaching innate and go further."

Lin Fei bowed respectfully.

"Good, I will grant you the Three Vitality Technique. This technique is a unique skill that I obtained when I traveled the world. Because it's special, it wasn't offered to the sect.

So even the Martial Arts Pavilion doesn't have this martial art, only my disciples can practice it... The Three Vitality Technique increases inner power only slightly, and once it's practiced to the peak, it's somewhat challenging to break through innate.

But its greatest effect is stability. It opens up the meridians very steadily. No matter how difficult the meridians are, they can be opened one by one, only the speed differs.

Ordinary people may not be able to reach their peak even after practicing for decades. That's because their basic inner power is average.

But you are different. When you practice the Three Vitality Technique, you can continuously gain inner power from your blood, skin, and bones.

So when your Three Vitality Technique reaches its peak, your inner power will also be immense. By then, breaking through innate will not be a problem at all."

Lin Fei seemed to understand and Zhao Kongming explained it to him in detail.

He even started practicing the Three Vitality Technique on Lin Fei's body.

Zhao Kongming used his innate true qi to help Lin Fei's inner power circulate one revolution, letting Lin Fei become a beginner in the Three Vitality Technique.

This was the benefit of having a master. He could be guided at any time, avoiding taking the wrong path.

Lin Fei stayed in the cave until dusk.

Zhao Kongming waved his hand and said, "Alright, you can go down the mountain first. Now that you have learned the Three Vitality Technique, if you want to learn any combat martial arts, you can go to the martial arts pavilion to choose.

Most martial arts are available in the pavilion. You will still live in the inner gate. If you have any questions about martial arts, you can come to the cave to find me directly."

"Yes, Master!"

Lin Fei nodded.

Although he had become the disciple of the grand elder, It was not that contribution points could be used infinitely, nor could martial arts be learned casually.

That was simply impossible.

With a master, the greatest benefit was to be able to receive guidance.

Lin Fei would continue to live his life as he always had.

"By the way, you have two senior brothers and a senior sister. You will know more about them when they come back."

Lin Fei nodded.

"Master, I take my leave!"

After speaking, Lin Fei didn't disturb Zhao Kongming any longer.

He went down the mountain directly and returned to his residence at the inner gate.

Once he arrived at his residence, Lin Fei recalled the Three Vitality Technique his master had taught him today.

For a moment, a gleam of light flashed in his eyes.

"The Three Vitality Technique is slow? Not necessarily."

Lin Fei silently thought to himself, "System."

The system panel appeared in front of him.

67. Triple Wave Technique

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired First Level

Three Vitality Technique: First Level (2% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (43% progress)

Saber-Drawing Technique: Beginner (80% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

Lin Fei saw the system panel and found the progress of his Three Vitality Technique had reached 2% in just twelve hours of training.

This technique could increase progress by 1% every six hours, making his progress quite steady and reliable, just as Zhao Kongming had said.

At this rate, with twenty-four hours of training per day, Lin Fei could cultivate without stopping and increase its progress by 4% every day. In less than a month, he could break through to the second level. As for the future, that was another matter. At least for now, Lin Fei's training speed was fast.

Lin Fei also learned that the Acquired realm was not the nine levels he had imagined, but twelve, corresponding to the twelve meridians, also known as the Twelve Regular Channels.

If the human body was compared to a country, these channels were like canals and roads that connected the whole body and were very important. The purpose of Inner Power was to slowly open these channels, allowing the Inner Power to flow freely.

Once one reached the peak of the twelfth level and accumulated enough Inner Power, they could attempt to open the Ren Du channel of the Eight Extraordinary Meridians. If successful, it would be the Innate realm. Therefore, Inner Power was just a tool for opening the channels.

Lin Fei chose the Hand Taiyin Lung Meridian as his first channel and opened a little bit every day. At this rate, in about twenty days, or less than a month, he could open the Hand Taiyin Lung Meridian.

Lin Fei carefully experienced this process. His Three Vitality Technique was constantly running within his body, generating strands of inner power from his membranes, blood, and tendons, which eventually converged together, making his inner power grow stronger and stronger.

"For now, I don't have to worry about inner power. As time passes, my inner power will become even stronger! Now, I can go pick some acquired-level lightness and fist techniques."

Lin Fei had already made a plan in his mind, but it was getting late in the day, so he decided to go to the martial arts pavilion tomorrow.

The night passed without incident, and Lin Fei rested for the night. Sure enough, after about twelve hours, his progress in the first level of the Three Vitality Technique had increased by 2%. It made a whole day's progress, reaching 4%, just as he had estimated, which made Lin Fei even more reassured.

Lin Fei could now use the remaining two free spots for martial arts with peace of mind. He left his residence and went to the martial arts pavilion.

Upon seeing Lin Fei, the elder of the pavilion narrowed his eyes and asked, "Lin Fei, which elder did you apprentice yourself to?"

"Disciple apprenticed to Grand Elder Zhao."

"Elder Zhao the 'Empty Abyss Sword'? Back then, Elder Zhao had a formidable reputation in the martial arts world with his 'Empty Abyss Sword'. His one-man, one-sword style was renowned throughout the world!

Unfortunately, it seems like you're using a saber, young man. If you're interested, I can recommend some powerful sword techniques for you."

The elder seemed to know something about Zhao Kongming's reputation, but Lin Fei shook his head and said, "Disciple is also comfortable with the saber, so there's no need to trouble Elder."

"Suit yourself."

The elder lost interest and reclined in his chair, closing his eyes. Lin Fei turned and left, heading to the second level of the pavilion.

Although his master was a master of the sword, Lin Fei had no intention of giving up his saber technique, as he was already close to producing saber intent. Once he produced saber intent, it would be on par with innate.

Switching to a sword now would be like giving up a watermelon to pick up a sesame seed.

Even if his martial arts could self-cultivate, it would still be difficult to master them to perfection and even to produce saber intent or sword intent.

Lin Fei had never expected to master everything. That was impossible. He only needed to master his saber technique, his fist technique, and his lightness skill.

Lin Fei wanted to pick a fist technique first. He had previously practiced the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist, which was already perfection level. He intended to use it to comprehend fist intent, so even if he had to pick an acquired-level fist technique, it would have to be a powerful and forceful type, similar to the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

Lin Fei walked up to a row of bookshelves. On them were all kinds of martial arts techniques.

"Empty Bright Fist."

"Seven Wounds Fist."

"Shaking Mountains Fist."

"Devil Bull Fist."

...

There were so many martial arts techniques that it was dazzling.

However, Lin Fei eventually picked one.

"Triple Wave Technique!"

This was the martial art that Lin Fei chose.

According to the introduction, the Triple Wave Technique could mobilize the power of the whole body, including the power of qi, blood, muscles, and bones.

Then, each punch would be stronger than the last, like waves in the ocean, one wave after another.

This was very suitable for Lin Fei.

Lin Fei had very strong physical fitness. If he couldn't use his physical advantages in martial arts, it would be a waste.

Then, Lin Fei also picked a lightness skill.

This technique was not as demanding.

The lightness skill that Lin Fei chose was called the "Leaping Technique."

It was very different from the "Flowing Clothes Skill."

The Flowing Clothes Skill was very light and agile, allowing for quick movements in a small space.

The Leaping Technique was different.

It was an instantaneous explosive lightness skill that could make people travel a long distance in an instant. Its speed was astonishing!

Lin Fei's lightness skill was actually very difficult to achieve perfection level. He didn't even think about achieving perfection.

Therefore, when he chose the lightness skill, he naturally tried to make up for some of its shortcomings.

The Flowing Clothes Skill was agile but lacked explosive power and speed.

The Leaping Technique made up for this deficiency.

Lin Fei chose the two martial arts techniques and went straight to the elder.

"Elder, I have chosen these two martial arts techniques."

The elder handed Lin Fei two secret manuals and said, "As usual, you can only read them for two hours."

Lin Fei entered the practicing room. He was familiar with the place.

Inside the practicing room, Lin Fei opened the Triple Wave Technique manual.

Before this, he had only seen a rough introduction to it.

But now, as he read through the contents, he realized just how extraordinary the Triple Wave Technique was.

It used the circulation of inner power to stack power in a special way.

The Triple Wave Technique only had three moves in total, but each move was more powerful than the last.

However, in the beginner and proficient stages, the amount of power the Triple Wave Technique could stack was very limited.

But once one reached mastery, it was different.

In the mastery realm, the second move could stack 30% of the power from the first move, and the third could stack 30% of the power from the second move.

If one reached transcendence, it could stack 50% of the power.

And if one reached perfection with the Triple Wave Technique, it was even more terrifying.

The power of the second move would be doubled, and the power of the third would be also doubled from the second.

This meant that if one used the third move of the Triple Wave Technique at the perfection realm, its power would be four times that of the first move.

It was equal to unleashing four times the amount of power!

68. Treasured Sabers

After some practice, Lin Fei got to the beginner stage of the Triple Wave Technique.

Next was the Leaping Technique.

The Leaping Technique was actually a way of propelling oneself upwards.

Although inner power only flowed through a few meridians, the span it would cross was very large, almost from top to bottom.

Such a long distance span would cause a great loss of inner power each time it was used.

So, even if an acquired martial artist used it, it would get very taxing on their inner power.

But Lin Fei was different.

His inner power was three-in-one.

Based on this, his inner power would only become more and more powerful in the future.

The Leaping Technique was very suitable for him.

After about half an hour, Lin Fei had basically understood the Leaping Technique.

He stood up.

The room was too narrow.

The Leaping Technique allowed him to move straight up and down, and he could cover a very long distance in one leap.

So, Lin Fei left the room.

"Whoosh."

The next moment, Lin Fei's inner power was activated.

Immediately, his legs seemed to have infinite strength.

Moreover, his body suddenly became light and ethereal.

His whole body was like a phantom.

In an instant, he leaped across dozens of meters.

"This Leaping Technique is really something!"

Lin Fei was very satisfied with the Leaping Technique.

"System."

The system panel appeared in front of Lin Fei.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired First Level

Three Vitality Technique: First Level (4% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (0% progress)

Triple Wave Technique: Beginner (5% progress)

Leaping Technique: Beginner (2% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (43% progress)

Saber-drawing Technique: Beginner (80% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

Lin Fei saw that he had entered the door for both the Triple Wave Technique and Leaping Technique.

Before reaching mastery or even transcendence, these martial arts would gradually improve.

There was also the Saber-drawing Technique, which was currently at the beginner level and had not yet reached proficiency.

"By the way, I've been using inner power to perform saber techniques lately. This saber seems to have trouble handling the explosive power of inner power.

Also, the Saber-drawing Technique is incredibly powerful. The longer I've been nurturing my saber, the more terrifying its power becomes.

So, I have to switch sabers. Only a treasured saber can withstand the explosive power of the Saber-drawing Technique!"

Lin Fei's saber was just an ordinary one.

It was fine for Body Refining, but not for the Acquired.

When an Acquired martial artist used inner power, the explosive force was not something an ordinary saber could handle.

After a few uses, the saber might break.

Lin Fei left the martial arts pavilion and went straight to the treasure pavilion.

He now had 300,000 contribution points.

There were also elders in the treasure pavilion, all of whom were Acquired-level martial artists.

There was no bargaining in the treasure pavilion, and it was different from ordinary shops.

He went to the elder in charge of the treasure pavilion and respectfully said, "Elder, I need a treasured saber that can withstand the explosive power of inner power."

The elder looked at Lin Fei and then walked over to a shelf full of sabers.

"All of these can withstand the explosive power of inner power. However, the weapon must fit the martial arts and be compatible with the techniques. What saber techniques do you practice?"

Lin Fei didn't hide anything and replied, "Elder, I practice the Nine Shadow Saber Technique and the Saber-drawing Technique. I've already reached perfection in the Nine Shadow Saber Technique."

"Hmm? I didn't expect you to be a saber genius. Your proficiency in saber techniques is so high."

"The Nine Shadow Saber Technique and the Saber-drawing Technique are both fast saber techniques. Therefore, the large saber on your back isn't suitable.

How about this, I suggest you choose two treasured sabers. One for everyday use with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, and one for nurturing the saber without unsheathing it."

Lin Fei thought it made sense.

Otherwise, he would only have one treasured saber, and he would have to unsheathe it every time he practiced the Nine Shadow saber Technique, which would prevent him from nurturing the saber.

He needed two treasured sabers.

Lin Fei respectfully bowed to the elder and said, "Disciple is not a master of the treasured saber. I hope the elder can help me choose one."

"For your Nine Shadow Saber Technique, use a good Star Saber. This Star Saber has a special material that can withstand the explosion of inner power, even if used at the peak of the acquired realm.

As for your Saber-drawing Technique, you need a truly treasured saber. Here is a Hidden Saber. It was specially crafted by a senior in our sect. That senior had perfected the Saber-drawing Technique.

With the Saber-drawing Technique, I had no idea how many strong enemies he had killed."

The Hidden Saber doesn't look conspicuous, but its material is even more special. Once the inner power explodes, the saber body can even become thinner, making the saber faster."

Lin Fei also nodded and said, "Since it is the elder's recommendation, Disciple will take the Star Saber and the Hidden Saber."

"Okay, the Star Saber is one thousand contribution points. As for the Hidden Saber, it is five thousand contribution points."

"So expensive?"

Lin Fei was surprised.

The Hidden Saber was really expensive.

It was equivalent to five thousand taels of silver.

This was a truly treasured saber!

However, the Hidden Saber was really suitable for the Saber-drawing Technique.

Moreover, Lin Fei was not lacking in contribution points now.

So, he spent six thousand contribution points to buy two treasured sabers.

Lin Fei carried the Star Saber on his back.

As for the Hidden Saber, its body was shorter and suitable for hanging on the waist.

And on the waist, it was also suitable for nurturing the saber.

Although Lin Fei spent six thousand contribution points, he had still over three hundred thousand contribution points.

And every month, inner disciples could get contribution points.

Therefore, contribution points were not lacking in the short term.

Lin Fei didn't need to do tasks.

Instead, he focused on staying in the inner sect.

In the following period of time, Lin Fei really didn't go anywhere.

He stayed in the Nine Profound Sect all the time.

Whether it was the Three Vitality Technique, Saber-drawing Technique, Leaping Technique, Triple Wave Technique, and so on, they were all in the early stages.

It was a time of rapid progress.

Therefore, Lin Fei didn't need to worry.

He just needed to wait patiently.

Time passed day by day.

In a blink of an eye, two months had passed.

In recent days, Lin Fei seemed to have heard that the inner disciples were discussing something.

It seemed that the Task Hall had issued an unusual task.

And it seemed to be issued by Ling Yao.

"Senior Sister Ling Yao encountered some trouble and actually went to the Task Hall to issue a task?"

Lin Fei had been in the inner sect for two months.

He had spent almost most of his time in his own yard.

He didn't have many friends in the inner sect.

Ling Yao was one of his close friends.

Since it concerned Ling Yao, Lin Fei was also very curious.

So, he got up and went straight to the Task Hall.

Inside the Task Hall, there were still many people.

Lin Fei glanced around.

Soon he found the task issued by Ling Yao.

"Recruiting disciples at the Fourth Level of Acquired or higher.

Assist Ling Yao in competing for the position of Princess, and you can get 500,000 contribution points after the event is completed.

The task may be life-threatening, so consider carefully when you come!"

The content of this task was very simple.

However, there was a lot of information revealed.

"Compete for the position of Princess?"

Lin Fei narrowed his eyes.

It seemed that Ling Yao's identity was not ordinary.

After all, the surname "Ling" was the royal surname of the Great Chang Dynasty!

69. Acquired Third Level

Lin Fei left the Task Hall, still thinking about Ling Yao.

Ling Yao was one of the top talents in the Nine Profound Sect, and her reputation precedes it.

She had befriended many inner disciples, so if she needed help, she could simply invite those disciples privately and many of them would be willing to assist her.

But why did Ling Yao publicly release a mission at the Task Hall, and why did she require a martial artist who acquired four levels at least to qualify?

How dangerous was the competition for the "Princess Position"?

Lin Fei looked up and said, "System."

Immediately, the system panel appeared before his eyes.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Third Level

Three Vitality Technique: Third Level (60% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (11% progress)

Triple Wave Technique: Mastery (65% progress)

Leaping Technique: Mastery (21% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (43% progress)

Saber-drawing Technique: Mastery (51% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

In just over two months, Lin Fei's martial arts made significant progress. He had achieved the third level of the Three Vitality Technique and was even close to the fourth level.

He has opened up the Lung Channel and Heart Channel and was currently working on opening the Pericardium Channel. He was now a genuinely acquired third level martial artist.

The cultivation speed was astonishing. However, he seemed to be having some trouble opening the Pericardium Channel, and his progress had slowed down a bit.

He could only increase his daily cultivation progress by 3%. It was estimated that it would take some time to completely open the third channel and advance to the acquired fourth level.

As for the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist, Lin Fei's practice of basic boxing increased his boxing skills, enabling him to achieve 11% progress in the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

However, he cannot raise it to the acquired level, as the inner power involved in boxing was very complex.

As for the Saber-drawing Technique, Triple Wave Technique, and Leaping Technique, Lin Fei made rapid progress and achieved mastery in all of them.

Especially the Saber-drawing Technique. Lin Fei wore the saber every day, nurturing the saber technique every day.

The saber had been nurtured for more than two months.

Once the saber was unsheathed, even Lin Fei didn't know what the power would be.

And there was inner power.

It was not displayed on the system panel.

But in reality, Lin Fei's inner power had made tremendous progress.

The three-in-one inner power allowed Lin Fei to have a continuous flow of inner power every day, gathering together.

The strength of Lin Fei's inner power was majestic.

Lin Fei felt that many acquired martial artists at the fifth, sixth, or even seventh level might not be as strong as him.

In just over two months, Lin Fei's comprehensive strength had at least increased tenfold!

With such strength by his side, Lin Fei remembered the help Ling Yao gave him in the beginning.

So, he had made up his mind.

In the beginning, Lin Fei owed Ling Yao a favor.

If Ling Yao needed help, he didn't mind lending a hand.

With this in mind, Lin Fei no longer hesitated and walked straight toward Ling Yao's courtyard.

...

In Ling Yao's courtyard.

Three female inner disciples sat around Ling Yao.

"Junior Sister Ling, have you contacted Senior Brother Chu and the others recently?"

"Yes, Senior Brother Chu used to be very fond of Junior Sister."

"Now that Junior Sister is competing for the position of Princess, it's time for Senior Brother Chu to show himself."

"With Senior Brother Chu, Junior Sister Ling will have a better chance of winning the position of Princess."

The Senior Brother Chu, the three female disciples kept mentioning, was a remarkable figure among the inner disciples of the Nine Profound Sect.

Young as he was, had already reached the seventh level of acquired.

His talent was even more amazing than Ling Yao's.

He was definitely an innate seedling!

Before, Ling Yao didn't dislike Senior Brother Chu.

If he could get innate, it would be a great help to her.

It was just that...

Ling Yao shook her head and said in a cold tone, "I've already contacted Senior Brother Chu, and he said he has important matters to attend to and has already left the mountain."

"What? Senior Brother Chu just broke through to the seventh level of acquired, how can there be any urgent matters? Moreover, no matter how important the matter is, can it be more important than Sister Ling competing for the position of the princess?"

"Hmph, it seems that Senior Brother Chu is also unreliable."

"Sister Ling, you can contact other senior brothers. Without Brother Chu, we still have hope."

"Yes, there are so many inner disciples in the Nine Profound Sect, it doesn't matter if we are missing one."

Ling Yao still said coldly, "I have already contacted Senior Brothers Zhao Yuanzheng, Luo Gang, Liu Fashi, and Zhang Yijian.

They are either in seclusion or have left the mountain, and none have come. And, I have already posted the task for several days. No one came here.

It seems that we can only rely on ourselves."

Although Ling Yao's tone remained unchanged, her heart had already grown cold.

She had thought that after so many years in the Nine Profound Sect, and having helped many fellow disciples, she would have received help in return when she needed it.

But now?

When she was in trouble and needed help, only a few close sisters were willing to help her.

"Sister Ling, when do we leave?"

"Yes, let's not wait any longer. If any inner disciple of Nine Profound Sect who meets the requirements is willing to help Sister Ling, they would have come already."

The other three female martial artists no longer wanted to wait.

"Okay, then we will leave tomorrow! Ling Yao thanks the three sisters for their help."

Ling Yao had already made up her mind.

However, she knew very well that the probability of success in competing for the position of the princess with these people was extremely low.

But she had no choice. She had to go!

"Senior Sister Ling."

At this moment, a male voice came from outside the courtyard.

"...Lin Fei?"

Ling Yao saw the figure outside the courtyard.

It was actually Lin Fei!

Ling Yao stood up, opened the courtyard door, and let Lin Fei enter.

Lin Fei saw three female disciples and knew they were all inner disciples.

So he clasped his fists and said, "Greetings to the three senior sisters!"

Ling Yao introduced, "This is Junior Brother Lin Fei, who just entered the inner sect a few months ago."

The three female disciples looked at Ling Yao when they heard Lin Fei had only been an inner disciple for a few months.

They showed disappointment and lost interest in learning more about Lin Fei.

After all, those who had just become inner disciples for a few months were mostly just Body Refining martial artists.

What could they do?

Lin Fei didn't care and directly asked Ling Yao.

"I saw the task you posted on the task hall, Senior Sister. If Senior Sister encounters any trouble, I'm willing to lend a hand!"

Lin Fei didn't beat around the bush and directly explained his intention.

Ling Yao still hadn't spoken.

One of the female disciples laughed out loud, "Junior Brother Lin, I didn't expect you to be braver than Senior Brother Chu and Liu.

At this time, there aren't many people willing to help Senior Sister Ling.

However, for Senior Sister Ling's matter, without having acquired strength above the fourth level, going there won't be of much help."

Lin Fei didn't speak but instead looked toward Ling Yao.

Ling Yao also sighed softly and said, "Not bad, Lin Fei. I'm glad you can come now. I understand your goodwill, but with your current strength, you cannot help me with my matter."

Ling Yao knew Lin Fei's background.

He had just entered the inner sect a few months ago.

How could he have the strength to help her now?

Lin Fei didn't say anything but went straight to the stone table of the three female disciples.

He reached out his hand and lightly pressed it on the stone table.

70. The Identity of Ling Yao

Ling Yao and several female disciples looked at Lin Fei curiously, wondering what he was going to do.

However, when Lin Fei gently pressed his hand on the stone table, there was a soft sound, then his hand lifted away from the table.

"This is..." Ling Yao's pupils suddenly shrank as she and the other three female disciples stared at the stone table, which had a palm print that was three inches deep!

Every martial artist present could break the stone table, but leaving a palm print three inches deep without breaking it was not something that anyone could do. It required extremely profound inner power and precise control.

"Lin Fei, did you break through to the acquired realm?" Ling Yao asked in surprise.

"Yes, I just broke through to the acquired realm two months ago," Lin Fei nodded and replied.

Ling Yao was surprised. She knew Lin Fei's background better than anyone else. In just a few months, Lin Fei had risen from the fourth level of Body Refining to the acquired realm. This speed of cultivation was unbelievable.

"Senior Sister Ling, can you tell me what's troubling you? Can you be specific?" Lin Fei asked. He wanted to help Ling Yao, so he needed to know the whole story.

Ling Yao nodded and said, "Of course. Actually, many people know the general idea of what happened.

I am the daughter of the South King of the Great Chang Dynasty. However, my mother was just a maid in the palace.

The South King had a one-night stand with my mother after drinking, which resulted in me.

I grew up in the palace, but my mother didn't have much status, even though she gave birth to me.

Later, my mother sent me to the Nine Profound Sect to learn martial arts through some connections.

Great Chang Dynasty is a country that values martial arts. Therefore, members of the royal family are also respected for their martial skills.

No matter whether one is the son or daughter of the South King, it still has to compete with others for the position of the crown prince or princess.

Even though I don't have a good background, I can still participate in the competition.

Every son and daughter of the South King can participate in the competition once. If successful, they will become the crown prince or princess and inherit the throne after the South King's death!

As for the age limit to participate in the competition, it must be before the age of eighteen at the latest.

I will be turning eighteen soon. So, I cannot delay any further and can only go for the position of the princess.

During the competition, it is allowed to invite some martial artists to help, but they must be martial artists that you have befriended.

So, I plan to invite some friends from the Nine Profound Sect to help me win the position of princess.

Once successful, not only will each person receive 500,000 contribution points that can be redeemed, but the princess can also participate in some sparring and competition among members of the royal family of the Great Chang Dynasty.

You will all receive various rewards beyond what an ordinary martial artist could imagine. So, if you choose to help me this time, there may be danger and even death. But equally, the rewards will be unimaginable!"

Ling Yao was very detailed in her explanation. There was no concealment.

After all, she needed everyone to work together and help her with all their might.

If there was any concealment, the loss would only be hers in the end.

Lin Fei also understood. This was a combination of danger and opportunity.

Lin Fei raised his head and calmly said, "Senior Sister Ling, I owe you a favor. This time, I'll go with you."

Lin Fei made his final decision.

As for danger? How could a martial artist not experience danger?

Besides, Lin Fei had confidence in himself.

With his current strength, even if he couldn't win, he should be able to save his life.

After all, he had been nurturing the saber for more than two months.

Once he displayed the Saber-drawing Technique, he didn't even know how terrifying its power would be.

"Okay, Junior Brother Lin, we are ready to depart. Do you need to prepare anything?"

Ling Yao didn't want to wait any longer.

"I don't have much to pack, just a few changes of clothes and I can leave at any time."

"Okay, we shouldn't delay. Let's meet in my courtyard tomorrow morning and set off!"

"Alright, I'll come tomorrow morning."

Lin Fei left Ling Yao's courtyard.

The three female disciples looked at Lin Fei's back.

They also glanced at the palm prints on the stone table.

One of the female disciples couldn't help but ask, "Senior Sister Ling, Junior Brother Lin only became an inner disciple a few months ago. Even if he has broken through to the acquired realm, his inner power shouldn't be so strong."

"Yes, without at least acquired fourth level, it's unlikely to produce this palm print," another disciple added.

"Acquired fourth level? Can any of you the acquired sixth level even do it?" Ling Yao's voice was deep and solemn as she spoke slowly, her gaze deep and profound.

Everyone shook their heads. They all had strong inner power, but they couldn't reach Lin Fei's level.

"There's one type of martial artist you've forgotten," Ling Yao said. "The three-in-one inner power! Only with it can one's inner power become so strong in just a few months."

"What, the three-in-one inner power?"

"That's the real innate seed!"

"Even Senior Brother Chu's potential is inferior to a genius with three-in-one inner power!"

"If it's really the three-in-one inner power, Senior Sister Ling, you must make sure to keep Senior Brother Lin. He could be the future innate strong."

"Yes, Brother Lin is loyal and trustworthy. He's willing to help you in such a dangerous mission. And he's highly likely to become the future innate strong. It's not easy to find someone like him."

...

Ling Yao watched as Lin Fei's figure gradually disappeared, and her gaze became more complicated.

Early the next morning, Lin Fei arrived at Ling Yao's yard.

The other three female disciples also arrived early.

"Senior Sisters and Junior Brother, let's go!"

Ling Yao didn't say anything unnecessary. Those who could help her were those who had already made up their minds. They didn't need any polite words.

The group of five quickly mounted their horses and arrived outside the mountain gate.

"Senior Sister Ling, is that Senior Brother Chu standing on the mountain behind us?" One of the female disciples suddenly called out to Ling Yao.

Ling Yao looked back and saw a tall man standing on the mountaintop, his gaze fixed on them.

"Senior Brother Chu..."

Ling Yao naturally recognized him, but what did it mean for him to watch her from the mountaintop at this time?

He never came out to help her.

Lin Yao glanced at Senior Brother Chu, who was on the hill, and then at Lin Fei, who had a calm expression on his face. It was obvious who was superior.

"Let's go!" Ling Yao gritted her teeth.

She mounted her horse and quickly left Nine Profound Sect, leaving a trail of dust.

71. Is It Okay To Kill?

A note from RighteousEgg

Due to plagiarism allegations, this story was removed from Royal Road. But now, everything has been sorted out.

The South King's Mansion in the capital city of Great Chang.

"Stop!"

Ling Yao, Lin Fei, and the other five people looked a bit dusty by now. Nine Profound Sect was very far from the capital city, and even with fast horses, it took them five days to get there.

Looking at the South King's Mansion, Ling Yao's expression was somewhat complicated.

She had lived in the mansion for a full ten years before being sent to the Nine Profound Sect to practice martial arts at the age of ten.

However, during those ten years, because of her identity, Ling Yao had a hard time having a good impression of the mansion's life.

Ling Yao dismounted her horse and went straight to the mansion's side door.

The main gate of the mansion was only opened to welcome very important people. Others usually entered through the side door.

"Stop."

The guards at the side door stopped Ling Yao, Lin Fei, and the others.

Ling Yao frowned and directly took out a token. "I'm Ling Yao."

"Is it Miss Nineteenth? Miss Nineteen, please come in."

The guards referred to the children of the South King by their numbers unless they held a title or an official position.

Recognizing Ling Yao's identity, the guards naturally did not dare to stop her.

Ling Yao led Lin Fei and the others directly into the mansion.

"Is that Miss Nineteenth? She's changed so much."

"Back then, when she was in the mansion, she was obedient and often bullied by the other princes. I didn't expect her to look so imposing now."

"That's because Miss Nineteen's mother has a low status, but Miss Nineteen's martial talent is excellent after being sent to Nine Profound Sect. From the looks of it now, she has a lot of confidence."

"Who would've thought that Miss Nineteen would come back to compete for the position of the princess."

For a while, the guards were discussing in a low voice.

In the South King's Mansion, competition for the position of the princess or prince happened from time to time if one had strength and ambition.

Although Ling Yao had a low status, she had excellent martial talent, and that was her biggest confidence.

Returning to the mansion, Ling Yao first went to see her mother.

Ling Yao's mother looked dignified and elegant and did not appear to be aging.

Although she was just a maid in the mansion, Ling Yao often sent money to her after showing her martial talent at Nine Profound Sect, so her mother's life had been much better in these years.

"Hello, Madam."

Lin Fei and the others also saluted Ling Yao's mother.

"Good, good. You've come from far away. Please sit down."

Upon seeing Lin Fei and the others, Ling Yao's mother only forced a smile and a hint of worry flickered in her eyes.

She held Ling Yao's hand and couldn't help but ask, "Yao, do you really want to compete for the position of Princess with Six?"

"Mother, I came back this time to compete for the position of Princess! Otherwise, why would I practice martial arts so hard at Nine Profound Sect?"

Ling Yao didn't hide her purpose for coming back.

Her mother sighed and said, "Yao, I am glad to see that you have ambition. However, Six has defeated six young ladies and eight young masters since becoming the Princess.

A total of fourteen competed for the position of Crown Prince, but they were all defeated by Six. Can you do it?"

Ling Yao's gaze was firm, and she said in a deep voice, "Mother, even if I can't, I have to try! You know the rules of the palace. Once a prince or princess turns eighteen and fails to win the position of Princess, they will be arranged to marry by the palace.

Once I'm married, I cannot practice martial arts at Nine Profound Sect. Without strong power, how can one control their own destiny?

Do I have to marry a fool like Thirteen Sister and cry all day long?

I don't want to accept such a fate. Therefore, no matter what, I have to try!"

The rule of the palace was that only the Princess could choose her husband after winning the position.

Only then could she control her own destiny!

"Okay, I can't control you. However, Six is shrewd. She must have already known about your return and will surely send someone to contact and investigate you.

Be careful and don't leave the palace if possible. Inside the palace, Six wouldn't dare to make a move."

Ling Yao nodded. Then, she asked the servants to arrange lodgings for Lin Fei and the others.

As the group of five walked towards the guest courtyard, they suddenly met two martial artists, one tall and thin, one short and fat.

"Nineteen, Princess heard that you came back and immediately asked us to bring you a message."

The tall and thin martial artist stopped Lin Fei and the others and said.

"Hmm? Fat Fool and Thin Fool, what message did Six send for me?" Ling Yao said coldly.

In the palace, only one person was qualified to be the Princess. That person was Six!

Only the person who won the position of Princess was qualified to be called Princess.

Of course, if it was a man, then he would be called the Prince.

"Nineteen, the Princess advises you to back down. Otherwise, if we really have to resort to force, you won't stand a chance! If you are willing to withdraw from the competition for the princess's position, then the princess can arrange a good marriage for you. Otherwise, if you lose, the princess has to choose a 'good husband' for you!"

The Fat and Thin Fools spoke in a strange tone.

It was clearly a threat.

If Ling Yao failed, the princess could choose a husband for her.

At that time, if she chose an idiot, then Ling Yao would be finished for life!

Ling Yao's eyes turned cold, "Sixth sister should be concerned about herself. She's not getting any younger, and if she fails and marries out, I'm afraid their marital relationship won't be too harmonious."

"Hehe, Nineteen, that's all I've to say. It's up to you what to do. However, I've heard that you have been helping fellow sect brothers everywhere in Nine Profound Sect these years. But when it comes to vying for the princess's position, you can't even find a martial artist who gets acquired seventh level. Moreover, what kind of experts can Nine Profound Sect produce? Miss Nineteen should give up as soon as possible with these people..."

After speaking, the Fat and Thin Fools left.

Several female disciples of the Nine Profound Sect, Li Yin, Ouyang Rong, and Xia Bing, were a little angry.

If it weren't for being in the palace, they would have taken action.

"Senior Sister Ling, where did these two come from?" Li Yin asked.

Ling Yao wasn't as angry as they were.

Instead, she said solemnly, "They are the Fat and Thin Fools under Sixth Sister, who are at acquired sixth level!

Their combined mastery can even fight against acquired seventh-level martial artists. And, besides them, Sixth Sister also has two acquired seventh-level experts under her.

In fact, our chances of winning are very small."

Ling Yao had already tried her best.

She trained hard for months and improved all the way to acquired sixth level from acquired fourth level.

Li Yin, Ouyang Rong, and Xia Bing, on the other hand, were all acquired sixth-level martial artists.

Their strength could not be underestimated.

However, they did not have an acquired seventh level martial artist.

This was their biggest disadvantage.

Originally, Ling Yao hoped that Senior Brother Chu could lend her a hand.

Senior Brother Chu had just broken through to the acquired seventh level.

Perhaps there would be more chances of winning.

Unfortunately, Senior Brother Chu was not willing to help Ling Yao compete for the princess's position.

"Sixth Sister's only weakness is that her own strength is lacking, only acquired fifth level.

But she has a deep background. With some connections from her mother's family, she has brought in some martial artists who get acquired sixth or even seventh level.

That's why she can defeat so many people and occupy the position of the princess for so many years."

Lin Fei secretly nodded.

He had already understood how the competition for the princess's position worked.

The strength itself might not be so important in the competition.

Instead, one needed some background, connections, and so on.

No matter where one finds these experts, in the eyes of the South King's Mansion, its ability to bring in these experts as support was a kind of strength in itself.

Relationships, connections, background - these were all part of one's strength.

And what about Ling Yao?

Her advantage lay in her high martial arts talent.

However, the competition for the position of princess required a comprehensive comparison of these strengths.

"Acquired seventh level is nothing. We can still give it a try!

Right, let's take care of Fat Fool and Thin Fool first when the competition begins. Then we'll focus on the two acquired seventh-level experts. We may still have a chance of winning!"

Li Yin, Ouyang Rong, and Xia Bing, the three female disciples, were all filled with fighting spirits.

They did have a chance of winning.

Especially Ling Yao, her skills in saber techniques were extraordinary.

She could even fight against an acquired seventh level martial artist for a period of time.

This would be an opportunity!

"Junior Brother Lin, are you scared now?"

Li Yin joked when she saw Lin Fei had been silent all along.

Lin Fei shook his head and didn't answer directly.

Instead, he looked in the direction where Fat and Thin Fools had disappeared.

In a calm tone, he said, "Senior Sister Ling, I just want to know one thing. Is it okay to kill in the competition?"

Although Lin Fei's tone was calm, for some reason, it made Ling Yao's heart skip a beat.

72. Killing Saber

Lin Fei's true strength remained a mystery to Ling Yao and the others, but he once disclosed that his realm was only at the Acquired Third Level.

Considering Lin Fei's exceptional saber technique, and highly possible that his inner power was three-in-one, challenging higher-level opponents was no difficult feat for Lin Fei.

Ling Yao had already raised her estimation of Lin Fei's strength, believing that he might be on par with Acquired Fifth Level.

It should not pose a problem restraining an Acquired Sixth Level martial artist, such as Fatty and Thin.

"Lin Fei, it won't be easy to deal with Fat and Thin Fools," Ling Yao warned.

"When the time comes, you can take on one of them while we deal with the other," she continued. "As for killing... except for Sixth Sister, you don't need to worry about killing anyone else."

Ling Yao's eyes flashed with a sharp light. "Even Sixth Sister can be killed according to the rules. But as a princess, let me do it. That way, the consequences and troubles that follow won't affect you."

Lin Fei nodded in understanding. He knew what Ling Yao meant.

The killing was allowed, even the princess. However, if they were to kill the princess, there would be repercussions and troubles that they would have to bear. As invited martial artists, it would be wiser to let Ling Yao handle it.

Lin Fei didn't say anything and retreated back into his usual silence. He rarely spoke throughout their journey, sometimes even making Li Yin and the others forget about his presence.

"Junior brother Lin, I see you have two sabers," Li Yin said with a smile. "The one on your back is probably a Star Saber, which is quite impressive. But the one on your waist doesn't look like a precious treasure saber. What's its use?"

Lin Fei glanced at the Hidden Saber on his waist and calmly replied, "It's also a killing saber. However, it cannot be drawn lightly. When the saber is drawn, blood must be shed."

Li Yin didn't take his words seriously, "You're quite the joker, Junior Brother Lin."

They were about to face Acquired Sixth and even Seventh Level experts. Even if Lin Fei drew his saber, what good would it do?

Lin Fei paid no attention to Li Yin's words and remained silent as usual.

However, Ling Yao took a deep glance at the saber at Lin Fei's waist for some reason. She seemed to somewhat believe in his words.

This saber could not be unsheathed lightly. When it was unsheathed, blood would be shed!

"Alright, everyone rests in the mansion for three days. After three days, we will officially begin the competition for the princess's position!" Ling Yao made up her mind.

So, Lin Fei and the others went to their rooms to rest.

...

In the courtyard of the princess's mansion in the South King's residence, there was only one person in everyone's mind when mentioning the princess, that was Ling Shuang!

Even among the capital of the Great Chang, Princess Ling Shuang was a household name.

She was very good at socializing and ambitious, with a deep background. She had been holding the position of princess for more than ten years by defeating one competitor after another.

At this moment, the Fat and Thin Fools arrived in front of Princess Ling Shuang.

"Your Highness, we have met Nineteenth. However, She seems unwilling to withdraw from the competition for the princess's position," Fat and Thin Fools reported respectfully.

Although the princess did not have much strength herself, she was very skilled at controlling her subordinates. Even the Fat and Thin Fools dared not be disobedient.

The princess was tall, with cold eyes. She glanced at the Fat and Thin Fools and chuckled, "Little Nineteen is of humble origin and has suffered a lot in the mansion since childhood.

Later, she was sent to the Nine Profound Sect, where she showed her talent in martial arts.

She will not give up. She must want to fight and become the princess to avenge her past and take control of her own fate!

However, she still doesn't understand that the competition for the princess's position is not something a lowly maid's daughter like her can participate in.

This time, except for Little Nineteen, I hope that no one by her side survives. Do you understand?"

"Yes, Your Highness, we understand!" The Fat and Thin Fools and the other martial artists behind the princess felt a chill in their hearts. They knew that the princess had taken murderous intent.

Three days passed in the blink of an eye.

During these three days, Lin Fei spent most of his time in his room.

As for gathering intelligence, that was left to Ling Yao.

Lin Fei was sure that Ling Yao would make good use of these three days to gather information about the experts under Princess's command.

Only by knowing oneself and the enemy could one have a chance of winning!

Today was the day of the battle for the position of Princess's successor.

Unlike Li Yin and the others, Lin Fei had a faint understanding that this battle would be extremely dangerous.

The attitude of the Fat and Thin Fools on the day of their encounter had already made it very clear.

Today, someone might die!

Lin Fei closed his eyes and gently touched the Hidden Saber at his waist.

Having nurtured the saber for more than two months, he could clearly feel how terrifying it was.

Once he unsheathed it, it would be a shocking strike.

But he didn't know if he could defeat Acquired Seventh Level experts with it.

"System."

Lin Fei brought up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Third Level

Three Vitality Technique: Third Level (87% progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (11% progress)

Triple Wave Technique: Mastery (74% progress)

Leaping Technique: Mastery (27% progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (43% progress)

Saber-drawing Technique: Mastery (60% progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% progress)

During these three days, Lin Fei's martial arts skills improved slightly.

Especially in the Three Vitality Technique, the training progress had reached 87%.

Although the progress of the Three Vitality Technique had decreased, Lin Fei was still able to make 3% progress every day.

In about four or five days, Lin Fei would be able to reach the acquired fourth level.

"Today is the day to fight for the position of Princess's successor. I'm still a little short of reaching the acquired fourth level.

But the difference between the third and fourth is just the amount of inner power. My inner power is enough!"

Lin Fei's gaze was calm.

Since he got the three-in-one inner power, he had already become different from ordinary martial artists, even in a class of its own.

Unless his opponent was a martial artist who also had the same three-in-one inner power, otherwise, his strength could not be judged by his level alone.

After all, even Acquired Sixth Level might not be able to surpass his current inner power. His three-in-one inner power had increased explosively by more than ten times before.

"Knock, knock, knock."

There was a knocking at the door.

Lin Fei stood up and opened the door.

"Senior Sister Ling."

It was Ling Yao who knocked on the door, followed by Li Yin and others.

"Lin Fei, are you ready?"

"I'm ready."

Ling Yao swept her gaze over everyone, her expression serious as she said in a deep voice, "In today's battle, don't hold back.

I have heard that my sixth sister is cruel and ruthless in her fights for the position of princess. There have been casualties in every battle.

So, in this battle, we must spare no effort to first kill the Fat and Thin Fools, and then go all out to deal with the remaining two Acquired Seventh Level martial artists. Only then can we have a chance of winning!"

Everyone nodded, indicating their understanding.

However, everyone felt heavy-hearted.

To concentrate their efforts on killing the Fat and Thin Fools first would not be easy.

This battle was destined to be a difficult struggle.

"Let's go!"

Ling Yao didn't say anything else.

She led Lin Fei and the others straight toward the martial arts arena in the palace.

73. The Weakest

The martial arts arena of the South King Mansion had already gathered many people early in the morning. Today was the day when the nineteenth daughter, Ling Yao, and the sixth daughter, Ling Shuang, would compete for the position of the princess.

The people of the mansion had been looking forward to this day for a long time.

"Does Miss Nineteenth have a chance?"

"I heard that Ling Yao has a good talent in martial arts. She is one of the top genius disciples in the Nine Profound Sect. If she can keep practicing, she might become innate."

"Innate? Don't even think about it. Do you think becoming innate is that easy? How many geniuses are stuck at the peak of acquired? It's too difficult to become innate.

Moreover, if Nineteenth fails to compete for the position of the princess, she will get married. Once she gets married and has children, her martial arts will be completely abandoned, and there will be no chance to achieve the innate."

"Will Miss Nineteenth definitely fail? What if she succeeds?"

"Succeed? Hmph, the princess has held the position for more than ten years and has defeated many opponents. You should know that the competition for the position of the princess is not just about talent in martial arts or one's own strength."

Many people were whispering and discussing quietly.

"She's here, Miss Nineteenth is here."

Ling Yao led the people and arrived at the martial arts arena first.

"Yao, don't try to be strong if you can't defeat them."

"Mother, don't worry. Your daughter knows what to do."

Swish.

Ling Yao's gaze instantly turned to the other side of the martial arts arena.

There was a familiar figure also coming here.

Princess Ling Shuang!

Ling Yao remembered that Ling Shuang had always been a princess since she could remember.

Ling Shuang didn't say anything but gave Ling Yao a cold glance, and then sat down in a chair and closed her eyes to rest.

Lin Fei's gaze also turned to the princess, but he was looking at the people behind her.

There were four martial artists standing behind the princess.

Two of them were the Fat and Thin Fools that Lin Fei had already seen.

The other two were both holding long swords.

They seemed to be swordsmen.

One person wore a cloak and black clothes, and his appearance was unclear, with a somewhat gloomy temperament.

The other person wore a white robe and had sword-shaped eyebrows and a starry look, appearing very handsome.

According to the information Ling Yao had obtained, these two were both Acquired Seventh Level martial artists.

"The martial artist in the black cloak is named Yuan Ming. His origins are unknown, and it's not clear where Ling Shuang found him. He is good at swordsmanship, ruthless and decisive, and good to kill with one strike.

The white-clad martial artist, named Zhao Tianlei, is a strong member of Ling Shuang's mother's family. He was specifically sent to help Ling Shuang maintain her position as the princess."

Ling Yao quietly introduced the strongman behind Princess Ling Shuang to Lin Fei and others.

Both of them reached the seventh level, which made them a master anywhere.

Not everyone practiced martial arts like Lin Fei.

In fact, there were many bottlenecks for martial artists.

Some people could get stuck in Body Refining for a lifetime.

Even if they were lucky enough to break through to Acquired, they were still below the fourth level.

It was harder than climbing to the sky to break through to acquired fourth level for some people.

Similarly, the seventh level of Acquired was also a bottleneck.

Many people were stuck in the acquired sixth level and cannot break through.

Li Yin, Ling Yao, and others were all in this situation.

Although Ling Yao seemed to cultivate quickly, it was also very difficult for her to break through the bottleneck of the acquired seventh level.

If she delayed for a few more years, she would have no hope of getting innate in this life.

Therefore, Princess Ling Shuang's ability to gain the support of two masters at acquired seventh level was already a very strong performance.

"The South King has arrived!"

Suddenly, a man dressed in a python robe, with a sturdy figure and extraordinary momentum, under the escort of many guards, came to the martial arts field. And he directly sat on the high platform.

That was the South King! Ling Yao's father.

Ling Yao looked at the figure of the South King on the high platform.

Her expression was somewhat complicated.

Actually, Ling Yao had no impression of her father.

Since birth, the South King had seen her only a handful of times.

After all, there are many children in the king's family.

Ling Yao was not outstanding.

How could she easily see the South King?

However, for such an important matter as competing for the position of the princess, the South King must be present.

"Ling Yao and Ling Shuang are competing for the position of a princess. Each person can bring four martial artists to assist. The winner will become the princess! Alright, let's begin."

The South King glanced at Ling Yao, but he remained expressionless as if there was no emotional attachment. It was as if she wasn't his daughter.

Ling Yao stood up, and Lin Fei and the others followed her. On the other side, Ling Shuang was also accompanied by four martial artists.

Both sides entered the arena.

The rules for competing for the position of the princess were simple - one only needed to defeat their opponent in the arena.

The Great Chang Dynasty was built upon martial prowess, and for the royal family, martial arts were the ultimate form of respect. Only those with strong martial abilities were eligible to hold the title of the South King.

Ling Yao and Princess Ling Shuang stood on the left and right sides of the arena respectively, staring at each other.

Princess Ling Shuang glanced at the South King and then smiled as she spoke to Ling Yao, "Little Nineteen, I never expected that the once meek and submissive you would now stand before me and even dare to compete with me for the position of the princess. Life is indeed unpredictable."

"Sixth sister, words are useless. No matter what, I must take control of my own fate. Otherwise, what's the point of practicing martial arts?" Ling Yao replied.

Both of them fell silent, and the atmosphere immediately became tense.

"Attack!"

Ling Yao shouted, and she took the initiative to strike first.

As planned, Ling Yao and her group wanted to pay any price to kill Fat and Thin Fools first. Thus, Ling Yao made her move, and her movements were like illusions as she swiftly approached them.

It was a very sophisticated movement technique, and Ling Yao's saber was swung instantly.

"Swish!"

Nine saber shadows.

One slash, nine shadows. This was the perfection level of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

"Clang!"

A light sound echoed.

Ling Yao's expression changed slightly, and she looked up to see a figure in white standing before her - Zhao Tianlei!

Acquired Seventh Level Zhao Tianlei suddenly appeared in front of Fat and Thin Fools. Moreover, Fat and Thin Fools moved like ghosts, rushing toward Lin Fei and Li Yin.

Obviously, this was not an impulsive decision but a planned attack.

Princess Ling Shuang had been standing behind Zhao Tianlei, and the mysterious martial artist Yuan Ming, who wore black clothing and a cape, was also standing next to her. Yuan Ming acted like a shadow and seemed to be protecting Ling Shuang.

"I know what you're planning, little Nineteen. You want to kill Fat and Thin Fools first and then join forces against Zhao Tianlei and Yuan Ming. Too bad your plan failed." Ling Shuang laughed as if everything was under her control.

"Lin Fei, Li Yin..." Ling Yao gritted her teeth, wanting to withdraw and support Lin Fei and the others. However, Zhao Tianlei's sword was as fast as a shooting star, leaving Ling Yao with no time to spare.

"We have four and they only have two," Li Yin and the others' eyes flashed with determination, not afraid of Fat and Thin Fools' strength.

Li Yin, Xia Bing, and Ouyang Rong displayed their agility and rushed forward. However, before they could engage in combat, Fat and Thin Fools suddenly changed their direction and rushed toward Lin Fei, who was behind them.

Their true target was Lin Fei!

"Hehe, we've already investigated you. You, an Acquired Third Level martial artist, dare to interfere in the competition!? Death!" The Princess had already investigated and deemed Lin Fei the weakest link, thus he became the target.

Fat and Thin Fools were both Acquired Sixth Level top experts. They used a combination attack, moving left and right, and charged toward Lin Fei.

Li Yin, Xia Bing, and Ouyang Rong's faces turned pale, but they were unable to keep up with Fat and Thin's speed. They could only watch as the duo's combined attack blocked all of Lin Fei's retreat paths.

Their combined attack was even comparable to Acquired Seventh Level experts!

Once it hit Lin Fei, he was bound to die!

74. If I Draw My Saber, There Will Be Blood

"Lin Fei..."

Ling Yao couldn't help but shout out loudly. However, she had only Acquired Sixth Level. Even though her saber skills were formidable, it was already good enough for her to deal with Zhao Tianlei.

How could she free herself and save Lin Fei? Now, no one could save Lin Fei!

"Swish."

The next moment, Lin Fei made his move. He didn't use his saber techniques. Instead, he used his fist like the Fat and Thin Fools.

"Triple Wave."

Lin Fei lifted his head calmly. Both hands were clenched into fists, and he punched towards the Fat and Thin Fools.

"Bang."

The fists of the three people collided heavily. Under Lin Fei's calm expression, his inner power erupted like a volcano. The terrifying inner power surged, combined with Lin Fei's blood, bone, and muscle strength.

It suddenly made the Fat and Thin Fools' faces change. Even their arms were trembling.

"You are an acquired third-level martial artist, how can you have such a profound inner power?"

"And the strength is so terrifying?"

The Fat and Thin Fools were shocked. But Lin Fei was calm. He immediately withdrew his fist. Then he punched again.

This was the second move.

Lin Fei had reached mastery in the Triple Wave Technique. Therefore, the second move's power was 1.3 times stronger than the first!

Lin Fei's punch was extremely fast. And the moves were connected. Just like real waves. It was difficult to even retreat.

The Fat and Thin Fools felt like their arms were about to break. Lin Fei's strength was even stronger than before.

"Retreat, quickly retreat!" They wanted to retreat. But Lin Fei's third move came again.

The punch, based on the second move, increased its power by thirty percent. The terrifying force was unstoppable, like a landslide.

It landed heavily on the two men's arms.

"Crack."

Their arms broke with a sound, and the two men screamed in pain. Their bodies were directly punched by Lin Fei and heavily fell to the ground. Their internal organs were in pain as if they were overturned, powerless to get up.

Suddenly, everyone was amazed.

"Fat and Thin Fools were defeated?"

"Fat and Thin Fools have joined forces and performed a combined attack technique that can rival the acquired seventh level. Who is this person who can defeat them in just a few moves?"

"Nineteen actually recruited such a master, even if he is not at the acquired seventh level, he is not far from it."

"Perhaps, this battle is really unpredictable."

Many people were surprised. Even Ling Yao, Li Yin, and others. They thought that Lin Fei could at most match an acquired fifth-level martial artist. Even with the Perfection-level Saber Technique, it was already impressive to hold back an acquired sixth-level martial artist.

But now?

Lin Fei defeated Fat and Thin Fools in just a few moves. His strength could even rival that of the acquired seventh level! This was unbelievable. They were very clear that Lin Fei was only in the acquired third-level realm.

"Junior Sister Ling, we'll help you."

At this moment, Li Yin and others were ready to help Ling Yao. But Ling Yao shook her head and said, "I can hold on. You go and attack Sister Six, if we defeat her, we'll win!"

Li Yin, Ouyang Rong, and Xia Bing's eyes lit up.

Yes, Princess Ling Shuang was the key. Princess Ling Shuang only had the strength of the acquired fifth level. And now, she only had one Yuan Ming to protect her. If they had all attacked together, which might just end the fight.

"Kill."

The three women jumped up and rushed toward Ling Shuang. Lin Fei's brows furrowed slightly. He felt a faint sense of threat from Yuan Ming for some reason. He always felt that this Yuan Ming was very dangerous.

More dangerous than Zhao Tianlei!

However, now was indeed a good opportunity. Once they defeat the Princess, they would win! Li Yin and the others knew that they needed to work together, so no one rushed toward the Princess first. After all, Yuan Ming was an acquired seventh level expert. If they were alone, they would probably be defeated one by one by Yuan Ming. But if they acted together, even if Yuan Ming was an acquired seventh level expert, she wouldn't be able to defeat them all at the same time.

The three women approached the Princess, but she seemed completely calm and collected, without any hint of panic. However, when she looked at the fat and thin duo lying on the ground, a flash of sharpness appeared in her eyes.

"Yuan Ming, leave no one alive!" The Princess's tone was as cold as ice. Yuan Ming beside her was like a cold wooden statue.

As Princess' words fell, he moved.

"Whoosh."

A white light flashed, reflecting off the sword's blade.

The sword was too fast. Li Yin, Ouyang Rong, and Xia Bing only felt a flash before their eyes, and then a cold sensation on their necks. Then, they felt lost all strength...

"Senior Sister Ling..."

Li Yin, Ouyang Rong, and Xia Bing all tightly held their necks. But they couldn't stop the blood flowing from the long wounds on their necks. Their bodies fell to the ground, lifeless.

"Li Yin, Ouyang Rong, Xia Bing..."

Ling Yao's eyes widened, bloodshot veins appearing in them. She wildly swung her saber, exploding her inner power.

She managed to repel Zhao Tianlei in one strike, but it was too late. Li Yin and the others were already dead.

At the same time, Lin Fei's whole body was covered in goosebumps. He felt danger approaching!

Without much thought, Lin Fei drew his saber, and he could vaguely feel a blurry shadow in front of him, even a sharp edge cutting his skin like it was going to cut his neck.

"Whoosh!"

Lin Fei slashed with his saber, and suddenly, countless sharp saber edges filled the sky, forming thirteen shadows.

"Ding!"

The sound of metal colliding echoed in Lin Fei's ears. Then, a powerful force came from the opponent's sword through Lin Fei's saber, and even his body couldn't completely offset the force.

"Bang Bang Bang!"

Lin Fei took three steps back in succession before regaining his stance. He raised his head and saw a figure with a short sword in hand standing not far from him.

It was not eye-catching, but there were droplets of blood falling to the ground.

Yuan Ming!

The acquired seventh-level martial artist was like a shadow. He killed Li Yin and the others with just one move and almost killed Lin Fei too.

"Lin Fei, are you okay?"

Ling Yao saw that Li Yin and the others were already dead and couldn't care about her grief and anger. She came to Lin Fei immediately, her face full of vigilance.

Lin Fei reached out and touched the skin on his neck, where a thin bloodstain had appeared.

Ling Yao was also shocked to see this. Lin Fei had taken a hit from the opponent's sword.

"Good swordsmanship," Lin Fei praised.

"Good hard martial arts," Yuan Ming replied coldly.

Finally, Lin Fei's Vajra Iron Cloth came in handy. Although the opponent's sword did not cut Lin Fei's neck, the sword energy did it, and if it were not for Vajra Iron Cloth, Lin Fei would have been hit by the sword energy and died.

Yuan Ming had mastered a terrifying perfection-level sword technique. This kind of martial artist was almost comparable to those at the acquired ninth level or higher.

Ling Yao was also sweating coldly at the moment. She looked at the bodies of Li Yin and the others on the ground and then at the bloodstain on Lin Fei's neck. Ling Yao seemed to have made a decision.

"Lin Fei, I give up, if we keep fighting, you will die too. We surrender," Ling Yao said.

Ling Yao had completely given up. Zhao Tianlei could at least be held back, but Yuan Ming was too terrifying. Even Senior Brother Chu would be certain to die!

Lin Fei remained silent. His gaze swept over the bodies of Li Yin and the others on the ground and then looked at Ling Yao, who was full of tears and self-blame.

Lin Fei's hand gradually gripped the Hidden Saber at his waist.

"I have one strike. If I draw my saber, there will be blood. Senior Sister Ling, you have helped me many times before. I owe you a favor, and this is worth it."

"Lin Fei, you..." Ling Yao was about to say something, but Lin Fei's figure had leaped in the direction of Yuan Ming all at once. A leap of several dozen meters. This was the Leaping Technique.

At the same time, Lin Fei's right hand had already gripped the saber at his waist.

75. Earth-shattering And Heaven-battering

Lin Fei had been nurturing the Hidden Saber for over two months.

It was the moment to draw the saber!

"Hmph, they really don't take me seriously."

Zhao Tianlei's face turned cold. He was also a powerful Acquired Seventh Level martial artist. But now, it seemed that no one took him seriously.

Ling Yao, an Acquired Sixth Level martial artist, was able to fight with him for a long time. And now Lin Fei, an Acquired Third Level martial artist, was somewhat special. Although he defeated Fat and Thin Fools, he actually went straight for Yuan Ming instead of him. Was he being treated as a decoration?

So Zhao Tianlei took a step forward. His long sword in hand instantly turned into a sharp blade. He directly stood between Lin Fei and Yuan Ming, stabbing Lin Fei with his sword. However, Lin Fei didn't even look at him.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei drew his saber!

This slash made an earth-shattering and heaven-battering noise!

No one could see the speed of the saber.

All they could see was a fleeting black light.

The saber was so sharp and it filled the sky.

Even if the audiences were far away, they felt they had been cut by the saber.

"Crack."

Lin Fei stopped.

His Leaping Technique, coupled with his Saber-drawing Technique, made his speed unimaginable. His Hidden Saber was now sheathed. He stood with his back to Zhao Tianlei, only three meters away from Yuan Ming. It was close enough to attack range. But Yuan Ming still held his sword in his hand, not to have made a move. He just stood there quietly.

"Yuan Ming...Zhao Tianlei! You..."

Ling Shuang's face finally showed a hint of panic. She had just thought everything was under control. But now, with Lin Fei's move, she was finally a little flustered.

Although she couldn't see clearly what Lin Fei's saber had done, she felt its terror.

As Princess's voice fell, the cloak of Yuan Ming split into two halves in an instant, revealing his true face hidden underneath. It was a thin face covered in scar after scar, each one more ghastly and terrifying than the last. A deep wound had appeared on his neck, which seemed to barely hold up his head.

With a "plop", Yuan Ming fell to the ground, lifeless. He never even got the chance to say a word before he died. And in the next moment, Zhao Tianlei also fell to the ground with his eyes wide open, as if in disbelief. He had died the same way as Yuan Ming, with a deep cut on his neck that could easily sever his head with a little more force.

For a moment, the arena was filled with corpses, and the air was thick with the smell of blood. The whole martial arts field was quiet, and no one had expected this kind of outcome.

"What kind of saber technique is that?"

"I didn't even see when he drew his saber."

"With just one saber strike, he killed two Acquired seventh level experts. Even Yuan Ming, who was comparable to an Acquired ninth level expert, was killed with one saber strike!"

"This saber technique's power is really earth-shattering and even comparable to an Acquired peak saber technique!"

"But he's a low-level Acquired martial artist, how could he draw such a terrifying saber technique?"

Many people did not see clearly the saber technique that Lin Fei had used. Among all those present, only South King had seen it clearly. His eyes became extremely sharp as he stared at Lin Fei.

"What a profound Saber-drawing Technique!" The South King exclaimed.

He knew Saber-drawing Technique very well, and in fact, it was practiced by many major martial arts schools.

The technique appeared to be excellent, accumulating power by nurturing the saber, and bursting out with astonishing power when the saber was drawn.

But in reality, few people practiced it because nurturing a saber was not that simple. Many people had nurtured their saber for a year and had not gained much power.

The reason for this was that many martial artists could not master Saber-drawing Technique.

Additionally, the time spent nurturing the saber each day was limited, and inner power would gradually be consumed. To be able to spend two hours nurturing the saber each day was considered good.

And what about Lin Fei?

His inner power was three-in-one. He was not afraid of consuming inner power. Moreover, his Saber-drawing Technique had already reached mastery.

In fact, given enough time, he could even reach transcendence and perfection, which would not be a difficult task for him.

Furthermore, Lin Fei's martial arts could operate on their own. It was constantly nurturing his saber. Although he had only nurtured his saber for just over two months, it was equivalent to other martial artists nurturing their saber for several years!

Therefore, when Lin Fei used his Saber-drawing Technique, its power was so terrifying that could kill two acquired seventh level experts with one strike!

"Lin Fei, that strike just now..."

Ling Yao hurriedly came to Lin Fei's side, her face full of shock.

This one saber strike was beyond her imagination. How could a mere acquired third level martial artist make such a terrifying saber strike?

"It's just the Saber-drawing Technique. I have been nurturing my saber for a long time, so I have the power of this strike. Ling Senior Sister, is this saber strike enough to repay your favor?" Lin Fei said calmly.

"It's more than enough," Ling Yao was still stunned by the power of Lin Fei's Saber-drawing Technique.

"I never thought that my help to you would give me the biggest surprise today! Sister Six, are you still fighting or admitting defeat?" Ling Yao stared straight at Ling Shuang. This was a battle for the position of the princess, and it was not over yet.

Ling Shuang lifted her head. At this moment, her face was pale. Although she was unharmed, she knew that she had lost. And lost completely!

Her own strength was only acquired fifth level. Ling Yao was acquired sixth level, and even beyond the ordinary acquired sixth level.

"Little Nineteen, you are very lucky to have met a top-notch expert like Lin Fei, who hides his true strength. This time, I lost. I will never have a chance to become a princess. However, little Nineteen, you are just lucky. You think being a princess is easy? Haha, I've been a princess for sixteen years, and now I've fallen so low... Someday, little Nineteen, you will follow in my footsteps..." With that, Ling Shuang leaped and left the martial arts arena.

"I concede," Ling Shuang's voice echoed through the arena.

She gave up. After being a princess for sixteen years, she ultimately lost. A new princess was born. Ling Yao, the new princess of the South King Palace!

Ling Yao's expression was complicated. She didn't know how terrible the consequences of Ling Shuang's defeat would be. But it wouldn't be simple. After all, the position of the princess wasn't hers alone.

The power and resources that had supported her for sixteen years were now wasted. What would become of her? But this was the cruelty of the fight for the position of the princess.

Losers are always in the wrong.

The South King paid no attention to Ling Shuang. He had seen such scenes many times before. He had too many children. Besides, the South King himself had become the crown prince after winning countless struggles and eventually became the South King. So, he was accustomed to it.

The South King immediately announced loudly, "My nineteenth daughter, Ling Yao, from today on, is the new princess of the South King Palace!"

At that moment, Ling Yao's wish was fulfilled. Finally, the position of the princess was hers.

76. Saber-drawing Technique Reached Transcendence

"Your Saber-drawing Technique which has slayed the strong enemies surpassed itself with ease, attaining a profound understanding of the true essence of drawing a saber, resulting in a 50% increase in the progress of cultivation."

"Your Saber-drawing Technique has reached transcendence!"

"Your Leaping Technique, combined with your Saber-drawing Technique, has comprehended the secret of 'leaping forward,' leading to a 50% increase in the progress of cultivation."

Suddenly, Lin Fei heard a voice from the system. He closed his eyes, and a memory of the Saber-drawing Technique appeared in his mind. His understanding of the Saber-drawing Technique had become even more profound, reaching the level of transcendence.

The Saber-drawing Technique at the level of transcendence had a significant improvement, both in terms of nurturing and drawing a saber. It was a qualitative leap.

His Leaping Technique also made great strides. Although its progress had not yet reached 100%, it had achieved a breakthrough.

This newfound comprehension brought Lin Fei closer to the level of transcendence in his Leaping Technique. Lin Fei thought it would not take long to reach it.

The battle for the position of the princess had ended, and Lin Fei returned to his room in the palace to rest. As for the aftermath of Li Yin, Ouyang Rong, and Xia Bing, Ling Yao would undoubtedly take care of it.

Lin Fei drew his Hidden Saber and savored the breathtaking sensation of his Saber-drawing Technique.

He could not use it anymore for the time being, as he needed to nurture his saber again. This was the way of the Saber-drawing Technique.

No matter how long he nurtured it, be it months or years, even decades, once he drew the saber, he would need to nurture it again.

With a snap, Lin Fei returned the Hidden Saber to its scabbard, and the technique of nurturing the saber began to work automatically.

Lin Fei had a vague feeling that his Hidden Saber was slowly gathering power, and it was much faster than before. After all, he had already reached the Transcendence realm in the Saber-drawing Technique.

If he nurtured his saber two months now, it would surely have even more terrifying power than before. If he could perfect the Saber-drawing Technique, it would be even more frightening.

"Dong Dong Dong."

At dusk, there was a knock on Lin Fei's door. He opened it to find Ling Yao standing outside in a new outfit, wearing the attire of a princess, looking elegant and dignified. And she seemed to have a touch more majesty on her.

"Lin Fei, sorry. I've been busy all day and only now have some free time. I haven't even thanked you for changing my destiny. I know the help I gave you before was insignificant, but today, you really saved me and changed my fate," Ling Yao said.

Lin Fei remained silent as Ling Yao continued, "Here are the 500,000 silver bills we agreed on, as well as the contribution points."

Lin Fei took the silver bills. He deserved it.

"By the way, I just obtained the position of the princess and received some news. Every three years, the various branches of the Great Chang royal family hold an internal competition among the royal family members. There are still a few months left until the competition, and followers can participate as well.

So, I want to invite you to participate in the competition with me. If we get in the top three, we can obtain the Heavenly Meridian Pill."

Lin Fei's heart was slightly moved and asked, "What kind of spiritual elixir is the Heavenly Meridian Pill and what does it do?"

Ling Yao explained, "The Heavenly Meridian Pill is a treasure for Acquired Martial Artists. If an Acquired Martial Artist takes one, it can help them open up a meridian except for the Ren and Tu channels. It's like directly increasing one's level.

Many Acquired Martial Artists use it to break through bottlenecks. Unfortunately, each Acquired Martial Artist can only take one Heavenly Meridian Pill. Taking a second one won't have any effect. Despite this, it is still a dream pill for many Acquired Martial Artists!"

Lin Fei's eyes brightened at the hearing of such a miraculous elixir.

"Is there a recipe for this Heavenly Meridian Pill?" Lin Fei asked. If there was a recipe, perhaps Lin Miao could refine it.

"Do you know how precious is the Heavenly Meridian Pill? Moreover, it's not martial artists who refine the Heavenly Meridian Pill, but immortal masters! And it is refined by immortal masters who have surpassed the Qi Condensation Realm. Even if there is a recipe, ordinary people cannot refine it. Only our Great Chang Dynasty and some powerful immortal masters possess the recipe for the Heavenly Meridian Pill."

Lin Fei understood. The recipe for the Heavenly Meridian Pill could not be obtained. However, the pill could be obtained through royal competition. Moreover, it was a benefit given by the royal family to its members. Ordinary people did not have the opportunity to obtain it.

"This is a good thing, and of course, I agree," Lin Fei said with a smile.

Ling Yao nodded and pondered for a moment before saying, "Lin Fei, there are still a few months before the royal competition. What do you think to stay in the palace?"

However, Lin Fei shook his head and said, "No, a few months is still a long time. I'd rather go back to Nine Profound Sect. If the date of the competition is confirmed, you can send a letter to Nine Profound Sect, and I will come here."

Lin Fei didn't want to stay in Chang City. Chang City was the center of the Great Chang Dynasty. Various forces were entangled there. Moreover, Ling Yao was now a princess with a special status. The situation she faced was even more complicated. Anyway, it was better to go back to Nine Profound Sect.

"Okay, when the date of the competition is confirmed, I will inform you by letter," Ling Yao also nodded.

It was evident that Ling Yao was very excited now. She even had a feeling of "grand ambitions." After all, she had just become a princess. This was Ling Yao's long-cherished wish. Now, it had finally come true. Naturally, she was very excited.

However, Lin Fei also reminded her, "Senior Sister Ling, we're martial artists, only martial arts are fundamental! Even if Senior Sister Ling is in Chang City, Senior Sister should focus on practicing martial arts. If you are obsessed with trivial worldly affairs, I'm afraid Senior Sister Ling's martial arts will hardly improve."

Ling Yao nodded. However, she sighed and said, "Thank you for reminding me, Junior Brother Lin. Indeed, martial arts are the foundation of martial artists. But I have become a princess. Once I sit in this position, there are some things that I cannot control.

Although martial arts must be practiced, it is impossible to put all those worldly affairs aside. Moreover, innate is so difficult to obtain. Not everyone can get innate.

Even if I do my best and focus solely on practicing martial arts, I cannot guarantee that I will achieve the innate. My father, the south king, has already reached the peak of acquired, just one step away from innate. But this step has trapped my father for twenty years."

Lin Fei understood. Ling Yao had chosen another path.

"Junior Brother Lin, you are a true innate seed. In the future, if I want to secure my position as a princess, I am afraid that I will need Junior Brother Lin's help.

If Junior Brother Lin needs anything, just say it. I will do my best to help Junior Brother."

This was Ling Yao's promise. It was also Ling Yao's attempt to win over Lin Fei. After all, in many years to come, Ling Yao wanted to secure her position as a princess and she still needed Lin Fei's support.

Lin Fei did not express any opinion, but nodded and said, "If I need anything, I won't be polite."

Ling Yao also breathed a sigh of relief. As long as Lin Fei was willing to support her, she would have more time to recruit more skilled experts and have the confidence to secure her position as a princess.

Ling Yao left.

For Ling Yao's choice, Lin Fei could only shake his head. He did not care about any power or status. Without immortality, after a hundred years, everyone would turn to dust.

Lin Fei was on the path to immortality. He would single-mindedly practice martial arts.

Without the talent of Qi cultivation, only martial arts could help Lin Fei achieve immortality. Therefore, he would spare no effort and pay any price to pursue the path of martial arts.

78. Cut In Half

Haizhou City was a city located by the East Sea, and it had ports. Merchants loaded their goods and sailed to other countries on the other side of the sea to do business, making huge profits from maritime trade. This was something that everyone knows.

Haizhou City was nominally under the jurisdiction of the Great Chang Dynasty, but in reality, as the Great Chang Dynasty had gradually declined over the years and there had been rebellions in various places, the government's control over the border areas had become weak, including Haizhou City. In fact, it was jointly governed by the government and the Nine Profound Sect, with the latter being the main authority.

Therefore, when pirates appeared near Haizhou City, the Nine Profound Sect became so nervous that they dispatched disciples to eliminate the pirates immediately. Lin Fei and his team of about 20 people arrived at Haizhou City and went to the Nine Profound Sect branch there. The branch leader Mo Wen was acquired fifth level but was already over forty years old and unlikely to make further progress in his lifetime.

Upon seeing Lin Fei sitting in the seat of honor, Mo Wen immediately respectfully greeted him, "Greetings, Chief. I am Mo Wen, the branch leader of the Nine Profound Sect in Haizhou City."

Mo Wen had received a pigeon message and knew that disciples from the Nine Profound Sect were coming, led by the "chief disciple" Lin Fei. He was to obey all of Lin Fei's orders. However, even though he knew the news beforehand, Mo Wen was still somewhat surprised to see such a young disciple becoming the chief disciple. Moreover, it seemed that Lin Fei's cultivation level was not very high?

Mo Wen was not sure, but a team of twenty inner disciples was quite terrifying, enough to sweep the entire Haizhou City.

"Mo Wen, tell me about the current situation in Haizhou City. Have there been any pirates?" Lin Fei asked directly.

Mo Wen thought for a moment and reported, "Reporting to the Chief, we haven't found any trace of pirates in Haizhou City at the moment. However, some nearby villages have encountered pirates.

Those pirates are extremely brutal, not only looting but also slaughtering people in nearby villages. Now, the villages outside Haizhou City have basically been looted by pirates, and no one dares to stay outside the city. They have all entered the city."

"Hmm, entered the city? You let people from outside the city come in?"

Lin Fei stared at Mo Wen with a cold gaze.

Mo Wen felt Lin Fei's sharp gaze like a saber and dared not look directly at him. Cold sweat even appeared on his forehead.

He cautiously replied, "This morning, I ordered some refugees from outside the city to enter the city. I carefully screened them, and they should be refugees, so it should be fine."

Lin Fei remained noncommittal and continued to ask, "How many refugees are there?"

"Probably more than a thousand people, all in tattered clothes, and they are all people who have survived from nearby villages by chance. I couldn't bear it, so..."

"Now give the order to surround all those thousand or so people. If there are any suspicious movements, kill them without mercy!"

Lin Fei gave the order.

"Yes, Chief."

Mo Wen didn't dare to delay and immediately gave the order.

Lin Fei turned to the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect and said, "Let's go. If we're any later, what we see may only be a dead city."

Many disciples were slightly intimidated by Lin Fei's words and felt that he was exaggerating. However, Lin Fei was the Chief, and they had to follow his orders. So they followed Lin Fei and quickly headed to the refugee camp.

At this moment, inside the refugee camp, the people from the Nine Profound Sect were distributing porridge. Many refugees were looking forward to it and hoping to eat the porridge as soon as possible.

Suddenly, a dense sound of footsteps could be heard. Large groups of people from the Nine Profound Sect and Haizhou City surrounded the camp.

There were about twenty or so refugees in the camp, and their faces changed drastically when they saw this scene.

"This is bad, we've been discovered."

"What do we do now?"

"We've already entered the city. Let's break out while the encirclement hasn't formed yet."

"Break out and rush towards the city gate, preferably opening the city gate to release the signal for attacking the city. When our people arrive, Haizhou City will be ours!"

At once, these twenty or so refugees began to move.

"Swish, swish, swish."

All of them were agile and their haggard appearances seemed to be disguised using some kind of disguise technique. These people were all insiders of the pirates outside the city.

The insider pirates began to break out in various directions. The people of Haizhou City were not well prepared, and these pirates were powerful, with many of them being acquired martial artists.

It was not an easy task to stop them. There were even acquired sixth level experts among them! Fortunately, Lin Fei led the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect and arrived in time.

Upon seeing this, Lin Fei immediately ordered, "Kill!"

Immediately, twenty Inner Disciples of the Nine Profound Sect each displayed their martial arts and blocked the pirates.

Mo Wen also witnessed this scene, with cold sweat running down his forehead. He actually let the pirates into the city, almost causing harm to the entire city!

"Chief, I'm guilty..." Mo Wen knelt in front of Lin Fei with an ashamed face.

"Of course, you're guilty. But it's not too late to make up for it before a major disaster occurs. Go, we can't let a pirate escape!"

"Yes, Chief." Mo Wen gritted his teeth, holding the big saber in his hand and rushing towards the pirates.

However, Mo Wen seemed to have encountered a powerful pirate. The opponent's figure flickered like a ghost and instantly appeared in front of Mo Wen. Then, the pirate swung his short saber in his hand.

"Spurt!"

Mo Wen screamed in pain. His hand was cut off by the pirate's short saber. However, the pirate did not seem to want to kill Mo Wen. Instead, he charged directly towards Lin Fei's direction.

Now, there were people surrounding them everywhere. Only a few people were in Lin Fei's direction, which seemed to be a weak point.

The pirate was extremely fast. Almost in the blink of an eye, he was in front of Lin Fei.

"Be careful, Senior Brother Lin, this pirate is at the Acquired Sixth Level..." The Inner Disciples of the Nine Profound Sect loudly warned. However, the pirate was too fast. They didn't have time to intervene.

The sharp short saber of the pirate was already within reach. It seemed that in the next moment, it would cut Lin Fei's throat open.

"Clang."

A clear sound. The Star Saber behind Lin Fei instantly fell into his hand.

"Swoosh."

Lin Fei swung his saber.

Thirteen saber shadows covered the pirate like a sky-shrouding blanket. The sharp saber edge made the pirate's soul tremble.

"You..."

The pirate's eyes widened. He immediately placed his short saber horizontally in front of his chest.

"Boom."

A muffled sound. The pirate's short saber broke with a "click" sound. At the same time, the momentum of Lin Fei's Star saber did not diminish. The pirate's body was instantly cut in half by Lin Fei's Star Saber.

Suddenly, blood splattered.

An Acquired Sixth Level pirate couldn't even block one strike from Lin Fei.

Both the person and the saber were cut in half by a single saber strike!

79. The Pirate Conspiracy!

Lin Fei had an expressionless face. But the surrounding Nine Profound Sect disciples couldn't help but feel a tremor in their hearts!

Though the sect master had mentioned that Lin Fei had slain two martial artists at the acquired seventh level and they were not doubting their leader's words, they had never witnessed Lin Fei's prowess firsthand. In their hearts, there was still a trace of uncertainty.

Now, seeing Lin Fei eliminate an acquired sixth level pirate with a single saber stroke, their doubts vanished.

Lin Fei truly deserved the title of "Chief Disciple"!

Having drawn his saber, Lin Fei had no intention of sheathing it again.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei displayed his Leaping Technique, darting to another pirate's side in an instant. With a slash of his saber, thirteen shadows enveloped the pirate.

"Thud."

The pirate's head was severed by Lin Fei's saber and fell to the ground.

More than twenty pirates in total. Those who were difficult to subdue or couldn't be stopped temporarily, Lin Fei personally dealt with. The Leaping Technique was perfectly suited to this situation, like a fish in water.

"Your Leaping Technique has demonstrated its might, invigorating its spirit and increasing its cultivation progress by 50%."

"Your Leaping Technique has broken through to transcendence!"

The system's voice resounded in Lin Fei's mind. It was the sound of the Leaping Technique's cultivation progress.

"This Leaping Technique must be lively in nature. The more I utilize it, the faster its cultivation progress will be. Perhaps, this Leaping Technique could reach perfection!"

Thoughts flashed through Lin Fei's mind.

For Lin Fei, his lightness skill didn't need to be overly demanding; it merely needed to be sufficient.

For example, the Flowing Clothes Skill. It had always been at the transcendence level. Once it reached transcendence, there was no further progress.

However, Lin Fei wasn't concerned. The transcendence level was more than enough.

However, it seemed that the Leaping Technique was more than just transcendence. It could very likely reach perfection.

With the transcendence Leaping Technique, Lin Fei moved even faster.

In the blink of an eye, among the twenty-odd pirates, nearly ten were slain by Lin Fei. Another ten were killed by Nine Profound Sect disciples. Only two were captured alive.

This was Lin Fei's command. They needed to keep some alive for questioning.

"Kneel!"

The Nine Profound Sect disciples brought the captured pirates before Lin Fei. These two pirates were only at the acquired first or second level. With their hands broken, they couldn't resist.

"So, what was your plan?" Lin Fei asked.

"We intended to infiltrate the city, then seize the opportunity to open the gates and signal our man. At that time, our people would be lying in ambush outside the city. Once the signal was released, they would storm into the city, seize the gates, and wait for more of our forces to enter Haizhou City, eventually occupying it."

"Where did you come from?"

"We are pirates, all of whom have committed various crimes and fled to the sea, where we were taken in by our leader. Our lair is on an island. As for its name and how to get there, only a select few are told."

Lin Fei understood.

These pirates had a lair on an island overseas. But the nautical chart was in the hands of the pirate leader. Only the leader knew the exact route.

Lin Fei continued to ask, "Why not just be pirates at sea and plunder ships instead take the risk of coming ashore to raid villages and towns? Even more so, attempting to attack Haizhou City doesn't seem like your typical pirate behavior."

Lin Fei's gaze was sharp. He stared coldly at the two pirates. They hesitated for a moment.

Lin Fei calmly said, "Separate them, whoever speaks the truth first can live. If someone speaks too late, kill him!"

Hearing Lin Fei's words, the two pirates no longer dared to conceal anything. They hurriedly blurted out, "We'll tell you, we'll tell you."

"You're right, attacking villages and even Haizhou City would result in greater losses.

But it's our leader's command, and no dissent is allowed. Those who disobey are killed by the leader.

As for why our leader insists on attacking villages and even Haizhou City, we have no idea."

Lin Fei continued to interrogate them further and he found that these two truly didn't know why the pirates were attacking villages and Haizhou City.

It was too difficult for the pirates to attack Haizhou City. The losses would be too severe. What could have driven the pirates to attack Haizhou City at any cost?

"Mo Wen."

At this moment, Mo Wen had already treated his injuries. His arm had been severed. It was now useless.

"Your arm was lost in the line of duty. I will report to the Nine Profound Sect, so your merits and demerits can offset each other. However, you can no longer serve as the city lord of Haizhou City."

"Thank you, chief!"

Mo Wen clenched his teeth. He was somewhat unwilling. However, he knew his career was essentially over. Now he could only return home to retire. For him, this might not necessarily be a bad thing. Living in the martial world, one might lose their life someday.

"Find out the real purpose of those pirates as soon as possible. Especially the villages, we must find out what the pirates have done."

Lin Fei issued the command. So, the people of the Nine Profound Sect began to take action. They sealed off the gates of Haizhou City and secretly sent out spies to investigate the villages that had been raided by the pirates. Apart from that, Lin Fei just waited quietly in Haizhou City.

One day, two days, three days...

As time passed day by day, Lin Fei remained in Haizhou City. He showed no intention of leaving. The Sect Master's order was for Lin Fei to lead the Nine Profound Sect disciples to eradicate the pirates.

But Lin Fei hadn't even taken anyone out of the city. How could they accomplish the Nine Profound Sect's mission? For a moment, the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect had their doubts about Lin Fei's approach.

"Why hasn't the chief left the city for such a long time?"

"We have already investigated, and the pirates have been entrenched in Haiping Town."

"With our strength, even if we go out, we can eradicate those pirates."

"That's right, we have already obtained solid information. Among those pirates, there isn't even a single acquired seventh-level martial artist. The strongest are only at the acquired sixth level."

"I don't know what the chief is worried about?"

Facing the turmoil outside, Lin Fei still insisted on his own view. He never went out. Because the more information he received, the more uneasy Lin Fei felt.

This group of pirates acted very strangely. Raiding villages and towns was normal. However, kidnapping all the young boys and girls without killing them was very abnormal.

Ordinary pirates, even if they needed to replenish their forces, would only recruit strong, able-bodied people. At the very least, they would kidnap some women.

But what about young boys and girls?

They were just children. They would consume a lot of food every day. This was not beneficial to the pirates at all. But this was what the pirates did in every village they raided. There must be a reason that Lin Fei didn't know.

Lin Fei felt there was a problem.

However, he had to complete the mission assigned by the Sect Master.

What should he do?

Lin Fei could only resort to the most cautious approach. That was to wait! He needed time to slowly nurture his saber.

Once the saber was nurtured for a certain period, No matter what plots the pirates had, Lin Fei would have the confidence to face them.

80. Sudden Event! Qi Cultivator

Haiping Town was occupied by the pirates. The pirates didn't even leave, instead, they blatantly entrenched themselves in Haiping Town.

The leader of the pirates was known as the Sea Yama King. He was a notorious pirate who had been active in the overseas world for more than a decade.

At this moment, the Sea Yama King was standing respectfully in a room. Inside the room sat a mysterious man in black. The face of the mysterious man in black was unclear, but the veins on the back of his exposed hands were blue-black, looking hideous and terrifying, unlike ordinary people.

"Master, there are no signs of the Nine Profound Sect disciples from Haizhou City coming out. The disciple leading them is said to be an acquired third-level disciple named Lin Fei. But he can easily kill acquired sixth-level martial artists, he must be a top genius of the Nine Profound Sect.

Master, if they continue to stay in Haizhou City and don't come out, what should we do?"

The Sea Yama King seemed to be very afraid of this man in black.

"If they don't come out, continue to raid the surrounding villages and towns. Do not worry about the losses. As long as we gather enough Yin Blood, any losses are worth it.

Moreover, Haizhou City has rich maritime trade benefits and is one of the important sources of wealth for the Nine Profound Sect. Now that we continue to raid, the sea merchants dare not go to sea.

We can afford to wait, but the Nine Profound Sect can't. They will definitely leave the city. Once they come to Haiping Town, we will annihilate them. At that time, attacking Haizhou City will be as easy as turning our hands."

The mysterious man in black's voice was old and hoarse.

"Master, I understand."

The Sea Yama King respectfully retreated.

......

Time hurriedly passed.

For a full two months, Lin Fei had been staying in Haizhou City. The Nine Profound Sect disciples who had come to Haizhou City with Lin Fei were already somewhat dissatisfied. However, they dared not say anything. After all, the sect rules were strict.

Lin Fei was the chief disciple. Whatever they should do was up to Lin Fei. But dissatisfaction was not only felt by the Nine Profound Sect disciples.

The sea merchants were also unhappy. For two whole months, not a single ship had set sail. The losses were enormous and hard to estimate. Some people even secretly contacted the Nine Profound Sect, hoping that the Nine Profound Sect could put some pressure on Lin Fei to make him deal with the pirates in Haiping Town.

At this moment, in Lin Fei's room.

"Swish."

Lin Fei opened his eyes.

"It's almost time. Nurturing the saber for two months is equivalent to nurturing it for more than three months previously!"

Lin Fei murmured softly. A glint flashed in his eyes. After all, Lin Fei's Saber-drawing Technique had now reached transcendence. Previously, Lin Fei's Saber-drawing Technique was only at the mastery level. The effect of nurturing the saber was naturally much better than before.

"System."

Lin Fei called up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Fifth Level

Three Vitality Technique: Fifth Level (22% Progress)

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist: Perfection (11% Progress)

Triple Wave Technique: Transcendence (12% Progress)

Leaping Technique: Transcendence (65% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection (43% Progress)

Saber-drawing Technique: Transcendence (75% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence ( 0% Progress)

In these two months, Lin Fei had not only been nurturing his saber. His Three Vitality Technique had also reached the fifth level.

Lin Fei was now a genuinely acquired fifth-level martial artist, with incredibly profound inner power. His inner power was even comparable to that of acquired eighth-level or ninth-level martial artists.

Lin Fei thought his inner power might be deeper than that of an average acquired ninth-level martial artist. If combined with his Saber-drawing Technique, the extent of Lin Fei's strength was unclear even to himself.

With a significant increase in strength, Lin Fei felt more confident. No matter what schemes the pirates had, Lin Fei was not afraid.

"Someone, summon the Nine Profound Sect disciples."

Lin Fei got up and went to the entrance of the Nine Profound Sect Branch. Soon, a large number of martial artists gathered at the entrance of the Nine Profound Sect Branch. In addition to the Nine Profound Sect disciples, there were many people who originally belonged to the branch. These were the forces that the Nine Profound Sect could mobilize. There were as many as two or three thousand martial artists!

Of course, the most important ones were the twenty inner disciples that Lin Fei had brought from the Nine Profound Sect to Haizhou City. Each of them was very strong and could fight ten or even a hundred enemies.

"Greetings to Senior Brother Lin."

"Greetings to the chief."

Everyone bowed when they saw Lin Fei.

Lin Fei glanced over and slowly said, "You've been holding these two months. But today, you'll get to kill to your heart's content! No matter what schemes the pirates have, just kill them. All listen to my command, attack Haiping Town. If the pirates do not surrender, kill them without mercy! Let's go!"

With a wave of Lin Fei's hand, the martial artists of the Nine Profound Sect immediately left Haizhou City in a mighty force, heading towards Haiping Town.

Haiping Town was not far from Haizhou City. It took about an hour to get there. When Lin Fei and the others arrived, they found that the pirates in Haiping Town had already prepared for the battle. This was also quite normal.

"Kill!"

Lin Fei didn't need any formation. After all, martial artists were different from armies. Martial artists had outstanding individual strengths. Having martial artists form a formation would actually restrict their performance.

"Whoosh, whoosh, whoosh."

One by one, the martial artists displayed their movement techniques and quickly rushed into Haiping Town. The pirates couldn't stop them at all. In terms of sheer strength, the pirates were still much weaker.

Lin Fei didn't even need to take action. He waited until everyone had entered Haiping Town before stepping in. In the town, bodies were everywhere. There were people from the Nine Profound Sect Branch, but there were more pirates.

"Are these pirates so weak? How could such weak pirates dare to occupy Haiping Town and even try to attack Haizhou City?"

Lin Fei found it very strange. He became even more cautious in his heart.

"Senior Brother Lin, the pirates have been surrounded in a manor. The manor is said to house the pirate leaders. Pirate leader Sea Yama King is also hiding inside."

A Nine Profound Sect disciple came to Lin Fei and reported.

"Let's go have a look."

Lin Fei's figure flickered and quickly went to the manor. Outside the manor, many Nine Profound Sect disciples had surrounded the entire place. They initially tried to attack, but they encountered strong resistance and suffered heavy losses. So, they waited for Lin Fei to make a decision.

Lin Fei carefully observed the manor. Shadows were moving inside. Obviously, there were many pirates in the manor. They should be the main force of the pirates. The ones killed in the town earlier were just cannon fodder. The enemy had retreated to the manor.

Were they preparing to use the manor as a defensive position? Or did they think there was something advantageous in the manor that could be used to resist the attack of the Nine Profound Sect disciples?

...

Lin Fei couldn't see anything strange about the manor. However, at this point, even though he had a faint feeling of unease, he didn't have time to worry about it.

"Charge in and kill everyone inside!"

Lin Fei finally gave the order.

"Kill!"

Immediately, the Nine Profound Sect disciples outside the manor charged into the manor. Lin Fei's figure also flickered. He used the Leaping Technique, instantly traversing dozens of meters, and entered the manor. Inside the manor, there were indeed many pirates and their strength was very formidable.

"Swish, swish, swish."

Lin Fei displayed the Leaping Technique. He was like a fish in water. Every time his saber slashed a pirate's head was sure to fall. Gradually, the entire manor's ground was stained red with blood. The air was filled with a strong smell of blood. Nobody noticed the sky above the manor seemed to gradually darken. Moreover, the blood on the ground seemed to flow slowly in a specific pattern.

"What's this...?"

Lin Fei was the first to notice something was wrong. Everyone in the manor seemed to have become bloodthirsty, even Lin Fei.

Deep inside, he felt agitated. He wanted to kill. This situation was obviously not right!

"Something's wrong, retreat!"

Lin Fei immediately issued the order. He used the Leaping Technique, trying to leave the manor.

"Buzz."

However, it was already too late. The next moment, the entire manor was enveloped in a layer of blood. It seemed as if an invisible wall had trapped Lin Fei and the others within the estate.

"Formation, there's a Qi cultivator!"

Lin Fei's eyes narrowed slightly. He immediately recognized that this was a formation that could only be set up by a Qi cultivator.

81. Drawing the Saber to Slay the Immortal Master!

"Nine Shadow Saber Technique!"

Lin Fei unleashed the Thirteen Shadows with a single saber strike. With a fierce slash, it met the invisible wall of air.

It did not work at all.

Lin Fei immediately understood that the large formation had been set up, and it would be difficult to break through it with the power of an ordinary martial artist.

"Senior Brother Lin, what's going on?"

"Chief, what should we do?"

"How did we get trapped here?"

For a moment, many people were panic-stricken and didn't know what to do.

"Everyone, gather around me and don't act recklessly. This is a formation set up by a Qi cultivator." Lin Fei shouted loudly.

"Qi cultivator?"

"An immortal master, Qi cultivator is the immortal master."

"Could it be that there's an immortal master among these pirates?"

"It's said that immortal masters have mysterious and unpredictable means, and ordinary martial artists are no match for them."

"Only innate experts can contend with immortal masters."

"How did we come across an immortal master?"

Lin Fei's words stirred the crowd once again.

Immortal Master! This name was lofty and unreachable to ordinary people. The title "Immortal Master" often represents mystery, power, and invincibility. How could ordinary martial artists contend with an immortal master?

At this moment, a group of pirates emerged from the manor.

A mysterious man in a black robe, along with the Sea Yama King and others, appeared not far from Lin Fei and the others. The Sea Yama King saw Lin Fei and the others trapped and a hint of excitement appeared on his face.

"Master, your Blood Refining Formation is indeed powerful, trapping these Nine Profound Sect members in an instant."

The mysterious man in the black robe removed his cloak, revealing a slightly aged face. There were no fluctuations of inner power on his body.

However, Lin Fei could see that there were fluctuations of spiritual power on the mysterious man in the black robe.

It was similar to Lin Miao's spiritual power fluctuations. Only, it was much more profound than Lin Miao's spiritual power and far beyond what Lin Miao could compare to.

The mysterious man in the black robe was indeed a Qi cultivator!

"Master, there are some powerful individuals among these Nine Profound Sect martial artists. Will your Blood Refining Formation be broken by them, allowing them to escape?" The Sea Yama King asked with some concern.

"Break the Blood Refining Formation?"

The mysterious man in the black robe sneered, "How can mere mortals understand the wonders of formations? You martial artists, no matter how strong, are still flesh and blood, mere mortals."

Once the Blood Refining Formation is set up, only innate martial artists may have a chance to break it. As for acquired martial artists? They can only become the nourishment for the Blood Refining Formation, enhancing its power!

After we deal with these Nine Profound Sect members, we'll attack Haizhou City and refine the entire city with blood. Hehe, by then, I'll definitely be able to refine the Yin Blood Pill!"

The mysterious man in the black robe had a hint of fervor in his eyes. Everything he did was for the Yin Blood Pill!

The moment the mysterious man in the black robe appeared, Lin Fei's body was tense.

Dangerous!

Qi cultivators were very dangerous!

Lin Fei had dealt with Qi cultivators before. Even Lin Miao was a Qi cultivator. Although he hadn't even reached the Qi Condensation first level, his various methods were extraordinary and magical. A slight carelessness could lead to danger.

Therefore, Lin Fei knew that when facing a Qi cultivator, there must be no hesitation.

Spare no expense. Strike to kill with one blow! Only in this way could there be a glimmer of hope for survival!

The moment the black-robed Qi cultivator appeared, Lin Fei was already preparing. He was looking for an opportunity.

Listening to the black-robed Qi cultivator speaking confidently seemed to be the most relaxed moment.

At this moment, Lin Fei made his move!

"Whoosh."

The transcendent Leaping Technique allowed Lin Fei to leap out, almost like a faint shadow.

As Lin Fei executed the Leaping Technique, his right hand was already gripping the Hidden Saber at his waist.

"Shoo."

Lin Fei shot out like an arrow released from its string.

The entire manor seemed to quiet down all at once.

In everyone's sight, there was only a faint glimpse of light.

A white light!

Only the mysterious man in the black robe, with eyes filled with spiritual power, could see.

There was a saber in Lin Fei's hand!

Saber-drawing Technique!

Nurturing the saber for two months was comparable to nurturing it for more than three months before.

Moreover, Lin Fei was now at acquired fifth level, not the third. This saber strike was earth-shattering! Even the acquired ninth or tenth level martial artist would likely be unable to withstand this slash.

This saber strike was comparable to the pinnacle of the acquired realm!

"Slash!"

As Lin Fei's word fell, it was like a startling thunderclap, his saber had already reached the mysterious man in the black robe.

With such a swift speed, no one could intercept it.

"How could this be? How could a mere mortal, a fleshly body, possess such a terrifying strike?"

The mysterious man widened his eyes. He had just been talking confidently, treating acquired martial artists as if they were nothing. But now, his entire body was ice-cold. He could feel the threat of death.

At this moment, he might have recalled that martial artists were fleshly bodies and mere mortals. And he, as a Qi cultivator, was no different from them.

The mysterious man's robe drew out a talisman from his hand.

"Snap."

The talisman instantly released a green light, enveloping the mysterious man in the black robe.

Lin Fei's saber finally fell.

"Pfff."

The green light only managed to slightly slow down Lin Fei's saber. Then, just like cutting through tofu. It easily sliced through the green light.

The green light vanished in an instant. And the mysterious man in the black robe could only watch helplessly as Lin Fei's sharp saber fell, cleaving him from head to toe.

Splitting him directly in half with one strike!

"Thud."

The two halves of the mysterious man in the black robe fell to the ground. Lin Fei stood in front of his body.

The pirates around him, including Sea Yama King dared not move a muscle as if they couldn't believe the scene before their eyes.

How could the confident and eloquent Immortal Master be dead? Moreover, his death was extremely tragic. Cut in half by Lin Fei's single saber strike!

"How could the Master, an Immortal Master, be dead?" Sea Yama King's face turned pale, and his body trembled.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei had no intention of sparing Sea Yama King. He slashed with his saber. Thirteen saber shadows emerged.

Sea Yama King, merely an acquired sixth level martial artist, was no match for Lin Fei's saber. As a result, with one strike, his head rolled to the ground.

"Spare us."

"Hero, please have mercy."

"We were all coerced by Sea Yama King, we surrender."

"Please, don't kill me..."

Seeing this scene, the sea bandits broke down. The Immortal Master and Sea Yama King were both dead. How could they dare to resist?

They all dropped their weapons and knelt on the ground. The inner disciples of the Nine Profound Sect also came to Lin Fei's side.

They looked at the Immortal Master who had been split in half on the ground. And then they looked at Lin Fei. Even at this moment, they seemed unable to believe it.

"...Senior Brother Lin, is this Immortal Master really dead?"

Even the acquired sixth level inner disciple of the Nine Profound Sect seemed to doubt it.

Immortal Masters were held in high regard in the hearts of martial artists. Who would dare to fight against an Immortal Master? That would be considered insane.

Yet now, they had witnessed Lin Fei unleashing an earth-shattering slash and even killing an Immortal Master with a single strike!

"What the Immortal Master? Using blood refinement techniques killed countless people. He was nothing but a devil. Moreover, Qi cultivators are also made of flesh and blood. Once killed, how could they come back to life?"

Lin Fei shook his head.

It seemed that these people had not seen Qi cultivators before. Over time, they had even deified them.

Lin Fei had not only seen Qi Condensation cultivators but had even killed one before. Furthermore, a Qi cultivator had become his subordinate. Controlled by him, serving as an alchemy tool.

Qi cultivators were human too! His saber could kill not only martial artists but also Immortal Masters!

82. The Showdown Of Two Perfection Level Martial Arts

With the death of the mysterious man in the black robe, the Blood Refining Formation naturally collapsed without the guidance of a Qi cultivator.

Lin Fei searched the mysterious man's body. He found some porcelain bottles and a secret manual. It turned out to be a Qi Condensation cultivation technique. Called the Yin Blood Sutra.

This Yin Blood Sutra seemed to be incomplete. It could only be practiced up to the fourth level of Qi Condensation.

Lin Fei took a look. The Yin Blood Sutra was indeed cruel and evil. The cultivation method required the use of Yin blood.

What was Yin blood?

It was actually the blood taken from a person's heart, killed during the Yin hours, and used for cultivation. The cultivation speed would be incredibly fast with it.

If one wanted to break through a bottleneck, they could even use the Blood Refining Formation to refine the Yin Blood Pill.

Consuming the Yin Blood Pill, one had a high probability of breaking through the bottleneck. If it didn't work, they could take a second Yin Blood Pill.

According to the information Lin Fei obtained from interrogating some pirates about this mysterious man in the black robe, he was preparing to refine the Yin Blood Pill.

He was likely planning to use it to break through to the fourth level of Qi Condensation. That was why he took the risk, leading the pirates ashore, plundering villages and towns.

He even planned to attack Haizhou City, using the blood of the people of Haizhou City to refine the pill.

The Yin Blood Sutra, even among Qi cultivators, was considered an extremely devilish technique. Cultivating people as nourishment was intolerable to the world. No wonder the mysterious man in the black robe chose to become a pirate.

Only as a pirate, drifting at sea, could he stay away from martial artists and Qi cultivators. And avoid being pursued and killed by other Qi cultivators or powerful martial artists.

"The Yin Blood Sutra is harmful and must be burned!"

Without any hesitation, Lin Fei burned the Yin Blood Sutra in front of everyone. So that no one would covet it.

A few hours had passed since the end of the battle, the interrogation was almost over. Lin Fei obtained a lot of information about the pirates. For example, the pirates' base.

Lin Fei found a sea chart on Sea Yama King's body. The specific location of the island was marked on it.

"Eliminate evil completely! There are still remnants of the pirates on the island. If we don't eradicate them this time, they might regroup after a while and pose a threat to Haizhou City. So, I plan to lead a team to sea and level the pirates' lair!"

Thus, Lin Fei led everyone back to Haizhou City. The Nine Profound Sect began to recruit some sea merchants' ships. In just a few days, they gathered more than a dozen large ships.

Lin Fei no longer hesitated and immediately led the fleet of over a dozen ships, leaving Haizhou City and heading out to sea.

In the vast ocean, a dozen large ships seemed very insignificant. Lin Fei stood on the deck, gazing at the boundless sea. He couldn't help but feel his own insignificance.

In the face of nature's power, Martial artists and Qi cultivators alike were insignificant.

Lin Fei recalled the situation when he killed the mysterious man in the black robe.

The man was too confident.

Although the man in the black robe was only at the Qi Condensation third level, Qi cultivators were different from martial artists. They had various means at their disposal.

Their strength depended more on spells, magical tools, talismans, formations, and so on. The difference in realms was just a matter of the amount of spiritual power.

If the man in the black robe had magical tools or powerful spells, killing a peak Acquired martial artist would be nothing.

There was once a Qi Condensation third level cultivator, with just a talisman, he killed a twelfth-level Acquired martial artist! That was a true Acquired peak martial artist. Only one step away from Innate.

That was why people were so in awe of cultivators. Even martial artists couldn't help but feel inferior when facing a cultivator. This was also the reason why many Acquired martial artists didn't dare to take action when encountering cultivators.

However, Lin Fei didn't have that much reverence. But this encounter made Lin Fei more determined that if he were to face a Qi cultivator, he must strike first and gain the upper hand.

Once he made a move, he had to kill the opponent with an overwhelming force. Otherwise, martial artists would be at a disadvantage when facing Qi cultivators.

In that manor, if the black-robed cultivator hadn't been so confident, he could have hidden in some corner of the manor, manipulating the Blood Refining Formation, slowly trapping Lin Fei and the others to death.

Given enough time, the Blood Refining Formation could erode everyone's minds and eventually drive them to madness and then death.

But the black-robed man was too confident. He didn't even take Acquired martial artists seriously. He thought that once they entered the Blood Refining Formation, Lin Fei and the others would be like meat on his chopping block, ready for him to slaughter.

As a result, he was killed by Lin Fei's Saber-drawing Technique in one strike.

However, although Lin Fei won, his victory was actually quite lucky.

"The means of Acquired martial artists are too limited. When facing Qi cultivators, we are naturally at a disadvantage. However, if I can comprehend the saber intent, with the invisible and formless saber intent attack, I won't be without countermeasures even when facing Qi cultivators."

Lin Fei wanted to comprehend the saber intent as soon as possible. However, he hadn't made any progress with it recently.

Lin Fei was helpless. He could only wait patiently.

...

The weather at sea was the most unpredictable. One moment it was clear skies, and suddenly, dark clouds filled the sky.

"Boom."

Huge waves surged. The waves in the sea constantly slapped against the large ships. People on the ship staggered from side to side.

If not careful, they could be thrown into the sea. Fortunately, the large ships were controlled by experienced sailors. Although the waves were huge, the ships were not in danger of capsizing.

Lin Fei stood on the deck, watching the huge waves that followed one after another.

Suddenly, a voice from the system sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

"Your Triple Wave Technique has witnessed the mighty power of the ocean waves and comprehended the secrets of the layered waves."

"Your Triple Wave Technique has now reached perfection!"

Suddenly, a memory emerged in Lin Fei's mind. It was as if he had instantly comprehended the secrets of great waves. One wave after another, just like the layering method of the Triple Wave Technique.

At this moment, the Triple Wave Technique had reached perfection! Lin Fei couldn't have imagined that the Triple Wave Technique, which he seldom used, would reach perfection even before his Saber-drawing Technique.

And Lin Fei immediately thought of the possibility that when similar types of martial arts reached perfection, they could be merged.

Lin Fei's Triple Wave Technique and Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had both reached the realm of perfection.

Once merged, which fist technique would be dominant? Or would both be present?

Lin Fei didn't dwell on his doubts for too long. Soon, he felt an unusual sensation in his body. He immediately returned to his cabin and sat cross-legged.

At this moment, there were rumbling sounds coming from within Lin Fei's body. Moreover, it seemed as if a series of images suddenly appeared in his mind.

Lin Fei seemed to "see" two balls of light constantly colliding in his mind. Gradually, the lights took on human forms.

A golden light slowly transformed into a giant with a dragon head and an elephant body. Another blue light resembled the ocean, with faint sounds of waves echoing within.

Clearly, the golden light represented the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist, while the blue light represented the Triple Wave Technique.

Now, these two perfection-level martial arts were about to determine their fate within Lin Fei's body.

83. Quadruple Wave Technique

"How amazing..."

Lin Fei found it quite novel as well. He had never encountered such a situation before.

For example, when the Nine Shadow Saber Technique absorbed and merged with other saber techniques, the system would directly notify him of the results.

But now, it was a first with the fist techniques so vividly appearing in his mind to compete!

Lin Fei believed that it was because the two fist techniques were evenly matched and quite similar, which led to this situation.

Regardless, the two martial arts within Lin Fei's body were now engaged in a fierce battle.

It was a rare opportunity for Lin Fei to witness this as an onlooker, quietly watching the two perfected fist techniques competing against each other!

The golden giant formed by the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist took the initiative to strike first. There seemed to be a faint dragon and elephant roaring in the air.

"Boom."

The golden giant launched a punch, causing the air to vibrate. This was the unique "shock power" of the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist, extremely firm and Yang in nature, full of explosive force.

The blue Triple Wave Technique also charged forward. However, it transformed into the shape of waves. A massive wave surged toward the golden giant with great force.

"Bang."

The two sides clashed forcefully.

The Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was not only perfect but also integrated with many basic fist techniques. With an 11% training progress in the realm of perfection, it was incredibly powerful! As a result, the explosive power of this punch managed to disperse the Triple Wave Technique.

However, this was only the first layer of the waves. It was merely Lin Fei's original strength. The next moment, the Triple Wave Technique launched another wave of water. This was the second layer of waves. Its power was twice as strong as the first layer!

"Bang."

In this clash, the Triple Wave Technique remained unshaken, and the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was equally stable. Both sides were evenly matched.

Immediately after, the Triple Wave Technique unleashed another wave. This was the third layer of the Triple Wave Technique. Its power had doubled again based on the second layer.

Lin Fei already knew the outcome at this point. The winner was clear!

"Boom."

As expected, with this collision, the golden giant formed by the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist seemed to roar angrily. It couldn't withstand the fourfold power of the Triple Wave Technique. It was shattered by the enormous wave.

The golden giant turned into strands of golden light, gradually merging into the blue light of the Triple Wave Technique.

"Your Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist and Triple Wave Technique engaged in an intense battle."

"Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist was defeated by Triple Wave Technique and willingly merged into it."

"Your Triple Wave Technique has mastered the skill of Shock Power."

"Your Triple Wave Technique's cultivation progress has increased by 50%."

"During the comprehension of the Triple Wave Technique, you unexpectedly derived a fourth move, and the technique was renamed Quadruple Wave Technique."

"The fourth move of the Quadruple Wave Technique has double the power of the third move."

In Lin Fei's mind, the system's voices echoed one after another. After a while, when the system's voice ceased, Lin Fei seemed to come back to his senses. Sorting out the system's information just now, he couldn't help but widen his eyes.

"Triple Wave Technique has become Quadruple Wave Technique? Derived the fourth move during comprehension? Triple Wave Technique merged with Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist, and the cultivation progress increased so significantly?"

Lin Fei was somewhat bewildered. So, he immediately accessed the system panel to check his current martial arts status.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Fifth Level

Three Vitality Technique: Fifth Level (28% Progress)

Quadruple Wave Technique: Perfection (50% Progress)

Leaping Technique: Transcendence (68% Progress)

Nine Shadow Saber Technique: Perfection ( 43% Progress)

Saber-drawing Technique: Transcendence (78% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Indeed, on the system panel, Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist had disappeared. Even Triple Wave Technique had vanished. Instead, it was replaced by Quadruple Wave Technique!

Of course, martial arts only disappeared from the system panel. It didn't mean that Lin Fei couldn't use these martial arts. Lin Fei could still use Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist or Triple Wave Technique. It's just that the two martial arts had merged into a more powerful one.

Moreover, the Quadruple Wave Technique had not only reached perfection, but its cultivation progress had also reached 50%.

"If I merge another martial art technique of the same level as the Triple Wave Technique, can the cultivation progress reach 100%, thus comprehending the fist intent?"

Lin Fei's heart was moved by this thought. It seemed like a method worth trying. However, he couldn't hold too high hopes for it. After all, Lin Fei's Triple Wave Technique reached perfection this time purely due to a combination of luck and coincidence.

It had witnessed the waves in the ocean, which allowed it to achieve perfection, only then could it merge with the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist.

Now that the Triple Wave Technique had transformed into the Quadruple Wave Technique, its power had increased significantly. The fourth move of the Quadruple Wave Technique was twice as powerful as the third move, which was almost eight times the original power!

How terrifying was this power? Even someone with innate divine strength couldn't compare to Lin Fei.

Lin Fei's Quadruple Wave Technique was now even comparable to a Saber-drawing Technique that had been nurtured for two months.

"If the Saber-drawing Technique could reach perfection and then merge with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, I wonder if saber intent could be born?"

Lin Fei's heart was filled with a hint of expectation.

The storm at sea continued for several hours. By the next day, the sea was calm again.

"Senior Brother Lin, we have found the lair of the pirates." A disciple from the Nine Profound Sect came to report outside the cabin.

"Found it?"

Lin Fei opened the cabin door and came to the deck. Sure enough, as he looked into the distance, he saw an island far away. Soon, the ship slowly approached the island. Everyone disembarked one after another.

There were many signs of human activity on the island. It didn't take much effort for the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect to find the pirates.

Once they confirmed that they were pirates, Lin Fei ordered to kill them all. However, there were still many innocent people on the island. Most of them were women who had been kidnapped by the pirates and forced to serve them on the island.

Lin Fei felt pity for these women. So, he ordered his men to bring the women along. He also ordered them to find the pirates' hidden treasures and bring them onto the ship.

Afterward, Lin Fei gave the order. The entire island was burned to the ground with a raging fire. The fleet soon returned to Haizhou City.

The pirates were completely wiped out. The merchants could once again set sail and resume their maritime trade. Haizhou City returned to its former prosperity.

Lin Fei had completed his mission in Haizhou City. He did not linger in the city's prosperity. He directly took the Nine Profound Sect disciples and returned to the Nine Profound Sect.

In the main hall of the Nine Profound Sect, the Sect Master summoned Lin Fei for a private meeting.

"Lin Fei, you've done an excellent job in this mission, eliminating the pirates in Haizhou City and ensuring the interests of our Nine Profound Sect.

As for the matter of the mysterious Qi cultivator, I've issued a gag order forbidding the Nine Profound Sect disciples from spreading the news.

I didn't expect that an evil cultivator among the Qi cultivators would become a pirate and even attempt to blood-refine Haizhou City. He truly deserved to die!"

The Sect Master's voice was filled with murderous intent. The actions of the black-robed Qi cultivator had enraged both humans and heaven alike. Naturally, he would be furious as well.

"Sect Master, if I hadn't been able to kill that Qi cultivator, how would the Nine Profound Sect have dealt with it?" Lin Fei asked.

"Lin Fei, you are different from ordinary martial artists. Ordinary martial artists would feel intimidated when facing a Qi cultivator and be afraid to fight.

However, you were able to fight back and kill the Qi cultivator in a desperate situation. Ordinary martial artists wouldn't be able to do that. Basically, acquired martial artists would be easily crushed by a Qi cultivator.

If you had failed this time, I would have personally requested several Grand Elders to descend the mountain and ensure the elimination of that evil Qi cultivator.

Although cultivators are powerful and their methods are unpredictable, innate experts can still contend with them, and even kill them."

Lin Fei understood.

Even without him, the Nine Profound Sect would have sent innate experts to descend the mountain and kill that Qi cultivator.

"Alright, since you have encountered a Qi Condensation cultivator, you must naturally be aware of their formidable power. Even though you killed him, it was because he was careless.

If your Saber-drawing Technique had not been effective, you would have likely faced a disastrous outcome. Only those who have reached the innate realm can contend with Qi cultivators!

Therefore, you must continue to practice martial arts diligently and strive to achieve the innate realm as soon as possible."

The Sect Master's words made sense.

Lin Fei nodded and said, "Disciple understands."

84. Saber-drawing Technique Has Broken Through To Perfection

"Only Innate can contend with Qi cultivators!"

Lin Fei returned to his courtyard. This was what he learned from the Sect Master's words.

Qi cultivators were superior. Only innate martial artists could generally fight against them.

As for the old Daoist, Lin Miao, and even the black-robed Qi cultivator that Lin Fei encountered, they were all rogue cultivators. And they were very low-level rogue cultivators.

According to the Sect Master, orthodox Qi cultivators were the strongest! They had complete Qi techniques, magical artifacts, talismans, and formations. Only such Qi cultivators could be considered true Qi cultivators.

And when facing such orthodox Qi cultivators, acquired martial artists would have no chance. As for rogue Qi cultivators, if luck was on their side, even ordinary people could kill them. They were not worth mentioning at all.

Lin Fei didn't become complacent. Although he had already killed two Qi cultivators, Lin Fei knew very well that if he faced the orthodox Qi cultivators mentioned by the Sect Master, who had spells, magical artifacts, talismans, and so on, he would have no chance.

Days passed by, and in the blink of an eye, a month had passed.

Lin Fei's life in the Nine Profound Sect returned to its former tranquility. During this month, Lin Fei's Three Vitality Technique progressed slowly. Every day, it only increased its cultivation progress by 1%. There was still some distance from reaching the sixth level.

"Your Leaping Technique has reached perfection after days of diligent cultivation,"

The system's voice echoed in Lin Fei's mind.

"Leaping Technique has reached perfection?"

Lin Fei was somewhat surprised. This month, he had been focusing on the Saber-drawing Technique. He didn't pay much attention to his agility skills. However, unexpectedly, the Leaping Technique reached perfection. This was a pleasant surprise.

Nevertheless, the difference between the transcendence and perfection of the Leaping Technique was not too significant. At most, it was just a slightly faster speed.

Lin Fei's main focus was still on the Saber-drawing Technique. Because, after a month of hard work in cultivating the Saber-drawing Technique, it had reached 99%. Progress was extremely slow.

If it was only the Saber-drawing Technique reaching perfection, Lin Fei might not have paid much attention to it. Once the Saber-drawing Technique reached perfection, its power would be impressive, and the efficiency of nurturing the saber would also be enhanced. However, it wasn't worth Lin Fei's undivided attention.

The significance of the Saber-drawing Technique reaching perfection was its fusion with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. And the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had long since reached perfection.

Moreover, the cultivation progress of the perfected Nine Shadow Saber Technique had reached 43%.

Lin Fei was looking forward to the fusion of the perfected Saber-drawing Technique and the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. Then, it might be possible to give birth to the saber intent!

Saber intent was the focus of Lin Fei's attention.

It is rumored that once a martial artist masters saber intent, they can be on par with Qi cultivators! Even more, when facing Qi cultivators, only those who have mastered saber intent can have a way to cope with them.

This saber intent was very important. Lin Fei had been looking forward to it for a long time. At this moment, the cultivation progress of the Saber-drawing Technique had reached 99%.

Lin Fei was quietly waiting in the courtyard. The breakthrough of the Saber-drawing Technique might happen within these few days. It could reach perfection at any moment.

Lin Fei didn't know how much time had passed. He felt that the Hidden Saber at his waist seemed to be vibrating.

"What is this..."

Lin Fei could clearly sense that his inner power was circulating wildly, entering the Hidden Saber in a special way, and then returning to his body from within the Hidden Saber.

With each round, the Hidden Saber accumulated terrifying power. This was the process of nurturing the saber. Moreover, Lin Fei had never felt the operation of the saber-nurturing as clearly as at this moment.

"Your Saber-drawing Technique has finally broken through to perfection after days of hard cultivation!"

"Boom."

As the system's voice echoed in Lin Fei's mind, a loud noise resounded in his head, followed by a segment of memory. A memory related to the "Saber-drawing Technique."

Perfection!

At this moment, Lin Fei's Saber-drawing Technique had finally reached perfection! The perfection realm of the Saber-drawing Technique also meant the perfection realm of the Saber-nurturing Technique!

At this moment, Lin Fei could clearly feel that the speed of nurturing the saber had increased by at least ten times!

Yes, ten times!

Endless inner power was pouring crazily into the Hidden Saber. If it weren't for Lin Fei's immense inner power, he might not have been able to sustain it.

At this rate, nurturing the saber for one day now was equivalent to ten days before. Nurturing the saber for a month was equivalent to nearly a year before!

This was too terrifying. Even Lin Fei himself felt it was too terrifying.

He never expected that the improvement of the Saber-drawing Technique upon reaching perfection would be so significant.

Lin Fei even vaguely felt that the Saber-drawing Technique should not be an acquired level martial skill. It could even be on par with innate martial skills!

Lin Fei didn't know how strong innate experts were, but he was certain that given a few months or a year to nurture his saber, the moment the saber was drawn, it would definitely slay an innate expert!

This was Lin Fei's confidence, or rather, his confidence in the perfection realm of the Saber-drawing Technique.

However, Lin Fei did not get up. He continued to wait quietly. The perfection of the Saber-drawing Technique was just the beginning.

What Lin Fei was really looking forward to was the fusion of the Saber-drawing Technique and the Nine Shadow Saber Technique! That was the true goal he had been waiting for all these days.

"Whoosh."

Sure enough, it didn't take long before a roar resounded in Lin Fei's mind. Following that, Lin Fei "saw" two balls of light appear in his mind.

Both balls of light were sabers. The two sabers were black and looked somewhat similar, but in reality, they were quite different.

Lin Fei could tell at a glance which one represented the Saber-drawing Technique and which one represented the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. After all, Lin Fei was very familiar with these two saber techniques.

Lin Fei was actually quite interested in the battle between the Nine Shadow Saber Technique and the Saber-drawing Technique. These were two completely different saber techniques.

The Saber-drawing Technique focused on killing with a single strike. No matter who the opponent was, it only took one saber! If it couldn't kill the enemy, then the master would die. It was an extremely extreme saber technique.

As for the Nine Shadow Saber Technique? It was a more common saber technique.

Normally, the Saber-drawing Technique would definitely be stronger. But the Nine Shadow Saber Technique was no longer the same as before. Now, the Nine Shadow Saber Technique was a single strike with thirteen shadows, not to be underestimated.

"Swish."

Both the Saber-drawing Technique and the Nine Shadow Saber Technique moved.

The two saber techniques were like two peerless saber masters.

At this moment, without a word, the two balls of light released their sharp saber edges and instantly flew toward each other.

The Nine Shadow Saber Technique had one saber with thirteen shadows, filling the sky with saber shadows.

The Saber-drawing Technique slashed out with one earth-shattering strike, leaving only that one saber between heaven and earth!

"Boom."

The two saber techniques collided fiercely. It was a head-on confrontation. Lin Fei's mind seemed to be shaking violently. The terrifying saber edge seemed to tear Lin Fei's mind apart.

"Crack."

In the end, the two saber techniques had their strengths and weaknesses.

When the Saber-drawing Technique and the Nine Shadow Saber Technique collided, the earth-shattering Saber-drawing Technique was clearly superior.

With just one slash, the huge black saber formed by the Nine Shadow Saber Technique instantly shattered into countless fragments.

The black light dots quickly flowed into the light of the Saber-drawing Technique.

"It's done, the Saber-drawing Technique still has the upper hand!"

Lin Fei knew that the outcome had been decided and the winner determined.

The Saber-drawing Technique won!

Suddenly, the light of the Saber-drawing Technique surged and even trembled faintly, as if it was about to explode at any moment.

This was something that hadn't happened when Lin Fei previously fused the Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist with the Triple Wave Technique.

The fusion of fist techniques and saber techniques should be similar and not cause any problems.

But now, after the Saber-drawing Technique had merged with the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, it seemed that there were some issues.

What was the difference between the fusion of the two saber techniques and the fusion of the two sets of fist techniques?

Lin Fei thought about it.

The only difference might be that the fusion of the two saber techniques could give birth to the saber intent!

After all, the cultivation progress of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique had already reached 43%.

With the fusion of the Saber-drawing Technique and the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, cultivation progress had skyrocketed.

Perhaps the saber intent was about to be born!

85. Saber Intent

At this moment, in Lin Fei's mind, the light of the Saber-drawing Technique surged. It seemed as if something was being nurtured within it. A terrifying power seemed to be trying to break out from the light.

Time passed by, minute by minute.

Surprisingly, the system's voice did not ring in Lin Fei's mind. Apparently, the system also determined that Lin Fei's fusion of saber techniques had not yet ended. No one knew how much time had passed.

"Boom."

Finally, the light of the Saber-drawing Technique in Lin Fei's mind burst instantly, turning into tiny spots of light. However, the shattering of the light was not the end, but merely the beginning.

Immediately after, a new force was born. This force was even sharper and purer than the Saber-drawing Technique. It was a more refined "saber" power. It was an "invisible" force.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei suddenly opened his eyes. At that instant, it seemed as if countless saber shadows faintly appeared above Lin Fei's head.

These saber shadows were invisible and intangible. They could only be sensed. Because this was the saber intent!

"Your Saber-drawing Technique and Nine Shadow Saber Technique have engaged in a fierce battle."

"Your Saber-drawing Technique has the upper hand, defeating the Nine Shadow Saber Technique."

"Nine Shadow Saber Technique willingly merged into the Saber-drawing Technique."

"Your Saber-drawing Technique's cultivation progress has reached 100%."

"Your Saber-drawing Technique has given birth to the saber intent!"

In Lin Fei's mind, one voice after another rang out, all were related to the Saber-drawing Technique.

"As expected, after fusing the Nine Shadow Saber Technique with the Saber-drawing Technique, the saber intent was successfully born!"

Without hesitation, Lin Fei immediately called up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Fifth Level

Saber Intent: Beginner (1% Progress)

Three Vitality Technique: Fifth Level (61% Progress)

Quadruple Wave Technique: Perfection (50% Progress )

Leaping Technique: Perfection (0% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

On the system panel, both the Saber-drawing Technique and the Nine Shadow Saber Technique disappeared. Of course, this didn't mean that the two martial arts techniques had vanished.

It was simply because they had reached their limits and could not be improved further. Therefore, they were no longer displayed on the system panel. This also saved panel space, making it easier to read at a glance.

Both saber techniques had reached their limits. So after fusing, the saber intent was successfully born.

This saber intent was just at the "beginner" stage.

"Saber intent..."

Lin Fei naturally had memories of saber intent in his mind. He was also proficient in mastering the saber intent.

In the next moment, Lin Fei unleashed his saber intent.

Although Lin Fei didn't draw his saber, His entire being seemed to transform into a peerless, sharp treasure saber, radiating a fierce saber edge, making people feel palpitations from a distance.

Lin Fei attached the saber intent to the Star Saber.

"Buzz."

At this moment, the Star Saber began to vibrate slightly. As if it was gently humming.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei drew his saber. Nineteen shadows with a single strike!

Yes, Lin Fei's Nine Shadow Saber Technique fused with the Saber-drawing Technique.

Although it merged into the Saber-drawing Technique, it didn't mean that Lin Fei couldn't use the Nine Shadow Saber Technique anymore. Not only could Lin Fei use the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, but it was even stronger!

It was as if the Nine Shadow Saber Technique, based on its perfection, had reached 100% in cultivation progress.

That meant nineteen shadows with a single saber strike!

The sky was filled with saber shadows. What was even more terrifying was that after attaching the saber intent, the speed and power skyrocketed.

It seemed to have been enhanced in all aspects. Moreover, the saber intent could attack independently. Invisible and intangible, making it difficult to defend against.

Once a martial artist comprehended saber intent, sword intent, or fist intent, their means of attack would become very diverse. Moreover, they could contend with Qi cultivators!

Lin Fei sorted through the memories in his mind. The birth of the saber intent had many benefits.

For example, the Saber-drawing Technique. The current Saber-drawing Technique not only had inner power nurturing it, but the saber intent was also nurturing it.

Once the saber was drawn, it would be earth-shattering. How powerful it would be, even Lin Fei himself was not sure. Moreover, the Saber-drawing Technique also integrated the Nine Shadow Saber Technique.

When drawing the saber, it could create nineteen shadows with a single strike!

In other words, when the Saber-drawing Technique was used with a single strike, it was actually nineteen strikes!

How powerful would that be?

Lin Fei didn't plan to test it now. After all, he had been nurturing the saber for a month. Nurturing the saber for a month was not easy. It couldn't be wasted casually.

But even without trying, Lin Fei was confident. His Saber-drawing Technique was very powerful!

In fact, Lin Fei felt that with the dual nurturing of inner power and saber intent, once he drew his saber, he might be able to defeat an innate expert!

"The saber intent has been born, and its progress has reached 1%. That is to say, the saber intent can actually be improved. However, I wonder how fast the saber intent can be improved?"

Many thoughts flashed through Lin Fei's mind.

Now that the saber intent was born. Lin Fei didn't need to worry about his saber techniques for the time being.

This Saber-drawing Technique could be used until the innate realm. Even among innate martial arts, it was very powerful. Lin Fei's saber intent could even contend with innate experts!

However, Lin Fei's martial arts realm was only at the acquired fifth Level.

"Now I can focus on improving my martial arts cultivation. The progress of the Three Vitality Technique is too slow; I need to think of a solution. Perhaps I can take pills."

A thought struck Lin Fei's heart.

His current weak point was actually his martial arts cultivation. The Three Vitality Technique itself was characterized by its stability. Its cultivation speed was quite ordinary. But there were almost no significant bottlenecks.

Lin Fei now felt that the cultivation speed of the Three Vitality Technique was too slow. He could use external help. So, Lin Fei got up and went directly to the Treasure Pavilion. Only the Treasure Pavilion had elixirs that could enhance acquired martial arts.

"Elder."

Lin Fei respectfully said to the elder of the Treasure Pavilion, "I would like some pills or other treasures that can enhance inner power. I wonder if the elder has any recommendations?"

"Enhance inner power?"

The elder glanced at Lin Fei and said indifferently, "Relying on pills and other external forces to enhance inner power will result in impure inner power, which requires a lot of energy to operate martial arts techniques and gradually purify it. It's not worth it. Are you sure you need an elixir to enhance inner power?"

Lin Fei thought for a moment, without hesitation, nodded, and said, "Please recommend one, Elder!"

Lin Fei naturally had his considerations.

Using pills to enhance inner power would indeed lead to impure inner power. And it would take time to purify. However, would this affect Lin Fei? His martial arts were so diligent that they cultivate almost every moment.

It was equivalent to cultivating martial arts techniques for twenty-four hours a day to purify inner power every day. So, Lin Fei wasn't worried about taking elixirs leading to impure inner power.

The Treasure Pavilion elder shook his head.

The young disciples nowadays were so eager for quick success and instant benefits. They hated not being able to achieve innate in just one or two years.

Is it possible? Many geniuses, because of their eagerness for quick success, took pills, which resulted in impure inner power.

They consumed a lot of energy to purify it. In the early stage, the cultivation speed was extremely fast. But in the later stage, especially after the acquired ninth Level, breaking through the realm was even more difficult than ascending to the heavens. There was no hope of achieving innate in their lifetime.

However, these matters had nothing to do with the Treasure Pavilion elder.

So, the elder took out a bottle of pills directly. He introduced it to Lin Fei, "This is the Gather Qi Pill, with a mild medicinal effect. It can to a certain extent speed up the circulation of inner power, thereby enhancing inner power."

Lin Fei thought for a moment. This Gather Qi Pill only accelerated the circulation of inner power. But his inner power was already circulating very quickly. And it was circulating every moment. The Gather Qi Pill had little effect on Lin Fei.

So, Lin Fei shook his head and said, "Elder, is there any pill with a strong effect that can quickly enhance inner power?"

"Strong effect?"

The elder's face darkened, and he said coldly, "Then you might as well use the Burst Qi Pill. One Burst Qi Pill can instantly increase inner power by ten to fifty percent.

However, the Burst Qi Pill is not a cultivation pill but is used by martial artists when fighting desperately. If you encounter a strong enemy and are in a life-threatening crisis, you can take the Burst Qi Pill, and your inner power will surge, thereby greatly increasing your strength in a short period.

However, once the effect of the Burst Qi Pill passes, there will be pill poison residue left in the inner power. It takes several months to gradually remove it.

Taking too many, the pill poison residue will be too much, and it will also affect the foundation of the martial artist."

The elder of the Treasure Pavilion was just speaking casually. No one would use the Burst Qi Pill for cultivation. They all used it as a trump card for desperate situations.

However, Lin Fei's eyes brightened after hearing this.

86. Letter From Lin Miao

"Elder, I would like to purchase one Burst Qi Pill," Lin Fei immediately decided, wanting to give it a try.

"One Burst Qi Pill costs ten thousand contribution points," the Treasure Pavilion Elder said indifferently.

Lin Fei was astonished, "Ten thousand contribution points? That's so expensive!"

To put things into perspective, Lin Fei's Hidden Saber had only cost him a mere five thousand contribution points. The Hidden Saber was indeed a genuine treasure and had been specifically crafted.

"The Burst Qi Pill is a life-saving treasure, and the materials used to create it are extremely precious. Naturally, the price is high," the elder explained. "Moreover, refining Burst Qi Pills is no easy task. Even an innate expert must expend a great deal of energy to produce them. Ten thousand contribution points is already a discounted price for inner disciples."

Lin Fei nodded and promptly exchanged one Burst Qi Pill. He previously had three hundred thousand contribution points, but now only had two hundred ninety thousand left.

On his journey with Ling Yao to Chang City, Lin Fei helped Ling Yao secure the princess's position, earning five hundred thousand silver bills. Instead of converting these silver bills to contribution points, he continued to carry them with him. At present, he wasn't in urgent need of contribution points, the silver bills were more practical.

Lin Fei left the Treasure Pavilion and returned to his room. He sat down cross-legged and took out the Burst Qi Pill from his pocket. The pill was about the size of an eye, with a light yellow hue and no noticeable fragrance.

"Let's give it a try," he thought, opening his mouth and swallowing the Burst Qi Pill. The pill had a faint bitter taste, but it dissolved instantly upon entering his mouth.

"Boom!"

The effects of the Burst Qi Pill erupted within Lin Fei's body, and his inner power seemed to ignite all at once. It surged rapidly and started to become agitated.

Lin Fei sensed that his inner power had increased by roughly thirty percent. This was a frightening number. An increase of thirty percent in inner power could potentially translate to a doubling or even more significant improvement in his overall strength. Martial artists would resort to using such a method as a desperate measure to save their lives.

Lin Fei's Three Vitality Technique was continuously operating within his body and clearing his meridians. He could indeed feel that his inner power had become impure. There were traces of black impurities attached to his veins, affecting the flow of his inner power. This was the pill poison.

A small amount of pill poison was not a big deal. However, if there was too much pill poison, it could block the meridians, and even previously cleared meridians could become obstructed again due to excessive pill poison.

Lin Fei tried to circulate his inner power to "cleanse" these impurities but found the process to be slow. Eventually, he decided to let the Three Vitality Technique handle the task on its own.

One hour, two hours, three hours... About twelve hours later, Lin Fei opened his eyes.

"The pill poison is gone?" Lin Fei sensed his body's meridians. The traces of pill poison that had been attached to his veins after consuming the Burst Qi Pill were now gone after twelve hours of the Three Vitality Technique's relentless cleansing.

Under normal circumstances, martial artists would take one or two months, or even longer, to cleanse the impurities caused by a single Burst Qi Pill.

Lin Fei pondered and concluded that this rapid cleansing might be related to his vast inner power.

Lin Fei's inner power was three-in-one, which provided him with an incredibly solid foundation. Now at the fifth level of the Acquired Realm, his inner power had increased exponentially, making it comparable to or even more profound than that of martial artists above the ninth level of the Acquired Realm.

With such vast inner power, it naturally wouldn't take long for Lin Fei to cleanse the pill poison left by a single Burst Qi Pill.

"Your Three Vitality Technique detected the pill poison impurities in your meridians and spent twelve hours diligently cleansing them. The progress of your Three Vitality Technique cultivation has increased by 2%."

A voice echoed in Lin Fei's mind, informing him that the progress of his Three Vitality Technique had increased from 61% to 63%. This delighted Lin Fei.

According to the speed at which the Three Vitality Technique cleansed the pill poison, it would take twelve hours to cleanse the poison from one Burst Qi Pill. This meant that Lin Fei could consume two pills per day and increase his cultivation progress from the current 1% to 4% daily. At this pace, it wouldn't take long for his Three Vitality Technique to reach the sixth, seventh level, and beyond.

Lin Fei was satisfied with the effects of the Burst Qi Pill. As he had anticipated, the pill poison had little impact on him. He could consume the pill long-term to accelerate his cultivation of the Three Vitality Technique. However, the cost of 10,000 contribution points per pill was quite expensive.

Moreover, the main issue was not the price, but the fact that Lin Fei couldn't openly purchase large quantities of Burst Qi Pills from the Treasure Pavilion. Buying one or two pills wouldn't be a problem, as they could be considered life-saving items, and having a few more on hand would be reasonable.

However, if Lin Fei were to frequently purchase Burst Qi Pills in large quantities, say dozens or even hundreds at a time, it would ultimately be too conspicuous. The elder of the Treasure Pavilion wasn't foolish. If Lin Fei were to buy large quantities of Burst Qi Pills and combined with his cultivation speed, they would surely suspect that he had resolved the pill's drawbacks. In the end, this would create unnecessary trouble for him.

"Perhaps I can find a way to obtain the pill recipe. Once I have the recipe, I can buy the ingredients and bring them back to the Lin family, letting Lin Miao try to refine the pills."

Lin Fei thought of a solution, which involved having Lin Miao refine the Burst Qi Pills. This way, even if he used a large number of pills, it wouldn't draw attention.

As for obtaining the pill recipe, Lin Fei didn't plan to solve this issue by himself. He had an existing connection that he could use.

"I'll leave the issue of the Burst Qi Pill recipe to Ling Yao. Now that she's a princess, her status is revered. A Burst Qi Pill recipe shouldn't be a problem for Ling Yao."

Lin Fei immediately thought of Ling Yao. This kind of task was most suitable for her. Besides, Ling Yao would probably be happy to help Lin Fei with this "small favor." So, Lin Fei promptly wrote a letter to Ling Yao and had it sent to Chang City.

In the following days, Lin Fei stayed at the Nine Profound Sect.

One day, two days, three days...

On this day, Lin Fei received two letters.

"Two letters?"

Lin Fei looked at the letters. One was from Chang City, likely a reply from Ling Yao regarding the matter he had asked her to handle. The other one came from Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

"Zhou Mountain Mansion City, did something happens at home?"

Frowning, Lin Fei immediately opened the letter. After reading its content, he found out that it was a letter from Lin Miao.

Lin Miao rarely wrote to Lin Fei. This time, he wrote to inform him of some good news: Lin Miao had made a breakthrough! In just a few months, he had reached the first level of the Qi Condensation Realm!

This was big news, which was why Lin Miao had written to inform Lin Fei. However, Lin Fei didn't feel too happy but was rather slightly concerned.

"Considering Lin Miao's aptitude and his previous cultivation speed, it would probably take him several years to break through to the first level of the Qi Condensation Realm.

Even with the Yin Gathering Formation, it should take more than a year for him to possibly break through. But now, it's only been a few months. How did Lin Miao make a breakthrough?"

Lin Fei felt that there might be a problem.

87. Yin Ren Mansion

Lin Fei then opened the letter from Ling Yao. In the letter, Ling Yao had indeed obtained the Burst Qi Pill recipe for Lin Fei, which was tucked inside the letter.

Lin Fei took out the recipe and memorized it carefully before putting it into his pocket. Afterward, he burned both letters.

"What a coincidence. Just as I've received the Burst Qi Pill recipe, Lin Miao has broken through to the first level of the Qi Condensation Realm. It seems I have to make a trip back to the Lin family. I need to find out what's going on with Lin Miao's breakthrough. And also have Lin Miao try to see if he can refine the Burst Qi Pills."

Lin Fei had a plan in mind. So, without any delay, he got up, rented a fast horse, and left the mountain once again.

...

Lin family, Zhou Mountain Mansion City

Lin Fei returned to the Lin family, looking tired and dusty. After meeting with his parents, he went directly to Lin Miao's courtyard.

The courtyard was still filled with Yin Qi, making people shiver. As soon as Lin Fei entered Lin Miao's room, a faint smell of decay filled the air.

"Hmm? Bloodstains!"

Lin Fei's senses were sharp, and he immediately noticed some bloodstains on the ground. Although the bloodstains had dried, it was evident that they had appeared recently.

Lin Fei quickly found Lin Miao, who was sitting cross-legged on a cushion, seemingly meditating and condensing Qi. An invisible layer of Yin wind surrounded him.

Lin Miao, now at the first level of Qi Condensation, seemed to have changed significantly from before.

"Lin Miao," Lin Fei called out.

"Whoosh."

Lin Miao suddenly opened his eyes.

"Young Master, you're back."

Lin Miao tried to show a smile, but his expression was somewhat stiff, perhaps due to his cultivation or some other reason.

Lin Fei got straight to the point, "Lin Miao, you wrote to me saying that you've advanced to the first level of Qi Condensation."

"Yes, Young Master. I had a stroke of luck recently, allowing me to reach the first level of Qi Condensation ahead of schedule." Lin Miao revealed a smile.

"Fortune? Is it related to the bloodstains on the ground?"

"You have sharp eyes, Young Master. My fortune is indeed related to the bloodstains on the ground. Ten days ago, a strange old man suddenly broke into my courtyard.

He was a Qi Condensation cultivator, probably at the second or third level, with profound spiritual power. Seeing that I hadn't even reached the first level of Qi Condensation, he ruthlessly attacked me, intending to kill me, seize my residence, and plunder my treasures.

Unfortunately for him, he didn't expect that I had been practicing the Zombie-refining Technique. Over time, I had already taken control of a few zombies.

Then, I caught him off guard and killed him instead. I obtained some good items from him, allowing me to break through to the first level of Qi Condensation ahead of schedule."

Lin Miao recounted the details of the incident.

Although Lin Miao made it sound simple, Lin Fei knew that the process was anything but. The old man was injured but not foolish. How could he have barged into the courtyard without any precautions, trying to kill Lin Miao?

The old man must have been prepared and even felt confident in his success. But even so, he was still killed by Lin Miao. This Lin Miao was not to be underestimated!

Lin Fei carefully recalled Lin Miao's appearance back in the broken temple.

Lin Miao had followed the old Taoist for so long. He seemed frail but had not been killed by the old Taoist. Later, Lin Miao was captured by Lin Fei and fell into his hands. Still, Lin Miao didn't die.

Now, a strange Qi Condensation cultivator came prepared but still died at Lin Miao's hands.

Once was an accident, twice was a coincidence. But three times, it was definitely not an accident or a coincidence. This Lin Miao was cunning and not as simple and innocent as he appeared on the surface.

However, Lin Fei didn't care what trump card or reliance Lin Miao had. Lin Miao was no threat to him. That was enough!

"Lin Miao, where is the old man's body?" Lin Fei asked again.

"I didn't dare to keep it, so I burned it with fire."

"And the things on the old man, you must have kept them, right?"

"I kept them. Young Master, please take a look. This is a piece of jade marrow that I obtained. It was this jade marrow that allowed my Qi Condensation speed to skyrocket, leading to my breakthrough. Unfortunately, it seems that the jade marrow is almost used up. And this token, it has 'Yin Ren Mansion' written on it. This old man must have come from Yin Ren Mansion."

Lin Miao took out many items he had obtained from the old man. He showed them all to Lin Fei without any concealment.

Lin Miao was a smart person. He knew very well what to do and what not to do. In front of Lin Fei, Lin Miao didn't dare to hide anything. After all, his life and death were in Lin Fei's hands.

"Yin Ren Mansion..."

Lin Fei glanced at the jade marrow, which was indeed almost used up.

This jade marrow should be able to increase a Qi cultivator's absorption of Spiritual Qi, thus accelerating its cultivation speed.

However, it was a consumable item. Once used up, it would be useless.

It was the "Yin Ren Mansion" token that made Lin Fei feel a little worried.

"I don't know what kind of power this Yin Ren Mansion has. You killed him recklessly, and although you burned the body, you still left some things behind. It's hard to guarantee that it won't be traced.

Now, burn all the things from the old man's body. Include this token, burn everything. Even if you can't burn it, destroy it completely. Don't leave any traces!"

Lin Fei said decisively. He had a feeling that this old man could be a problem.

"Yes, Young Master. I will deal with all the things from the old man's body immediately."

Lin Miao didn't hesitate. He took out all the things from the old man's body. Then, in front of Lin Fei, he burned everything.

Lin Fei even saw a Qi cultivation method and some secret manuals. Lin Miao might have read these methods and secret manuals.

This was Lin Miao's opportunity. Lin Fei didn't point it out. After all, if Lin Miao's strength and realm were higher, it would actually be a good thing for Lin Fei.

"Lin Miao, my purpose for coming back this time is to let you try refining the Burst Qi Pill. Here is the pill recipe, study it for one night. Tomorrow, I'll bring you the materials listed in the recipe and let you try to refine the Burst Qi Pill."

Lin Fei handed the Burst Qi Pill recipe directly to Lin Miao.

Lin Miao glanced at it and said with a smile, "Young Master, I am now at the first level of Qi Condensation. And with the Yin Gathering Formation, I can quickly recover my spiritual power. There should be no problem with this Burst Qi Pill."

"Good, start refining the pills tomorrow."

After giving instructions, Lin Fei turned and left the courtyard.

...

Outside Zhou Mountain Mansion City, a Taoist in a robe was about to enter the city.

Suddenly, the Taoist raised his head and looked towards the city.

"The connection has been severed... I placed a Thousand-Mile Tracking Technique on the identity token of that Yin Ren Mansion remnant. He didn't notice it before, but just now the connection was severed. Was it discovered?"

The Taoist frowned, with many thoughts flashing through his mind.

"Hmph, what if it was discovered? You're already injured, and you can't escape far even if you try. You should still be in Zhou Mountain Mansion City. If the city gates are closed, where will you run?"

The Taoist sneered. He asked the city guard soldiers and learned the direction of the Prefecture Yamen. Then, the Taoist headed straight to the Prefecture Yamen.

A note from RighteousEgg

More than 30 chapters on my Patreon.

88. Something Terrible Has Happened

Lin Mansion, the side courtyard.

Lin Fei brought the materials for the Burst Qi Pill recipe to Lin Miao.

"Lin Miao, these medicinal ingredients are not cheap. You must refine them with care," Lin Fei said, looking at Lin Miao.

"Young Master, I studied the Burst Qi Pill recipe last night. There should be no problem," Lin Miao said with confidence.

Lin Fei nodded and stepped back, watching Lin Miao refine the pill carefully.

It was no wonder Lin Fei reminded Lin Miao. These medicinal ingredients were indeed not cheap. Just buying the materials for one furnace cost about 10,000 taels of silver. Lin Fei bought almost enough materials for ten furnaces, spending 100,000 taels of silver.

This was only the price of the raw materials for the Burst Qi Pill. If it also factored in the cost of hiring an innate expert to refine the pill... Nine Profound Sect's treasure pavilion sold Burst Qi Pills for 10,000 taels of silver each was not expensive!

Lin Miao was already familiar with refining pills. After throwing the materials into the pill furnace. he started a fire and turned the materials into a sticky liquid.

This was the pill liquid.

Then, Lin Miao controlled the heat with his spiritual power, slowly refining the pill.

"Young Master, refining the Burst Qi Pill is not easy and takes a long time. You can go down and rest first, and I will notify you when it's ready." Lin Miao said to Lin Fei.

"No problem, I have nothing else to do anyway. Watching you refine the pill will also expand my knowledge."

Lin Fei didn't mind. He wanted to watch the refining of the Burst Qi Pill personally.

While Lin Fei watched Lin Miao refining the Burst Qi Pill, at the Zhou Mountain Prefecture Yamen, Prefect Wang was now standing in front of a Taoist, bowing slightly, said with a flattering smile, "Immortal Master, the city gates have been closed.

Moreover, according to the portrait and the information provided by Immortal Master, we have sent people to inquire about every household. Please rest assured, Immortal Master, there should be news soon."

The Prefect looked at the Immortal Master with a hint of desire in his eyes.

An Immortal Master!

The Prefect had some understanding of Immortal Masters. According to rumors, these Immortal Masters were capable of living forever. Moreover, the Taoist in front of him was an Immortal Master from He Mountain Dao.

He Mountain Dao was a sect recognized by the imperial court. It belonged to the orthodox Daoist school. The Immortal Masters of He Mountain Dao had the imperial court's credentials.

As a prefect, he dared not offend the Immortal Masters of He Mountain Dao. Besides, encountering an Immortal Master was a great opportunity.

"You've done well. After the matter is accomplished, I will reward you with a pill. It won't make you live for hundreds of years, but at least you won't suffer from illnesses and can enjoy your twilight years."

This was the promise given by the He Mountain Dao Taoist to the Prefect.

Pills! These were things that many ordinary people dreamed of having.

"Report." At this moment, a voice came from outside.

"Come in." The Prefect said calmly.

Soon, a yamen runner entered with a quick step, and reported to the Prefect, "My lord, we have investigated and confirmed that the wanted person in the portrait did appear in Zhou Mountain Mansion City. The last time he was seen was near Dan Gui Street."

The Prefect nodded and then asked the Taoist, "Immortal Master, shall we go to Dan Gui Street and take a look?"

"Of course, lead the way."

So, the Prefect led the He Mountain Dao Taoist, along with a group of yamen runners, they left the yamen and arrived at Dan Gui Street.

There were already many yamen runners and constables here. Almost the entire Dan Gui Street was blocked.

"Who saw the wanted person?" The Prefect asked the yamen runners.

Then, a yamen runner brought an old man. He was about fifty years old, with slightly dark skin and short stature. His eyes were constantly moving, appearing quite shrewd.

However, seeing the grand entourage of the Prefect and the others, the old man was somewhat frightened and stammered, "It was me who saw the person in the portrait. He was wearing a cloak and a black robe, just hanging around this area. It seemed like he was looking for something. He disappeared in the evening."

The He Mountain Dao Taoist's gaze swept across the nearby Dan Gui Street.

"Hmm? The fluctuation of Yin Qi?"

The Taoist's eyes narrowed slightly, looking towards the other end of Dan Gui Street. He saw a huge mansion.

"What place is that?"

The Taoist asked.

Following the direction pointed out by the Taoist, the Prefect took a closer look. Immediately, the Prefect was somewhat surprised and carefully answered, "Immortal Master, that is the mansion of a wealthy merchant named Lin in our city."

"Lin family?"

The Taoist said coldly, "Search the Lin Mansion. The remnants of the Yin Ren Mansion are in the Lin Mansion!"

"Ah? Immortal Master, that must not be done."

"Hmm? Why not?"

The Prefect said with a bitter smile, "Immortal Master, you may not know. Although the Lin family is just a wealthy merchant, they have a son named Lin Fei. Lin Fei is an inner disciple of the famous martial arts sect, the Nine Profound Sect and his martial arts skills are unfathomable.

It is precise because of this that the Lin family has become the top wealthy family in Zhou Mountain Mansion City. Searching the Lin Mansion would be very difficult..."

The Prefect was unwilling to offend the Lin family. After all, the influence of the Lin family in Zhou Mountain Mansion City was growing day by day.

Even he, as the Prefect, had to cater to the Lin family. If he offended the Lin family. The Prefect would hardly be able to accomplish anything in Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

"You're afraid of offending the Lin family, but not afraid of offending me?"

The Taoist's words made the Prefect even more embarrassed.

"Let people search the Lin Mansion! As for Lin Fei, what does a mere disciple from a martial arts sect amount to? Among the servants and subordinates of my He Mountain Dao, all are acquired martial artists. If Lin Fei dares to obstruct, this Daoist will kill him!"

The Taoist's words made the yamen runners and constables look at each other in dismay.

The Prefect glanced at the He Mountain Dao Taoist. He then looked at the Lin Mansion. Thinking about the status of the Taoist, even martial artists wouldn't amount to much in front of him.

With this thought, the Prefect gritted his teeth and said, "What are you all waiting for? Obey the Taoist's orders!"

"Yes, my lord!"

Thus, many yamen runners and constables quickly rushed toward the Lin Mansion.

......

In the side courtyard of the Lin Mansion.

Lin Fei watched Lin Miao, who had been refining Burst Qi Pills for almost two hours.

How much spiritual power must this consume?

Yet even so, the pills still hadn't been successfully made.

Compared to the previous time when he refined Blood-Increasing Pills, this time, it was obviously much more difficult to refine Burst Qi Pills.

Fortunately, Lin Miao's cultivation had reached the first level of Qi Condensation. His spiritual power was much deeper. Furthermore, he had the support of the Yin Gathering Formation. Otherwise, Lin Miao wouldn't have been able to endure continuously refining Burst Qi Pills for two hours.

Just as Lin Fei was about to close his eyes and rest. Suddenly, his ears twitched. He heard a chaotic noise.

The housekeeper, panting, had a trace of panic in his eyes, and hurriedly ran to the side courtyard.

Upon seeing Lin Fei, he shouted, "Young Master, something terrible has happened. The Prefect has led the yamen runners and constables into the Lin Mansion. They said they were looking for some wanted person."

"The Prefect led people to break into the Lin Mansion?" Lin Fei frowned.

The housekeeper couldn't explain exactly what was going on. He only saw that the yamen officials were aggressively entering and immediately ran to inform Lin Fei.

"Lin Miao, continue refining Burst Qi Pills. I'll take care of the situation outside."

Lin Fei instructed Lin Miao.

Then he left the side courtyard quickly with the housekeeper.

89. Magical Artifact

The Lin Mansion was now in a state of panic. A large group of yamen runners and constables searched the Lin Mansion in all directions. Moreover, they were also interrogating some of the servants and maids of the Lin Mansion.

"What's the panic?!"

A loud shout came from the Lin Mansion. Immediately, the many servants dared not make any noise. Lin Wen was also at the Lin Mansion at this time.

At this moment, he stared at the Prefect with a gloomy expression and said coldly, "My lord, you lead the search of the Lin Mansion. Is this the attitude of the Wang family? Or, does my lord want to capture the entire Lin family in one fell swoop?"

The Prefect had a Wang family behind him. A large family, all in Zhou Mountain Mansion City. The Prefect's actions were tantamount to completely tearing off his face. It was a complete break from his previous low-key and discreet demeanor.

Therefore, Lin Wen was very puzzled. What caused the Prefect's drastic change of attitude?

The Prefect's face was solemn, and he said coldly, "The Taoist is catching a demon. Some people have seen that your Lin Mansion is harboring a demon. By the Taoist's orders, we will search your Lin Mansion thoroughly, not let any demon go! Anyone who interferes with the yamen's affairs will be arrested and thrown in jail!

"How dare you! This is the Lin Mansion, don't be presumptuous!" Lin Wen shouted loudly. Immediately, many Lin family guards stepped forward. They drew their sabers one after another, blocking the yamen officials.

The Prefect's face turned pale. Seeing that the Taoist didn't speak, he understood the Taoist's intention. This was to test his performance.

Thinking about this, the Prefect took a deep breath and said sternly, "The yamen is arresting demons, and anyone who resists will be killed without mercy!"

"Swish."

Immediately, the yamen's constables and runners also drew their sabers one after another. Suddenly, the bright sabers, under the sunlight, reflected dazzling rays of light, causing fear in people's hearts.

At this moment, the entire Lin Mansion became quiet. The atmosphere was extremely tense.

"Whoosh."

Suddenly, a figure burst out from the backyard of the Lin Mansion.

The figure stopped.

Everyone could see clearly.

"Young Master Lin Fei!"

The people of the Lin Mansion seemed to have found their backbone. Their morale soared instantly, and they looked at the yamen officials with murderous intent.

Everyone knew the real "core" of the Lin family was actually Lin Fei.

"With just you, you dare to show your sabers in front of me?"

The next moment, Lin Fei released a sharp aura from his body. It was as if he had transformed into a peerless treasure saber in an instant.

"Hum."

The sabers of those yamen runners and constables actually began to tremble slightly as if they were about to be pulled out of their hands.

"Get back!" Lin Fei shouted loudly.

For the first time, Lin Fei unleashed his saber intent in front of others.

Saber intent is invisible and intangible. It can only be sensed.

At this moment, in front of a martial artist who had comprehended saber intent, drawing a saber was a luxury.

"Clang."

Suddenly, the sabers of the yamen runners and constables, which were originally drawn out, seemed to be controlled by an invisible force, instantly pulling back into their sheaths.

Moreover, no matter how hard the yamen runners and constables tried to draw their sabers, they simply could not pull them out. It was as if these sabers had grown roots.

"You..."

The Prefect's face was full of horror as if he had seen a ghost. Everyone was shocked beyond belief. Especially those constables and yamen runners. Their whole bodies were trembling. In front of Lin Fei. They couldn't even draw their sabers. What kind of technique was this?

"Immortal, we can't draw our sabers!"

"Immortal, is this a demon technique?"

"How could this be?"

Many constables and yamen runners all turned to the Taoist for help. In their eyes, Immortals were omnipotent, representing invincibility!

Even if Lin Fei had some tricks up his sleeve, how could he compare with the high and mighty immortal?

The Taoist from He Mountain Dao frowned at this moment. He had been a Qi cultivator since he was a child. The servants on the mountain were all acquired martial artists.

The Taoist looked down upon acquired martial artists, and even all martial artists. So why would he bother to understand the techniques of martial artists? Therefore, the Taoist knew nothing about Lin Fei's saber intent.

So, the Taoist sneered and said, "It's just some insignificant tricks of a martial artist. Daring to show off in front of me is simply seeking death!"

The Taoist flicked his finger. Suddenly, a talisman emitted a brilliant light.

It instantly transformed into a small sword, as fast as lightning, directly stabbed towards Lin Fei.

"Ding."

Lin Fei forcefully drew the Star Saber from behind his back.

And with a single slash, nineteen saber shadows instantly merged into one, striking the black light.

The small sword, or rather, the talisman sword.

Lin Fei's slash cut the talisman sword into two pieces.

It fell to the ground and transformed back into a talisman.

This was not a real magical artifact. It was merely a talisman.

"He actually broke my talisman sword?"

The Taoist's eyes narrowed slightly. He was somewhat surprised.

His talisman sword was extremely fast. Although it wasn't a real magical artifact, such speed was rarely reacted to by acquired martial artists.

Basically, when the Taoist released the talisman sword, it was a one-hit kill for acquired martial artists, without exception.

But now, the unexpected happened.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei moved. His figure suddenly leaped forward.

In the blink of an eye, he reached the front of the Taoist.

This was the Leaping Technique, and it was the perfection realm Leaping Technique. The speed was incredibly fast, beyond imagination.

Lin Fei knew that the Taoist was a Qi cultivator. Moreover, he should be an orthodox Qi cultivator. He even had talismans.

Who knew how many mysterious and strange techniques he had?

Facing a Qi cultivator, Lin Fei never dared to be careless. Therefore, he made his move. He went all out from the start.

Lin Fei's hand was already holding the Hidden Saber at his waist.

"Swish."

He drew the saber from his waist.

Saber-drawing Technique!

Lin Fei had been nurturing his saber for more than a month. Moreover, it was the perfection realm Saber-drawing Technique.

The saber had been nurtured for a month, its power was incredibly strong. Far stronger than nurturing the saber for two or three months before!

The entire Lin Mansion, everyone's eyes widened.

At this moment, it seemed as if everyone's thoughts had come to a halt.

In their line of sight, there was only this one saber.

That ball of white light filled with cold and sharp saber intent.

It made everyone feel as if they were standing on a mountain of sabers. As if they were surrounded by sharp saber edges in all directions!

At the moment of drawing the saber, there were nineteen saber shadows.

However, when the saber slashed down, there was only one saber shadow left.

This was the union of nineteen saber strikes.

Saber-drawing Technique and Nine Shadow Saber Technique had completely fused together.

Lin Fei's inner power had fully exploded to this saber. He felt that this saber could even cut through the innate realm!

"Bang."

Finally, the saber fell. It struck directly at the top of the Taoist's head.

With a muffled sound, Lin Fei's eyes suddenly widened.

His gaze was fixed on the Taoist in front of him.

His saber was right above the Taoist's head.

However, Lin Fei's saber couldn't fall further.

Because, above the Taoist's head, a small shield was floating, as if out of nowhere.

This small shield was only the size of a palm. It emitted a green light, like a protective barrier, protecting the Taoist within.

Even Lin Fei's fully powered saber, nurtured for a month that Lin Fei had confidence could cut through the innate realm, still, it couldn't break through the green light of the small shield.

"Magical artifact!"

Lin Fei said in a low voice. He instantly understood what the green small shield was.

One of the strongest means of a Qi cultivator was magical artifacts!

90. Powerful Saber Intent

The Daoist was startled by the earlier saber strike.

It was simply too fast. Even if he could sense and clearly see Lin Fei's saber, what difference would it make? The speed was so fast that his body couldn't dodge it. Fortunately, there was a magical artifact!

"You martial artists possess brute strength and painstakingly study combat techniques. But what's the use? If you were an Innate martial artist, perhaps your Innate True Qi could pose a threat to me. However, you are merely an Acquired martial artist. Your inner power is nothing more than mundane strength. How can it possibly affect my magical artifact?"

Lin Fei understood. Finally, he realized why the Sect Master said that Acquired martial artists had difficulty resisting orthodox Qi cultivators.

It turned out that the inner power, brute strength, and combat techniques of Acquired martial artists had little effect on orthodox Qi cultivators. Because a single protective magical artifact could render all these methods useless.

This was the gap between the two power systems. It was impossible to make up for it.

Even if Lin Fei's Saber-drawing Technique was stronger and nurtured for a month or even a year, as long as it was nurtured with inner power, it wouldn't be able to break the Qi cultivator's magical artifact.

Only Innate martial artists, who could unleash Innate True Qi, might be able to break these Qi cultivators' magical artifacts.

"Daring to attack an Immortal Master, you lowly martial artist, you deserve death!" The Daoist coldly snorted.

The next moment, he directly pulled out a handful of talismanic slips from his bosom.

That's right, a handful. Just like the talismanic slips earlier.

Lin Fei's pupils constricted abruptly. He felt threatened.

His movement technique was fast, the earlier talismanic sword couldn't hurt him. But what about ten or twenty?

"Our He Mountain Dao lineage is passed down through talismanic slips. Now, as a mere Acquired mortal, you should feel proud to die under so many talismanic swords!"

With that said, the talismanic swords in the Daoist's hands began to emit beams of light. The Daoist had already infused spiritual power.

He started activating the talismanic swords.

Once the talismanic swords were activated, Lin Fei would face the attack of dozens of them, even an Acquired Twelfth Level martial artist would undoubtedly die!

This was the terrifying aspect of Qi cultivators.

Acquired martial artists couldn't harm Qi cultivators with defensive magical artifacts. On the other hand, Qi cultivators could unleash numerous miraculous and powerful spells to defeat Acquired martial artists. No wonder Acquired martial artists couldn't hold their heads up in front of Qi Condensation cultivators.

Qi Condensation cultivators were naturally born to suppress Acquired martial artists.

"You hide in this turtle shell, thinking I can't do anything to you? An Acquired martial artist can kill you too!"

Lin Fei's eyes were icy cold. At this moment, he no longer hesitated.

"Boom."

Lin Fei fully unleashed his saber intent.

"Buzz, buzz, buzz."

The sabers in the hands of the bailiffs, guards, and even Lin's family guards around him all trembled simultaneously. It was as if they were emitting a faint humming sound.

"Here it comes again, here it comes again."

"What is this?"

"The Second Young Master is emanating such a terrifying aura..."

Ordinary people and martial artists couldn't see the changes in Lin Fei. They could only vaguely sense it. But Qi cultivators were different.

The Daoist had divine sense. With a sweep of his divine sense, he immediately saw an illusory saber appearing above Lin Fei's head.

This saber emitted an endless saber edge. Its sharp aura instantly locked onto the Daoist.

"Could this be... the legendary saber intent of martial artists?"

At this point, the Daoist finally remembered.

There were predecessors who once said that a particular kind of martial artist could pose a strong threat to Qi cultivators.

Those who comprehended the real meaning of martial arts, such as sword intent, saber intent, fist intent, etc. They also were known as Martial Dao True Intent.

The Martial Dao True Intent was invisible and intangible. It was somewhat similar to divine sense but completely different.

It could ignore all spells and magical artifact defenses. Only those with strong divine sense and unwavering will could resist the Martial Dao True Intent of martial artists.

However, comprehending Martial Dao True Intent was extremely difficult. Even many Innate martial artists couldn't comprehend it. The difficulty of understanding Martial Dao True Intent was even greater than achieving Innate!

The Daoist didn't expect that during this trip down the mountain, he would encounter an Acquired martial artist who had comprehended Martial Dao True Intent.

Moreover, it was the saber intent, which had a very powerful attack force among Martial Dao True Intents!

"Slash!"

Lin Fei shouted loudly.

The invisible and intangible saber intent erupted instantly. It was as if a real invisible great saber was descending upon the Daoist.

"No..."

The Daoist finally felt fear. He was scared.

However, the attack of the saber intent couldn't be dodged.

Even though the Daoist desperately activated his magical artifact, it was of no use.

"Thump."

Without any warning, the Daoist fell straight to the ground with his eyes wide open. Although his body remained intact, there was no sign of life left in him.

He was dead!

The Daoist from He Mountain Dao, a respected immortal master.

Just a moment ago, he was showing off his magical artifact, as if he were a real immortal.

But now, with his eyes wide open, he lay dead on the ground, unable to close them.

Silence!

The entire Lin Mansion seemed to become very quiet.

One could hear a pin drop!

Ordinary people or general martial artists couldn't understand what had just happened at all.

It seemed that Lin Fei had just said "slash," They didn't see Lin Fei draw his saber or make any other movements. As a result, the immortal master fell to the ground, completely lifeless.

"What just happened?"

"How could the immortal master be dead?"

"Sir, what should we do?"

For a moment, numerous yamen's constables and runners retreated a few steps away from Lin Fei and looked at each other in disbelief.

Only Lin Fei knew that the Daoist in front of him had been slain by his saber intent. This was also the first time Lin Fei had used saber intent against an enemy, and it was against a powerful and orthodox immortal master!

"Saber intent is truly terrifying! This Daoist should also be at the third level of Qi Condensation.

But he had talisman seals, magical artifacts, and spells, making him countless times stronger than the black-robed Qi cultivator I encountered in Haizhou City.

In fact, there is no comparison. This is a true orthodox Qi cultivator and Acquired martial artists have no qualifications to fight against them.

Any martial artist below Innate, when encountering an orthodox Qi cultivator, can basically only be crushed and have no power to resist. But my saber intent can instantly kill such an orthodox Qi cultivator..."

Lin Fei was also shaken by this realization.

Terrifying!

Too terrifying!

The power of the saber intent far exceeded Lin Fei's imagination. Even, the existence of Martial Dao True Intent could restrain Qi cultivators. At least, it could restrain low-level Qi cultivators.

Lin Fei raised his head and looked at the Prefect. This matter was not over yet. The Daoist was dead. But the Prefect was still there.

"Prefect, do you still think my Lin Mansion is harboring a demon?"

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back, his gaze as sharp as a saber, and calmly looked at the Prefect.

91. Big Trouble

The Prefect's face turned pale, and his hands even trembled unconsciously.

He glanced at the breathless Daoist on the ground and his eyes filled with horror.

How did the powerful and omnipotent immortal master, a Qi cultivator, die so suddenly?

"Lin... Of course, the Lin Mansion has not harbored any demons. This official must have been misled by troublemakers. However, Young Master Lin, the death of the immortal master is a serious matter, and this..."

The Prefect began to worry at this point. This was an immortal master, after all. He died in the Lin Mansion and died in Zhou Mountain Mansion City.

Could the He Mountain Dao take this lightly?

This was not just any rogue cultivator. He had a certificate of immortal cultivation. He was as orthodox an immortal master as one could be.

"Where does this Qi cultivator come from?" Lin Fei asked.

"Young Master Lin, he is an immortal master from He Mountain Dao, with a certificate of immortal cultivation on him. He Mountain Dao is one of the immortal sects recognized by the imperial court."

Lin Fei's eyebrows furrowed slightly.

He Mountain Dao?

Although he had never heard of it before, the fact that the imperial court acknowledged it meant that the other party was not some wild rogue cultivator. Instead, they were orthodox Qi cultivators, backed by a Daoist sect!

The death of a Qi cultivator was by no means a trivial matter. Lin Fei could already imagine the uproar this incident would cause.

As for covering it up?

It was simply impossible to cover it up.

Many people knew that the Daoist had come to Zhou Mountain Mansion City. Besides, so many people had witnessed him killing the Daoist today. Lin Fei couldn't possibly kill everyone present.

"Why did this Daoist want to break into the Lin Mansion?" Lin Fei continued to ask.

"The immortal master came to Zhou Mountain Mansion City because he was hunting down a demonic cultivator from the Yin Ren Mansion. Some people saw the demonic cultivator from the Yin Mansion appear on Dan Gui Street. When we arrived at Dan Gui Street, the immortal master seemed to sense some Yin Qi from the Lin Mansion, so he wanted to break in and search for the demonic cultivator from the Yin Ren Mansion. But we didn't expect that Young Master Lin would kill the immortal master..."

The Prefect truly felt that a great calamity had befallen him.

The immortal master of the He Mountain Dao was dead. Regardless of the outcome for Lin Fei in the end, He had certainly gotten himself into big trouble.

"Yin Qi..."

A thought crossed Lin Fei's mind.

He had a vague idea of why the He Mountain Daoist wanted to search the Lin Mansion. It must be the Yin Gathering Formation set up by Lin Miao.

This formation absorbed Yin Qi. The He Mountain Daoist was a Qi cultivator. Naturally, he detected the traces of Yin Qi and insisted on entering the Lin Mansion to investigate.

Moreover, Lin Fei further speculated. The reason the Yin Ren Mansion's Qi cultivator tried to ambush Lin Miao in the first place was probably that he discovered the Yin Gathering Formation set up in the Lin Mansion's side courtyard.

Otherwise, how would the Yin Ren Mansion's Qi cultivator know about Lin Miao's existence?

"It seems that the issue with the Yin-gathering Formation must be resolved. Either hide it or remove it altogether to avoid being discovered by other Qi cultivators in the future and causing more trouble."

Many thoughts flashed through Lin Fei's mind. However, the current issue was how to deal with this Daoist matter. That was the top priority.

"Prefect, take the Daoist's body back with you. Then report to the imperial court, and they will inform the people of He Mountain Dao. Remember, you must explain the whole story. The He Mountain Dao immortal master trespassed into the Lin Mansion without reason and was killed by me. Do you understand?"

Lin Fei said coldly. He was not afraid that the Prefect would not follow his instructions. The Prefect should know what was more important.

After all, the Prefect had offended the He Mountain Dao. If he didn't listen to Lin Fei now, Even if he was an official, the Prefect might not even be able to keep his whole corpse, let alone anything else.

"Yes, yes, this official understands."

The Prefect quickly nodded. Lin Fei was filled with killing intent at the moment. If he didn't agree with Lin Fei quickly, who knew what Lin Fei would do?

Even though he was the Prefect. But now, in various places of the Great Chang Dynasty, were there few Prefects who had been killed? Many officials died inexplicably.

"See the guests out!"

Lin Fei waved his hand.

Immediately, the Prefect ordered people to carry the body of the He Mountain Dao immortal master and hurriedly left the Lin Mansion. At this moment, Lin Fei's eldest brother Lin Wen and his parents quickly approached.

Lin Wen looked at the retreating figure of the Prefect and frowned, "Second Brother, you killed the immortal master of He Mountain Dao, I'm afraid this will bring no small trouble, right?"

Everyone knew that the status of immortal masters was very high. Although the Great Chang was founded on martial power, the status of immortal masters was even higher than that of martial artists.

"There will definitely be some trouble. But I'm not without background either. Behind me is the Nine Profound Sect, and my master is an innate expert! Although He Mountain Dao is an immortal sect, I didn't kill their Daoist without reason.

It was the Daoist who trespassed into the Lin Mansion first. Moreover, I have a good relationship with the Princess of the South King. When the Prefect reports to the imperial court, the princess can also use her influence in the court to put pressure on He Mountain Dao.

For just one Qi Condensation disciple, even if He Mountain Dao is dissatisfied, they probably can't do anything to me."

Lin Fei had already thought of a solution. This matter was big or small, depending on who had the stronger backing.

The Nine Profound Sect alone, Lin Fei felt, might not be enough to deter He Mountain Dao. But if he added the princess, it would be different.

The princess could represent a part of the imperial court's intentions. After all, the world still belonged to the imperial court! He Mountain Dao would certainly have some reservations.

"It's good that you have a plan, but this Prefect..."

Lin Wen was already very dissatisfied with the Prefect.

"The Prefect must be replaced and replaced with someone from our Lin family. From now on, the Lin family must control everything that happens in Zhou Mountain Mansion City! We can't let what happened today happen again. I'll leave this matter to you, Elder Brother. You just need to find a suitable candidate for the Prefect, someone who can be controlled by our Lin family. I can ask the princess to arrange for the Prefect to be replaced by our person..."

A hint of coldness in Lin Fei's eyes. If it weren't for the fact that the Prefect represented the Great Chang Dynasty. How could the Prefect have survived just now?

Although Lin Fei didn't kill the Prefect, he couldn't just let it go either. When they found someone to replace the Prefect, they would deal with the Wang family later.

Lin Fei gave many instructions. Then he went to the side courtyard.

"Hmm? Lin Miao, did you refine the Burst Qi Pill?"

Lin Fei saw that the pill furnace's fire had been extinguished. Lin Miao took out a porcelain bottle and handed it to Lin Fei.

"Young Master, I have already refined the pills, and there are five of them!"

"Five? That's not bad."

Lin Fei calculated. The raw materials cost 10,000 taels of silver. Five pills were produced. So it was equivalent to 2,000 taels of silver per pill.

Compared to the Burst Qi Pill at the Nine Profound Sect's treasure pavilion, which cost 10,000 contribution points per pill, this was already a good deal.

"Young Master, when you killed the He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator earlier, I was in the crowd. It's all my fault. I didn't know that the Yin Gathering Formation would be discovered by other Qi cultivators.

That's why Yin Ren Mansion's people targeted me, which in turn attracted He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator. And it caused such big trouble for Young Master..."

Lin Miao was a smart person. He had also heard the words of the He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator. Naturally, he could deduce that all the trouble was caused by his Yin Gathering Formation.

The Yin Gathering Formation was very conspicuous in the eyes of other Qi cultivators. As long as they got close, they would definitely be able to sense it.

The Yin Ren Mansion's Qi cultivator discovered the Yin Gathering Formation in this way. The He Mountain Dao Daoist also wanted to forcefully break into the Lin Mansion for the same reason.

"First, withdraw the Yin Gathering Formation. Before figuring out a way to hide the Yin Gathering Formation, do not set it up again. However, don't stop refining pills.

I will be leaving the Lin family for a while. But I will leave you a large amount of Burst Qi Pill raw materials. It should be enough for you to refine fifty batches of Burst Qi Pills. As for the rest, you don't need to worry about it. I will handle it."

Lin Fei gave some instructions. Originally, he planned to stay in the Lin Mansion for a while, continuously taking Burst Qi Pills. However, it seemed that he had to leave the Lin Mansion now.

He had to return to the Nine Profound Sect immediately and report this matter to his master and the sect leader. And write a letter to Princess Ling Yao, asking her to help operate and put pressure on He Mountain Dao. Only in this way can this matter be resolved!

"Qi cultivator..." Lin Fei murmured softly.

Killing a mere third level of Qi Condensation cultivator actually caused so much trouble. In fact, it was still because his strength was not enough!

When the time comes that he can kill Qi cultivators as easily as killing chickens, who would dare to cause him trouble then?

After arranging everything, Lin Fei set off overnight, heading towards the Nine Profound Sect.

92. Return to Nine Profound Sect

Inside the main hall of the Nine Profound Sect, there were only three figures at the moment.

One was Lin Fei, standing quietly there. The other two figures were sitting in chairs. One of them was the sect master. The other was Lin Fei's master, Grand Elder Zhao Kongming.

"Master, Sect Master, this is what happened. The Daoist broke into the Lin Mansion. I had no choice but to take action, and accidentally, the Daoist was killed. Later, I learned that he was a cultivator from He Mountain Dao."

As soon as Lin Fei returned to the Nine Profound Sect, he immediately went to see the Sect Master and his Master and reported in detail about his killing of the He Mountain Dao cultivator.

Of course, Lin Fei also concealed the matter of Lin Miao. He didn't want anyone to know that the Lin family had a Qi cultivator.

After all, Lin Miao was Lin Fei's alchemy tool person. He was important to Lin Fei. Lin Fei still wanted to protect Lin Miao.

When Lin Fei finished speaking, neither the Sect Master nor Zhao Kongming spoke for a long time. The entire hall fell into a silent silence.

"Lin Fei, you said that you accidentally killed the He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator when you went down the mountain this time?"

It was finally the Sect Master who asked.

"Reporting to the Sect Master, when I took action, it was indeed due to a reason. The Qi cultivator of He Mountain Dao was too arrogant and overbearing and forcefully broke into the Lin Mansion. I had no choice but to kill him."

Naturally, Lin Fei wanted to put himself in the "wronged" party.

And Qi Condensation cultivators being arrogant and overbearing was nothing new.

"It's not about that. You said you had no choice but to kill the He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator. What did you use to kill him?"

"Under the circumstances, I had to use my newly comprehended saber intent to kill him..."

"Swish."

Before his words fell, Lin Fei felt two burning gazes staring at him closely.

"Apprentice, be more specific. You killed him with your saber intent?"

"Yes, my newly comprehended saber intent..."

"Then release your saber intent, and let your master take a closer look."

Zhao Kongming's voice seemed to tremble slightly, seeming to be forcefully suppressing it.

"Saber intent."

The next moment, Lin Fei activated his saber intent.

"Boom."

Above Lin Fei's head, it seemed as if a large, illusory saber suddenly appeared.

"Buzz."

In the hall, there were many large sabers on the weapon rack. At this moment, they were all "buzzing" and trembling incessantly.

The Sect Master and Zhao Kongming both saw this scene.

"Saber intent, hahaha, it really is saber intent! Our Nine Profound Sect finally has someone who has comprehended Martial Dao True Intent. Heaven blessed our Nine Profound Sect!"

At this moment, Zhao Kongming could no longer contain himself. He couldn't help but laugh loudly. His voice was filled with endless excitement and joy.

He could never have imagined that a disciple he had just taken in not long ago had actually comprehended the Martial Dao True Intent. And it was one of the strongest attacking intents - saber intent!

Among all Martial Dao True Intents, sword intent and saber intent were undoubtedly the most powerful martial intents!

The Sect Master looked at Lin Fei with a complicated expression.

Killing a Qi cultivator of He Mountain Dao!? That was not just some rogue cultivator but a legitimate Qi cultivator of He Mountain Dao with spells, talismans, and magical artifacts.

Facing such a legitimate Qi cultivator, acquired martial artists would almost be a crushing defeat. Even the acquired peak martial artist. In front of a legitimate Qi cultivator, they would be of no use.

But Lin Fei?

He had directly killed a legitimate Qi cultivator. This was something that even the Sect Master could not achieve.

Only an innate martial artist could contend with a legitimate Qi cultivator, besides the Martial Dao True Intent!

Martial Dao True Intent was an extremely special existence among martial artists. Moreover, it was a key factor in whether a martial sect could flourish.

"Master, I killed a cultivator of He Mountain Dao. If I brought trouble to the sect, I am willing to accept punishment!"

Lin Fei's attitude was very humble.

Everyone knew martial artists had no advantage against cultivators. So when Martial sects faced Daoist sects, it was actually the same.

Born at a disadvantage.

If He Mountain Dao pressed hard, the Nine Profound Sect might not be able to withstand it.

"Punishment? Hahaha, apprentice, what fault do you have?

You killed the disciple of He Mountain Dao, so be it. It was just a Qi cultivator at the third level. Does He Mountain Dao really dare to threaten our Nine Profound Sect? Our Nine Profound Sect is, after all, a major martial sect with innate powerhouses!

He Mountain Dao has no Foundation Establishment cultivators, so what can they use to threaten our Nine Profound Sect? Besides, apprentice, you have comprehended saber intent, which makes you the future hope of our Nine Profound Sect! How could our Nine Profound Sect punish you?

You don't need to worry about this matter. I will shoulder the pressure from He Mountain Dao for you."

Zhao Kongming was now extremely happy.

If one would dare to punish Lin Fei, Zhao Kongming would be the first to disagree!

Lin Fei was really surprised. He opened his mouth, wanting to speak but hesitated.

He Mountain Dao was a major cultivation sect. The death of a Qi cultivator at the third level was not a trivial matter.

But the Nine Profound Sect not only did they show no intention of punishing him, but it seemed that they were even willing to do everything possible to protect him.

Was it because he was a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect? Or was it because of the saber intent?

However, no matter how strong saber intent was, it was only on par with innate martial artists. And when innate martial artists faced high-level Qi cultivators, they were still at a disadvantage.

Seeing the confusion in Lin Fei's eyes, the Sect Master sighed and said, "Lin Fei, you indeed acted rashly this time. It would have been fine if you killed other Qi cultivators, like the evil cultivator in Haizhou City. But you killed a Qi cultivator of He Mountain Dao.

Those cultivation sects often look down on us martial sects with arrogance. They don't take our martial sects seriously. If it had been before, the Nine Profound Sect would have protected you, but not to this extent.

However, since you have mastered saber intent, it's different. The biggest disadvantage for martial artists facing Qi cultivators is that they can't injure them.

Even if innate martial artists can use their innate true qi to break a Qi cultivator's spells or magical artifacts, it's not easy for them either, and it's even extremely difficult.

Only Martial Dao True Intent can ignore various spells and magical artifacts of Qi cultivators, even killing them without leaving a trace, making their techniques useless.

Such martial artists, if they reach the innate level, will have no weaknesses when against cultivators. Sects with disciples who have comprehended Martial Dao True Intent will also see their status rise significantly.

Lin Fei, do you now understand how valuable your saber intent is?"

Lin Fei suddenly realized.

A glint flashed in his eyes.

The power of Saber Intent was so great. It can even be without the weaknesses of other martial artists facing Qi cultivators. No wonder the Nine Profound Sect was determined to protect him.

Lin Fei would be the future hope of the Nine Profound Sect!

93. Seeking Immortality Atop Ancestral Master Peak

"Thank you, Master and Sect Master!"

Lin Fei said respectfully. He couldn't help but breathe a sigh of relief in his heart. As long as the Nine Profound Sect could help him bear the pressure from He Mountain Dao, that would be enough.

"Lin Fei, although our Nine Profound Sect does not fear He Mountain Dao, those cultivation sects are arrogant, and if they become furious, we don't know what they might do. So for the time being, don't leave the Nine Profound Sect. Wait until this matter is completely resolved, then it won't be too late to go down the mountain." The Sect Master said after pondering for a while.

This was also for Lin Fei's safety. At this time, staying in the Nine Profound Sect was the safest option.

Lin Fei was not arrogant enough to think that just because he had comprehended saber intent, he could be fearless against Qi cultivators.

Those high-level Qi Condensation cultivators, with their powerful divine sense and strong will, would not be afraid of Lin Fei's saber intent. After all, Lin Fei had just comprehended saber intent and was still in the beginner stage.

It might be effective against low-level Qi cultivators. But if he were to face some high-level Qi cultivators with a strong will, Lin Fei's saber intent might not have much effect.

"Thank you for the reminder, Sect Master. I won't leave the sect in the near future."

Lin Fei paused, then continued, "Sect Master, the matter with He Mountain Dao ultimately started because of me. I have written a letter to Senior Sister Ling Yao, asking her to use the power of the imperial court to put pressure on He Mountain Dao. I hope this will make He Mountain Dao cautious and not cause any more trouble."

The Sect Master nodded in satisfaction, "Well done, Lin Fei. It's good that you're making preparations beforehand. Although the imperial court is weak now, it still rules the world. With Ling Yao intervening as the princess, He Mountain Dao should not pursue the matter further. But as I said, don't go down the mountain yet. Wait until everything has settled down."

"Yes, Sect Master."

Having said that, Lin Fei prepared to leave.

"Follow me to a place, disciple." Master Zhao Kongming floated away.

Lin Fei also performed the Leaping Technique and followed closely behind.

This time, Zhao Kongming moved very quickly. But Lin Fei didn't fall behind. With each leap Lin Fei made, he covered a distance of more than thirty meters. Soon, the two arrived at a towering mountain peak.

Zhao Kongming stopped. He glanced at Lin Fei, a hint of surprise in his eyes.

"Leaping Technique? And if I'm not mistaken, it should be the perfection realm Leaping Technique. Otherwise, the speed wouldn't be so fast."

Zhao Kongming spoke slowly.

"Master's discerning eyes are indeed sharp; I have indeed cultivated the Leaping Technique. Furthermore, by sheer luck, I have managed to cultivate the Leaping Technique to the perfection realm."

Zhao Kongming nodded and didn't ask how Lin Fei had cultivated the Leaping Technique.

For any martial art, reaching perfection could only be achieved through fortuitous encounters and coincidences. Following the routine cultivation process was impossible to reach perfection. So, there was no point in asking.

The wind on the mountain peak was strong. It was even a bit chilly.

The whole mountain peak seemed quite empty. In the center stood a huge stone tablet.

The stone tablet seemed to have been there for many years.

It had been weathered by the wind and sun, with some parts even eroded away.

"My disciple, do you know what this place is?" Zhao Kongming asked.

"I don't know," Lin Fei shook his head.

He had only just been promoted to the inner sect a short while ago. At most, it had only been a few months. He didn't even know many places within the inner sect, let alone this desolate mountain peak.

Zhao Kongming's expression became serious, and he spoke solemnly, "This is Ancestral Master Peak. As the name implies, this is the mountain peak where the founder of our Nine Profound Sect once lived.

After the founder's death, he was also buried on this mountain peak. The founder was extraordinarily talented and stepped into the martial path with a very ordinary basic martial art. Overcoming all obstacles along the way, he ultimately achieved the status of an innate grandmaster!

An innate martial artist must reach the true limit of great perfection in order to be called a grandmaster! Since the founder of our Nine Profound Sect, there has been no other martial arts grandmaster.

How extraordinary was our founder's talent? He excelled in fist, sword, and saber techniques, comprehending fist intent, sword intent, and saber intent, and even reached perfection in all three martial arts!

With his unparalleled martial arts, the founder dominated the world. From Foundation Establishment cultivators and below, he was unmatched. Even those Qi cultivators, no matter how strong their magical artifacts or how profound their spiritual power, were all insignificant and easily defeated in front of the founder!

At that time, the Nine Profound Sect was at its most prosperous! All disciples of the Nine Profound Sect took pride in this, and no one thought that martial arts were inferior.

Qi cultivators didn't dare to provoke the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect. Hahaha, that was the glory of our Nine Profound Sect and the martial arts world!"

Lin Fei listened with surging emotions. He seemed to envision the founder of the Nine Profound Sect.

Striding across the world, displaying his unparalleled style. Whether it was martial artists or Qi cultivators, whether it was magical artifacts or spells, all were insignificant.

No martial artist could rival an Immortal Master. In front of the Nine Profound Sect's founder, it was a completely different situation. Martial arts practice to the extreme was also terrifying!

Lin Fei had comprehended the saber intent. Therefore, he knew how difficult it was to comprehend it. Moreover, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect excelled in saber, sword, and fist techniques and had comprehended three intents.

Such a person was truly unparalleled in his time. Anyone in front of the founder of the Nine Profound Sect would pale in comparison.

"Our founder was unparalleled, and no one could match him! With the body of a mere martial artist, he dominated the world. Without Foundation Establishment cultivators, the founder was invincible!

Unfortunately, even though the founder dominated the world and had profound martial arts cultivation, he still died. In the end, he couldn't resist the passage of time.

Finally, the founder only left behind a stone tablet. On the stone tablet, there were no martial arts techniques. Instead, it contained Martial Dao True Intent left by the founder. Sword intent, saber intent, and fist intent were all left within the stone tablet.

Whenever someone in the Nine Profound Sect comprehends Martial Dao True Intent, they can come to the founder's stone tablet and sharpen their own Intent with the help of the founder's Martial Dao True Intent."

Lin Fei understood.

His master had brought him here to let Lin Fei refine his saber intent.

Gazing at the towering stone tablet before him, Lin Fei's saber intent erupted instantaneously.

"Om."

The next moment, as if stimulated by Lin Fei's saber intent, terrifying fist intent, sword intent, and saber intent erupted from the stone tablet.

These three Martial Dao True Intents were too powerful. Far surpassing Lin Fei's saber intent.

The mere fact that they had remained in the stone tablet for so many years without dispersing was something that the current Lin Fei couldn't achieve.

These three Martial Dao True Intents seemed to let Lin Fei "see" the unparalleled founder of the Nine Profound Sect.

A fist that could shake mountains and rivers.

A sword that could cleave opens a great river.

A saber that could shatter the void.

However, such an extraordinary person still died. He died an old man atop this desolate mountain.

Lin Fei felt a trace of sadness in his heart.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei withdrew his saber intent.

He looked at Zhao Kongming and asked solemnly, "Master, you once told me that martial arts could grant eternal life! Why couldn't such an extraordinary and peerless figure like the founder achieve immortality?"

94. Fist Intent

"Immortality..."

Zhao Kongming murmured softly.

Then, he sighed deeply, "Indeed, the Martial Dao can grant immortality. However, achieving immortality through the Martial Dao is difficult! Extremely difficult! Even harder than reaching the heavens!"

Lin Fei frowned. Of course, he knew it was difficult. There were so many people in the world. If it were easy, wouldn't everyone be immortal? That was simply impossible!

Nevertheless, no matter how difficult, Lin Fei was confident.

"Please enlighten me, Master. How can one achieve immortality through the Martial Dao?"

Lin Fei asked solemnly. This had always been his doubt.

Martial artists practiced their skills, inner power, and true qi, step by step. Since none of these could grant immortality, how could the Martial Dao lead to immortality?

Zhao Kongming glanced at Lin Fei, and a faint smile appeared on his lips as he slowly said, "I didn't tell you before because I feared you would aim too high and lose more than you gained. However, since you've comprehended the saber intent, which is comparable to the innate realm, there's no harm in telling you.

Martial artists are divided into Body Refining, Acquired, and Innate. Body Refining refines one's blood, muscles, and skin, enhancing physical qualities. Acquired cultivates inner power, while Innate cultivates true qi. Neither inner power nor true qi can grant immortality.

The reason lies in our bodies, which are merely mortal flesh. According to Qi cultivators, they are mundane. To attain immortality, one must transcend the mundane. At the very least, the body must not be composed of mortal flesh.

When a martial artist reaches Innate Perfection, or the Grand Master realm, no matter how much they practice, their true qi has reached its limit, and even their body has reached its limit, unable to advance.

At this point, we must build our foundation, transforming our bodies. The so-called foundation building is the establishment of the foundation for immortality.

Qi cultivators build the foundation for the Immortal Dao, while we martial artists build the foundation for the Martial Dao. Once the foundation is successfully built, both martial artists and Qi cultivators will undergo a rebirth, gaining extended lifespans.

Those who succeed in building their foundation will have a lifespan of at least several hundred years!"

A glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

He murmured to himself, "Foundation building, the foundation of the immortal Dao, and the foundation of the Martial Dao. Both are the basis for immortality. So that's how it is..."

Lin Fei understood. He understood completely.

Whether a martial artist or a Qi cultivator must build the foundation to achieve immortality. Otherwise, they would remain mortal flesh, forever unable to attain immortality.

"Since one can build their foundation, why couldn't the founder achieve immortality?" Lin Fei asked again.

"Yes, everyone knows that building one's foundation can lead to immortality. But, how many can actually do it? Those Qi cultivators, high and mighty. Do you really think it's because they have magical artifacts and spells?

Actually, it's not. Qi cultivators look down on martial artists simply because it's relatively easier for them to build their foundation compared to us. Qi cultivators study the Dao, nature, and the universe. They have created miraculous elixirs like the Foundation Establishment Pill.

By taking the Foundation Establishment Pill, Qi cultivators can make up for some of their shortcomings, thus successfully building their foundation. This is what they call seizing the fortunes of heaven and earth.

From this perspective, Qi cultivators truly do seize the fortunes of heaven and earth. But it's different for us martial artists. If martial artist wants to build their foundation, they can only rely on their own strength, unable to use external aids.

Martial artists attribute all their power to themselves. Building their foundation is inherently more difficult than it is for Qi cultivators, and they don't have access to miraculous elixirs like the Foundation Establishment Pill.

Over time, there have been almost no successful martial artists in building their foundation. Among the Qi cultivators, although the success rate of building their foundation is also low, there have always been successful individuals.

Therefore, as one side wanes and the other waxes, the rise of the Immortal Dao and the decline of the Martial Dao can be foreseen."

Zhao Kongming spoke with a hint of lament.

It made sense. Building the foundation of the Martial Dao was too difficult. Even someone as outstanding as the Nine Profound Sect's founder failed to achieve a successful foundation building in the end, not to mention others.

A martial artist who successfully built their foundation would be a Martial Saint!

Becoming a saint with a mortal body, indestructible, and eternally present in the world! At that time, the martial artist would be incredibly powerful. They could even defeat an immortal cultivator who had built their foundation!

"Martial Saint..."

Lin Fei suddenly raised his head. He looked at the distant stone tablet.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei stepped forward. Using the Leaping Technique, he reached the stone tablet almost instantly.

Lin Fei gently stroked the stone tablet. The weathered stone tablet felt cold to the touch. But in Lin Fei's mind, the unparalleled elegance of the Nine Profound Sect's founder seemed to emerge.

It was a pity that the founder of the Nine Profound Sect, who was invincible in his lifetime, failed to build his foundation successfully. He was only a step away from becoming a Martial Saint.

Yet, it was this one step that had stopped countless outstanding martial artists in their tracks.

"Exhausting one's entire life, still unable to build the foundation...Ancestral Master, you left behind three strands of Martial Dao True Intent, wanting to cultivate the younger generation.

You hoped that a martial artist could successfully build their foundation. As your disciple, Lin Fei, I will definitely fulfill your long-cherished wish. I will build the foundation of martial arts, display the power of martial arts, and stand proudly in this world!"

"Boom."

At this moment, Lin Fei's conviction exploded. He had never doubted that he could achieve immortality. As long as martial arts could lead to immortality, he would definitely reach that step.

Therefore, with unwavering conviction, Lin Fei's saber intent surged. The saber intent, fist intent, and sword intent on the stone tablet also erupted. All enveloping Lin Fei's body.

Suddenly, Lin Fei felt immense pressure. The founder's fist intent was at the level of perfection. It contained everything. It was the founder's comprehension of the fist technique.

Similarly, the sword intent and saber intent were the same. They contained countless sword techniques, saber techniques, and so on.

Fortunately, the Nine Profound Sect's founder had no ill intent. Otherwise, these three strands of Martial Dao True Intent would even be enough to suppress an innate martial artist!

And now, these three strands of Martial Dao True Intent were honing Lin Fei's saber intent. Even more, it wasn't just the saber intent. There was also the fist intent.

Lin Fei closed his eyes and sat cross-legged. In his mind, the Quadruple Wave Technique appeared. It was like a violent wave.

But at this moment, the founder's fist intent surrounded the Quadruple Wave Technique. Then, it seemed like countless fist techniques were demonstrated to the Quadruple Wave Technique.

Immediately after, Lin Fei's mind heard the system's voice.

"Your Quadruple Wave Technique is being ravaged by the fist intent of the perfection realm, feeling depressed, in unbearable pain, and unwilling to cultivate."

The voice in Lin Fei's mind made him slightly stunned. The Quadruple Wave Technique was unwilling to cultivate?

In his mind, Lin Fei could "see" it.

The Quadruple Wave Technique was indeed tragic, ravaged by the perfection realm's fist intent, without any power to resist.

However, it was so badly ravaged that the Quadruple Wave Technique had become unwilling to cultivate.

Isn't this a bit counterproductive?

But soon, Lin Fei's mind heard the system's voice again.

"Your Quadruple Wave Technique was defeated by the fist intent, realized its own shortcomings, became determined to make up for them, and increased its cultivation progress by 10%."

"Your Quadruple Wave Technique was stimulated by the perfection realm's fist intent and decided to strive harder, raising its cultivation progress by 10%."

"Your Quadruple Wave Technique has fallen into sudden enlightenment..."

Lin Fei remained motionless in front of the stone tablet. The system's voice kept ringing in his mind, one after another.

Lin Fei didn't pay any attention to it.

10%, 20%, 30%, 40%, 50%...

Finally, Lin Fei's Quadruple Wave Technique's cultivation progress increased by 50%.

Adding the original 50%, the cultivation progress of the Quadruple Wave Technique reached 100%.

"Boom."

The next moment, in Lin Fei's mind, the wave transformed by the Quadruple Wave Technique suddenly expanded. At the same time, an earth-shattering momentum burst out from Lin Fei's body. Vaguely, a huge fist seemed to appear above Lin Fei's head!

"Fist intent!"

Zhao Kongming suddenly looked up, staring at the top of Lin Fei's head.

His heart was filled with immense shock!

95. Good News

A note from RighteousEgg

Ah, my bad, messed up the chapter order.

At this moment, Lin Fei had indeed comprehended fist intent.

His Quadruple Wave Technique had already reached 50% in cultivation progress. Now, it was even more honed by the perfection realm fist intent left by the Nine Profound Sect's founder, reaching 100% in cultivation and giving birth to fist intent.

It couldn't be more normal. Lin Fei had anticipated this.

What was perfectly normal in Lin Fei's view, however, was anything but normal in Zhao Kongming's eyes. It was even shocking!

Zhao Kongming originally thought that Lin Fei only had talent in saber techniques. That was why he was able to comprehend saber intent.

He brought Lin Fei to the Ancestral Master Peak to also hone Lin Fei's saber intent to make it stronger.

But now what?

Lin Fei had comprehended fist intent in just a few hours on the Ancestral Master Peak. Moreover, this fist intent was vast and boundless. Just like waves, one after another, seemingly never-ending.

This was an incredibly powerful fist intent!

"He not only comprehended saber intent but now also comprehended fist intent. Could it be that he is a top martial arts genius like the founder?"

Zhao Kongming's heart was shaken. He thought of a possibility.

Initially, the Nine Profound Sect's founder excelled in saber, sword, and fist techniques. He comprehended three kinds of Martial Dao True Intent! This was the true pinnacle of martial arts genius.

For an ordinary martial artist, to comprehend one kind of Martial Dao True Intent would be extremely fortunate. Even if they spent their entire life, they might not be able to cultivate it to perfection.

However, the Nine Profound Sect's founder cultivated all three kinds of Martial Dao True Intent to perfection. Such talent was simply despair-inducing.

Now, Lin Fei was the same. The talent he displayed made even Zhao Kongming feel somewhat desperate.

"Swish."

Lin Fei opened his eyes. A trace of fierceness seemed to flash in his eyes.

"Fist intent!"

Lin Fei, of course, knew that he had comprehended fist intent.

Even in his mind, not only had the Quadruple Wave Technique been honed, receiving huge benefits, and comprehending fist intent, but the saber intent had also been continuously honed, making significant progress.

"Your saber intent fought against the perfection realm saber intent, and although your saber intent was defeated, it kept fighting and increased the cultivation progress by 10%."

In Lin Fei's mind, that group of saber intent was continuously expanding and improving with the honing.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately summoned the system.

Instantly, the system panel appeared in front of Lin Fei.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Realm: Acquired Fifth Level

Saber Intent: Beginner (Progress 11%)

Fist Intent: Beginner (Progress 5%)

Three Vitality Technique: Fifth Level (Progress 63%)

Leaping Technique: Perfection (Progress 0%)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

On Lin Fei's system panel, there was indeed an additional "Fist Intent." But the "Quadruple Wave Technique" had disappeared.

Of course, it wasn't that the Quadruple Wave Technique could no longer be used. Lin Fei could still use the Quadruple Wave Technique. As long as Lin Fei had learned a martial art, he could naturally use it.

It was just that the Quadruple Wave Technique had reached its limit and disappeared from the system panel to avoid occupying the system panel's space.

Otherwise, with so many martial arts Lin Fei had practiced displaying on the panel, it would make the panel look very bloated and complicated.

Under the honing of the three Martial Dao True Intents inside the stele, Lin Fei's saber intent and fist intent both improved very quickly.

"Disciple, it seems you've gained something on Ancestral Master Peak."

Seeing Lin Fei open his eyes, Zhao Kongming also spoke.

"Master, the founder's three Martial Dao True Intents have been of great help to me. I want to stay on Ancestral Master Peak for a while. So that my fist intent and saber intent can be honed by the founder's Martial Dao True Intent stronger!"

Lin Fei made a request. He didn't even want to leave Ancestral Master Peak. He wanted to be constantly stimulated by the Martial Dao True Intent on the stele to rapidly improve his own Martial Dao True Intent.

Zhao Kongming nodded and said, "Of course, that's not a problem. Ancestral Master Peak has always been empty. If you want to stay, just stay. However, you can't damage anything here."

"I understand, Master. Thank you!"

"Alright, you can stay on Ancestral Master Peak, I'll go back."

Zhao Kongming went down the mountain and returned to his cave dwelling.

Lin Fei stayed on Ancestral Master Peak.

Days passed one by one.

One day, two days, three days...

In the blink of an eye, more than a month had passed.

"Disciple."

One day, Zhao Kongming arrived at Ancestral Master Peak.

"Master."

Lin Fei respectfully greeted him.

Zhao Kongming smiled and said, "Good news. With the efforts of our Nine Profound Sect and Princess Ling Yao, He Mountain Dao has decided not to pursue your responsibility. So, you can now leave the mountain or stay on the mountain without any problems."

Lin Fei nodded, "Indeed, it's good news. But, would He Mountain Dao let go so easily? After all, their disciple has died."

Lin Fei felt that He Mountain Dao shouldn't be so indifferent, with no reaction at all.

"Who said He Mountain Dao let go easily?"

Zhao Kongming said solemnly, "He Mountain Dao has vented their anger. Your Zhou Mountain Mansion City's prefect was imprisoned by the court, and it won't be long before he's executed.

Moreover, the court promised to crack down on Yin Ren Mansion. This is He Mountain Dao's sworn enemy. And the court's promise to suppress Yin Ren Mansion is all thanks to Princess Ling Yao's mediation."

Lin Fei suddenly understood, so that's how it was. He Mountain Dao indeed lost a disciple. But their real enemy was Yin Ren Mansion.

He Mountain Dao had once destroyed Yin Ren Mansion. However, in recent years, Yin Ren Mansion had been resurrected.

He Mountain Dao naturally felt uneasy, so they hunted down the Qi Condensation cultivators of Yin Ren Mansion everywhere.

But even so, Yin Ren Mansion still couldn't be wiped out completely. However, with the court's help this time, He Mountain Dao might be able to completely eliminate the remnants of Yin Ren Mansion.

So, He Mountain Dao had made a profit. After all, the Qi Condensation cultivator Lin Fei killed was just a third-level disciple. He wasn't an important figure in He Mountain Dao.

"By the way, there's a letter from Ling Yao for you."

Zhao Kongming took out the letter.

"Thank you, Master."

Zhao Kongming didn't stay on Ancestral Master Peak for long and returned to his cave dwelling.

Lin Fei opened Ling Yao's letter.

The content of the letter was quite simple. It was mainly Ling Yao's reply to Lin Fei, saying that she had used all her connections and pressured He Mountain Dao. The problem was basically solved.

Finally, the letter included a request from Ling Yao. The royal family competition had already been scheduled. It would take place in two months. Therefore, Ling Yao hoped that Lin Fei could visit Chang City in two months and lend her a helping hand.

After reading the contents of the letter, Lin Fei understood.

Although Ling Yao made it sound simple, in fact, she must have put in a lot of effort to settle the He Mountain Dao matter.

This time Ling Yao went to great lengths to settle the He Mountain Dao issue and resolved Lin Fei's trouble. Naturally, Lin Fei had to repay Ling Yao.

"Two months, huh?"

Lin Fei slowly stood up.

After being honed by the three strands of Martial Dao True Intent left by the Ancestral Master on the Ancestral Master Peak.

Lin Fei's saber intent and fist intent had advanced by leaps and bounds.

In just over a month, Lin Fei's saber intent and fist intent had both crossed the beginner stage and reached mastery!

However, the more Martial Dao True Intent on the stone tablet was used, the less there was.

After Lin Fei's fist intent and saber intent both reached minor accomplishments, the Ancestral Master's Martial Dao True Intent was not as helpful to Lin Fei as before.

The progress was now slow, staying on the mountain would only consume the Martial Dao True Intent within the stone tablet.

Lin Fei's Three Vitality Technique had also been diligent on the Ancestral Master Peak.

He didn't take any Burst Qi Pills and spent more than a month to reach the sixth level. That is to say, Lin Fei had now reached the acquired sixth level.

However, this acquired sixth level was far from enough. Lin Fei's goal was to build the foundation of Martial Dao and achieve longevity!

He was now merely at the acquired sixth level. Not even innate yet, let alone building the foundation of Martial Dao and achieving longevity.

"It seems I need to return to the Lin family. I wonder if Lin Miao has refined all fifty furnaces of Burst Qi Pills? If they are all refined, then with the Burst Qi Pills, my Three Vitality Technique cultivation speed will definitely advance rapidly!"

Lin Fei hesitated no more. He immediately stood up and left Ancestral Master Peak. He rented a fast horse and quickly descended the mountain.

96. Acquired Eighth Level

Lin Family, the side courtyard.

Upon returning to the Lin family, Lin Fei immediately sought out Lin Miao.

"Lin Miao, how's the refining of the Burst Qi Pills coming along?"

"Young Master, after you left, I've been refining Burst Qi Pills every day, and I've finally finished all fifty furnaces of Burst Qi Pills. Even the efficiency has improved a bit; one furnace of Burst Qi Pills now yields not just five but around six pills. So, there are a total of three hundred and eight Burst Qi Pills, all stored in these porcelain bottles."

Lin Fei followed Lin Miao's gaze. The table was covered with densely packed white porcelain bottles. There were dozens of bottles.

"Lin Miao, you've done a great job. However, it seems you haven't dismantled your Yin Gathering Formation yet?"

Lin Fei's eyes turned cold. Upon entering, he had already sensed the place was still filled with chilling Yin Qi. Clearly, Lin Miao hadn't removed the Yin Gathering Formation.

Lin Fei remembered that he had instructed him very clearly to remove the Yin Gathering Formation.

"Thud."

Lin Miao immediately knelt on the ground.

With a trace of panic on his face, he quickly explained, "Young Master, I removed the Yin Gathering Formation after you left. However, after removing the Yin Gathering Formation, my spiritual power couldn't sustain the refining of Burst Qi Pills.

My spiritual power has indeed increased a lot, even reaching the first level of Qi Condensation. But the refining of Burst Qi Pills consumes a lot of spiritual power. So, I had no choice but to rely on the support of the Yin Gathering Formation to barely refine the Burst Qi Pills.

But don't worry, Young Master. Remember the cultivation manuals and secret scrolls I found on that Yin Ren Mansion's Qi cultivator? Among them were some Formation formations. I chose two types of formations, the Concealment Formation and the Concealing Breath Formation, to wrap the Yin Gathering Formation within.

From the outside, the Lin residence looks the same as any other place, with no trace of Yin Qi. Only by coming to the side courtyard and observing carefully can one see the Yin Gathering Formation in place."

Lin Fei looked at Lin Miao. He knew he wouldn't dare lie. Setting up two more formations outside the Yin Gathering Formation, which was indeed quite cautious.

"Alright, remember, we need to keep a low profile now. Although the matter with He Mountain Dao has been dealt with, I don't want any more unnecessary trouble in the future, understand?"

Lin Miao hurriedly nodded, "Rest assured, Young Master, I'll be even more careful and cautious in the future, not causing trouble for the Lin family or for you."

Lin Fei still had quite some trust in Lin Miao.

"Alright, you continue your cultivation, strive to reach the second level or even the third level as soon as possible. As for your incomplete cultivation techniques, if you diligently refine pills for me and help me with my affairs, I will make up for it in the future."

Lin Fei also gave Lin Miao a glimmer of hope.

"Thank you, Young Master!"

Lin Miao was overjoyed in his heart.

Although Lin Fei was a martial artist, Lin Miao didn't dare to underestimate him at all. Lin Fei was someone who easily killed a legitimate Qi cultivator at the third level.

Saying he would complete Lin Miao's techniques, which wasn't boasting. He truly had the strength to do so.

Back in his room. Lin Fei specifically instructed the Lin family members that he would be in seclusion and that no one was allowed to disturb him.

Lin Fei took out a Burst Qi Pill. He began to take it.

"Boom."

As always, Lin Fei's inner power skyrocketed.

"Your Three Vitality Technique has consumed a Burst Qi Pill, causing it to feel restless and agitated, and begins to forcefully open up your meridians."

"Your Three Vitality Technique's cultivation progress has increased by 2%, and your meridians are at risk of damage."

The voice of the system echoed in Lin Fei's mind. Just like before, one Burst Qi Pill increased the cultivation progress of the Three Vitality Technique by 2%.

As for the risk of meridian damage, it wasn't really a big deal. It was just some pill poison.

It would only take twelve hours for the Three Vitality Technique to naturally clear all the pill poison.

In this way, Lin Fei could take two Burst Qi Pills every day, increasing his cultivation progress by 4%.

One day, five days, ten days...

Time passed day by day. Soon, fifty days had passed.

"Your Three Vitality Technique has consumed a Burst Qi Pill, causing it to feel restless and agitated..."

"Your Three Vitality Technique has advanced to the eighth level!"

The voice of the system echoed in Lin Fei's mind again.

For a full fifty days, Lin Fei had been taking Burst Qi Pills every day. His Three Vitality Technique was improving every moment. As a result, Lin Fei's speed of opening up his meridians was astonishingly fast.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei opened his eyes.

"System."

He called up the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Eighth Level

Saber Intent: Mastery (11% Progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (5% Progress)

Three Vitality Technique: Eighth Level (2% Progress)

Leaping Technique: Perfection (0% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

During these fifty days, Lin Fei consumed a total of 100 Burst Qi Pills. As a result, his Three Vitality Technique directly advanced from the sixth level to the eighth level...

The progress could be described as incredibly fast! Moreover, even after reaching the eighth level. Lin Fei's Three Vitality Technique's cultivation progress did not slow down.

In other words, the Burst Qi Pills could be used continuously for a long time. At least, Lin Fei still had 208 Burst Qi Pills left.

If he consumed them all and if the effect didn't diminish, Lin Fei could even reach the acquired tenth level!

"Perhaps after reaching the acquired tenth level, the effect of Burst Qi Pills will weaken. But there should still be some effect. So, the production of Burst Qi Pills should continue."

Although Lin Fei still had more than two hundred Burst Qi Pills, It was better to be prepared. The Burst Qi Pills must continue to be refined.

However, Burst Qi Pills required silver. A large amount of silver.

Lin Fei thought for a moment and decided not to continue his seclusion. After all, it had been fifty days now. There wasn't much time left before the two-month agreement with Ling Yao.

Naturally, Lin Fei couldn't break his promise. Moreover, Lin Fei also wanted the royal family's Heavenly Meridian Pill. At least, it could help Lin Fei reach the peak of acquired twelfth level. It could save Lin Fei a lot of time.

However, before leaving for Chang City. Lin Fei went to see his eldest brother, Lin Wen. He asked for five hundred thousand taels of silver from his brother.

This was a large sum. However, Lin Wen still readily agreed.

In the Lin family now, the one who appeared to be in charge on the surface was Lin Wen. But in reality, everyone knew that the Lin family's current position was all because of Lin Fei.

So, when Lin Fei needed silver for his martial arts training, the Lin family naturally gave their full support.

With five hundred thousand taels of silver, Lin Fei bought the ingredients for another fifty furnaces of Burst Qi Pills.

"It shouldn't take too long to go to Chang City. At most, it will take two or three months. Lin Miao, you must refine the Burst Qi Pills at the fastest speed!"

Lin Fei instructed Lin Miao.

He told Lin Miao to go ahead and refine the Burst Qi Pills. By the time Lin Fei returned from Chang City, perhaps he could harvest another 300 Burst Qi Pills.

"Young Master, rest assured, I will do my best to refine the pills."

Lin Fei nodded. He didn't linger any longer. After bidding farewell to his parents and elder brother, Lin Fei mounted his horse and once again headed toward Chang City.

97. Royal Competition

In six days, Lin Fei arrived at Chang City once again.

Although it had only been a few months since his last visit to Chang City, his changes in these few months could be described as earth-shattering. It was incomparable to a few months ago.

Moreover, during these six days of travel, Lin Fei had not been idle. He still consumed two Burst Qi Pills every day.

Three Vitality Technique was tenacious in character and constantly working hard to cultivate. Thus, during these few days. The cultivation progress of Lin Fei's Three Vitality Technique was steadily improving.

"Lin Fei, you're finally here!"

At the South King Mansion, Lin Fei met Ling Yao.

Ling Yao, who had been a princess for a few months. Her temperament had undergone obvious changes. She had become graceful and luxurious, seemingly no different from other noble ladies.

In the past, Ling Yao was one of the top geniuses in the Nine Profound Sect. She had a strong martial artist aura. But now, it was gone. However, this was Ling Yao's own choice.

Behind Ling Yao, there were also several martial artists. They should all be martial artists newly recruited by Ling Yao. After all, Ling Yao might also have to face competition from others for the position of the princess. She couldn't always rely on Lin Fei to take the stage. Therefore, Ling Yao naturally cultivated her own forces.

"Lin Fei, let me introduce them to you. This is You Shaotian, an acquired seventh-level expert. His Astonishing Cloud Sword Technique makes him extremely powerful!

This is Batu Ganbu, a secret sect expert. Acquired sixth level, and his strength is also extraordinary.

This is..."

Ling Yao introduced them one by one to Lin Fei. Lin Fei simply nodded in acknowledgment.

Among the experts Ling Yao recruited, only You Shaotian and Batu Ganbu could be considered as talents.

As for the others, Lin Fei didn't even remember their names.

Although Lin Fei's expression was calm and somewhat proud, You Shaotian and Batu Ganbu dared not to be negligent.

Since they had joined Ling Yao, they naturally knew about Ling Yao's past. It was with Lin Fei's help that Ling Yao defeated the previous princess and won the position.

Last time, Lin Fei was able to defeat two acquired seventh-level experts.

They couldn't say for sure that they could defeat two acquired seventh-level martial artists. Especially one with a sword technique at perfection, which could even rival a great expert at the acquired ninth level. As a result, they were defeated by Lin Fei's saber. In front of Lin Fei, they dared not to be arrogant.

So, they all bowed and said, "Greetings, Young Master Lin!"

"We have long heard of the Young Master's ability to defeat two acquired seventh-level experts with a single saber."

"We are all very impressed by the Young Master's martial arts and strength!"

You Shaotian took a humble attitude.

Lin Fei didn't answer, but turned his gaze to Ling Yao and asked directly, "Senior Sister Ling, when will the Royal Competition begin?"

"In three days, the Royal Competition will begin. Lin Fei, your timing is just right."

Ling Yao paused and said to You Shaotian and the others, "You can go now."

"Yes, Your Highness the Princess."

Then, You Shaotian and the others left one after another. In the living room, only Lin Fei and Ling Yao remained.

"Lin Fei, what do you think of these people?" Ling Yao suddenly asked.

Lin Fei thought for a moment and slowly said, "They can be defeated with a single slash!"

"Uh..." Ling Yao shook her head helplessly and said, "I'm not asking how they compare to you but to ordinary martial artists. You've comprehended saber intent and killed a Qi cultivator from He Mountain Dao with it. Who can compare to you?"

Ling Yao, of course, knew Lin Fei's "details." After all, the last time Lin Fei asked for Ling Yao's help to jointly pressure He Mountain Dao. Finally, they resolved Lin Fei's trouble.

"Compared to ordinary martial artists, they're not bad. However, if you want to rely on these people to maintain your position as princess, I'm afraid it will be difficult."

Lin Fei didn't mince his words and spoke directly.

"Of course, I know I can't rely on them alone. Isn't there still you? If we really encounter a powerful competitor, having you take action will surely be reliable!"

A smile appeared on Ling Yao's face. If she had any worries before, now Ling Yao had no concerns at all.

Her position as a princess would definitely be very secure. The reason was naturally Lin Fei's presence. Lin Fei, who had comprehended saber intent, was comparable to an innate martial artist!

Even South King hadn't broken through to innate. This showed how important innate martial artists were.

With Lin Fei's support, why would Ling Yao worry about losing her position as a princess?

"Tell me about this Royal Competition. Are there any difficult opponents?"

Lin Fei was more concerned about the Royal Competition. Moreover, he had to fight for the top three.

Because only the top three could get the Heavenly Meridian Pill.

This Heavenly Meridian Pill was something Lin Fei was determined to obtain!

"Difficult opponents..."

Ling Yao frowned and said, "This time's Royal Competition seems a bit different. In the past, the helpers invited by the royal family members were mostly martial artists. But this time, as far as I know, many helpers around the royal family members have actually become Qi cultivators, and they are orthodox Qi cultivators."

"Huh? Qi cultivators?"

"Qi cultivators shouldn't be interested in the Heavenly Meridian Pill. So, what is the purpose of these Qi cultivators participating in the Royal Competition?"

Lin Fei's brows furrowed slightly. He had seen quite a few Qi cultivators and had dealt with them as well.

These Qi cultivators were generally arrogant and proud. They considered themselves above the mundane and believed they were worlds apart from ordinary people.

Therefore, under normal circumstances, they would not stay with ordinary people. Even royal family members were still considered mundane in the eyes of Qi cultivators.

The mere Heavenly Meridian Pill was useless to Qi cultivators. How could they possibly travel a long distance to help royal family members participate in the Royal Competition?

"I also find it very strange. So I asked around and finally consulted my father. In the end, my father told me the reason.

The top three in this Royal Competition will not only be rewarded with Heavenly Meridian Pills. Moreover, the royal family will open a secret realm, allowing the top three in the Royal Competition to enter it."

"A secret realm?"

This was the first time Lin Fei had heard of it.

If it could attract so many orthodox Qi cultivators to compete in the Royal Competition, this secret realm must not be simple.

"Yes, the secret realm, even I heard about it for the first time.

Originally, the Great Chang founding emperor established the nation with martial arts and suppressed the world with supreme martial arts! This secret realm was captured by the founding emperor and became a secret realm of our royal family!

In the secret realm, there are some extremely precious spiritual herbs, which can even be used to refine Foundation Establishment Pills. That's why it attracted countless Qi cultivators."

Whether they are orthodox Qi cultivators or rogue cultivators, they have all gathered in Chang City now. They are waiting for the Royal Competition to begin, competing for the top three spots, and the qualification to enter the secret realm!"

Lin Fei's heart trembled.

Spiritual herbs capable of refining Foundation Establishment Pills.

No wonder Qi cultivators came to the royal family members' side.

Their goal was probably to enter the secret realm to obtain the spiritual herbs needed to refine Foundation Establishment Pills.

"Wait a minute, the secret realm is the royal family's secret realm. The spiritual herbs in the secret realm are also all owned by the royal family. Why would the royal family want to 'give away' such precious Foundation Establishment Pill herbs in this way?"

A hint of unusual light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. Perhaps, the royal family's possessions were not so easy to obtain.

98. If I unsheathe my saber, you will die!

Ling Yao fell silent for a while. Then she slowly said, "Perhaps, it's to look for talents."

"Talents?"

Lin Fei raised his eyebrows, not quite understanding.

"Yes, talents. Lin Fei, maybe you don't know the current situation of the royal family. All over Great Chang, there are natural disasters and man-made calamities, unrest everywhere, and the situation is unstable.

The royal family no longer has the ability to suppress the world. Now, the royal family is using the Royal Competition to attract some rogue cultivators, probably to win them over and have them serve the royal family.

After all, for a rogue cultivator to obtain a Foundation Establishment Pill, how difficult is that? But if they are favored by the royal family, it's a different story.

Of course, even if the royal family is short of talent, they only need top-notch geniuses. So the Royal Competition can basically show whether those rogue cultivators have potential worth cultivating."

Lin Fei understood.

This Royal Competition, to put it bluntly, was actually a smokescreen. The gimmick of entering the secret realm was just to attract some rogue Qi cultivators. These rogue Qi cultivators were not recognized by other immortal sects. But maybe some top-notch geniuses were worth cultivating.

If they could cultivate a Foundation Establishment expert, no matter the cost, it would be worth it.

"I see. So, in fact, we martial artists are just background. The real goal of the royal family is those rogue Qi cultivators."

Lin Fei completely understood. However, he didn't care. His goal was the Heavenly Meridian Pill.

"Lin Fei, martial artists are not entirely just background. If we manage to win the qualification to enter the secret realm and you don't want to enter the secret realm, you can exchange this quota for some resources."

"Really? It can exchange people?" Lin Fei was somewhat surprised.

"Of course, strictly speaking, you martial artists or Qi cultivators are not qualified to participate in the Royal Competition. After all, you are not royal family members and do not have royal blood. You are participating in the Royal Competition as a follower.

And this follower status can be changed by the royal family members at any time. At that time, if you don't want to enter the secret realm, you can 'exchange' your quota.

After all, there's no danger in the secret realm. I guess I don't need to tell you the usefulness of this quota. You can almost trade it for anything you want."

Lin Fei understood.

In fact, compared to the Heavenly Meridian Pill, this quota to enter the secret realm was the most important.

Once this quota was obtained, not to mention one Heavenly Meridian Pill, even ten Heavenly Meridian Pills could be exchanged for.

"Since that's the case, I'll take the top three spots in the Royal Competition!"

Lin Fei said indifferently. His tone was calm, but it revealed incredible confidence!

"Lin Fei, don't be careless! High-level Qi cultivators may not necessarily fear your saber intent. However, this time, there seem to be no Qi cultivators above the seventh level."

The royal family isn't stupid. Those orthodox Qi cultivators, send some low-level Qi cultivators to participate, just as a gesture. High-level Qi cultivators wanting to freeload on the royal family's resources, how is that possible?"

Lin Fei nodded. Qi cultivators above the seventh level were called high-level Qi cultivators. Such Qi cultivators, within the immortal sects, were also considered the core strength.

Basically, when the immortal sects need to deal with very important matters, it was handled by Qi cultivators above the seventh level.

Those high-level Qi cultivators stayed in the immortal sects to cultivate. The mortal environment didn't have many benefits for the cultivation of Qi cultivators.

The royal family's goal this time was to recruit rogue Qi cultivators, allowing those immortal sects' Qi cultivators to compete was already giving face to those sects.

As for high-level Qi cultivators, the royal family would definitely not allow it. The relationship between the royal family and the immortal sects was far from good.

The current unrest in various parts of Great Chang, in fact, had the shadow of those immortal sects behind it. These immortal sects have always wanted to secretly control the world's power. They were not on the same path as the royal family.

With this situation going on, the royal family and those immortal sects would eventually have a complete falling out.

"By the way, this time the Eleventh Prince seems to have recruited a sixth-level Qi cultivator. And from the information I gathered, the other party is from He Mountain Dao. We may not necessarily encounter them in the Royal Competition. But if we do, Lin Fei, you must be careful!"

Ling Yao reminded with a serious expression.

"He Mountain Dao has also sent someone?" Lin Fei nodded, indicating that he understood.

There had never been any reconciliation between him and He Mountain Dao.

Lin Fei was very clear about this. If he encountered a Qi cultivator from He Mountain Dao again, the other party would definitely not be polite.

"If we really meet, I'll just cut them down!" A thought flashed through Lin Fei's mind.

Lin Fei stayed at the South King Mansion.

As the Royal Competition approached, Chang City also gathered many extraordinary people. Most of them were invited by the royal descendants from various places, coming to participate in the Royal Competition.

This Royal Competition was not just the royal's lineage, nor was it just the royal descendants of Chang City. It was for all the royal descendants of Great Chang.

They could send outstanding members to participate in the competition. So, the number of people was quite large.

During the three days, Lin Fei continued to take Burst Qi Pills to enhance his cultivation progress in the Three Vitality Technique. At the same time, he gave some pointers to the experts Ling Yao had recruited.

Although the experts Ling Yao recruited knew Lin Fei was strong and they were very respectful on the surface, hearing is not as good as seeing.

After Lin Fei demonstrated a little bit of his fist intent, without even using his saber intent, these martial artists were sincerely convinced.

Receiving Lin Fei's guidance on some fist techniques and saber techniques, their martial arts abilities all improved to varying degrees.

Finally, three days later.

The day of the Royal Competition had finally arrived!

Lin Fei stood beside Ling Yao.

Ling Yao, accompanied by a group of guards, rode in a carriage, slowly heading towards the palace.

Although Lin Fei had been to Chang City once before, he had never been to the palace. He had only seen it from afar and hadn't noticed anything special.

But now, as Lin Fei arrived outside the palace with Ling Yao, Lin Fei looked up the entire palace seemed to be shrouded in an invisible glow. Moreover, this glow was familiar to Lin Fei.

"Formation!"

Lin Fei recalled. This formation had similarities to the one set up by Lin Miao.

Qi cultivators were best at setting up formations. Perhaps even Ling Yao hadn't noticed how terrifying this formation was. Once the formation was activated, it would be impossible for anyone to escape.

"No wonder they are the rulers of the world, the Great Chang Dynasty that has suppressed the world for 900 years!" Lin Fei murmured to himself.

Great Chang had enjoyed the world for 900 years. Its profound foundation was hard to imagine. Such a large-scale project was probably beyond the reach of even high-level Qi cultivators.

Foundation Establishment!

Only Foundation Establishment experts could set up such a large formation covering the entire palace. The royal family had Foundation Establishment experts. After seeing the formation on the upper level of the palace, Lin Fei was very certain.

"Oh, isn't this the South King Princess? Not long ago, the princess stirred up the court, suppressed He Mountain Dao, and gained a lot of attention.

This prince would like to advise the princess that when it comes to important matters of the court, one should be cautious and prudent in their words and actions.

Moreover, He Mountain Dao is part of the Great Chang Dao sect. To suppress the Dao sect for the sake of a mere martial arts sect and a mere martial artist is to lose the bigger picture.

Think about the priorities, and I hope the princess will reflect on this."

Suddenly, another carriage stopped outside the palace gate. From inside the carriage, a young man's voice could be heard.

"Hmm?"

Ling Yao turned her head. Seeing the carriage, she immediately understood.

"So it's the Eleventh Prince. Of course, we should think carefully about matters of the court. However, it seems that the Eleventh Prince has forgotten that our Great Chang was founded on martial arts. In the beginning, our founding emperor swept across all directions with his martial arts, invincible and unparalleled.

Finally, he unified the world, and that's how our Great Chang enjoyed 900 years of peace and prosperity! How did it become a mere martial artist in the prince's mouth? If the founding emperor knew about this, I wonder what he would think of the Eleventh Prince?"

Ling Yao's words were like a hidden dagger, directly confronting the prince. She didn't give the Eleventh Prince any face.

"Hmph, Uncle South King really needs to discipline his princess."

The Eleventh Prince's tone was clearly tinged with anger.

"There's no need for the Eleventh Prince to worry about that. I think the prince should go back and read more about the teachings of the founding emperor."

Ling Yao sneered. Although the other party was a prince, he was not on the same side as her. Ling Yao wasn't afraid of the Eleventh Prince.

Moreover, it was said that the Eleventh Prince was close to He Mountain Dao. Naturally, Ling Yao wouldn't be polite to the Eleventh Prince.

"Your Highness, the princess is indeed eloquent. I presume you must be Lin Fei from the Nine Profound Sect. An acquired martial artist who has comprehended Martial Dao True Intent is indeed extraordinary.

It was his fault that my junior brother was killed by you. However, during the upcoming competition, I would like to experience your Martial Dao True intent to see if it's as magical as the legends say."

Suddenly, a Daoist in robes next to the Eleventh Prince's carriage spoke slowly, and his gaze was fixed on Lin Fei.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei had been resting with his eyes closed, at this moment, he opened them.

"A Qi cultivator from He Mountain Dao? If all the Qi cultivators of He Mountain Dao are as weak as your junior brother. I'm afraid I will be very disappointed."

After saying that, Lin Fei closed his eyes again, no longer speaking. He didn't want to engage in a war of words. Arguing with words was meaningless. If he couldn't stand it, he would cut it down with a saber.

The Daoist from He Mountain Dao stopped talking and stood quietly beside the carriage, waiting.

An hour passed, and many more carriages arrived one after another.

"Rumble."

Finally, the heavy palace gates slowly opened. The carriages of numerous royal family members entered the palace.

The royal family competition took place in a spacious open area. This open space was very large. It was suitable for displaying spells or martial arts.

The competition was presided over by three elders of the royal family. However, this elder was not a martial artist. They were Qi cultivators. And high-level Qi cultivators at that!

Three little-known royal family high-level Qi cultivators. This showed how profound the royal family's background was.

"The rules of the Royal Competition: no further attacks are allowed after the opponent admits defeat. Otherwise, I will personally step in and execute the offender on the spot! Alright, now go draw lots and start the competition."

The royal family elder didn't say much. He briefly introduced the rules and then proceeded to draw lots.

Ling Yao drew the number twenty-three. It was unclear who her opponent was. But it should be in the twenty-third round. It was one of the last few rounds. Not bad, at least she could watch the other matches beforehand.

The competition was between the royal family members and their followers. However, starting from the first match, as long as a royal family member went up, they would basically hide behind, letting their followers fight. Once their followers were defeated, they would immediately admit defeat.

This scene made the three royal family elders shake their heads.

"These years, the royal family's children have become increasingly unbearable. Even when they step onto the arena, they dare not fight themselves."

In memory of the royal family elders, the royal family competition in the past was not like this. Although there were followers, at that time, the royal family's children would generally also participate in the fights. There were even some outstanding royal family children who could defeat their opponents' followers. Unfortunately, such royal family members had been rarely seen in recent decades.

Lin Fei was also watching the competition. There were martial artists and Qi cultivators participating. However, the situation was not optimistic.

Martial artists were completely defeated!

In every confrontation between martial artists and Qi cultivators, martial artists were utterly defeated! Not a single martial artist defeated a Qi cultivator.

Lin Fei even saw a martial artist at the eleventh level of the acquired realm and he had even practiced a sword technique to the perfection realm.

His strength was so strong that it was difficult to find an opponent below the innate realm.

Presumably, he came to participate in the royal family competition to obtain the Heavenly Meridian Pill, break through the shackles, and reach the twelfth level of the acquired realm.

He encountered a genuine Qi cultivator at the fourth level of Qi Condensation.

What was the result?

The eleventh-level acquired martial artist displayed his perfect realm sword technique, but he couldn't do anything against the opponent's magical artifact.

The Qi cultivator just stood there, letting the eleventh-level acquired martial artist launch a fierce sword attack.

What was the result?

The Qi cultivator was unscathed! In the end, the Qi cultivator used a few spells to defeat the martial artist, and even seriously injured him.

This scene made the eyes of all martial artists dim. Acquired martial artists were practically crushed when facing Qi cultivators. There was even no glimmer of hope to defeat their opponents.

Many had practiced for decades, enduring heat and cold.

And the result?

They couldn't even break the magical artifacts of Qi cultivators. This feeling made all martial artists feel desperate.

Even Ling Yao, at this moment, also clenched the armrests of her chair. With a solemn face, she said nothing.

Obviously, this result made her feel very uncomfortable. After all, she was also a martial artist.

"Princess of South King versus Princess of Sang Yang!"

It was finally Ling Yao's turn.

"Princess of Sang Yang!"

Ling Yao's heart trembled. She immediately whispered to Lin Fei, "Lin Fei, be careful. The follower of Princess Sang Yang is also a Qi cultivator. And she is a genuine Qi cultivator from the Green Jade Gate. Although she is only at the fourth level of Qi Condensation, she possesses the magical artifact Yin Yang Nine Rings, which is strong in both offense and defense!"

Lin Fei looked up. He saw a female Daoist beside Princess Sang Yang. That must be the Qi cultivator from Green Jade Gate.

"How is the relationship between Princess Sang Yang and Senior Sister Ling?" Lin Fei suddenly asked.

"Princess Sang Yang and I have an okay relationship. Last time during the He Mountain Dao incident, Princess Sang Yang actually helped. Otherwise, how could I know so much information about her follower? It's because I am very close to Princess Sang Yang."

Ling Yao said with a bitter smile. Unexpectedly, she would encounter Princess Sang Yang in the first round. Her luck was really not good.

"I see."

"Since Princess Sang Yang has a good relationship with Seniot Sister Ling, I won't use heavy hands."

"Uh..."

Ling Yao didn't know what to say. She felt that Lin Fei was too confident, wasn't he? Even though Lin Fei had killed a Qi cultivator from He Mountain Dao. But that opponent was only at the third level of Qi Condensation.

Princess Sang Yang's follower was at the fourth level of Qi Condensation. And she even had a powerful magical artifact.

"Let's go, the sooner we settle this, the sooner we can move on to the next round," Lin Fei directly leaped and arrived at the martial arts stage.

At this moment, both parties were on the martial arts stage. Princess Sang Yang and Ling Yao both stood behind their respective followers. The real competitors were actually the followers.

The female Daoist slightly bowed her head and said, "Green Jade Gate, Yu Xiangzi!"

"Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei."

Lin Fei also took a step forward and stood quietly. However, Lin Fei didn't unsheathe his saber. Instead, he clenched his palms into fists, preparing to use a fist technique.

"Hmm?"

Yu Xiangzi frowned and asked, "Why don't you use your saber?"

Yu Xiangzi obviously learned from Princess Sang Yang's mouth that Lin Fei had comprehended the saber intent. Saber techniques were Lin Fei's strongest methods.

"If I unsheathe my saber, you will die!"

Lin Fei looked deeply at Yu Xiangzi and spoke calmly.

99. Fist Intent Shows Power

"Brazen boasts!"

Upon hearing Lin Fei's words, Yu Xiangzi grew angry as well. She was a dignified Qi cultivator and possessed a magical artifact. And Her aptitude was also top-notch.

Her true goal this time came to Chang City to participate in the Royal Competition was to win a top-three spot and thus gain entry into the secret realm.

But now, a mere martial artist, although he had comprehended saber intent and had slain a Qi cultivator, he was so arrogant.

How could Yu Xiangzi not be furious? So, she went all-out as soon as she made her move.

"Yin-Yang Nine Rings!"

Yu Xiangzi activated her magical artifact. In an instant, nine rings of indeterminate metal or jade released a hazy light all at once, enveloping Yu Xiangzi within.

Next, the ring-shaped magical artifacts transformed into a ray of light, directly shooting toward Lin Fei.

Under the martial arts stage, many people were watching this battle.

Some well-informed individuals naturally knew that Lin Fei had mastered saber intent and had once slain a Qi cultivator from He Mountain Dao.

But hearing rumors and seeing with their own eyes were clearly different. So, they were also curious. Was the Martial Dao True Intent really that powerful? Could it enable a martial artist to slay a Qi cultivator?

It must be known that in the recent Royal Competition, any acquired martial artist was defeated by Qi cultivators. Qi cultivators utterly dominated martial artists!

Seeing the Yin-Yang Nine Rings flying towards him, Lin Fei stood motionless. The next moment, he stimulated his fist intent. On Lin Fei's body, a heaven-shaking fist intent suddenly erupted.

Some with keen perceptions felt as if Lin Fei had transformed into a towering giant, releasing endless fighting intent.

And those Qi cultivators with divine consciousness clearly "saw" a phantom fist appearing above Lin Fei's head.

It was this phantom fist that lightly pressed down toward Yu Xiangzi.

"Boom."

Yu Xiangzi's mind went blank. She felt endless fear.

In her mind, she saw an incomparable fist descending from the sky.

In her vision, it seemed everything else had vanished.

Only that one fist remained.

"It's fake, this is fake, Martial Dao True Intent is all fake..."

Yu Xiangzi clenched her teeth, repeatedly chanting in her heart that everything was an illusion.

Yet, she still couldn't help but fear and tremble. Even feeling a sensation of being "crushed" in her mind.

"Snap."

A soft sound.

Yu Xiangzi looked around.

It seemed like everything had vanished. But she was already drenched in sweat, and she couldn't even muster a bit of strength. This was the manifestation of excessive mental exhaustion.

"Is this the Martial Dao True Intent? It's terrifying. I knew it was fake, that it was an illusion. But I still couldn't block it."

Yu Xiangzi felt incredibly bitter in her heart. She looked at Lin Fei again, but her eyes already held a hint of fear.

That's how the Martial Dao True Intent was. If one couldn't block it, that would be true. This wasn't some illusion technique.

"I admit defeat..." Yu Xiangzi spoke with difficulty. She had to admit defeat. If Lin Fei hadn't withdrawn his fist intent just now, she might have been crushed by that terrifying fist intent. By then, even uttering the words "I admit defeat" would be a luxury.

Lin Fei had indeed spared her once. So, Yu Xiangzi was convinced both in heart and mouth. From then on, she would never underestimate martial artists or martial arts.

Fist intent...It's been so many years since I've seen such a young martial artist comprehend it. This Lin Fei comes from the Nine Profound Sect, and the Nine Profound Sect has always been on good terms with our royal family. I think we can win him over.

If his fist intent can advance further, reaching transcendence, he will be fearless even when facing high-level martial artists! Disciples of the Nine Profound Sect... How extraordinary and peerless was the founder of the Nine Profound Sect? It seems that this young one has indeed inherited some of his founder's elegance.

"Alright, announce it."

"Victory goes to the princess of the South King!"

As the Princess of Sang Yang conceded defeat, the three royal elders announced the victor of this match.

"Boom."

With the announcement of the result by the three royal elders, the audience below erupted in an uproar. Especially the martial artists who were unaware of the reasons behind the outcome were left bewildered.

"What happened? How did Lin Fei win?"

"Lin Fei didn't even make a move, and the Qi cultivator was drenched in sweat, seemingly suffering immense pain before conceding defeat. What kind of martial art is that?"

"Incredible, truly incredible. Before, not even a single martial artist could win. But now, a martial artist defeated a Qi cultivator without making a single move."

"No, Lin Fei made a move. That terrifying aura from him earlier, if I'm not mistaken, that should be the legendary Martial Dao True Intent!"

"Martial Dao True Intent? Someone actually comprehended the Martial Dao True Intent?"

"Even an innate martial artist would find it difficult to comprehend the Martial Dao True Intent..."

These martial artists were incredibly excited. The Martial Dao True Intent had appeared once more and it was so powerful. Defeating a Qi cultivator without even making a move was such an overwhelming feat!

This was a true martial artist! This was the Martial Dao!

In an instant, many martial artists who had been defeated by Qi cultivators were invigorated. Lin Fei defeated a Qi cultivator with the power of a martial artist. This proved that martial artists were not weaker than Qi cultivators!

Martial artists need Martial Dao faith. Only with Martial Dao faith can one become more courageous in battle. Lin Fei's emergence undoubtedly rekindled the Martial Dao faith for these defeated martial artists.

Even the Eleventh Prince was solemn at this moment. He turned to the Immortal Master He Shan beside him and asked, "Immortal Master, can you withstand Lin Fei's Martial Dao True Intent? Is the Martial Dao truly that powerful?"

The Eleventh Prince also practiced martial arts. However, he wasn't particularly skilled. In fact, he didn't even have Martial Dao faith. Thus, seeing Lin Fei defeat Yu Xiangzi without making a move, his expression became somewhat complicated.

At this moment, the Qi cultivator from He Mountain Dao stared at Lin Fei in the distance.

He spoke calmly, word by word, "For a martial artist to comprehend Martial Dao True Intent is even more difficult than achieving innate. My junior brother did not die in vain! However, Martial Dao True Intent is not invincible. As long as one's will is resolute, the Martial Dao True Intent cannot affect me!"

The Qi cultivator from He Mountain Dao stopped speaking and began to close his eyes, recuperating and adjusting his condition.

Lin Fei still stood on the stage, his eyes closed, not speaking. Because, at the moment when Yu Xiangzi conceded defeat, a system's voice sounded in Lin Fei's mind.

"Qi cultivator Yu Xiangzi was defeated by your Fist Intent, and she wholeheartedly submitted, fearing your Fist Intent."

"Your Fist Intent is filled with pride, enjoying the victorious posture."

"Under the elation, your Fist Intent cultivation progress has increased by 10%."

Lin Fei was still somewhat stunned after hearing the system's voice. The personality of this Fist Intent was... rather unique. It had character! And Lin Fei liked martial arts techniques with character. Because only with characterful martial arts could he "cater to their preferences." Then, his martial arts could naturally advance by leaps and bounds!

100. It will decide life and death

"It's been a long time since I've encountered such a martial art with character."

Lin Fei had already left the stage and returned to his original position, still thinking about Fist Intent.

A martial art with character could progress more quickly. It seemed that Lin Fei needed to consider displaying his Fist Intent more frequently. This Fist Intent clearly enjoyed being in the limelight. It was different from Saber Intent.

Saber Intent was cold. It seemed that only through hard work and battle could improve it. For example, under the stone tablet at Ancestral Master Peak, Saber Intent improved the fastest. Fist Intent was a bit slower. It wasn't that Fist Intent was truly weak or had poor comprehension. It was a difference in character. It relished being the victor.

If Lin Fei wanted to speed up the progress of Fist Intent, he needed to give it more opportunities to shine.

"System," Lin Fei summoned the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Eighth Level

Saber Intent: Mastery (11% Progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (15% Progress)

Three Vitality Technique: Eighth Level (38% Progress)

Leaping Technique: Perfection (0% Progress )

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Lin Fei glanced at the progress of his Fist Intent on the system panel.

The progress of Fist Intent had already reached 15%. It even surpassed the progress of Saber Intent. This was something Lin Fei hadn't expected. After all, when he honed his Fist Intent and Saber Intent in front of the stone tablet at Ancestral Master Peak, Saber Intent could still improve, but Fist Intent could not be improved further.

Unexpectedly, now, after merely defeating Qi cultivator Yu Xiangzi, Fist Intent had increased its progress by 10%. This was indeed a pleasant surprise.

"Lin Fei, was that Saber Intent you displayed just now?" At this moment, Ling Yao couldn't help but ask.

"No, it wasn't Saber Intent. It was Fist Intent!" Lin Fei didn't hide it. Moreover, he couldn't hide it. Although Martial Dao True Intent was rare, this place was the imperial palace. There were many experts here. How could no one recognize Lin Fei's Fist Intent?

"Fist Intent... So, this is the second Martial Dao True Intent you've mastered. You've mastered two kinds of Martial Dao True Intent?"

"That's right, I've comprehended two kinds of Martial Dao True Intent. Is there a problem, Senior Sister Ling?"

Ling Yao didn't answer. Instead, she looked at Lin Fei with a strange expression. It seemed as if Lin Fei thought it was normal for him to master two kinds of Martial Dao True Intent. But, was it really normal?

Ling Yao was not only a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect, but also a member of the royal family and the princess of South King. She knew many secrets that ordinary people didn't.

For a martial artist, even a supremely talented one, being able to master one kind of Martial Dao True Intent was already a heavenly blessing. They belonged to the extremely lucky ones. Even for those who could achieve the innate realm, comprehending a Martial Dao True Intent was as difficult as climbing into the sky.

As for two kinds of Martial Dao True Intent, it was unheard of. Perhaps only some legendary martial artists could master two or more Martial Dao True Intents.

But those martial artists, each of them had a prestigious reputation. Even some of them were top-notch experts who stirred up the world. In their respective era, they must have stood at the pinnacle of martial arts! Could it be that Lin Fei would also stand at the pinnacle of martial arts in this era?

The Royal Competition continued.

Although Lin Fei had defeated Yu Xiangzi and had preserved the last shred of dignity for martial artists, after the first round, except for very few martial artists who were lucky enough not to encounter Qi cultivators, the rest of the martial artists were all eliminated.

The second round of the competition began.

The number of participants suddenly decreased by half. Those martial artists were no longer so lucky.

When encountering Qi cultivators, even if they had the will to fight and conviction, without Martial Dao True Intent, they couldn't harm the Qi cultivators at all.

In the end, they were all defeated. All that was left of the martial artists was Lin Fei alone.

In the second round, Ling Yao and Lin Fei went on stage.

This time, their opponent was still a Qi cultivator. However, this cultivator was far inferior to Yu Xiangzi. He was stunned by Lin Fei's Fist Intent and even passed out directly.

This was because Lin Fei didn't use lethal force. Otherwise, he could have directly killed the opponent with his Fist Intent.

This was the terrifying aspect of Martial Dao True Intent in the mastery realm. It was far stronger than when it was just in the beginner realm.

Of course, up until now, Lin Fei hadn't displayed his Saber Intent.

Saber Intent and Sword Intent were the strongest attacking Martial Dao True Intents among all.

Once Lin Fei displayed his Saber Intent, most of his opponents would be directly killed by it.

This was just a competition. There was no deep hatred or resentment. Lin Fei didn't see the need to use his Saber Intent.

Moreover, displaying Fist Intent allowed the "Fist Intent" to feel great in the spotlight. As a result, the cultivation speed increased.

Two rounds, three rounds, four rounds...

Lin Fei didn't encounter any challenges along the way until the fifth round. This was the most crucial match because there were only four matches left in this round. It would directly decide the top three.

Only the top three could qualify to enter the royal family's secret realm and obtain a Heavenly Meridian Pill.

"Princess of South King against the Ninth Princess!"

Lin Fei and Ling Yao went on stage in this round. Lin Fei's opponent was a Qi cultivator at the fifth level.

However, the opponent shook his head and said, "Princess, I admit defeat."

"Admit defeat?"

Lin Fei's eyes narrowed slightly. The opponent had admitted defeat without even fighting. It seemed that the opponent was saving his energy to compete with the loser of the other match for third place with full strength.

If he were to fight with Lin Fei, he might not be able to withstand Lin Fei's Fist Intent. At that time, if he were injured, how could he compete for the third place? So, he simply took the initiative to admit defeat!

It saved Lin Fei and Ling Yao some trouble. However, in this round, Lin Fei's Fist Intent couldn't be improved. No battle, no chance to show off. How could Fist Intent improve?

Now, Lin Fei's cultivation progress of Fist Intent had already reached 45%. Such an improved speed was simply astonishing. Perhaps Fist Intent could get transcendence in no time.

The other match started quickly.

The two Qi cultivators competed with various spells and magical artifacts. It was an eye-opener for everyone. In the end, the Eleventh Prince won. The Daoist from He Mountain Dao advanced to the finals.

Ling Yao saw this and frowned slightly, "Lin Fei, we have already achieved our goal of being in the top three in the Royal Competition. The final decision for the first place doesn't have much significance.

At most, it's just an empty title. The Daoist from He Mountain Dao has ill intentions toward you. Although you are not afraid of him, there is no need to fight him in this situation. How about I just admit defeat? I don't need this empty title!"

Lin Fei glanced at the Daoist from He Mountain Dao. Then he nodded and said, "It's indeed meaningless to fight for pride in this situation. Since Senior Sister Ling has agreed to give up the empty title of first place, let's just admit defeat."

Lin Fei didn't necessarily have to have a showdown with the Daoist from He Mountain Dao. There was no benefit to it.

So Ling Yao directly stood up and said, "There's no need for the final match, I admit defeat."

As soon as her words fell, there was an uproar among the crowd.

"Admit defeat, not competing?"

"The immortal master from He Mountain Dao is at the sixth level of Qi Condensation, with deep accomplishments in magical artifacts, spells, and talismans, and is very powerful! Lin Fei's martial intent is indeed strong, but is it really invincible? I don't think so. However, if they don't compete now, won't we not know who is stronger and who is weaker?"

For a moment, many people were discussing and felt very regretful. They had already vaguely treated the confrontation between Lin Fei and the immortal master of He Mountain Dao as a battle between martial artists and Qi cultivators. However, now that Ling Yao had admitted defeat. It meant that this confrontation was off the table.

"Wait."

At this moment, the Daoist from He Mountain Dao spoke. He looked at Lin Fei and said loudly, "Lin Fei, as a martial artist, you killed an official disciple of my He Mountain Dao. You made my He Mountain Dao lose face in front of many fellow immortal cultivators.

Although for various reasons, my He Mountain Dao and your Nine Profound Sect have temporarily put this matter aside, today I want to take this opportunity to learn from you. Do you dare?"

The voice of the He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator echoed in everyone's ears. Many people only then realized that Lin Fei had actually killed an official disciple of He Mountain Dao.

At this point, people became even more interested. However, would Lin Fei accept or not the provocation of the He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator? After all, this confrontation was no benefit. The only significance might be to resolve the conflict between He Mountain Dao and Lin Fei.

"Swish."

Lin Fei raised his head, his gaze sharp as a saber.

"If I unsheathe my saber, it will decide life and death! Are you prepared for death?"

Lin Fei's calm tone now seemed as cold as ice. As soon as his words fell, everyone held their breath and focused. The entire arena became silent, so quiet that one could hear a pin drop.

101. You can't block my saber

"Kill me?"

The He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator sneered, "Martial artists' Martial Dao True Intent is indeed powerful, but it's only effective against those with weak wills. Since my childhood, I have practiced the Heart-Calming Technique with an unblemished mind and unwavering will. What's the use of Martial Dao True Intent?"

The He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator, who dared to challenge Lin Fei, must have had confidence. His confidence was the Heart-Calming Technique!

This was a method that trained the will and strengthens the divine sense. It required a lot of mental energy. But for those in the Qi Condensation realm, it didn't have much use.

The only use was to slightly increase the probability of success during the Foundation Establishment stage. However, very few Qi Condensation cultivators would spend so much energy practicing the Heart-Calming Technique to increase the success rate of Foundation Establishment by a little bit. It seemed somewhat not worth it.

Of course, there was another type of person who might practice the Heart-Calming Technique. Those who have absolute confidence in their own Foundation Establishment. They felt that they could definitely succeed in Foundation Establishment 100%. Therefore, they were willing to spare no effort to increase the success rate of the Foundation Establishment even a little bit.

Obviously, this Qi cultivator from He Mountain Dao had such confidence, feeling that he could succeed in Foundation Establishment 100%. So he practiced the Heart-Calming Technique since he was a child.

Martial Dao True Intent, on the other hand, targeted the will and the mind. In this regard, Qi cultivators were far inferior to martial artists.

After all, martial artists had been honing their physical fitness since childhood and training martial arts at the coldest and hottest periods of the year.

Martial artists persist for decades. This unwavering determination was far from what those Qi cultivators, who practiced in the mountains, could compare to. Therefore, Martial Dao True Intent could directly damage the minds of Qi cultivators.

But for martial artists, at most, it could only intimidate them for a moment. Of course, if Lin Fei were to deal with martial artists, with his Martial Dao True Intent-enhanced fist and saber techniques, the power would be multiplied and equally extraordinary.

"Swish."

Lin Fei stood up.

"Lin Fei…" Ling Yao was a bit worried.

"Senior Sister, some things can't be avoided. Since he wants to fight, then I'll accomodate him. This time, I'll unsheathe my saber! Senior Sister Ling's Nine Shadow Saber Technique has also reached perfection, theoretically, you could also comprehend saber intent. Senior Sister, watch closely and see what saber intent is…"

Lin Fei took one step at a time, walking onto the arena.

This battle was not for ranking or profit. Only for victory!

Watching Lin Fei walk onto the stage, everyone under the stage held their breath and focused intently. They knew that this would definitely be a spectacular battle. A great battle between a martial artist and a Qi cultivator!

Both of them stood on the stage, looking at each other from afar.

"He Mountain Dao, He Yunzi!"

"Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei!"

Both of them announced their names.

It was the first time that Lin Fei learned the name of this He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator, He Yunzi. Obviously, He Yunzi was the strongest Qi cultivator participating in the Royal Competition this time.

He Mountain Dao had invested heavily, sending He Yunzi down the mountain. And He Yunzi did not disappoint, he secured a spot in the top three of the competition. He could enter the secret realm now.

However, what he wanted to do even more was to defeat Lin Fei to restore the reputation of the He Mountain Dao.

Ever since Lin Fei killed the He Mountain Dao's Qi cultivator, the He Mountain Dao's disciples had been ridiculed among the many Qi cultivators from various immortal sects, losing all face. He Yunzi intended to take it all back from Lin Fei.

"Draw your saber, or else you won't be able to hurt me," He Yunzi said indifferently. A magical artifact had already enveloped He Yunzi's body.

Aside from Martial Dao True Intent and innate true qi, no other power, however strong, could break through the Qi cultivator's magical artifact.

Lin Fei did not speak. Instead, he silently stimulated his fist intent.

"Boom."

This was Lin Fei's fist intent. Imposing and vast, it rolled towards He Yunzi.

"Huh?"

He Yunzi's face changed slightly. It wasn't saber intent.

He knew Lin Fei had saber intent. Lin Fei had previously displayed his fist intent as well. Lin Fei had two types of Martial Dao True Intent.

Although He Yunzi was full of confidence, he was confident but not arrogant, and not reckless either. He was very cautious about Lin Fei's Martial Dao True Intent.

Thus, the moment Lin Fei unleashed his fist intent. He Yunzi had already executed the Heart-Calming Technique.

"Heart-Calming Technique. My thought is a mountain. Nothing can shake my spirit! Even Martial Dao True Intent is nothing but an illusion."

He Yunzi remained motionless, chanting under his breath. Obviously, facing Lin Fei's fist intent, he wasn't as relaxed as he claimed.

One step, two steps, three steps.

Lin Fei did not use the Leaping Technique. Instead, he took one step at a time toward He Yunzi. Because he was stimulating his fist intent, using his fist intent to continuously suppress He Yunzi. With each step closer, the deterrence Lin Fei's fist intent had on He Yunzi became even stronger.

He Yunzi's spirit and willpower were indeed much stronger than those of other Qi cultivators. Even when faced with Lin Fei's mastery fist intent, his mental defense remained unbroken.

His willpower remained unwavering. Even the spiritual power in his body had no fluctuations.

Flawless!

He Yunzi was now almost flawless.

If a Qi cultivator's spiritual power had no fluctuations, then a martial artist's saber, inner power, and martial techniques cannot break through its spiritual power.

However, Lin Fei's fist intent also put immense pressure on He Yunzi. It was like a huge mountain, continuously increasing its weight. He Yunzi was left with no opportunity to use other techniques. He could only endure!

Ling Yao was also a martial artist. Moreover, a martial artist with a perfected saber technique. She had a certain understanding of Martial Dao True Intent. She knew that Martial Dao True Intent could not last long. Martial intent was the embodiment of a martial artist's willpower. It was impossible to maintain it indefinitely.

Although Lin Fei seemed to have the upper hand using his fist intent, preventing He Yunzi from using other techniques. In reality, Lin Fei could not hurt He Yunzi.

As long as He Yunzi's spiritual power remained stable, the defensive magical artifact activated could block any of Lin Fei's attacks, placing him in an invincible position. As time went on, Lin Fei's Martial Dao True Intent would be unable to sustain itself. That would be He Yunzi's opportunity to counterattack!

So, although Lin Fei seemed to have the upper hand now, in fact, his situation was not very optimistic.

However, besides fist intent, Lin Fei also had saber intent. Lin Fei had not used his saber intent. He was looking for a weakness in He Yunzi.

Very few people could see the complicated situation between Lin Fei and He Yunzi. However, everyone could see the situation between the two seemed to be at a stalemate. Moreover, He Yunzi had not made a move. But once he did, Lin Fei would most likely be defeated!

No one said another word. Everyone was silently focusing on the movements in the arena, afraid of missing any details.

In the arena, Lin Fei's pace was neither fast nor slow. He still approached He Yunzi step by step.

Originally, the distance between the two was about twenty steps. And now, Lin Fei had already covered half the distance. The pressure of his fist intent had almost reached its peak that even cold sweat appeared on He Yunzi's forehead. Obviously, He Yunzi was not at ease.

It was said that Martial Dao True Intent was an illusion, but that was not entirely true. Martial Dao True Intent was merely intangible and invisible.

It was a real attack. It was a form of power. It can't be called an illusion. If one cannot block it, then it cannot be blocked. There was no luck involved.

He Yunzi had been practicing Heart-Calming Technique since he was a child. It did make his spirit and willpower much stronger than ordinary Qi Condensation cultivators.

However, a Qi Condensation cultivator was still just a Qi Condensation cultivator. No matter how strong their spirit and willpower were, there was a limit.

Therefore, Lin Fei's mastery fist intent was already the limit that He Yunzi could endure. Not revealing any flaws was He Yunzi's greatest fortune.

Nine steps, eight steps, seven steps, six steps, five steps...

He Yunzi's pressure was getting heavier and heavier. A thought began to emerge in his mind.

Lin Fei still had saber intent that he hadn't used. Once he used the saber intent, could he withstand it?

Once this thought appeared, it could not be erased. It even became uncontrollable, intensifying and echoing in He Yunzi's mind.

Suddenly, Lin Fei stopped, at a distance of three steps in front of He Yunzi. His gaze was fixed on He Yunzi. His eyes were calm as if nothing could affect his emotions.

"Your spirit has finally shown a flaw! You can't block my saber!"

Lin Fei's hand slowly grasped the Hidden Saber at his waist!

102. Kill

"You can't shake my spirit! These little tricks are not worth showing off. My spirit is as solid as a rock. What if you have saber intent? You can't do anything to me!"

He Yunzi's eyes were calm. He constantly used the Heart-Calming Technique to stabilize his own spirit.

However, he didn't know that the more he used the Heart-Calming Technique to stabilize his spirit, the more he had actually exposed the flaws in it. Because his subconscious was wary and afraid of saber intent. His subconscious wanted to guard against Lin Fei's saber intent.

This was the flaw!

Of course, this kind of flaw was also because Lin Fei first used his fist intent to constantly suppress He Yunzi. That was why He Yunzi's spiritual flaw was created. He even magnified He Yunzi's spiritual flaw step by step.

By now, He Yunzi's spiritual flaws had been in front of Lin Fei. It was full of holes.

The next moment, Lin Fei didn't hesitate any longer.

"Shoo."

Lin Fei drew his saber. He had been nurturing this saber for two full months. Moreover, he nurtured the saber under the condition of the Saber-drawing Technique perfection, even with the nourishment of saber intent.

Nurturing inner power and saber intent together for two months, even Lin Fei himself didn't know how powerful this saber was. He only knew, if he drew his saber, He Yunzi wouldn't be able to block it!

No one could see the speed at which Lin Fei drew his saber. Everyone could only see a white light flashing through the void. However, not seeing the saber didn't mean they couldn't sense the saber intent.

Saber intent was different from fist intent. Saber intent was sharp and extremely fierce.

The moment Lin Fei drew his saber, it was as if he had transformed into an unparalleled treasure saber. It seemed like the sky was full of sharp saber edges. Even down in the arena, far away, they could still feel the sharpness of the saber blade.

It seemed to be cutting their skin, making the skin feel a faint pain.

"Slash!"

As Lin Fei drew his saber, the fierce saber intent erupted like a volcano.

Down in the arena, many martial artists carried sabers with them. But now, these sabers were shaking violently. Even the sabers in their sheaths were making a faint ringing sound. It was as if there was an invisible force controlling everyone's sabers.

"Is... is this the saber intent?"

"It's said that once the saber intent erupts, any saber wielder, in front of a martial artist who has comprehended saber intent, can't even hope to draw their saber."

"The saber intent can control all sabers. I originally thought it was an absurd legend, but now it seems to be true..."

"I... I really can't control my saber anymore..."

This scene was simply incredible. It shocked many martial artists and Qi Condensation cultivators! This completely overturned their previous understanding of martial artists. When did martial artists become so terrifying?

If a martial artist comprehended saber intent, once on the battlefield, wouldn't it mean that with just a thought, the sabers in the hands of thousands of soldiers would be instantly controlled? Even drawing the saber would be a luxury.

What would happen on a battlefield?

A martial artist who has comprehended saber intent was no longer as simple as fighting one against a hundred, but one against ten thousand. A true enemy of ten thousand!

At this moment, martial artists seemed to have made a deep impression on many Qi cultivators' hearts. It turned out that martial artists were not just what they usually saw. Martial artists also had "divine powers." This saber intent could be compared to a "divine power."

The people below the arena were merely shocked, but in the arena, He Yunzi, who was facing Lin Fei's saber intent directly. It was not as simple as being shocked.

The moment Lin Fei drew his saber, in his line of sight, it seemed like there was only a ball of white light.

In his mind, which was originally pitch black. At this moment, it seemed to have been "cut open" by a beam of light.

That was a saber!

An indescribable saber!

It flashed by in an instant.

It disappeared into his mind in an instant.

Suddenly, a violent tearing sensation clearly emanated from his mind.

He Yunzi felt as if his mind had been forcibly "cut open."

Then, his vision went dark.

He lost all consciousness.

"Pa."

Lin Fei sheathed his saber. His saber seemed as if it had never left its sheath.

He Yunzi showed no reaction. The only change might be the light from the defensive magical artifact on his body, it disappeared.

No one knew when it disappeared. Perhaps it was the moment Lin Fei drew his saber, or perhaps it was the moment He Yunzi's mind fell into darkness.

In any case, He Yunzi's magical artifact had lost its glow. This meant that without the support of spiritual power, the magical artifact was just a pile of scrap iron.

"Pfft."

From He Yunzi's head, a line of blood appeared from top to bottom. The next moment, He Yunzi's body incredibly split into two halves. Blood splattered everywhere and a strong smell of blood filled the air.

He Yunzi was dead! And he died in such a miserable and shocking way. The two halves of his body fell to the ground with a "plop."

Suddenly, everyone was in an uproar.

"He Yunzi is dead?"

"How could he die?"

"Even if He Yunzi was defeated, he shouldn't have died."

"Besides, he could have admitted defeat, why didn't He Yunzi surrender?"

"He Yunzi had a magical artifact on him, as long as his mind wasn't broken, he wouldn't die as long as he had spiritual power to support him."

"He Yunzi is dead, will He Mountain Dao let this go?"

Many people were shocked. They thought at most one side would lose. Losing, at worst, meant surrendering. How could one side die? Moreover, the death was so tragic.

Lin Fei silently glanced at He Yunzi's corpse on the ground and looked at the three elders presiding over the royal competition.

Lin Fei calmly said, "Saber-drawing Technique, once the saber is drawn, it cannot be stopped! He Yunzi couldn't withstand my saber intent and couldn't maintain the flow of spiritual power. So, he couldn't block my saber either!"

The three royal elders were witnesses and there were so many people witnessing it. He Yunzi was dead, and that was it.

The three royal elders exchanged glances. Others couldn't see it clearly, but as high-level Qi Condensation cultivators, their divine senses were incredibly powerful. Naturally, they saw the whole scene clearly. And it was as Lin Fei said, there was no discrepancy.

Lin Fei just used the Saber-drawing Technique. The saber was drawn, and it was earth-shattering! The speed was so fast, and the saber intent was so sharp made the three royal elders feel a chill in their hearts.

Facing such a terrifying saber intent, He Yunzi couldn't withstand it and his mind was instantly shattered by Lin Fei's saber intent. He Yunzi's willpower was broken by Lin Fei, and he naturally couldn't maintain his own spiritual power.

Without spiritual power, the magical artifact lost its protective function. Then, Lin Fei's saber struck He Yunzi's body, easily cutting him in half with one saber stroke.

The speed of Lin Fei's Saber-drawing Technique was simply too fast, even the three royal elders, who were high-level Qi Condensation cultivators, couldn't intervene in time to save him.

"Lin Fei, this is the arena, and the saber has no eyes. He Yunzi was weak and was killed by you, which is within the rules. We witnessed it with our own eyes and will report the truth to He Mountain Dao. You don't need to worry."

"Thank you, three seniors!"

Lin Fei's expression remained calm as he turned around and slowly walked off the stage.

103. Destroy The Gate Of He Mountain Dao

The following events had nothing to do with Lin Fei.

In another contest for third place, the follower of the Ninth Princess admitted defeat to Lin Fei to preserve his strength. As expected, it worked wonders, he easily won the third place.

From then on, the top three were determined. The royal competition came to an end.

This time's royal competition was filled with climaxes and unexpected changes. No one could have imagined an acquired martial artist could actually kill a sixth-level orthodox Qi Condensation cultivator. The legendary Martial Dao True Intent reappeared.

As a result, with the departure of these people, Lin Fei's name instantly spread throughout all the forces of Great Chang. Regardless of whether they were martial arts sects or lofty immortal sects, they all knew about Lin Fei.

However, sometimes fame in the world was not necessarily a good thing. It might even bring trouble!

...

In the South King Mansion, Ling Yao's expression was serious, and she called Lin Fei to the hall.

"Lin Fei, this is the Heavenly Meridian Pill, one for each of us," Ling Yao handed a pill to Lin Fei. This was what Lin Fei deserved.

This Heavenly Meridian Pill had many pill patterns on it. Whenever there were pill patterns, it meant that the refining process was extremely difficult.

Taking one Heavenly Meridian Pill could open up a meridian and increase inner power by one level. For acquired martial artists, it could be considered the best pill.

Ling Yao also received a Heavenly Meridian Pill. She could use it to break through the bottleneck and advance to the seventh level acquired martial artist.

However, Ling Yao's expression was very serious. She didn't seem to be very excited.

"Lin Fei, there is some trouble with your situation," Ling Yao said with a serious tone.

"Hmm? Is it about He Yunzi?" Lin Fei looked up. He could roughly guess.

Ling Yao looked at Lin Fei with a complex expression and nodded, "No one expected that you could kill He Yunzi. Afterward, I asked the three elders and learned about He Yunzi's identity. He Yunzi had an extraordinary status in He Mountain Dao, and he was considered the most promising disciple to successfully build his foundation in the past 300 years. He didn't need to participate in this royal competition. But He Yunzi insisted on coming down the mountain. His purpose was to meet you in the royal competition, defeat your momentum, and save face for He Mountain Dao. As a result, he was killed by you..."

Lin Fei's expression remained calm as if nothing could make him emotional. However, Lin Fei understood Ling Yao's words.

"So, the high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao might take action against me?" Lin Fei said indifferently.

"It's not a possibility, it's certain! Even with the support of the royal family, He Mountain Dao is one of the immortal sects, and it's not that easy to deal with them. Besides, you are not a member of the royal family. The royal family cannot protect you at all costs under these circumstances.

However, Lin Fei, as long as you stay in Chang City or simply return to the Nine Profound Sect and never come down the mountain, He Mountain Dao can't do anything to you. Don't underestimate the Nine Profound Sect. Although it is a martial arts sect, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect was an extraordinary talent and left behind many treasures. It's delusional for He Mountain Dao to think they can attack the Nine Profound Sect."

Lin Fei understood. Those high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao would definitely take action against him, but Lin Fei wasn't without a place to go.

The Nine Profound Sect mountain and Chang City were safe places.

Those high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao wouldn't dare to act recklessly in Chang City, nor would they dare to attack the Nine Profound Sect.

However, Lin Fei knew that it was not as simple as Ling Yao said.

If He Mountain Dao wanted to kill Lin Fei, they would naturally find a way to make Lin Fei leave Chang City or the Nine Profound Sect. For example, the Lin family in Zhou Mountain Mansion City!

Those immortal sects might not take direct action themselves. However, they could secretly manipulate some evil and demonic people to cause chaos in Zhou Mountain Mansion City and threaten the Lin family.

At that time, Lin Fei would inevitably come down the mountain. That would be He Mountain Dao's opportunity.

"Thank you, Senior Sister, for telling me all this," Lin Fei thanked her with a bow.

"Lin Fei, it was me who let you participate in the royal competition. Otherwise, this kind of thing would never have happened. So, I am the one who got you into trouble..." Ling Yao bit her lip. She was responsible for this!

She deeply blamed herself. She wanted to use some connections and methods to help Lin Fei. However, He Yunzi was dead and nothing could be undone. In this world, strength ultimately prevailed!

"I will write a letter to have the Lin family temporarily move into the Nine Profound Sect and I will not leave Chang City unless it's absolutely necessary," Lin Fei said calmly.

"Don't worry, Lin Fei, I will arrange for someone to escort the Lin family to the Nine Profound Sect as quickly as possible."

Ling Yao immediately went to make arrangements. She was a princess. With her token, Officials from all over would cooperate.

"Thank you, Senior Sister."

Lin Fei returned to his room. He recalled the words Ling Yao had said.

He Mountain Dao was about to seek revenge. Even with the protection of the Nine Profound Sect and the mediation of the royal family, Lin Fei killed He Yunzi. He Mountain Dao wouldn't let this go easily. They would definitely try every means to kill Lin Fei.

This world was so cruel, strength was supreme! Sometimes, even if one is in the right, it doesn't matter.

"My strength is still not enough!" A cold light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

If his strength was strong enough, he could easily deter He Mountain Dao with just one word. If his strength was strong enough, he could directly attack He Mountain Dao, trample down He Mountain Dao's sect gate, and extinguish their lineage, just like the founder of the Nine Profound Sect.

How carefree it would be to dominate the world and be invincible? Who would dare threaten the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect?

"System."

Lin Fei called out the system panel.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Eighth Level

Saber Intent: Mastery (16% Progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (45% Progress)

Three Vitality Technique: Level 8 (38% Progress)

Leaping Technique: Perfection (0% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Three Vitality Technique, currently only at the eighth level. His fist intent improved by 30% today and saber intent also improved by 5%.

As long as he used saber intent to kill strong enemies, it could be improved during combat. Fist intent, however, required victory and attention.

Nevertheless, Lin Fei was well aware, neither fist intent nor saber intent, reaching transcendence would happen overnight.

"Those above Qi Condensation Seventh Level are called high-level Qi Condensation cultivators. Those who can break through seventh level have strong mental will. Moreover, the spells and magical artifacts they control are very powerful.

Mastery in martial intent cannot deal with high-level Qi Condensation cultivators. At most, it can only intimidate them for a moment; killing them is almost impossible. Therefore, it is necessary to reach the transcendence level, or break through the Ren and Du meridians and advance to innate!

By then, innate true qi can break the magical artifacts of Qi Condensation cultivators and injure them. Combined with Martial Dao True Intent, killing high-level Qi Condensation cultivators should not be a problem!"

Lin Fei analyzed his current strength. In terms of Martial Dao True Intent, Lin Fei was already quite strong. But his cultivation was only at Acquired Eighth Level. There was still a gap to reach innate.

"I still have a large amount of Burst Qi Pills, which can be used to speed up the improvement of my inner power. If the Burst Qi Pills are not enough, I can write a letter to Lin Miao, asking him to disguise the Burst Qi Pills and send them to Chang City, which shouldn't be a problem.

If even Burst Qi Pills are not very useful, I can use Heavenly Meridian Pill. I will strive to improve to Acquired Twelve Level! By then, reaching innate will be possible! Once I reach innate, what can high-level Qi Condensation cultivators do? If He Mountain Dao's high-level Qi Condensation cultivators really dare to come, I will really dare to kill!"

Lin Fei's heart was also filled with killing intent. He Mountain Dao repeatedly made things difficult for him. Even a clay figure has a temper. It was He Mountain Dao's people who provoked Lin Fei in the first place. Lin Fei fought back and killed them, but now he had to bear the consequences?

If He Mountain Dao really dared to make a move, once I achieve great success in martial arts, I will definitely destroy the gate of He Mountain Dao!

104. The "Greedy" Three Vitality Technique

For a while, Lin Fei stayed in the South King Mansion. Moreover, Lin Fei spread the news. He was willing to trade the quota for entering the secret realm. However, it must be exchanged with pills or treasures that can enhance a martial artist's inner power.

A chance to enter the royal secret realm, for many Qi cultivators, was very attractive. After all, they might be able to obtain the spiritual medicine for Foundation Establishment Pill.

The royal family allowed them to take the spiritual medicine away. In that case, with the spiritual medicine, the Qi cultivators could try to refine a batch of Foundation Establishment Pills.

For Qi cultivators, it would mean a few more chances to establish their foundation. After all, even in the Immortal Sects, under normal circumstances, they would only give a Foundation Establishment Pill to disciples who had the potential to establish their foundation.

Foundation Establishment Pill could be taken multiple times. In theory, the more Foundation Establishment Pills one took, the greater the chance of successful foundation establishment. Many Qi cultivators would spare no effort to obtain the spiritual medicine for Foundation Establishment Pill from the royal secret realm.

As a result, many Qi cultivators tried their best to collect some pills or treasures that can enhance inner power. However, for three consecutive days, the things brought by the Qi cultivators were not satisfactory to Lin Fei.

...

"Lin Fei, Daoist Yu Xiangzi is here."

Ling Yao brought a "familiar face" to Lin Fei. It was Yu Xiangzi from the Green Jade Gate. She was defeated by Lin Fei in the martial arts competition. Lin Fei showed mercy and didn't hurt her mentally.

"Nice to meet you, Young Hero Lin," Yu Xiangzi slightly bowed her head. Now that Lin Fei had killed He Yunzi, the only benefit, perhaps, was his reputation.

Lin Fei's fame skyrocketed. No longer a nobody. Even the aloof Acquired Realm martial artists, when they met Lin Fei, would no longer dare to be as arrogant as before.

"Daoist Yu Xiangzi, there's no need to be so polite. I heard that Daoist Yu Xiangzi also wants to exchange the quota for entering the secret realm. I wonder what good things Daoist Yu Xiangzi has in her possession?" Lin Fei asked curiously. Just now, Ling Yao had told him that Yu Xiangzi had something good. That's why Lin Fei decided to meet with Yu Xiangzi.

Yu Xiangzi smiled slightly and said, "Young Hero Lin, I am aware of your requirements. Although there are many pills that can enhance inner power, it is difficult for you to find a pill similar to the Heavenly Meridian Pill. Even among the Immortal Sects, the pills they refine to enhance inner power are no better than the royal Heavenly Meridian Pill. And the Heavenly Meridian Pill can only be taken once, so I suppose Young Hero Lin doesn't need a second one.

Indeed, there is no better pill than the Heavenly Meridian Pill. But after much effort, I finally obtained a hundred-year-old Gold Crown Treasure Snake from my senior fellow disciples. This Gold Crown Treasure Snake has been nurtured for a hundred years and has consumed countless precious supplements.

Its fresh blood can nourish a martial artist's body, greatly enhancing muscles, skin, and vitality. And inner power is nothing more than what's produced by muscles, skin, and inner power itself. Drinking the blood of the treasure snake, it shouldn't be difficult to improve inner power. I have brought a jar of the treasure snake's blood here. Young Hero Lin can have a taste first. If you are satisfied, we can then exchange the quota for entering the secret realm. What do you think, Young Hero Lin?"

Lin Fei's eyes lit up. He then smiled and said, "Since Daoist Yu Xiangzi is so sincere, how can I not agree?"

Lin Fei agreed. Yu Xiangzi brought the treasure snake's blood and she let Lin Fei try it first. Clearly, she was very sincere. What could Lin Fei be unsatisfied with? So, Yu Xiangzi poured a small bowl of the treasure snake's blood from the jar.

Lin Fei drank it immediately. Instantly, he felt a warmth in his abdomen. After a while, this warmth had spread throughout his entire body.

Lin Fei's vitality, muscles, and skin, all seemed to experience a "second growth." They were constantly improving and strengthening. The blood of the treasure snake did not directly enhance inner power. Instead, it enhanced muscles, skin, and vitality.

As Lin Fei's vitality, muscles, and skin became stronger, the inner power produced naturally became faster and greater. Thus indirectly enhancing inner power.

About half an hour later, Lin Fei opened his eyes. He felt the inner power within his body. He was incredibly shocked. In just this short period of time, his inner power had actually increased by 10%!

"Your Three Vitality Technique has tasted the blood of the treasure snake and is in high spirits, full of energy, and the cultivation speed has greatly increased."

"Your Three Vitality Technique cultivation progress has increased by 5%."

The system's voice rang out in Lin Fei's mind. It was actually an increase in the cultivation progress of the Three Vitality Technique.

Rare indeed, truly rare.

Ever since Lin Fei began cultivating the Three Vitality Technique, he knew that this Three Vitality Technique was a calm and steady technique. It was difficult for anything to stimulate the Three Vitality Technique.

Therefore, all this time, the Three Vitality Technique had been steadily improving, little by little. There was basically no significant improvement through sudden enlightenment or the like.

But now, after Lin Fei drank the blood of the treasure snake, the Three Vitality Technique finally showed a response. The cultivation progress had improved somewhat. It seemed that the Three Vitality Technique was quite "greedy."

5% wasn't much, but that was just a small bowl of treasure snake blood. What if it were a whole jar of treasure snake blood?

"Daoist Yu Xiangzi, I'll trade this jar of treasure snake blood for entry to the secret realm! I'll give you the entry quota. I hope that in the secret realm, Daoist Yu Xiangzi can protect my senior sister," Lin Fei showed a slight smile on his face and said to Yu Xiangzi.

"Great, Young Hero Lin. I'm so grateful to you. I will definitely protect the princess."

Yu Xiangzi was overjoyed. Lin Fei really agreed to exchange the quota! Although the treasure snake was precious, how could it compare to the elixir for the Foundation Establishment Pill?

If they really obtained the elixir in the secret realm, Yu Xiangzi might have several Foundation Establishment Pills in the future. That's equivalent to having several more chances for Foundation Establishment than others. This was simply an opportunity to succeed in cultivation! How could Yu Xiangzi not be excited?

"Senior Sister Ling, I won't get involved in the matter of entering the secret realm. You can discuss it with Daoist Yu Xiangzi. I hope Senior Sister and Daoist can gain great harvests in the secret realm!"

After saying that, Lin Fei excused himself and left. He hurried back to his room and informed the servants of the South King Mansion that they should not disturb him unless there was something important. Lin Fei was going into seclusion!

With the Burst Qi Pill and this jar of treasure snake blood, Lin Fei believed his cultivation would definitely advance by leaps and bounds. He might not reach the twelfth level of the acquired stage, but reaching the tenth or eleventh level should not be a problem.

"Three Vitality Technique, I'm afraid you'll have to work hard during this time," Lin Fei muttered softly.

Lin Fei was going to take Burst Qi Pills and swallow the treasure snake blood. The Three Vitality Technique was destined to be several times busier than before. Fortunately, the Three Vitality Technique had a calm and steady temperament, and would not be impatient. Otherwise, Lin Fei would be a little worried. The Three Vitality Technique might go on "strike" and refuse to work.

"Let's begin."

Lin Fei took a deep breath. He poured out another large bowl of treasure snake blood and swallowed it directly.

105. Acquired Peak

In the blink of an eye, more than a month passed by in a hurry, Lin Fei had been in seclusion for a month. The blood of the Gold Crown Treasure Snake had already been consumed. The effect of taking the treasure snake blood and Burst Qi Pill together was beyond imagination.

Lin Fei's Three Vitality Technique, almost every day, advanced by about 14% in cultivation progress.

The ninth level, the tenth level, the eleventh level, the twelfth level...

In the blink of an eye, Lin Fei's inner power reached the twelfth level! The twelfth level of the acquired realm was also known as the peak of the acquired realm. All twelve meridians had been cleared.

Now, the surging inner power within Lin Fei's body could flow unimpeded through the various meridians, completing a small cycle. However, the inner power could only circulate within the body. It could only be considered a small cycle. If it were a large cycle, it would inevitably pass through the Ren and Du meridians.

But opening up the Ren and Du meridians was extremely difficult. This was related to whether one could advance to the innate realm.

The Ren and Du meridians were also known as the bridge between heaven and earth in the human body. Once the Ren and Du meridians were opened, one could connect with heaven and earth.

When the inner power circulates, it could form a large cycle, capture the spiritual qi between heaven and earth and transform it into innate true qi. Once it transformed into innate true qi, it was actually equivalent to a Qi Condensation cultivator's spiritual power.

This was why only innate martial artists could confront Qi cultivators. Because, in a sense, once a Qi cultivator developed their qi sense, in fact, it was equivalent to the true qi of an innate expert. Even at the first level of Qi Condensation, they were on par with innate experts.

Of course, comparing innate true qi with spiritual power only means they were at the same level. It did not mean their combat power was the same.

Some rogue cultivators who encountered innate martial artists wouldn't fare well. They might even be crushed by innate martial artists.

However, if it were orthodox Qi cultivators with magical artifacts, spells, talismans, and even the ability to set up formations, in such cases, it would depend on the martial arts strength and battle experience of the innate expert, as well as the strength of the Qi cultivator's magical artifacts, spells, formations, etc. Who was stronger and who was weaker could only be known after a fight.

Lin Fei swallowed a Burst Qi Pill directly.

"Buzz."

Lin Fei felt his inner power churning within his body, and then, there was no more. He swallowed another Burst Qi Pill. It merely made his inner power churn for a moment. Then, the inner power gradually calmed down.

As for increasing a certain percentage of inner power? Lin Fei sensed his current inner power. The Burst Qi Pill was like a drop of water entering the vast ocean. It couldn't stir up any waves at all.

Because Lin Fei had already reached the peak of the acquired twelfth level! His inner power could no longer advance!

"Sure enough, when inner power reaches its limit, even Burst Qi Pills are of no use."

A glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. He seemed to have anticipated this. After all, the human body is just mortal flesh. There is ultimately a limit.

For example, acquired martial artists use their bodies to contain inner power. There must be a limit to that. Lin Fei had now reached the limit of what his body could contain.

"System."

He immediately activated the system panel to check his martial arts progress.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Acquired Peak

Saber Intent: Mastery (Progress 16%)

Fist Intent: Mastery (Progress 45%)

Three Vitality Technique: Twelfth Level (Progress 0%)

Leaping Technique: Perfection (Progress 0%)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (Progress 0%)

In just over a month, Lin Fei's Three Vitality Technique had finally reached the twelfth level limit. It could no longer be improved. Moreover, Lin Fei still had a large number of Burst Qi Pills that he hadn't taken. This was also a miscalculation by Lin Fei.

He didn't expect that the effect of the Gold Crown Treasure Snake's blood would be so good. It allowed him to make rapid progress in just over a month, directly reaching the peak of the acquired twelfth level.

At this time, even Burst Qi Pills were useless. For Lin Fei, there was only one path for him now. That was to assault the Ren and Du meridians.

Once he succeeded in the assault, he would be able to advance to the innate realm. However, assaulting the Ren and Du meridians was extremely dangerous. One must not attempt it without full confidence. Because once the assault failed, the Ren and Du meridians would collapse. At that time, they would be completely blocked. And one would never be able to achieve the innate realm in their lifetime.

That's why the number of innate martial artists was so rare. It was because of the danger of assaulting the Ren and Du meridians, many people wasted decades at the peak of the acquired realm. They never dared to give it a try. By the time they were truly old and tried to give it a go, it was already too late.

"My inner power should be enough. After all, it is a combination of the three. Based on this foundation, my inner power far surpasses other acquired twelfth level peak martial artists. However, to assault the Ren and Du meridians, I must be well-prepared and ensure success. The experience of advancing to the innate realm is crucial."

Lin Fei furrowed his brows. He didn't have the experience of advancing to the innate realm. This was extremely important. If he were in the Nine Profound Sect, this wouldn't be a problem.

Lin Fei's master, Zhao Kongming, was an innate martial artist. He had enough experience to teach Lin Fei how to open the Ren and Du meridians and advance to the innate realm.

However, Lin Fei couldn't return to the Nine Profound Sect. What if He Mountain Dao's high-level Qi Condensation expert ambushed him on the way? Lin Fei didn't dare to take the risk, especially at this critical moment of advancing to the innate realm.

Lin Fei couldn't take any chances.

"Let's wait a bit longer. Senior Sister Ling Yao hasn't returned from the secret realm yet. Once she returns, with her identity as Princess, she must be able to find some experiences of martial artists assaulting the Ren and Du meridians. I've endured it for over a month, and now there's only one step left. I can't be impatient now!"

The more critical the moment, the more composed one should be. In this way, a few more days passed.

"Lin Fei, I'm back!" Ling Yao returned and there was excitement in her eyes.

"Senior Sister Ling Yao, what benefits did you gain from spending so long in the secret realm?" Lin Fei knew that Ling Yao must have obtained some advantages.

"Hahaha, Lin Fei, you wouldn't have guessed that in the secret realm, I found two Zhu Fruits. These Zhu Fruits can prolong one's life, strengthen the body, and invigorate the spirit. If acquired martial artists consume them, their inner power will definitely increase greatly.

Remember that I had previously taken the Heavenly Meridian Pill and reached the acquired seventh level, right? Now, after consuming one Zhu Fruit, I've already reached the acquired eighth level! I brought the last Zhu Fruit out for you, as you definitely need it!"

Ling Yao took out a box and she opened it. Inside was a red fruit, it emitted a unique fragrance.

"Senior Sister is truly blessed. Even able to encounter Zhu Fruits."

Ling Yao laughed and said, "Isn't it all thanks to you? If it weren't for you, I wouldn't have had the chance to enter the secret realm, and how could I have obtained Zhu Fruits? Lin Fei, hurry up and take it.

With the Zhu Fruit and the Heavenly Meridian Pill, you'll definitely reach the acquired tenth level! If you continue to practice diligently, reaching the acquired twelfth level peak in one or two years is a sure thing. By then, you'll be able to attempt opening the Ren and Du meridians and have a chance to enter the innate realm!"

The dream of martial artists was to achieve innate realm! But it was too difficult. It had stumped countless martial artists. Even though Ling Yao was now at the acquired eighth level, she still didn't have the confidence to achieve the innate realm.

Lin Fei took a deep look at the Zhu Fruit. Then shook his head, pushed the Zhu Fruit back, and calmly said, "Senior Sister, I appreciate your kindness, but there is no limit to the number of times the Zhu Fruit can be consumed. If I'm not mistaken, Senior Sister can consume another Zhu Fruit. Breaking through to the acquired ninth level shouldn't be a problem."

Ling Yao shook her head and said, "Lin Fei, don't refuse. What's the point of me reaching the acquired ninth level? This Zhu Fruit will be put to its greatest use when given to you. It's a pity that there are only two Zhu Fruits. I originally wanted to give them both to you, but I didn't recognize the Zhu Fruit before and mistakenly swallowed one, so now there's only one left..."

Ling Yao still felt it was a waste that she had eaten one Zhu Fruit.

"Senior Sister, I'm not refusing. But this Zhu Fruit is already useless to me. I don't even need the Zhu Fruit now, let alone the Heavenly Meridian Pill. Because I've already reached the acquired twelfth level and am at the peak of the acquired realm!"

The next moment, Lin Fei's inner power erupted completely. A terrifying aura emanated from Lin Fei's body, causing Ling Yao to tremble all over!

This wasn't Martial Dao True Intent. It was pure inner power. Acquired twelfth level, the true peak of the acquired realm, was only one step away from the innate realm!

106. Ascending Dragon Chamber

Lin Fei's majestic inner power was like a vast ocean. It surged powerfully, circulating within his meridians. One could even hear the thundering sound.

How strong was this inner power?

Ling Yao couldn't even withstand the aura of Lin Fei's inner power alone and took a step back. Her eyes widened, and her face showed disbelief.

"Lin Fei, you... you've reached the acquired peak? In just over a month, from the acquired eighth level to the acquired twelfth level? How did you manage to do that?"

Even if Lin Fei was a top-tier genius or even a once-in-a-century genius, to go from the acquired eighth level to the acquired twelfth level in just over a month was too exaggerated.

Ling Yao was a martial artist herself. Therefore, she knew how difficult this was. It was simply like a fairy tale.

"Gold Crown Treasure Snake! I also have to thank Daoist Master Yu Xiangzi. The treasure snake's blood was just too effective, which allowed my body to grow for a second time, thereby greatly increasing my inner power. In just over a month, I broke through four levels and reached the peak of the acquired realm. I didn't even use the Heavenly Meridian Pill..."

Lin Fei took out the Heavenly Meridian Pill. Originally, his trip to Chang City to participate in the Royal Competition was to help Ling Yao enter the top three. His biggest goal was this Heavenly Meridian Pill.

But what was the result?

Lin Fei didn't even use the Heavenly Meridian Pill and had already reached the acquired peak. This Heavenly Meridian Pill was now useless to Lin Fei. Not to mention the Zhu Fruit.

Seeing the Heavenly Meridian Pill in Lin Fei's hand, Ling Yao had to believe it. Lin Fei had really reached the acquired peak in just over a month!

"Is the blood of the Gold Crown Treasure Snake really that magical?" Ling Yao couldn't help but want to catch a Gold Crown Treasure Snake to try it out.

Of course, Ling Yao also knew that the Gold Crown Treasure Snake's blood exchanged between Yu Xiangzi and Lin Fei was actually fed with various precious supplements for more than a hundred years. There was basically only one unique snake. She couldn't try it even if she wanted to.

"Lin Fei, this is also your good fortune. Originally, I thought that obtaining the Zhu Fruit in the secret realm was already a great fortune. But I didn't expect that you would gain such a great opportunity just by exchanging a spot in the secret realm..."

Ling Yao's expression was a bit complicated. She couldn't help but think of an idea that if she had been given the jar of Gold Crown Treasure Snake's blood, would she be able to reach the acquired peak?

However, when this thought had just emerged, Ling Yao immediately extinguished it herself. She was not Lin Fei. She didn't have such a profound foundation and martial arts talent.

If the snake blood had really been given to her, it would probably be a waste. But for Lin Fei, achieving the innate realm was hardly a problem.

"By the way, Lin Fei, when do you plan to break through the Ren and Du meridians and attack the innate realm?" Ling Yao asked.

If Lin Fei could achieve the innate realm, it would also be of great benefit to her. It basically meant that her position as a princess would be as stable as a mountain! Even no one would dare to compete with her for the position of princess anymore. The deterrence of an innate martial artist was just so immense!

"I've been waiting for Senior Sister Ling to come back. Although my inner power is based on the fusion of three and is incredibly profound, I have no experience in breaking through the Ren and Du meridians, nor do I have an innate martial artist to teach me some techniques.

To be cautious, I didn't rashly attempt to break through the Ren and Du meridians. I wanted to ask Ling Senior Sister to think of a way, to see if she could find me some experiences of martial artists breaking through to the innate realm. So that it would be more secure!"

If possible, Lin Fei wanted to break through the Ren and Du meridians and achieve the innate realm with a hundred percent certainty, taking no risks at all.

"Lin Fei, you're doing the right thing. Even if your inner power is profound and you have a great chance, don't be anxious. If you want to attack the innate realm, you must make sure that there is no room for error. Just wait, I'll go to the palace. Our Great Chang was established on martial power, and the royal family has many good things. Maybe they can help you break through to the innate realm."

Having said that, Ling Yao immediately set off for the palace. Lin Fei sat cross-legged in the room. Ever since Ling Yao came back, his mood had completely calmed down. No matter if Ling Yao could bring him good news or not, he would try to break through the Ren and Du meridians and attack the innate realm. And success was the only option, failure was not allowed!

Time passed bit by bit. The sky outside gradually darkened. Suddenly, Lin Fei heard hurried footsteps from outside.

Lin Fei opened his eyes. Ling Yao was back.

"Senior Sister Ling," Lin Fei opened the door and welcomed Ling Yao into the room.

Ling Yao said solemnly, "Lin Fei, I went to the palace today and told the royal elders about your situation. The elder agreed to give you some detailed records of martial artists breaking through the Ren and Du meridians. Moreover, the elder allowed you to enter the royal family's secret place, the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber,' for cultivation.

This 'Ascending Dragon Chamber' is very mysterious. I only know that many of the innate martial artist elders, high-ranking Qi cultivators, and so on in my royal family are all in the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber.' I'm sure it must be a good place able to help you advance to the innate realm!"

Lin Fei looked at Ling Yao and said calmly, "Senior Sister, tell me about the conditions of the royal family. I don't believe that the royal family would give me such good things for nothing. There must be some conditions, some requirements!"

The things offered by the royal family were not something that could be given casually. Even with the face of Princess Ling Yao, it was no different.

The royal elders were an existence that even the Great Chang Emperor had to respect. How could the relationship of a princess persuade the royal elders?

"Conditions?" Ling Yao shook her head and said, "It's strange, but the elders didn't mention any conditions. Usually, the elders are not as easygoing as they were today. But as soon as I mentioned that it was for you, the elders agreed. By the way, the elders said something about forming a good bond with you. Just like when the royal family and the founder of the Nine Profound Sect formed a good bond."

Lin Fei's eyes flickered, and he whispered, "The royal family has a relationship with the founder of the Nine Profound Sect? Even forming a good bond..."

"I'm not sure about that. After all, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect is a figure from hundreds of years ago. But it's true that the relationship between the Nine Profound Sect and the royal family is quite good. Lin Fei, you can't miss this 'Ascending Dragon Chamber.' Even I don't have the qualifications to enter the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber'; there must be some special benefits."

Ling Yao said very seriously. She was also considering Lin Fei. Otherwise, she wouldn't go to the palace to ask the elders for help.

"Senior Sister Ling, I'll go! Since it helps me advance to the innate realm, I must go no matter what."

Without hesitation, Lin Fei immediately made a decision. In any case, Lin Fei's top priority now was just one thing. That was to advance to the innate realm! As long as he could successfully advance to the innate realm. Everything else was just a minor matter.

"Good, let's get going right away."

"Please lead the way, Senior Sister."

Lin Fei and Ling Yao got into a carriage together, quickly heading towards the palace.

107. Well Prepared

At the entrance of the palace, the carriage slowly came to a halt. A eunuch was already waiting at the entrance. Lin Fei got off the carriage.

Ling Yao couldn't help but lean out and say, "Lin Fei, follow this eunuch, he can take you to the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber.'" Then, Ling Yao spoke to the eunuch, "Thank you, eunuch."

The eunuch hurriedly bowed and said, "Your Highness, you're too kind. Young Master Lin, please follow me."

Lin Fei nodded. He then followed the eunuch into the palace. Lin Fei followed the eunuch all the way to the center of the palace. They slowly approached a palace wall. The eunuch searched for a while on the wall and then pressed hard.

"Click."

The ground slowly cracked open, revealing layers of stairs, forming a downward staircase. But the inside was not pitch black. There were candles on the walls, illuminating the passage.

"Young Master Lin, please go ahead. There will be someone inside to receive you, so I won't go down."

Lin Fei nodded. He went straight down the stairs. Lin Fei realized that the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber' should be underground. Moreover, as soon as he stepped on the stairs. Lin Fei immediately had a feeling.

"Is this... a formation?"

Although Lin Fei was not a Qi cultivator and couldn't set up a formation, he had seen quite a few formations.

For example, the Yin Gathering Formation, Concealment Formation, and so on. Therefore, Lin Fei had a good understanding of the formations set up by Qi cultivators.

At a glance, he could see that there was a formation here. Furthermore, the formation here was vast and extremely terrifying!

Soon, Lin Fei arrived at the end of the passage. Looking ahead, it was a huge underground hall. The place was filled with lit candles. The lighting was bright. However, there seemed to be very few people. There were only three elders sitting on cushions in the hall.

Lin Fei took a closer look. These three elders were the same ones who had presided over the royal competition earlier.

"Lin Fei pays his respects to the three seniors!"

Lin Fei took a step forward and bowed to the three elders.

"Lin Fei, you've arrived. The princess has told us about your situation. You want to unblock the Ren and Du meridians and break through to the innate realm?"

Lin Fei nodded and said, "Yes, my current inner power has reached its limit. The next step is to unblock the Ren and Du meridians and advance to the innate realm!"

The three elders nodded and said, "Then you've come to the right place. This is the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber', where only high-level Qi cultivators and innate martial artists can stay. As for the benefits of the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber', you'll naturally find out once you enter the secret chamber and try to unblock the Ren and Du meridians.

Here are the records of innate martial artists unblocking the Ren and Du meridians that the princess has obtained for you. These three books contain detailed records and insights from our royal family's innate martial artists. They should be of some help to you."

Lin Fei took the three books.

He hesitated for a moment but still asked, "Senior Sister Ling once said that the three seniors simply wanted to form a good connection with me, just like the founder of the Nine Profound Sect. May I ask the three seniors, why is this? Or, what is the connection between the Nine Profound Sect founder and the royal family?"

This was also a doubt in Lin Fei's heart.

The three elders smiled slightly and said, "You don't need to worry. When we say we want to form a good connection with you, it definitely means a good connection. Besides, there must be a reason for allowing you to enter the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber.' However, none of this is important. If you don't become an innate martial artist, you don't need to know the reason. If you do become an innate martial artist, this old man will tell you the reason."

Lin Fei understood. The innate martial artist was the key. Even if the three elders allowed him to enter the "Ascending Dragon Chamber" and wanted to form a good connection with Lin Fei, they must be looking to form a good connection with Lin Fei after he became an innate martial artist. If he didn't become innate, it would all be in vain.

Even if Lin Fei had comprehended Martial Dao True Intent and had killed He Yunzi, if he wouldn't become an innate martial artist, in the eyes of these royal elders, he wouldn't even be qualified to know the "reason."

"Alright, go to the Heaven Room. It's currently vacant, and you can practice in there."

"Thank you, three seniors."

Lin Fei took the nameplate. Following the direction pointed out by the three elders. Lin Fei quickly found the secret chamber of the "Heaven Room." So, he quickly opened the secret chamber and went in.

Watching Lin Fei enter the secret chamber, the gazes of the three elders were somewhat profound.

"Another martial arts genius has emerged from the Nine Profound Sect. However, it's unknown if this martial arts genius can inherit the mantle of the Nine Profound Sect's founder? Letting him enter the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber' and forming a good connection with him, is it worth it? If he doesn't become innate, it would all be in vain..."

The three elders sighed deeply. In their eyes, things like Martial Dao True Intent, or three-in-one inner power, were all useless, only by becoming innate would they truly "catch" their eyes.

At this moment, inside the "Heaven Room" secret chamber, as soon as Lin Fei entered the secret chamber, he immediately smelled a strange fragrance. This fragrance could refresh one's mind, and the chaotic thoughts gradually calmed down. Obviously, this fragrance was likely a very precious item.

Lin Fei didn't think about anything else. Instead, he completely calmed his mind. With his whole heart and soul, he prepared to unblock the Ren and Du meridians and try to break through to the innate realm! However, before that, he still needed to read the three books in his hands.

Lin Fei opened one of the books. This was the experience and insights of a royal family's innate martial artist when breaking through to the innate realm. This royal family's innate martial artist's experience was to push forward with all his might and directly unblock the Ren and Du meridians. Apparently, this innate martial artist's inner power was very strong.

The second book contained a different approach. This innate martial artist's inner power was not too strong. So, he used a more gentle approach. First, he slowly unblocked the Ren meridian and then the Du meridian. It took him a full three days to succeed. The process was also very thrilling.

The third book was similar to the experience in the first book. Both were pushing forward with all their might and directly unblocking the Ren and Du meridians.

After a long time, Lin Fei closed the three books. He appeared to be deep in thought.

"It seems that the most important factor for martial artists to break through to the innate realm is inner power! If inner power is strong enough, one can break through the Ren and Du meridians in one fell swoop. If inner power is slightly weaker, one has to use a more gradual approach, slowly unblocking the Ren and Du meridians, and taking a certain risk. So, which method should I choose?"

Lin Fei muttered to himself. Many thoughts flashed through his mind. However, Lin Fei quickly made a decision. His inner power had already merged threefold, his body had undergone a second growth, and the depth of his inner power was unimaginable, far surpassing other acquired peak martial artists.

In addition, the Three Vitality Technique was very good at unblocking meridians. For Lin Fei, he had at least a 90% chance of successfully becoming an innate martial artist

"The techniques to unblock the Ren and Du meridians, the precautions to be aware of. And the special place of the 'Ascending Dragon Chamber,' which helps martial artists advance to the innate realm. Enough, everything is well-prepared. There's no need to hesitate. Martial artists should be aggressive and not look back. So, let the breakthrough to the innate realm begin..."

Lin Fei hesitated no more. At this moment, he cleared all distracting thoughts from his mind. His mind was completely calm. He "saw" the Ren and Du meridians within his body, which like two chasms, separated Lin Fei's body from communication with the outside world.

"With one burst of energy, break through the Ren and Du meridians, and connect the bridge between heaven and earth!"

Lin Fei's thoughts moved. All the inner power within his body, like a restless volcano, erupted with a bang!

109. Martial Arts Inscribed On The Wall By The Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor

Lin Fei stepped out of the secret chamber and arrived at the underground hall. He saw three elders still sitting cross-legged on meditation cushions.

"Thank you, three seniors!"

Lin Fei respectfully bowed. Breaking through to the innate realm in the Ascending Dragon Chamber helped him consolidate his realm, saving him months or even a year's worth of hard work. It truly was a great place!

One of the elders, with a glint in his eyes, smiled and said, "We provided the Ascending Dragon Chamber, but you had to achieve the innate realm before realizing its benefits. However, calling you out of the Ascending Dragon Chamber isn't due to stinginess. The consumption of the secret chamber in the Ascending Dragon Chamber is massive.

For example, the Heaven Room you were in required us to activate the formation, assist you in cultivation, and provide you with a vast amount of Spiritual Qi. The consumption for just one hour is unimaginable for ordinary people. So, under normal circumstances, After breaking through and consolidating their cultivation in the secret chamber, one must leave immediately.

Even high-ranking Qi cultivators aren't allowed to enter the secret chambers in the Ascending Dragon Chamber for cultivation at will. They must make significant contributions to the royal family."

Lin Fei understood that the Ascending Dragon Chamber was even more valuable than he had imagined. The royal family's kindness to him this time came at no small cost.

"Three seniors, can you tell me now why I was allowed to cultivate in this incredibly precious Ascending Dragon Chamber?" Lin Fei was now an innate martial artist. He was on the same level as the three royal family elders. He was also entitled to know the "reason."

One of the elders sighed and slowly said, "Actually, the reason is simple. It's because you're a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect."

"Huh? A Nine Profound Sect disciple, just for that reason?"

Lin Fei found it very strange. There were many Nine Profound Sect disciples. Thousands upon thousands. The royal family didn't provide help to them. So why did they help Lin Fei? This reason seemed somewhat unconvincing.

"This has to start with the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor. After the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor achieved the Grand Master realm, he was distressed by the lack of a path to build a foundation, so he came to Chang City and sought the royal family.

He wanted to obtain the foundation-building secret of Great Chang's founding emperor. Our Great Chang founding emperor established the country with martial arts, and it wasn't just lip service. Nine hundred years have passed, and many people don't know that our Great Chang founding emperor was a Martial Saint who swept across all directions, invincible, and suppressed all those who defied him! Eventually, he established the Great Chang dynasty!

The Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor wanted to know the secret of how our Great Chang founding emperor achieved the Martial Saint realm. In the end, a Foundation Establishment cultivator from the royal family spoke up and granted the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor access. The Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor then entered the royal palace, entered this 'Ascending Dragon Chamber', and viewed the martial arts secret records left behind by the founding emperor.

How astonishing was the talent of the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor? His martial arts aptitude was no less than that of the founding emperor. The royal family originally had high hopes for the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor to become the second Martial Saint of Great Chang!

Unfortunately, after the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor read the martial arts secret records left by the founding emperor, he kept exclaiming, 'I don't believe it.' Then, the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor left a martial arts technique in the Ascending Dragon Chamber and left.

Later, the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor found some excuses and destroyed the mountain gates of several immortal sects. Those immortal sects had grievances against our Great Chang royal family, even secretly opposing the royal family. However, the Foundation Establishment cultivators of the royal family couldn't take action.

As a result, the problem was solved by the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor. We know that the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor was repaying the royal family's kindness. It's precisely because of this connection that when we learned you were a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect with outstanding talent, we were willing to establish a good relationship."

The three elders recounted the story of that year. It was as if they had witnessed the peerless elegance of the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor himself.

The Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor in his lifetime was not inferior to anyone. Even the Foundation Establishment cultivators greatly admired the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor. But why didn't such a stunning figure as the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestor build a foundation and become a Martial Saint? It's rather puzzling.

However, Lin Fei now had a faint guess. Perhaps it was related to the "martial arts secret records" left behind by the Great Chang founding emperor. This could also be considered part of the royal family's "secrets."

Lin Fei didn't expect that the Great Chang founding emperor was actually a Martial Saint! With his Martial Saint realm, he swept across all directions and suppressed everything! He must have also suppressed many Foundation Establishment cultivators from various immortal sects. Otherwise, how could he have established the Great Chang dynasty?

Saying that Great Chang was established with martial arts was indeed not a mistake. Especially since the founding emperor left behind martial arts secret records. These must be records related to martial arts foundation building.

Lin Fei felt a burning desire in his heart.

"Three elders, I wonder if I could have a look at the martial arts secret records left by the founding emperor?" Lin Fei directly asked the three elders.

The three elders shook their heads slightly and said, "Regarding the martial arts secret records, the founding emperor stated that only Martial Arts Grand Masters are allowed to view them. Otherwise, no one is permitted to see them! What a pity, how rare are Martial Arts Grand Masters in this world? Even though the founding emperor left behind many secret martial arts techniques for the royal family, we, the descendants, have no chance to pursue the path of martial arts.

For nine hundred years, not a single Martial Arts Grand Master has emerged from the royal family. Nowadays, the royal family has to rely on Foundation Establishment cultivators to barely maintain the balance and suppress the four directions. Therefore, Lin Fei, since you have not yet achieved the Grand Master realm, the martial arts secret records left by the founding emperor cannot be shown to you for the time being."

Upon saying this, the three elders shook their heads and sighed. With the various resources the royal family can obtain by controlling the world, it still cannot give birth to a Martial Arts Grand Master. It showed how difficult the path of martial arts is, as difficult as ascending to heaven!

Lin Fei understood. The martial arts secret records left by the founding emperor could only be viewed by Martial Arts Grand Masters.

"So, once I achieve the Grand Master realm, can I view the martial arts secret records?"

"Of course. The founding emperor left the martial arts secret records in hopes that a second Martial Saint would be born. By that time, the martial artist who has viewed the martial arts secret records, if they become a Martial Saint, would naturally owe the royal family a favor. If the royal family faces danger, the Martial Saint who has read the martial arts secret records would naturally lend a helping hand.

This is also a path left by the founding emperor for us, the descendants of the royal family, to form connections with Martial Arts Grand Masters. If you, Lin, become a Grand Master, you can come to see the martial arts secret records anytime."

Lin Fei nodded. The Great Chang founding emperor was indeed far-sighted. He took the initiative to leave behind martial arts secret records, generously allowing Martial Arts Grand Masters to view them.

Once they do, the Martial Arts Grand Masters would undoubtedly owe the royal family a favor. How could they not protect the royal family in the future? So, the royal family was able to maintain its power for nine hundred years.

"Thank you, three seniors. I have now reached the innate realm and need martial arts techniques in the innate realm. Therefore, I need to return to the Nine Profound Sect. If I ever achieve the Grand Master realm, I will definitely come to bother the three seniors again!"

After saying this, Lin Fei prepared to leave. After all, without innate realm techniques, Lin Fei would be unable to cultivate. He needed to hurry back to the Nine Profound Sect as soon as possible.

"Wait a moment."

At this point, one of the elders spoke, "Lin, my friend, why do you need to return to the Nine Profound Sect to obtain innate realm techniques?"

"Uh?"

Lin Fei was puzzled. Could it be that these royal elders would give him the techniques left behind by the Great Chang founding emperor? But that was simply impossible. Those martial arts techniques could only be practiced by members of the royal family. No matter how one looked at it, Lin Fei was not a member of the royal family.

"Lin, my friend, as I mentioned earlier. After the founder of the Nine Profound Sect viewed the martial arts secret records, he left behind a martial arts technique in the Ascending Dragon Chamber. That martial arts technique is truly profound and indescribable. Moreover, as far as I know, for some reason, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect did not leave this martial arts technique within the sect. Are you interested, Lin?"

Lin Fei's eyes lit up. A martial arts technique left behind by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect and it was left behind after viewing the martial arts secret records.

At that time, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect had reached the pinnacle of his martial arts cultivation throughout his life. The techniques he left behind must be extraordinary.

"In that case, I will trouble the three seniors."

"Of course."

So, the three elders immediately stood up. They led Lin Fei toward a distant secret chamber.

"Our 'Ascending Dragon Chamber' has many secret rooms. Back then, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect viewed the martial arts secret records in the Yi Room. He also left this martial arts technique in the Yi Room. Our royal family has completely sealed off the Yi Room and does not open it during normal times. Only innate martial artists are qualified to enter the Yi Room and view the martial arts technique left by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect."

As the stone door of the Yi Room opened, Lin Fei entered the Yi Room.

"Whoosh."

At first glance, Lin Fei saw the huge wall in the Yi Room. It was engraved with one large character after another. Even more surprisingly, these large characters were actually emitting an immense Martial Dao True Intent.

110. True Intention Scroll

A note from RighteousEgg

Qi = Energy. But when a type of energy approaches the nature of Qi, I would represent it as Qi. When it is released or transformed into other energy, I would represent it as energy.

"Buzz."

Lin Fei's saber intent and fist intent involuntarily burst out. They faintly confronted the Martial Dao True Intent within the large characters on the wall.

"Indeed, it's a martial arts technique left by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect!"

Lin Fei retracted his Martial Dao True Intent. He was naturally more than familiar with the Martial Dao True Intent of the founder of the Nine Profound Sect. At Ancestral Master Peak, Lin Fei would hone his fist intent and saber intent daily using the founder's Martial Dao True Intent. He could feel that the Martial Dao True Intent in these large characters on the wall was exactly the same as the Martial Dao True Intent in the steles at the founder's peak.

"This martial arts technique is called 'True Intention Scroll'! It is an innate technique that combines Martial Dao True Intent with innate True Qi. That is to say, only innate martial artists can cultivate it. Moreover, one must comprehend Martial Dao True Intent. It's too difficult to comprehend Martial Dao True Intent right after reaching the innate realm.

So, over the years, not a single innate martial artist in the royal family has practiced this martial arts technique. If they wait until they comprehend true intent before attempting to cultivate it, they must first disperse their cultivation.

Most innate martial artists are probably unwilling to disperse their cultivation. Therefore, over time, this martial arts technique has been shelved, with no one able to master it. Perhaps, this is an innate technique created by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect in a moment of inspiration, but the conditions are too stringent, making it difficult for anyone to meet them. Therefore, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect did not leave this True Intention Scroll martial arts technique within the Nine Profound Sect."

Lin Fei nodded. Regardless of why the founder of the Nine Profound Sect created this martial arts technique or why he didn't leave it in the Nine Profound Sect, it was unimportant to Lin Fei. What was important was that he was attracted to this martial arts technique.

Upon closer inspection, Lin Fei realized that this martial arts technique was indeed a cultivation method, not a combat technique. Cultivation methods were used for cultivation and realm improvement.

All innate martial artists basically absorb the spiritual Qi of heaven and earth and then transform it into innate True Qi. However, the True Intention Scroll was different. It took an unconventional approach.

Although it also transforms the spiritual Qi of heaven and earth into innate True Qi, the True Intention Scroll adds an extra step. That was to integrate one's Martial Dao True Intent. It allowed Martial Dao True Intent to fuse with innate True Qi. Then, the two complement each other. Then, a very unique power would be born, that was the innate True Qi containing Martial Dao True Intent!

It might sound a bit convoluted, but this was the essence of the True Intention Scroll. If innate True Qi fused with sword intent, it was called Sword Qi. If it fused with saber intent, it was called Saber Qi.

The True Intention Scroll also stated that the stronger the Martial Dao True Intent fused, the stronger the power produced. Therefore, under normal circumstances, it is fused with sword intent or saber intent. Fusing with fist intent was also possible, but it was slightly inferior.

Martial Dao True Intent regarded sword intent and saber intent as supreme. This was not just self-praise from swordsmen or saber users but proven in countless real battles.

The "Sword Qi" or "Saber Qi" cultivated with the True Intention Scroll far surpasses innate True Qi in quality. If one could cultivate it all the way to the peak, even reaching grand perfection and achieving the status of a grandmaster, it would be virtually invincible below the Foundation Establishment realm!

Moreover, Lin Fei faintly felt that with the founder of the Nine Profound Sect's extraordinary talent, creating this cultivation method might not only be for the sake of achieving great power in combat. It might also be related to building the foundation of martial arts and becoming a Martial Saint!

As for being invincible below the Foundation Establishment realm, the founder of the Nine Profound Sect did not need this technique to achieve that.

The sword qi or saber qi cultivated with the True Intention Scroll, when combined with a powerful combat martial arts technique, might not only be invincible below the Foundation Establishment realm but could even surpass it.

Lin Fei even felt that the founder of the Nine Profound Sect's vision might be able to counter-kill the Foundation Establishment cultivators!

This was somewhat insane.

After all, the Foundation Establishment was transcendental, a metamorphosis. It was an entirely different level of life. Yet the founder of the Nine Profound Sect had created a cultivation method that could potentially defy the Foundation Establishment!

From this cultivation method, Lin Fei seemed to understand the founder of the Nine Profound Sect more clearly. What an unparalleled elegance, dominating the world!

"True Intention Scroll, I have decided to give it a try. I'll be cultivating the True Intention Scroll in the Yi Room, which doesn't require the spiritual Qi of heaven and earth. So, please, seniors, there's no need to activate the formation; just allow me to practice in the Yi Room for some time."

Lin Fei respectfully addressed the three royal elders.

"Hahaha, this True Intention Scroll is something only young friend Lin Fei can cultivate. After all, Lin Fei had comprehended Martial Dao True Intent even in the Acquired Realm."

"Lin Fei, rest assured and practice in the Yi Room. No one shall disturb you! As long as the formation is not activated, there's no problem with how long you practices."

The three royal elders agreed readily. Lin Fei had become an innate martial artist. Having comprehended Martial Dao True Intent, his future prospects were immeasurable! The elders naturally wanted to befriend Lin Fei. They had already formed a good relationship before. Now, they were allowing Lin Fei to cultivate the True Intention Scroll. It was all to befriend Lin Fei.

"Lin Fei thanks the three seniors!"

"Alright, young friend Lin Fei, you practice in the Yi Room, and we won't disturb you."

Thus, the three elders took the initiative to leave the Yi Room. Then, the Yi Room slowly closed. The three elders looked at the closed Yi Room with mixed emotions.

"The True Intention Scroll, according to the Grand Elder, is extraordinary. Even among all the martial arts left behind by the founding emperor, none could compare to this True Intention Scroll. Especially its lofty intentions, even a Foundation Establishment expert would find it difficult to fathom. The founder of the Nine Profound Sect was truly astonishing. Had he become a Martial Saint, he might have surpassed the founding emperor. However, the path of martial arts is difficult, as hard as ascending to the sky. It's truly a pity for the founder of the Nine Profound Sect. I wonder, does Lin Fei have the potential to become a Martial Saint?"

A glint of sharpness flickered in the eyes of the three elders. However, their "good intentions" had already been extended. No one could predict how far Lin Fei could go in the future, which would depend on him.

At this moment, inside the secret chamber of the Yi Room. Lin Fei slowly walked over. He reached out and touched each character on the wall. Images seemed to emerge in Lin Fei's mind as if he had witnessed the founder of the Nine Profound Sect carving these large characters on the wall.

These characters were not carved with innate True Qi, nor with a saber or sword, and not with a finger, but with Sword Intent! The founder of the Nine Profound Sect had used pure Sword Intent to carve these characters.

"The Sword Intent at the perfection realm is so formidable that it can inscribe characters on the wall out of thin air..." Lin Fei murmured softly.

This refreshed his understanding of Martial Dao True Intent. It seemed that once Martial Dao True Intent reached perfection, it might undergo some special changes. At least, Lin Fei was sure that transcendent Martial Dao True Intent would not be able to inscribe characters on the wall.

Lin Fei felt along the wall for a while. After sensing the Martial Dao True Intent of each character, Lin Fei sat down cross-legged.

"I have basically comprehended the True Intention Scroll. If I cultivate it, I will definitely choose to integrate Saber Intent. However, it's not easy to begin cultivating the True Intention Scroll; it requires some contemplation..." Lin Fei muttered softly.

How difficult was it to cultivate such a peerless martial art? Even knowing the specific content, it takes a lot of effort to begin.

"Let's begin."

Lin Fei closed his eyes. Following the steps in the True Intention Scroll, he began to integrate strands of Saber Intent into his innate True Qi.

One hour, three hours, six hours...

Lin Fei cultivated for several hours. However, he still couldn't find the way in. Compared to the Three Vitality Technique, the True Intention Scroll was indeed too difficult. The difficulty increased tenfold or even a hundredfold!

Lin Fei had been attempting for so long, yet, he still couldn't begin.

"Ding, the peerless martial art True Intention Scroll despises your comprehension and voluntarily becomes your martial art."

"Your True Intention Scroll martial art has been waiting in the Yi Room for hundreds of years and has finally been fulfilled today by your cultivation."

"Your True Intention Scroll martial art is excited, increasing its cultivation speed by 50% and progress by 10%."

"Your True Intention Scroll martial art attempts to suppress your Saber Intent, making it subordinate to the True Intention Scroll."

"Your Saber Intent fights back."

"Your True Intention Scroll and your Saber Intent have begun a tug-of-war..."

The system's voice rang in Lin Fei's mind again. However, this time, there were more system voices. One after another. Moreover, the content revealed in the system's voice made Lin Fei's eyes widen, showing a strange expression.

This peerless martial art was a bit too "enthusiastic and proactive." There was actually a martial that stuck to him and begged him to cultivate it?

111. Saber Qi

"This True Intention Scroll has quite a...domineering and self-righteous personality."

Lin Fei saw through the "personality" of the True Intention Scroll at a glance.

Lin Fei was very clear that once martial arts reached him, they all had "personalities." Especially the more distinctive martial arts, if he found the right match for their "personality" and catered to their preferences, the martial arts would advance rapidly.

Most martial arts were diligent and conscientious, but the True Intention Scroll was the complete opposite. Not only did it actively "cling" to Lin Fei, but it even wanted to suppress Lin Fei's Saber Intent.

Keep in mind that Lin Fei really liked the "personality" of Saber Intent. Diligent and conscientious. Tough and not talkative.

When needed, Saber Intent was absolutely powerful. With Saber Intent, Lin Fei had slain countless formidable enemies. Just as the True Intention Scroll arrived, it wanted to suppress Saber Intent? Lin Fei wouldn't agree!

"Boom."

The struggle between the two martial arts was indeed astonishing. At this moment, in Lin Fei's mind, he saw a ray of light resembling a hidden saber. That was Lin Fei's Saber Intent. Another light group looked like individual characters.

Upon closer inspection, they were indeed characters. Each character of the True Intention Scroll combined to form the True Intention Scroll. The characters of the True Intention Scroll flew out one by one, surrounding Saber Intent from all directions.

Although Saber Intent kept erupting, the True Intention Scroll seemed to restrain Saber Intent effectively. In the struggle between the two, Saber Intent gradually fell into a disadvantage. Considering the reasons behind the struggle between these two martial arts, it became clear.

The True Intention Scroll was originally a martial art formed by the fusion of innate True Qi and Martial Dao True Intent. Its intention was to integrate Saber Intent. Therefore, the True Intention Scroll naturally restrained Saber Intent.

Lin Fei usually let the struggle between martial arts take its course. But this time, Lin Fei decided not to let it go. The domineering nature of the True Intention Scroll needed to be tamed.

"Saber Intent must be integrated with the True Intention Scroll. Only then can the True Intention Scroll be cultivated smoothly. However, who should be the dominant one is up for debate."

A sharp glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes.

"Boom."

In the next moment, Lin Fei mobilized his Fist Intent. Since Saber Intent was no match for the True Intention Scroll, how about adding Fist Intent? Suddenly, a gigantic fist appeared in Lin Fei's mind, ruthlessly smashing the True Intention Scroll.

"Bang."

The characters of the True Intention Scroll were scattered all over the sky. However, the True Intention Scroll seemed even more infuriated. It split some more characters and surrounded the Fist Intent.

The key was that even with some characters separated, the True Intention Scroll managed to suppress the Fist Intent. Now, the True Intention Scroll was simultaneously suppressing both Fist Intent and Saber Intent. With its personality, the True Intention Scroll would likely become even more arrogant.

"Innate True Qi, suppress!"

Lin Fei mobilized his innate True Qi. Immediately, a massive amount of innate True Qi erupted within Lin Fei's body. At the same time, in Lin Fei's mind, a phantom of innate True Qi appeared as well. Majestically, it pressed toward the True Intention Scroll.

"Bang."

Finally, the True Intention Scroll could no longer hold on. It was suppressed by the innate True Qi, Fist Intent, and Saber Intent combined. At this moment, the True Intention Scroll seemed to realize Lin Fei's intentions but was utterly helpless.

"Your True Intention Scroll feels wronged, and its cultivation speed is halved."

"Your True Intention Scroll is suppressed by your Saber Intent and starts to merge."

"Your Saber Intent triumphs over a strong enemy, feeling invigorated, and cultivates diligently, increasing the cultivation progress of True Intention Scroll by 10%, and Saber Intent cultivation progress by 10%."

The system's voice echoed in Lin Fei's mind again. Although the True Intention Scroll felt wronged and its cultivation speed was halved, making little progress in cultivation, it didn't matter.

After being suppressed by Saber Intent, the True Intention Scroll had to behave. Because now, the True Intention Scroll had fused with innate True Qi and Saber Intent.

With Saber Intent as the dominant force, the True Intention Scroll became Saber Intent's little brother. As Saber Intent cultivated diligently, the True Intention Scroll didn't dare to slack off.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately pulled up the system to check his martial arts progress.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Realm: Innate Martial Artist

Master: Early Stage

True Intention Scroll: Early Stage ( 20% Progress)

Saber Intent: Mastery (21% Progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (45% Progress)

Leaping Technique: Perfection (0% Progress)

Flowing Clothes Skill: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Lin Fei's True Intention Scroll had just begun cultivation, yet its progress had already reached 20%. This was truly astonishing. And Saber Intent, having suppressed the True Intention Scroll, seemingly, Saber Intent had also increased its progress by 10%.

"Saber Intent has merged into the True Intention Scroll, with Saber Intent being the dominant force. If the True Intention Scroll improves, wouldn't it also drive the Saber Intent to a certain extent?"

Lin Fei thought to himself. It seemed to be the case. Likewise, the improvement of Saber Intent should also be able to drive the cultivation progress of the True Intention Scroll to a certain extent.

At this moment, Lin Fei finally understood how profound the True Intention Scroll created by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect was. It could even be improved alongside Martial Dao True Intent!

Under normal circumstances, once Martial Dao True Intent was born, there would be no specific cultivation method. Because Martial Dao True Intent required tempering, refining, and comprehension. As for following a schedule like acquired cultivation techniques cultivating every day and then increasing inner power, that would be impossible.

Many people's Martial Dao True Intent might not make any progress for decades. But now, with the True Intention Scroll, As long as the True Intention Scroll improved, saber Intent could improve as well.

In a sense, the True Intention Scroll is also a method to cultivate Martial Dao True Intent. As the True Intention Scroll operated, Lin Fei carefully observed the innate True Qi within his body.

The original innate True Qi was semi-transparent. It was a gaseous substance. But now, with the fusion of Saber Intent, the innate True Qi gradually took on a hint of black. As more and more Saber Intent merged, the innate True Qi completely transformed. In the end, it was entirely converted into a black gaseous substance.

Lin Fei stretched out his hand.

"Go!"

With a thought, Lin Fei sent the innate True Qi flying directly toward the distant wall.

"Swish."

This wisp of Lin Fei's innate True Qi directly penetrated the wall and even created a tiny crack in the wall. This was only a strand of innate True Qi! Previously, a strand of innate True Qi was far from being this powerful.

"Now, the gaseous substance within my body is no longer innate True Qi. It should be called Saber Qi! Other martial artists absorb the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth, transforming it into innate True Qi. While I absorb innate True Qi, transforming it into Saber Qi! Saber Qi not only contains Saber Intent but even possesses the sharp and domineering attributes of a saber. It has completely changed innate True Qi, creating a brand new power!"

Lin Fei was shocked. The emergence of Saber Qi meant that Lin Fei might not even need to use a saber anymore. Because his Saber Qi was sharper and more domineering than a saber!

Moreover, every strike contained Saber Intent. In the future, opponents would not only have to withstand the sharpness of Saber Qi but also the attack of Saber Intent.

Especially when dealing with Qi Condensation stage practitioners. There would be no need to unleash Saber Intent separately.

A single Saber Qi slash could directly split the spells and magical artifacts of Qi cultivators! It would be equivalent to facing a double attack!

Particularly since Lin Fei's Saber Intent had only just reached mastery and the True Intention Scroll was only in the early stage. If Lin Fei could reach the perfection stage of Grandmaster and his Saber Intent reached perfection as well, at that time, when Lin Fei unleashed a hundred-meter-long saber energy slash, who could possibly withstand it?

112. Hidden Saber Shattered

Lin Fei withdrew the Saber Qi. The Saber Qi inside his body gradually became quiet. He even couldn't feel the True Intention Scroll refining the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth within his body. It seemed as if it had suddenly stopped. At this moment, a system message echoed in Lin Fei's mind.

"Your True Intention Scroll was just about to slack off when it was severely beaten by your Saber Intent."

"Your True Intention Scroll is filled with grievances, but under the coercion of your Saber Intent, it has no choice but to continue cultivating with doubled efforts."

As the system message faded away, Lin Fei distinctly felt that the Saber Qi in his body started moving again. And it was refining the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth like crazy.

However, the formation in the room hadn't been activated, the Spiritual Qi was scarce. But time was on his side.

Given the level of effort by the Saber Intent would constantly push the True Intention Scroll to practice diligently every single moment of the twenty-four hours each day.

In no time, Lin Fei would likely advance from the early Master stage to the middle Grandmaster stage!

"Indeed, helping Saber Intent to suppress the True Intention Scroll was the right decision. Otherwise, with True Intention Scroll's domineering, self-righteous, and even lazy nature, its cultivation speed would definitely be much slower than it is now…"

Lin Fei was very satisfied with the Saber Intent. As for the True Intention Scroll, it must be suppressed and driven by the Saber Intent.

"Now that the innate cultivation method problem is solved. It's time to solve the issue of combat martial arts."

The first thing that came to Lin Fei's mind was the Saber-drawing Technique. After all, the Saber-drawing Technique was Lin Fei's strongest martial art in the acquired realm.

"Your Saber-drawing Technique, due to the absence of inner power, is in low spirits and cannot nurture the saber."

Just as Lin Fei thought about the Saber-drawing Technique, the system's voice echoed in his mind. Apparently, the system wouldn't remind Lin Fei of every message. It would only prompt messages when Lin Fei needed them.

"Unable to nurture the saber…"

Lin Fei's brow furrowed slightly. He had thought about this possibility. After all, the Saber-drawing Technique was specifically designed for inner power. Without inner power, how could one nurture the saber?

"Let's try using Saber Qi to nurture the saber…"

Lin Fei had just started to circulate the Saber Qi. He prepared to follow the meridian circulation of the Saber-drawing Technique to nurture the saber.

However, as Lin Fei's Saber Qi started to circulate, as soon as it touched the hidden saber,

"Crack."

the next moment, the Hidden Saber shattered instantly.

"Shattered?"

Lin Fei looked at the broken Hidden Saber on the ground. It should be known that this Hidden Saber was a treasured weapon specifically crafted for the Saber-drawing Technique.

The material was of very high quality. But now, it was shattered by Lin Fei's Saber Qi in an instant. This demonstrated the incredible strength of Lin Fei's Saber Qi.

"Sure enough, the Saber-drawing Technique is no longer usable. The Saber-drawing Technique requires inner power to nurture the saber. Even drawing the saber requires inner power to circulate through specific meridians, unleashing unparalleled power. But my Saber Qi is completely different from inner power, even poles apart. Naturally, I can't nurture the saber, let alone use the Saber-drawing Technique."

Lin Fei had guessed this outcome. If the Saber-drawing Technique could be executed with Saber Qi, then the Saber-drawing Technique wouldn't be an acquired martial art. It should be an innate martial art.

Lin Fei just felt a bit regretful. The Saber-drawing Technique helped Lin Fei comprehend Saber Intent. Moreover, it had defeated numerous strong opponents in the acquired realm. Now suddenly it had lost its usefulness. Even the Hidden Saber was shattered.

Lin Fei tried but failed to elevate the Saber-drawing Technique to the innate level.

Every innate martial art was the crystallization of wisdom, far surpassing the acquired level. Elevating an acquired level martial art to the innate level was even more difficult than creating a new innate martial art.

"Let's try the Nine Shadow Saber Technique."

A thought crossed Lin Fei's mind and he thought of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. So, Lin Fei directly drew the Star Saber.

"Swish."

Lin Fei slashed with the saber. Immediately, the saber light surged. At the same time, nineteen saber shadows instantly merged into one. One saber, nineteen shadows!

"The Nine Shadow Saber Technique is still usable. After all, the essence of the Nine Shadow Saber Technique is actually a martial art at the Body Refining level. It's merely a saber technique and has nothing to do with the use of inner power or Saber Qi. However, using the Star Saber to execute the Nine Shadow Saber Technique doesn't bring out its full power. I can just use Saber Qi directly."

Lin Fei could now condense saber energy a dozen meters long. It was more than enough to perform the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. The only weakness might be the difficulty in sustaining Saber Qi. After all, Lin Fei was currently only in the early stage of the Master realm. His Saber Qi was far from being considered abundant.

However, if he reached the middle or even late stages of the Master realm, his Saber Qi would be extremely abundant, enough to replace a treasured saber with saber energy. Even now, as long as Lin Fei could finish the battle quickly, there should be no problem using saber energy to replace a treasured saber.

Next, Lin Fei tried his hand at fist techniques. The Quadruple Wave Technique could no longer be executed. Or rather, even if it could be executed, it wouldn't have much power. It's impossible to multiply the power by ten or more times.

Dragon-Elephant Vajra Fist could still be executed and its power was not bad. In other words, Lin Fei could now only use martial arts at the Body Refining level. All inner power martial arts could no longer be executed. Or even if executed, they would not have much effect. The same was true for lightness techniques.

Of course, this didn't mean that Lin Fei's fist techniques and saber techniques had weakened. That was not the case. Lin Fei now had Saber Intent and Fist Intent.

As long as he used fist or saber techniques, with the blessing of Fist Intent and Saber Intent and the explosive power of Saber Qi, the power would be many times stronger than in the acquired realm.

Now, Lin Fei could casually slash with his Saber Qi and he wouldn't even need to use the Nine Shadow Saber Technique. A casual slash with Saber Qi would be stronger than Lin Fei's Saber-drawing Technique after months, or even a year of nurturing the saber!

Innate represented a qualitative transformation! Moreover, Lin Fei cultivated the True Intention Scroll, transforming Innate True Qi into Saber Qi. It was almost like a second metamorphosis!

Lin Fei tried out his fist techniques, saber techniques, and lightness techniques. None of them were satisfactory and none of them were innate martial arts, nor could they utilize Saber Qi to maximize its power.

"It seems that I have to return to the Nine Profound Sect and select a few more combat martial arts," Lin Fei decided in his heart.

Combat martial arts were indeed necessary. High realm and powerful combat martial arts combined make up the true strength of a martial artist! Both aspects were indispensable.

However, to return to the Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei would inevitably have to leave Chang City. The threat of He Mountain Dao still loomed. Given He Mountain Dao's influence, there were bound to be spies in Chang City. Once Lin Fei leaves Chang City, He Mountain Dao's high-ranking Qi Condensation cultivators would most likely take action.

"Now that I have gotten innate realm, I am dozens of times stronger than before! Moreover, Saber Qi is more threatening to Qi Condensation cultivators than Innate True Qi. Even high-ranking Qi Condensation cultivators might not be able to withstand my Saber Qi.

If He Mountain Dao's high-ranking Qi Condensation cultivators dare to ambush me on the way, I'll let them have a taste of my Saber Qi!"

A hint of killing intent flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. He Mountain Dao had provoked him time and time again, Lin Fei would naturally not be polite. Especially now that Lin Fei had advanced to the innate realm. He already possessed strength that was not inferior to any high-ranking Qi Condensation cultivator.

In fact, Lin Fei could even rival top-tier Qi Condensation cultivators. He was even less afraid of He Mountain Dao. If He Mountain Dao really dared to attack him, Lin Fei wouldn't mind using Saber Qi to slay He Mountain Dao's high-ranking Qi Condensation cultivators.

He could even learn from the Nine Profound Sect's founder and find some random excuses to obliterate the He Mountain Dao's sect!

113. Left Chang City

"Rumble."

The stone door of Yi Room slowly opened. Lin Fei slowly walked out of Yi Room. The three royal elders were still sitting cross-legged in the hall. Upon seeing Lin Fei, they immediately noticed the difference that Lin Fei's eyes were filled with a sharp edge. It seemed like just one glance would make them feel a faint sting in their eyes. The three royal elders were shocked.

"Lin Fei, my young friend, it seems you have gained a lot from your retreat in Yi Room!"

The three elders had some guesses already.

Lin Fei slightly bowed his hand and calmly said, "Thank you, three seniors, for giving me this opportunity. Otherwise, I wouldn't have been able to practice this unparalleled martial art."

"Indeed, Lin Fei, you are truly a prodigy, having successfully cultivated the extraordinary skill left behind by the Nine Profound Sect's founder!"

Although they had already guessed, Lin Fei's admission still shocked the three elders. After all, the True Intention Scroll had been in Yi Room for hundreds of years. Not a single person from the royal family had been able to successfully cultivate it.

But Lin Fei, in just a few hours, had already succeeded. Lin Fei was a disciple of the Nine Profound Sect and the True Intention Scroll was left by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect. It was too much of a coincidence. Perhaps there was some connection.

Of course, Lin Fei wouldn't tell the three elders. It was the "True Intention Scroll" that begged him to cultivate it. Even though he couldn't practice this martial art himself, even starting was difficult, but the True Intention Scroll "stuck" to Lin Fei and automatically succeeded!

"Three seniors, I have now advanced to the innate realm and have cultivated the True Intention Scroll, so I will take my leave!"

The three royal elders nodded their heads. So, Lin Fei turned around and quickly left the palace. When Lin Fei returned to the South King Mansion, it was already getting late.

"Senior Sister Ling."

"Lin Fei, you're back? You..."

Ling Yao had obviously been waiting for Lin Fei for a long time. As a result, Lin Fei had just returned to South King Mansion when Ling Yao found him. Ling Yao's eyes were filled with anticipation. Although she also noticed that there seemed to be some changes in Lin Fei, she couldn't pinpoint the changes. She needed a definite answer.

Lin Fei knew what Ling Yao wanted to ask. He smiled slightly. He stretched out his hand and pointed at a flower bed in the distance.

"Whoosh."

Saber energy instantly penetrated the air, crossing a distance of several dozen meters. It struck directly into the flower bed. The flowers and plants in the flower bed seemed to have been cut by the sharp saber edge, leaving a clean slice.

"Releasing from the body! Innate True Qi! Lin Fei, did you really successfully advance to the innate realm?" Ling Yao was overjoyed, her voice trembling with excitement.

In any place, innate martial artists were figures who dominate their surroundings. They could be called Masters. That was to say, innate martial artists could establish their own sects.

"Yes, I have advanced to the innate realm!" Lin Fei personally confirmed. As for Ling Yao mistaking the Saber Qi for Innate True Qi, Lin Fei didn't explain. After all, Ling Yao only needed to know that Lin Fei had advanced to the innate realm, and that was enough!

"Innate, truly advanced to the innate realm..."

Ling Yao was still somewhat dazed. At this moment, she seemed to remember that she had only known Lin Fei for at most half a year. In less than a year, Lin Fei had made rapid progress all the way, astonishingly achieving the innate realm! It was like a dream. but the facts before her eyes proved that all of this was real!

"Senior Sister Ling, now that I have advanced to the innate realm, I need to return to the Nine Profound Sect to find innate-level martial arts to practice. So, I'm planning to leave Chang City tomorrow. If you need anything, you can send me a letter."

Lin Fei also revealed his plan. There was no need to stay in Chang City any longer. He had to return to the Nine Profound Sect.

However, Ling Yao frowned and said, "Lin Fei, it might be dangerous for you to leave Chang City now. I've been closely monitoring the movements of the He Mountain Dao during this time. Chang City must have spies from He Mountain Dao. I have already investigated some, but I haven't taken any action yet. Once you leave Chang City, He Mountain Dao will definitely know about it at first moment. Then, you'll be in danger."

Ling Yao's expression was very serious. He Mountain Dao was an immortal sect. They had high-level Qi Condensation cultivators and even top-notch ones. Their strength was extraordinary.

Lin Fei calmly said, "Senior Sister, I can't stay in Chang City forever. Besides, now that I've become innate, how can I be afraid? We, martial artists, should be aggressive and fearless of strong enemies. If we lose our courage and determination to face everything, our martial path will stagnate. He Mountain Dao is indeed a threat, but I am not weak. If their high-level Qi Condensation cultivators dare to take action, I'll cut them down!"

Lin Fei's tone was firm. Clearly, Lin Fei had made up his mind and would not easily change it. Ling Yao opened her mouth to say something, but in the end, she didn't speak. She wanted to persuade Lin Fei that if it were her, she would stay in Chang City for a lifetime rather than take risks.

But Lin Fei was not her. Lin Fei still had to pursue the martial path. If Lin Fei truly feared He Mountain Dao and stayed in Chang City forever, his martial path might really be cut off.

"Fine, I won't try to convince you. Now that you've become innate and also have Martial Dao True Intent, your strength is indeed enough to contend with high-level Qi Condensation cultivators. As long as you're careful, there shouldn't be too much danger. Just don't be careless. He Mountain Dao is a thousand-year-old immortal sect. Although there are no Foundation Establishment cultivators in the current generation, He Mountain Dao once had some, and their foundation is deep. So, be cautious about everything. No matter when there's hope as long as you're alive!"

Ling Yao's expression was solemn, her gaze fixed on Lin Fei.

"Sister Ling, don't worry, I'll be sure to stay alive. After all, only by living can I continue on the path of martial arts. Tomorrow morning, I will leave Chang City alone. You don't need to see me off, so as not to be discovered by He Mountain Dao's spies."

"Alright, I hope you'll be careful, Junior Brother Lin."

With that, Ling Yao left. There was no conversation that night. The next day, as soon as the sky began to brighten, Lin Fei opened his eyes. In fact, now that Lin Fei had advanced to the innate realm, his energy had become even more vigorous. He only needed about four hours of deep sleep each day.

The rest of the time, he hardly needed to rest at all. Moreover, Lin Fei faintly discovered that once he reached the innate realm, his body seemed to be undergoing some subtle changes at all times.

His True Intention Scroll absorbed the Spiritual Qi of the heavens and the earth, transforming it into Saber Qi. More than 99% of this Saber Qi was stored, but there was still a tiny bit of Saber Qi, slowly merging into his body's blood, muscles, and skin. In the long run, Lin Fei's body would undergo tremendous changes.

"Perhaps, the bodies of innate martial artists are slowly metamorphosing. It's just not very noticeable, only when the body has metamorphosed to a certain extent at the innate great perfection stage will it stop. Then they will attempt to build the foundation of martial arts, achieve Martial Saint, and completely transform. Without the changes brought about by Innate True Qi during the innate realm, it would probably be impossible to succeed in building the foundation."

A flash of insight crossed Lin Fei's mind. Perhaps, the reason why many innate martial artists fail to build their foundation was because their bodies haven't been "remodeled" enough. However, this was just Lin Fei's speculation. There must be many other factors in building the foundation of martial arts.

"Your martial arts skill, True Intention Scroll, has been practicing diligently all night due to the pressure of saber intent, and its progress has increased by 1%."

The system's voice echoed in Lin Fei's mind.

"In one night, the True Intention Scroll only increased by 1%. That is to say, in a whole day, the progress of the True Intention Scroll's practice may only increase by 2%. But it wasn't this slow when I was in the Ascending Dragon Room. Perhaps, it's because of the spiritual qi..."

Lin Fei furrowed his brow. The slow progress of the True Intention Scroll was something he hadn't anticipated. Because, based on his previous experience, when he first started practicing martial arts, he generally made rapid progress. The True Intention Scroll seemed to be lagging behind. The cultivation speed was very slow. Of course, this could not be blamed on the True Intention Scroll.

Under the "encouragement" of saber intent. The True Intention Scroll was definitely putting in its best effort to practice. But the practice results were still unsatisfactory.

There might be only one reason.

Spiritual Qi!

After all, Saber Qi was derived from the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth.

"The biggest difference between innate martial artists and acquired or body refining martial artists is probably that innate martial artists have requirements for their environment. They need a place with dense Spiritual Qi to practice faster."

However, this wouldn't pose a problem for Lin Fei. As long as he returned to the Nine Profound Sect, he believed that the Spiritual Qi on the mountain of the Nine Profound Sect would be abundant.

Moreover, Lin Miao was now at the Nine Profound Sect. At worst, he could ask Lin Miao to set up some formations to gather Spiritual Qi. That would certainly be enough for the practice of the True Intention Scroll.

After a night's time, the True Intention Scroll could still improve slowly. But saber intent didn't seem to be so easy. Even if the True Intention Scroll could drive the practice of saber intent, It would only be possible to boost saber intent if the True Intention Scroll had a significant increase. Otherwise, saber intent would still need to be honed or experienced sudden insight to continue improving.

"It's time to leave."

Lin Fei glanced at South King Mansion. Then, without alerting anyone, he rode a fast horse and quickly left Chang City.

When Lin Fei left the city gate, he used Princess Ling Yao's token. One of the soldiers guarding the city gazed at Lin Fei's retreating figure, and a strange glint flashed in his eyes.

"Lin Fei has left Chang City, inform the Immortal Master."

He Mountain Dao's spies had infiltrated the ranks of the city gate guards. So, no matter when Lin Fei left Chang City, he couldn't escape the eyes of He Mountain Dao!

114. I Have Been Waiting For A Long Time

Lin Fei sped up on his horse, which could cover 200 kilometers a day. However, he didn't rush on his journey. Instead, he moved at a leisurely pace as if he was waiting for something.

"Boom."

A thunderclap sounded out of nowhere.

Lin Fei looked up at the sky. Unbeknownst to him, dark clouds had gathered in the sky, even the sky had suddenly darkened.

Lin Fei looked around. There were mountains on all sides, with only one official road. Looking up the official road towards the mountain, there was a dilapidated temple halfway up the mountain.

"This is an excellent place to lay low. The sky is getting dark, and there's a heavy downpour. Let's stay here."

Lin Fei's eyes were deep, with a profound meaning. He didn't want to continue and he would wait here. So, Lin Fei led his horse and slowly walked towards the dilapidated temple on the mountainside. Soon, a man and a horse arrived at the dilapidated temple halfway up the mountain.

At this moment, the sky was pouring rain.

There were candles burning inside the temple. Lin Fei went in and saw about a dozen people inside the temple. There were men and women. The men were dressed as guards. The women seemed to be maids, and there appeared to be a madam and a lady among them. These people didn't look like a merchant group, but they were carrying a lot of things. Large and small packages, it looked like they were moving.

Lin Fei didn't pay attention to these people or greet them either. He just found a clean corner, then he sat down cross-legged, closed his eyes to rest, and waited quietly.

However, Lin Fei's arrival at the temple aroused the vigilance of the people inside.

"Madam, this man seems a bit strange."

"Strange? Judging by his appearance, he should be a wandering traveler, just coming to the temple to take shelter from the rain."

"Yes, just a wandering traveler, Uncle Liu, you don't need to be too nervous."

Both the lady and the maids shook their heads. How many wandering travelers had they encountered on this journey? They all dressed like this. It was normal to come to the temple to take shelter from the rain.

Uncle Liu, a bearded, burly guard, said solemnly, "Miss, it's pouring rain outside. But look at this man, is there any trace of rain on his clothes or shoes?"

"Hmm?"

At this moment, the lady looked carefully at Lin Fei. Indeed, as Uncle Liu said, there was not a single trace of rain on Lin Fei's clothes. In such heavy rain, even with an umbrella and raincoat, it would be impossible to have no wet traces on the body.

"Let me think... when this man came here just now, maybe it wasn't raining outside yet?"

The lady thought for a moment. It seemed that she couldn't remember whether it was raining when Lin Fei arrived at the temple.

Uncle Liu didn't say anything else. He was a guard. All he needed to do was to be secretly vigilant and ensure the safety of the lady and a smooth arrival in Chang City.

The rain outside was getting heavier and heavier and there were howling winds. The temple was drafty and leaking and rainwater splashed in from all sides. The lady and other women huddled in a corner where there was no rain leakage.

It was getting late. The guards and women started eating their dry rations. They stared at Lin Fei for a long time, but they didn't see him eating anything.

After hesitating, the lady said to a maid, "This wandering traveler may not have brought any rations. Xiao Ya, give him a portion of our rations."

"We shouldn't provoke strangers while we're away from home. Especially since this man is quite peculiar, we should avoid him if possible," Guard Liu hurriedly spoke, trying to stop the maid from giving food to Lin Fei.

"It's just some rations, it's fine. Xiao Ya, bring the rations to that young man."

The lady didn't change her mind. She watched Xiao Ya walk over, then turned to Guard Liu, "Guard Liu, it's true that we shouldn't provoke strangers while we're away from home. But what if this person is, as you say, a remarkable individual? My father sent us to Chang City, saying there might be an evil cultivator targeting us. If there's a remarkable person, maybe they could help us fend off the evil cultivator because of this ration. If he's just an ordinary traveler, it's just some rations, no big deal."

Guard Liu's eyes widened and seemed that he understood her point. So, he nodded, "You're quite thoughtful."

However, when Xiao Ya brought the rations to Lin Fei, he didn't even open his eyes. There was no response. Xiao Ya had no choice but to put down the rations and report back.

"Miss, he didn't respond," The maid said.

"We should be cautious about everything when we're away from home. Maybe he's worried that there's something wrong with the rations. But we've already given them to him, whether he eats them or not is up to him."

The lady didn't insist.

The rain outside was getting heavier.

"Boom!"

A thunderclap shook the sky. Accompanied by lightning, a figure seemed to appear faintly outside the temple.

"Who's out there?" Guard Liu immediately stood up. Everyone was startled.

"Hehe, you guys ran away pretty fast. Zhou Yuan is quite vigilant, sending his family to Chang City. If you had really made it to Chang City, I wouldn't dare to attack you there, that would indeed be troublesome. But this heavy rain came just in time to trap you here."

From outside the temple, a sharp, piercing voice gradually approached. Following that, everyone saw a black-robed Taoist, step by step, walking into the temple from the outside. Moreover, this Taoist seemed unaffected by the pouring rain. There seemed to be a layer of white light around him, keeping the rainwater away from his body.

After entering the temple, there was not even a trace of rainwater on him. Seeing this scene, the guards and women turned pale. Guard Liu's voice trembled as he shouted, "Qi Cultivator, you're an evil Qi Cultivator!"

"Whoosh."

Guard Liu drew his saber. However, holding the sharp saber in his hand didn't make him feel safe at all. He was just a mere acquired martial artist. What chance did he have against a Qi Cultivator?

"Mere martial artist."

The black-robed Daoist flicked his finger. A flash of blood-red light appeared in an instant. In the next moment, the guard Liu widened his eyes. An unknown wound appeared on his neck and blood spurted out instantly.

With a "thud," Guard Liu fell to the ground. None could see how the black-robed Daoist attacked.

"Ah..."

The women in the temple screamed in fear. However, the numerous guards didn't dare to approach the black-robed Daoist.

"Hehe, capturing you will surely make Zhou Yuan reconsider. Will he choose the magical artifact or his family? Being a mere mortal, keeping the magical artifact he accidentally obtained will only bring disaster."

The black-robed Daoist sneered, ready to make his move. At this moment, everyone's eyes turned to Lin Fei. However, Lin Fei remained motionless. Disappointment filled their hearts.

"Mother, it seems we cannot escape this fate. Who knows what torture we'll endure at the hands of this demonic Daoist. Mother, I'll go first!"

She fiercely pulled out a dagger she carried with her, preparing to end her life.

"Boom."

At that moment, thunder and lightning flashed outside. The black-robed Daoist seemed to sense something.

"Whoosh."

He abruptly turned his head, looking towards the broken temple's entrance.

"Who?"

The black-robed Daoist stared intently at the temple's exterior. Now, two more figures appeared outside the broken temple. Two gray-robed Daoists stood mid-air outside the temple. Step by step, they seemed to "float" into the temple.

...

The black-robed Daoist became extremely cautious, speaking in a deep voice, "Have you two also come for Zhou Yuan's family? Unfortunately, they've already fallen into my hands. You two should just leave."

The black-robed Daoist carefully pondered. The news of Zhou Yuan accidentally obtaining a magical artifact hadn't spread and he had only found out by chance. If it weren't for the difficulty of making a move in Chang City, would he have gone through all this trouble to capture Zhou Yuan's family? Now that he had captured Zhou Yuan's family, the black-robed Daoist had no intention of giving up.

However, the two gray-robed Daoists didn't respond. Instead, they glanced at the black-robed Daoist. Then, one of the gray-robed Daoists extended his hand, pointing at the black-robed Daoist.

"Rogue cultivators like you are definitely demonic beings, deserving death!"

"You..."

The black-robed Daoist's face changed dramatically. His spiritual power surged, ready to cast a spell, but it was too late.

"Splash."

The next moment, the black-robed Daoist's eyes widened, his body trembling. Then, his corpse fell straight to the ground.

Dead!

He couldn't even withstand a single attack. The guards and women became even more desperate. The black-robed Daoist was already powerful. Now, two stronger gray-robed Daoists had arrived. What hope did they have?

However, the two gray-robed Daoists didn't even glance at the guards and women. Instead, they slightly bowed to the corner of the temple, saying, "He Mountain Dao's He Yuanzi and He Qingzi pay respect to Layman Lin!"

The lady and the women in the temple were taken aback. They looked at Lin Fei in the distance with surprise.

"These two Daoists aren't here for us?"

Regardless of what the women and guards thought, The gray-robed Daoists' gazes were fixed on Lin Fei.

Lin Fei opened his eyes and looked at the two Daoists with a calm gaze.

"You're too slow, I've been waiting for a long time!"

115. High Level Qi Condensation Cultivators

"Mm?"

He Yuanzi and He Qingzi's eyes slightly narrowed.

"Layman Lin knew we were coming, yet he calmly stayed here. It seems Layman Lin is quite confident. Originally, we didn't mind the insignificant disciple you killed, as you have the princess and Nine Profound Sect on your side. He Mountain Dao didn't care.

But He Yunzi, you shouldn't have killed! He Yunzi was the future hope of our He Mountain Dao. Now, our sect leader is furious. So, we have to use Layman Lin's head to pay tribute to He Yunzi!"

The two Daoists spoke of murder, yet their tone was nonchalant as if it was merely an ordinary matter, not taking it to heart at all.

"Using my head to pay tribute to He Yunzi. Well said. If I were the He Mountain Dao sect leader, I would do the same. However, there's one point you may have overlooked. Can you actually kill me?"

The next moment, Lin Fei slowly stood up. At the same time, the saber intent within him exploded instantly.

"Boom."

Lin Fei's saber intent erupted. To ordinary people, they wouldn't be able to sense the saber intent. But they could feel Lin Fei transforming into a supreme treasure saber, suddenly revealing his sharpness, imposingly aggressive.

"Hum."

The next moment, the sabers in the guards' hands began to hum softly as if they wanted to unsheathe themselves.

"What's going on?"

"My saber seems to want to unsheathe itself."

"What kind of spell is this?"

These guards were utterly astonished. They didn't know what was happening.

"No... it's not a spell, it's not a spell at all. If I'm not mistaken, this is saber intent! The legendary Martial Dao True Intent that only martial artists can cultivate. Unexpectedly, this man has actually cultivated Martial Dao True Intent, even daring to confront two Qi cultivators, it's... unbelievable!"

Speaking was the young lady, her face full of disbelief. Although she hadn't practiced martial arts, she had been well-educated since childhood and she was quite interested in martial arts. Therefore, she had read many martial arts secrets and she knew some secrets of martial arts.

Lin Fei's display of saber intent at this moment caused the sabers of the many guards to "hum" loudly as if they couldn't control their sabers. This was characteristic of saber intent! In front of a martial artist who comprehended saber intent, drawing a saber was a luxury.

At this moment, in the eyes of He Yuanzi and He Qingzi, a phantom great saber appeared above Lin Fei's head. That was the saber intent!

Lin Fei didn't display his fist intent. He knew that in terms of lethality, fist intent was ultimately inferior to saber intent. Facing high-level Qi Condensation cultivators, Lin Fei still "respected" his opponents. Not underestimating them in the slightest, he fully unleashed his saber intent!

"What a saber intent!"

A glint flashed in He Yuanzi's eyes. At the same time, He Yuanzi and He Qingzi both displayed their magical artifacts, protecting themselves by their side.

"Slash!"

Lin Fei's saber intent fiercely slashed down.

"Boom."

He Yuanzi and He Qingzi felt their minds shake.

Their willpower was quite strong. Moreover, they didn't have any mental flaws. But even so, they felt as if their minds were being torn apart by a raging storm and painful to the extreme. Saber intent wasn't that easy to endure. Even if they could withstand it, it would still be very painful.

However, He Yuanzi and He Qingzi eventually resisted Lin Fei's saber intent.

He Yuanzi's face was a bit pale, and he smiled coldly, "Do you know the difference between high-level Qi Condensation cultivators and low-level ones? The biggest difference is actually the spiritual power within their bodies. When a Qi Condensation cultivator reaches the seventh level, their spiritual power can circulate autonomously.

Even if their consciousness stops, their spiritual power can still circulate. That is to say, no matter how strong your saber intent is, as long as it doesn't kill us in an instant, you can't break through our magical artifact defense. Our spiritual power will keep circulating without any pause. Acquired martial artists may be able to kill low-level Qi Condensation cultivators by relying on some tactics or luck. But acquired martial artists will never be able to kill high-level Qi Condensation cultivators!"

He Yuanzi and He Qingzi resisted Lin Fei's saber intent. In their opinion, Lin Fei had no hope left. He was undoubtedly going to die! Because no matter what, Lin Fei, an acquired martial artist, couldn't break through their magical artifact defense. This was the advantage of high-level Qi Condensation cultivators!

"High-level Qi Condensation cultivators..."

Lin Fei calmly looked at He Yuanzi and He Qingzi. The opponents were high-level Qi Condensation cultivators. Indeed, they were somewhat different from He Yunzi.

Although He Yunzi was at the sixth level of Qi Condensation, when he encountered Lin Fei, his consciousness was heavily damaged by the saber intent.

He Yunzi's spiritual power stopped for a moment. Then Lin Fei found an opportunity and killed him with a single saber strike. But facing high-level Qi Condensation cultivators, Lin Fei couldn't find any "opening" anymore.

When martial artists vs. high-level Qi Condensation cultivators, There was only one way to defeat them. That was to fight them head-on, breaking the high-level Qi Condensation cultivators' magical artifacts or spells.

Lin Fei suddenly withdrew his saber intent. He no longer used his saber intent. Apparently, his current mastery realm saber intent only had a few effects on high-level Qi Condensation cultivators. As for directly killing with saber intent, Lin Fei's saber intent hadn't reached that level yet.

"Have you given up? An acquired realm cultivator who can comprehend saber intent, your talent probably rivals that of the founder of the Nine Profound Sect. But unfortunately, you are still mortal. How can a mortal body fight against us Qi Condensation cultivators?"

He Yuanzi stepped towards Lin Fei, one step at a time. Beside He Yuanzi, a small sword floated. It was not a talisman but a real magical artifact flying sword. High-level Qi Condensation cultivators could use it to kill from a distance.

Even innate martial artists were extremely wary of flying swords. The flying sword emitted a chilling and sharp aura. As long as He Yuanzi had a thought, he could instantly pierce Lin Fei's head.

"Whoosh."

A soft sound.

It wasn't He Yuanzi who used the flying sword, but Lin Fei.

Lin Fei surprisingly didn't retreat but advanced, even rushing towards He Yuanzi.

"The so-called bravery of a martial artist is nothing more than a futile struggle before death."

He Yuanzi shook his head slightly.

"Go."

He Yuanzi had a thought. Immediately, the flying sword turned into a flash of white light. It instantly flew towards Lin Fei.

At this moment, Lin Fei was only dozens of meters away from He Yuanzi, but this short distance seemed like an insurmountable chasm. He Yuanzi seemed to be able to "see" the look of despair and fear on Lin Fei's face at the end.

The flying sword arrived in an instant. Not only was the flying sword in Lin Fei's line of sight but also He Yuanzi, who was dozens of meters away.

Suddenly, Lin Fei stopped. At this distance, Lin Fei felt it was about right.

The next moment, Lin Fei extended his fair right hand. He didn't draw his saber. Instead, he lifted his hand.

"Slash!"

Lin Fei let out a low shout. His hand slashed fiercely through the air, aimed at He Yuanzi.

116. Thirty Meters of Saber Energy

Lin Fei's slash was made with his hand instead of a saber. In the eyes of others, it seemed like child's play.

Lin Fei obviously had a saber, so why didn't he draw it? How could a fleshly hand replace a fine steel treasure saber?

However, in the next moment, everyone's eyes widened. Lin Fei's hand slashed down fiercely.

"Boom."

Like a volcanic eruption, a violent surge of blackish airflow burst out from Lin Fei's right hand.

It was actually condensed into a saber!

Saber Qi!

This was the purest Saber Qi!

For the first time, Lin Fei exerted his full strength to release Saber Qi.

Immediately, the Saber Qi followed Lin Fei's hand and erupted all at once.

A thirty-meter-long saber energy, descending from the sky, slashed directly at He Yuanzi.

"Splatter."

He Yuanzi originally used his flying sword. However, under the impact of Lin Fei's thirty meters saber energy, it was instantly cut down and broken in two.

At the same time, Lin Fei's saber energy landed on top of He Yuanzi's head. He Yuanzi originally had a magical artifact protecting his body, but Lin Fei's Saber Qi cut through it like cutting tofu.

Without any hindrance, it directly penetrated the protective shield of the magical artifact. He Yuanzi was split in half from the top of his head.

"Thump."

He Yuanzi's two halves fell to the ground. He might not have understood why he died even until his death.

"Saber...saber light? A thirty-meter-high saber light?"

"No, that's not saber light anymore. It's saber energy, similar to Innate True Qi, but with a terrifying saber intent!"

The women among the spectators whispered softly. At this moment, everyone was almost dumbfounded. They stared in amazement at the terrifying saber energy in the void.

Even innate martial artists, who could project Innate True Qi from a distance and even combine it with their treasure sabers, could only unleash a little saber light.

Half-a-meter saber energy was already impressive. A meter saber energy was shocking enough.

And now?

Lin Fei didn't use a saber. He only used a pair of fleshly hands.

With his flesh and blood body, he actually stimulated thirty-meter saber energy.

This was simply unbelievable!

"Miss... have you ever seen a thirty meters saber energy?" The maid asked with a trembling voice. The Miss didn't speak but stared intently at Lin Fei.

Thirty-meter saber energy! Not only had she never seen it before, but she had never even heard of it. And now, she was witnessing it with her own eyes.

A martial artist who could unleash a thirty meters Saber Qi and even kill a high-level Qi Condensation cultivator with a single slash!

Such means, such power, it was simply like a mythical tale.

She would never believe it if she hadn't seen it with her own eyes.

"He Yuanzi!"

He Qingzi was somewhat stunned. He hadn't made a move before because he thought He Yuanzi's single move was enough. All he needed to do was guard against Lin Fei's escape.

And now?

He Yuanzi was dead right in front of him. Killed by Lin Fei's thirty meters saber Qi.

A thirty meters Saber Qi? Was Lin Fei really a martial artist?

"Go!"

He Qingzi made a decisive decision. He didn't even bother with He Yuanzi.

He immediately unleashed his spiritual power and shot toward the broken temple's exit like a streak of light.

He Qingzi wanted to escape and was so decisive.

Facing a monster like Lin Fei, He Qingzi had completely lost his confidence.

How could he dare to make a move?

"Think you can escape?"

Lin Fei's eyes turned cold, and his hand faced He Qingzi's direction: "Go."

"Whoosh."

Immediately, a saber energy, like an arrow leaving the bow, flashed through the air and disappeared.

In an instant, it flew towards He Qingzi.

He Qingzi also had a protective shield from his magical artifact. Moreover, he had even cast a defensive spell. It was like two layers of spells.

However, facing Lin Fei's saber energy, was like cutting tofu.

The shield was instantly broken by the saber energy.

And in the blink of an eye, the saber energy penetrated He Qingzi's body.

"Splatter."

He Qingzi's figure paused.

Finally, his body fell heavily to the ground.

Motionless, devoid of the breath of life.

He was dead!

He Qingzi was also dead. Killed by Lin Fei's single saber energy with ease.

The strength of Lin Fei's saber energy even exceeded Lin Fei's own imagination.

Looking at the two halves of He Yuanzi's corpse on the ground and then at He Qingzi's corpse being washed by the rain outside the broken temple, Lin Fei's mind was stirred.

"The power of Saber Qi cultivated from the True Intention Scroll is specifically designed to counter Qi Condensation cultivators. The greatest reliance of Qi cultivators is the protective shield formed by spiritual power or magical artifacts. However, the transformed Saber Qi, which has merged with the saber intent, can easily cut through the defense shield of Qi cultivators like chopping vegetables. Once the defense shield is gone, Qi cultivators are naturally vulnerable!"

Lin Fei fell silent. He finally understood now why the founder of the Nine Profound Sect left the True Intention Scroll in the Ascending Dragon Chamber but didn't leave it for the Nine Profound Sect.

This True Intention Scroll seemed to be just a martial arts technique. But in reality? It almost specifically counters Qi cultivators.

If this were to be spread and known to Qi cultivators, would they let it go?

Perhaps those immortal sects and Daoist schools would have attacked the Nine Profound Sect. How could the Nine Profound Sect continue for hundreds of years?

The True Intention Scroll was truly powerful. If it could be cultivated to the perfection realm and achieve the status of a Grandmaster, wouldn't it be able to counter-kill Foundation Establishment Cultivators?

"The founder's talent is truly amazing. I admire him!"

Lin Fei couldn't help but admire the founder of the Nine Profound Sect in his heart. Although the founder of the Nine Profound Sect did not build the foundation and become a Martial Saint, Lin Fei knew the founder of the Nine Profound Sect was not inferior to a Martial Saint.

In terms of martial arts talent, he was even stronger than a Martial Saint! Otherwise, how could he create such a magical and profound True Intention Scroll?

The heavy rain continued. Occasionally, there was muffled thunder echoing between heaven and earth.

In the broken temple, the thick smell of blood permeated the air. Outside the temple, under the washing of the rain, He Qingzi's corpse could not even be seen with bloodstains. It was all washed away by the rain to the foot of the mountain.

No one could have imagined that in this remote and broken temple, two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators had died. If this news were to spread back to He Mountain Dao, it would surely shake the entire He Mountain Dao!

However, Lin Fei didn't care. It was impossible to hide. Even if he killed everyone in the broken temple, he still couldn't hide it. After all, the two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao were here to intercept and kill Lin Fei.

Now, both high-level Qi Condensation cultivators were dead. Lin Fei was alive. The result, naturally, was self-evident.

Lin Fei turned his head. His calm gaze swept over the group of people in the broken temple.

All the guards and women lowered their heads. The ladies and maids were shivering with fear. Only the Miss, though also frightened, looked at Lin Fei with a somewhat "fanatical" gaze.

In her heart, a storm had already been set off. Martial arts could actually be so powerful!? Saber energy could be thirty meters high! With a wave of the man's hand, two Qi Condensation cultivators died. Without even a chance to fight back. This even exceeded her understanding of martial arts.

Lin Fei bent down, picked up the dry food from the ground, and tucked it into his arms. He didn't speak, nor did he pay attention to the group of people in the broken temple.

Lin Fei led the horse, facing the pouring rain, and walked out of the broken temple. His body was covered in a layer of saber energy. Even with the heavy rain falling on him, not a single corner of his clothes was wet.

Afterward, Lin Fei's figure gradually faded away and finally disappeared into the night.

"It seems like that man has gone far away. And he took the dry food with him."

The maid's voice trembled continuously.

"Yeah, he took the dry food. One portion of dry food in exchange for our lives. Let's go, we must leave this place immediately..."

With gritted teeth, the Miss had made a resolute decision.

Even if it was raining heavily outside, they had to leave.

117. Immortal Slayer Saber

"Buzz."

Ripples appeared in the void. Following that, a huge mountain gate appeared in the void.

An old man sneered, "These immortal sects really have a high opinion of themselves. I come on behalf of the Royal Supreme Elder, yet they don't come out to greet me but instead ask me to enter."

The old man's eyes were cold. However, this was the current situation in Great Chang. The royal family was continuously weakening and their control over local areas was far from what it used to be. Especially when it came to immortal sects, they had almost no control.

If it were nine hundred years ago when the Great Chang founding emperor was still alive, would these immortal sects dare to be so presumptuous? With a single imperial edict from the Great Chang founding emperor, an entire immortal sect would be annihilated!

However, he had important matters to attend to. So he could only step into the He Mountain Dao mountain gate.

"Swish."

The old man stepped into the mountain gate of He Mountain Dao. Immediately, the scene before his eyes changed instantly. Layers of mountains were piled up, with immortal cranes flying and dancing, just like a fairyland.

"Whoosh."

In front of the old man, a white jade staircase appeared. This staircase seemed to lead to the highest peak.

The old man sneered but did not step onto the white jade staircase. Instead, he shouted loudly towards the mountain, "By order of the Royal Supreme Elder, He Mountain Dao is not allowed to send high-level Qi Condensation experts down the mountain to deal with Nine Profound Sect disciple Lin Fei. If He Mountain Dao defies, the Royal Supreme Elder will personally come to the mountain and level He Mountain Dao!"

After finishing his words, the old man didn't care about the anger of the people on the mountain and directly turned around and disappeared without a trace. Apparently, he had already left the mountain gate of He Mountain Dao.

"Presumptuous!"

"The royal family is too overbearing."

"Hmph, does the royal family still think it is the royal family from nine hundred years ago? With just an oral order, can it make our He Mountain Dao bow down?"

In the main hall of the highest peak of He Mountain Dao's mountain gate, elders and high-level Qi Condensation cultivators scolded loudly. Their expressions were filled with boundless anger.

"Reporting to the Sect Leader, He Yuanzi and He Qingzi are dead. It must have been Lin Fei who did it. We, He Mountain Dao, absolutely cannot let this go!"

"That's right, a martial artist, killing our He Mountain Dao's Qi Condensation experts time and time again, is unforgivable!"

"He Yuanzi and He Qingzi were our He Mountain Dao's elders. Sect Leader, even if Lin Fei is very strong, we can send top Qi Condensation experts down the mountain, along with sect treasures, to ensure that they kill Lin Fei!"

These elders and high-level Qi Condensation cultivators were all filled with righteous indignation as if they had received a great insult. And in fact, they did feel insulted. It was just a mere martial artist that they had never taken him seriously. But he had killed the top disciples and even elders of He Mountain Dao. This was simply a mockery of He Mountain Dao.

"Enough!"

The sect leader's cold gaze swept across, and the elders below stopped talking. The authority of He Mountain Dao's sect leader was not something these elders could challenge.

"Lin Fei must have achieved innate by now, otherwise, he wouldn't be able to kill He Yuanzi and He Qingzi. Moreover, Lin Fei has returned to the Nine Profound Sect now. Do you really think you can kill your way into the Nine Profound Sect and demand them to hand over Lin Fei? And there's one more important point.

The Royal Supreme Elder has intervened. He wants to protect Lin Fei personally, just like the deep connection between the royal family and the Nine Profound Sect's founder. Do you really think the old folks of the royal family can't wield their sabers?"

Upon hearing the sect leader's reprimand, many elders stopped talking for a moment. Their angry emotions gradually calmed down.

Yes, the Royal Supreme Elder was the current cornerstone of the royal family! He was a real Foundation Establishment cultivator! It was precise because of this, even if the royal family's control over the world has weakened, as long as the Royal Supreme Elder is still alive, the royal family won't be in chaos and won't collapse.

Moreover, the Royal Supreme Elder was a ruthless figure. If the Royal Supreme Elder were truly provoked, destroying sects and exterminating clans wouldn't be impossible.

"Sect Leader, are we just going to let this go?" Someone couldn't help but ask.

"How could we possibly let this go? The old man from the royal family won't live much longer; his time is near. Once he dies, it will be a time of chaos and disintegration for the world. At that time, it will be the time for us, the immortal sects, to return to the world and take control! However, at this moment, we cannot provoke that old man from the royal family. Therefore, the matter of Lin Fei will be put on hold for now, and no one is allowed to mention it again.

We will focus on refining Foundation Establishment Pills for the supreme elder. The supreme elder is confident that after taking at most three more Foundation Establishment Pills, he will surely succeed in Foundation Establishment! Once our He Mountain Dao has a Foundation Establishment cultivator, hmph, we will settle the score with the Nine Profound Sect and the royal family one by one."

A glint flashed in the eyes of the He Mountain Dao sect leader. He had his eyes on the world, paying attention to the overall situation. However, no matter how much he looked at the world, he needed corresponding strength.

Foundation Establishment was the basis for competing in the world!

As for Lin Fei? He was just a martial artist. Even if he had extraordinary talent like the Nine Profound Sect's founder, so what? In the end, he didn't succeed in Foundation Establishment. A hundred years later, he would turn into a handful of soil. Therefore, being a martial artist was not worth worrying about!

...

Five days later, Lin Fei finally returned to the Nine Profound Sect.

Ever since Lin Fei had killed two high-ranking Qi Condensation cultivators of the He Mountain Dao in the broken temple, the journey afterward had been very peaceful no twists and turns had occurred.

"Did He Mountain Dao give up? Or has He Mountain Dao not received the news yet? Or perhaps, even if He Mountain Dao wanted to send more Qi cultivators to intercept, it's already too late..." Lin Fei frowned, many thoughts flashing through his mind.

Several days passed, and it was impossible for He Mountain Dao not to have received the news. However, regardless of the situation, Lin Fei finally returned to the Nine Profound Sect.

This place felt like home to Lin Fei. Lin Fei had developed a sense of belonging to the Nine Profound Sect.

"Whoosh."

Saber energy burst forth under Lin Fei's feet.

Lin Fei's speed was incredibly fast even without using any lightness techniques. In the blink of an eye, he arrived at the top of the mountain.

Lin Fei originally planned to return to his courtyard, but he thought about it that he had killed two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao on his way. This was no small matter. He should report to the sect master first.

In case He Mountain Dao targeted the Nine Profound Sect, this would allow the Nine Profound Sect to be prepared. Thus, Lin Fei headed directly toward the sect master's main hall.

"Huh?"

As Lin Fei entered the main hall, he saw the sect master and his master, Zhao Kongming, sitting inside. The two seemed to be discussing something.

"Disciple pays his respects to Master and Sect Master."

Lin Fei greeted his master and the sect master with a bow.

"Whoosh."

Zhao Kongming and the sect master turned their heads abruptly. Their gazes instantly fell upon Lin Fei.

"Lin Fei is back?"

"Your aura, no doubt, it's innate! Hahaha, our 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei has finally returned!"

Both the sect master and Zhao Kongming showed a hint of surprise and delight in their eyes when they saw Lin Fei. However, Lin Fei furrowed his eyebrows slightly. He heard that there seemed to be a lot of information in the sect master's words.

"Sect Master, what's this 'Immortal Slayer Saber' all about?" Lin Fei asked immediately.

A note from RighteousEgg

Yes, cultivators should detach themselves from the secular world, but this is only at the initial stage of cultivation. Many resources can be obtained from the secular world, so even cultivators cannot avoid being involved in it.

More chapters on my Patreon and fewer cliffhangers.

118. Grand Elder

"Lin Fei, you didn't know? That day, when you were in the royal competition in Chang City, you drew your saber and killed the sixth-level Qi Condensation cultivator He Yunzi and gained quite a reputation among many martial artists.

Later, those martial artists called you the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' based on your past experience of killing two He Mountain Dao Qi Condensation cultivators who claimed to be disciples of the immortal sect. This should be your first title earned in the martial arts world, right?" The sect master said with a smile.

Immortal Slayer Saber, what a domineering name! However, it might cause discomfort to some people. For example, Qi cultivators! These cultivators claim to be immortal cultivators. Facing Lin Fei, the "Immortal Slayer Saber," any cultivator would hardly be pleased.

"Disciple, you have now reached the innate realm. What's the big deal about a title like 'Immortal Slayer Saber'? As martial artists, we fight against the heavens and the earth, so what's wrong with truly 'slaying immortals'? Besides, you have killed two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao. Once this news spreads, it will probably further solidify your reputation as the 'Immortal Slayer Saber.'"

Master Zhao Kongming had a slight smile at the corner of his mouth. Satisfaction could be seen in his eyes.

"Huh? Master, Sect Master, you already knew about me killing the two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao?"

Lin Fei raised an eyebrow, feeling a bit puzzled. He was about to report the incident of killing the two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao to his master and the sect master. Unexpectedly, the sect master and his master seemed to have known it already.

"Lin Fei, this is a letter sent by the royal family through a carrier pigeon. You have done a big thing, killing two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao. But you don't need to worry about He Mountain Dao's retaliation.

The Royal Supreme Elder, a Foundation Establishment expert, has personally issued an order, commanding He Mountain Dao not to take any action against you. If He Mountain Dao defies the order, the royal family's Foundation Establishment ancestor will personally take action, flattening He Mountain Dao! Lin Fei, the Royal Supreme Elder has placed great expectations on you and it has also made our Nine Profound Sect owe the royal family a huge favor!"

Lin Fei was shocked. He knew that the royal family was trying to win him over. This was evident from the attitude of the three elders of the royal family. However, Lin Fei didn't expect that it would alarm the royal family's Foundation Establishment expert! That person was the royal family's pillar of support and it was not to be disturbed for trivial matters.

"Disciple, I have some doubts. Why would the Royal Supreme Elder attach so much importance to you? You must know that, no matter how strong you are, even if you reach the peak of a grandmaster, you are still a martial artist after all. And a Foundation Establishment expert would not pay so much attention to a martial artist," Zhao Kongming asked curiously.

Qi cultivators had a clear advantage over martial artists. This was a fact. Foundation Establishment experts would look down on martial artists even more. But the Royal Supreme Elder, in order to protect Lin Fei, even threatened He Mountain Dao, vowing to destroy the entire He Mountain Dao sect. This was more than just ordinary attention.

Lin Fei had some guesses in his heart. He raised his hand and said softly, "Perhaps, it's because of my Saber Qi."

"Saber Qi?"

The sect master and Zhao Kongming looked at each other. They had no impression of "Saber Qi."

"Master, take a look at this wisp of Saber Qi from me."

Lin Fei stretched out his finger.

"Whoosh."

Suddenly, a wisp of Saber Qi flew toward Zhao Kongming through the air. Zhao Kongming reached out and grabbed it, covering his hand with his Innate True Qi.

"Sizzle."

Zhao Kongming's hand caught the wisp of Saber Qi. However, the Saber Qi instantly broke through Zhao Kongming's Innate True Qi and even injured his palm.

This was just a wisp of Saber Qi. It was insignificant. If the amount of Saber Qi were ten or a hundred times more, Zhao Kongming's palm would definitely not be safe.

"What kind of True Qi is this? No, it doesn't seem to be True Qi. It seems to have something else fused into it, fused with saber intent? Innate True Qi fused with Martial Dao True Intent... This is unheard of!"

Zhao Kongming was deeply shaken. Innate True Qi fused with Martial Dao True Intent. He had never even thought about it.

"Yes, it's Innate True Qi fused with Martial Dao True Intent, forming this completely new power. Because I fused it with saber intent, I named it Saber Qi! And this martial art is called True Intention Scroll, left behind by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect in the royal family's Ascending Dragon Chamber..."

Lin Fei didn't conceal anything. He explained everything about the True Intention Scroll. Zhao Kongming and the sect master listened to Lin Fei's account of the True Intention Scroll. For a moment, both of them had extremely solemn expressions.

"Disciple, you mean, this Saber Qi can easily cut through the spell defense shields of high-level Qi Condensation cultivators?"

Zhao Kongming seemed to be restraining his excitement.

"Yes, I killed He Mountain Dao's He Yuanzi and He Qingzi in just two strikes! I didn't even use any combat martial arts. I simply released a thirty-meter-high saber energy, and with a light slash, they were dead."

"Thirty-meter-high saber energy..."

The sect master and Zhao Kongming looked at each other. They were astonished.

"Disciple, unleash your saber energy with full force," Zhao Kongming said.

"Right here?"

"Yes, right here. Even if it destroys something, we can always have someone repair it," Zhao Kongming said carelessly.

"Alright, let the disciple give it a try."

Lin Fei took a deep breath. Then, he stretched out his hand.

"Slash!"

Lin Fei used his hand as a saber and slashed down instantly.

"Boom."

A thirty-meter-high saber energy burst out of Lin Fei's palm in an instant, condensed, and took shape, emitting a terrifyingly sharp aura. Then, the saber energy left Lin Fei's hand. It fell towards the ground of the main hall.

"Rumble."

The entire main hall shook violently as if a dragon was turning over beneath the ground. Of course, this didn't last long. It was only for an instant. Then, the thirty-foot-high saber energy directly split the ground open with a single slash, forming a huge crack.

From a distance, it looked like a giant saber had forcefully cleaved it open.

If the Saber Qi were even larger, for example, hundreds of meters, the entire mountain peak would likely be split in half with a single slash!

"It is said that a Martial Saint's strike can turn rivers and split mountains. I didn't believe it before. Now, I believe it..."

After a while, Zhao Kongming sighed deeply, his heart full of emotion.

"The founder was truly astonishing, creating such a terrifying technique. True Intention Scroll... It's a pity that this martial art is too difficult to practice. Entering the innate realm and comprehending Martial Dao True Intent at the same time is no easy task.

Of all the years in the Nine Profound Sect, only Lin Fei has met the cultivation requirements of the True Intention Scroll. However, the founder's foresight in not leaving this martial art within the Nine Profound Sect was the right choice. If the True Intention Scroll were to spread, the consequences would be unimaginable..."

The sect master immediately understood the concerns of the Nine Profound Sect's founder. The True Intention Scroll should be practiced only by those who are destined. It's not suitable for widespread promotion and publicity within the sect. Otherwise, it would bring endless trouble!

"Alright, Lin Fei. Now that you have become an innate martial artist, you should be a Master! There's absolutely no precedent in the Nine Profound Sect for an innate realm master who is still a disciple.

According to the rules of the Nine Profound Sect, any martial artist who advances to the innate realm, regardless of their status, can become a Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect. So, from today onwards, Elder Lin, you are the Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect!"

"Grand Elder?"

Lin Fei was slightly stunned. He was just a disciple a moment ago. And now, he was a Grand Elder! Could this be considered a meteoric rise?

119. Those Who Are Destined Will Come

Lin Fei became the Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect. Even Lin Fei himself was a little dazed. However, Lin Fei soon calmed down and he went to visit the Lin family members.

The Lin family members were now all in the Nine Profound Sect. As for the business in Zhou Mountain Mansion City, the Lin family naturally handed it over. Now, there was no trouble in Zhou Mountain Mansion City for Lin family. His parents and elder brother wanted to return. But after weighing the pros and cons, Lin Fei decided against it.

"Elder brother, our Lin family needs to shift our focus. In the future, gradually move our business to the towns near the Nine Profound Sect. And the Lin family should stay on the Nine Profound Sect mountain, which is the safest. Now, I am already the Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect. I have enough status to arrange for the Lin family."

After careful consideration, Lin Fei decided to move all of the Lin family's properties and slowly relocate them near the Nine Profound Sect. The Lin family members would live on the Nine Profound Sect mountain.

After all, as Lin Fei's strength grew stronger, it was inevitable that he would offend some people. And the strength of those people would grow stronger and stronger, and their power would become more terrifying.

If the Lin family were still in Zhou Mountain Mansion City, Lin Fei would not only be distracted but he would also be unable to guarantee the safety of his parents and relatives.

Moving the entire family was the wisest choice. Lin Fei's move also tied him completely to the Nine Profound Sect. This was also his sense of belonging to the Nine Profound Sect.

Thinking about the founder of the Nine Profound Sect who was once amazingly talented and unparalleled and considering the current sect master and his master's various treatments of him, Lin Fei had absolute trust in the Nine Profound Sect.

They would prosper or decline together!

Although his parents were somewhat reluctant, they were all reasonable people. Especially his elder brother, who finally agreed after careful consideration. He began to arrange for the relocation of the Lin family's properties.

Lin Fei left these matters to his elder brother, Lin Wen, without interfering.

Lin Fei then found Lin Miao.

"Lin Miao, do you know how to set up a Gathering Spirit Formation?" Lin Fei asked Lin Miao.

Now that he had achieved the innate realm and even became the Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect. He had killed not just one or two Qi Condensation cultivators, even two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators had been killed by him. He would not be afraid of exposing a mere Qi Condensation cultivator like Lin Miao who was only at the first level.

Lin Miao nodded and said, "The Qi Condensation cultivator from the Yin Ren Mansion had some formations on him. The Gathering Spirit Formation is a very simple one, the effect might not be very good, but I can set it up."

"It doesn't matter. As an innate cultivator, although I need the Spiritual Qi of heaven and earth, I don't need it as much as you Qi Condensation cultivators. You can set up a simple Gathering Spirit Formation in my cave."

So, Lin Fei took Lin Miao to his new cave.

Lin Fei was now a Grand Elder. Naturally, he had a new cave. He even had his own mountain peak, just like his master, Zhao Kongming. Anyway, there were many vacant mountain peaks in the Nine Profound Sect. If one day, all the mountain peaks in the Nine Profound Sect were occupied, It would probably be the most prosperous time for the Nine Profound Sect!

Soon, Lin Miao finished setting up the cave.

Lin Fei said to Lin Miao, "Lin Miao, now that you are in the Nine Profound Sect, you don't have to hide anymore. You can cultivate or refine pills as you wish. If you encounter any trouble or problems, come directly to me. I think the sect master would also be very welcome to have a Qi Condensation cultivator like you staying on the mountain."

Lin Miao was overjoyed upon hearing this. This meant that he was truly free! Previously, in the Lin Mansion, Lin Miao had been hiding from others. People from the Lin Mansion didn't dare to come to where he lived and he didn't dare to interact with others either. But now, he had come to the Nine Profound Sect. He no longer needed to worry about his identity as a Qi Condensation cultivator.

"Thank you, Young Master."

"Alright, you can go now."

Lin Fei waved his hand, letting Lin Miao leave.

"Now that I've advanced to the innate realm, how can I not have a suitable combat martial art? I need to visit the Martial Arts Pavilion again."

Lin Fei got up and went straight to the Martial Arts Pavilion. Soon, Lin Fei arrived at the Martial Arts Pavilion. The Martial Arts Pavilion was bustling with people coming and going, just as lively as before.

The elder guarding the Martial Arts Pavilion still holding a wine gourd, occasionally took a sip of the fine wine in the gourd. Lying on the chair, squinting his eyes, he seemed very comfortable.

Lin Fei walked into the Martial Arts Pavilion. The elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion didn't even look at him, just lazily said, "The first floor contains Body Refining level martial arts, and the second floor has acquired level martial arts, go in and choose for yourself."

"Snap."

A token was thrown in front of the elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion. At the same time, a familiar voice rang in the elder's ears, "Where can I choose martial arts at the innate level?"

"Innate level martial arts?"

The elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion suddenly stood up. His murky eyes seemed to clear up instantly. He saw Lin Fei and he seemed to remember Lin Fei. When he was just about to get angry feeling that Lin Fei was teasing him, he saw the token on the table.

It read, "Grand Elder, Lin Fei."

Seeing the identity mark on the token, the elder widened his eyes.

"You are... the inner sect disciple who chose three Body Refining martial arts in the Body Refining realm and combined three types of inner power at the acquired realm?" The elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion recognized Lin Fei.

Lin Fei calmly said, "It seems that Elder still has some impression of me."

"But your token..." The elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion was a bit confused. He had never encountered such a situation before.

"I've advanced to the innate realm, so the sect master gave me this token, is there a problem?"

The elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion's eyes narrowed slightly. His heart was even more shocked by the news.

Innate Realm! Lin Fei actually achieved the innate realm?

He had been in the Nine Profound Sect for decades and had only reached the third level of the acquired realm. He was inferior to many disciples. Otherwise, he wouldn't have been guarding the Martial Arts Pavilion.

"No... No problem. When I first saw Grand Elder Lin, I felt that Grand Elder Lin was extremely talented and had unlimited potential! Now it seems, how could Grand Elder Lin be just extremely talented? You're almost on par with the founder of our sect!"

The elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion's face turned red. Obviously, saying these words was somewhat difficult for him.

"Alright, I've just advanced to the innate realm and need innate-level martial arts. Tell me, where are the innate level martial arts?"

"Grand Elder Lin, the innate level martial arts are all on the third floor. Furthermore, as a Grand Elder, you can browse all the martial arts of our sect without paying any contribution points. And you can practice innate martial arts right on the third floor."

Lin Fei nodded. The elder of the Martial Arts Pavilion respectfully handed the token back to Lin Fei. Lin Fei turned around and headed straight for the third floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion.

There were many people on the first and second floors. But on the third floor, there was only Lin Fei. Moreover, the third floor was almost empty, and there were only a few rows of bookshelves.

The martial arts secret books on the shelves were sparse and very rare. After all, innate level martial arts, even in the Nine Profound Sect, there weren't many. Among them, many were martial arts collected by the founder of the Nine Profound Sect when he traveled the world.

"I don't need any cultivation techniques. The True Intention Scroll, it's probably better than any innate-level cultivation technique. The key is combat martial arts. Saber technique, fist technique, and lightness technique, I should choose one of each."

Lin Fei had a plan in mind. He needed to choose a saber technique first. After all, Lin Fei's body had been cultivated with Saber Qi by the True Intention Scroll. It was a natural fit for saber techniques. With the saber technique displayed by Saber Qi, combined with the support of saber intent, the power would probably be unimaginable.

On the shelves, there weren't many innate-level saber techniques, but each one was extraordinary.

"Water Splitting Chop! When cultivated to perfection, a single saber can cut through a river."

"Mountain Cleaving Slash! When cultivated to perfection, the saber can cleave mountains!"

"Three Abyssal Sabers! When cultivated to perfection, one will surely develop saber intent. The saber emerges as if hell descends, an Asura is born, and its killing intent can sever souls!"

"Twenty-Three Sabers! When cultivated to perfection, one will comprehend saber intent and can use Innate True Qi to control the saber to kill enemies!"

Lin Fei looked at the shelves, filled with various saber techniques, and was quite shocked in his heart. These saber techniques, every single one of them was an earth-shattering divine skill.

Some saber techniques even explicitly stated that once cultivated to perfection, one would be able to develop saber intent. Such saber techniques could already be considered top-notch.

However, which saber technique should Lin Fei choose?

Lin Fei followed the bookshelves, carefully examining each saber technique. Although these saber techniques were very powerful and their power could be considered earth-shattering, they were not Lin Fei's most satisfactory martial arts.

Choosing martial arts wasn't about necessarily having the strongest power, but it must be the one that suits oneself best. And Lin Fei was now selecting the most suitable saber technique for himself.

However, with so many choices, Lin Fei really had difficulty choosing.

"Right, why should I pick one by one? Let these martial arts come to me on their own."

A flash of inspiration appeared in Lin Fei's mind. He thought of a method. So, Lin Fei spoke to a row of saber technique secret books on the bookshelf: "I currently lack a saber technique. I have Saber Qi and saber intent. If you feel compatible with my saber intent and Saber Qi, then take the initiative to come to me."

The next moment, Lin Fei burst out with saber intent.

"Boom."

The saber intent exploded in the empty third floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion, sweeping all directions. At the same time, Lin Fei stretched out his hand. From his hand, a thirty meters high saber energy suddenly condensed, spanning across the void!

"Those who are destined, come forth! Perhaps you can become my martial art!"

Lin Fei's voice echoed throughout the third floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion.

120. Heavenly Saber Art

Lin Fei unleashed his Saber Intent on the third floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion. Unbeknownst to him, his Saber Intent permeated through the third floor, enveloping the entire Martial Arts Pavilion.

Thus, Lin Fei's Saber Intent erupted. Everyone in the Martial Arts Pavilion felt as if a peerless treasure saber hung above their heads. Even some saber-wielding martial artists found their sabers humming uncontrollably, as if eager to break free from their sheaths.

"What's going on?"

"Why can't I control my saber?"

"What a terrifying aura, who is responsible for this?"

In an instant, martial artists on both the first and second floors felt the Saber Intent. The Martial Arts Pavilion elder instantly sobered up. His eyes widened as he looked towards the third floor.

"Is this... Saber Intent? Did Grand Grand Elder Lin not only advance to the Innate realm but also comprehend Saber Intent?"

As a Martial Arts Pavilion elder, he was well-versed in Martial Dao True Intent. Naturally, he recognized that this was Martial Dao True Intent and most likely released by Lin Fei.

"Saber Intent, huh! I wonder what martial art Grand Elder Lin has chosen? But if he continues releasing Saber Intent like this, the disciples won't be able to choose their martial arts..."

The Martial Arts Pavilion elder could only shake his head, a bitter smile on his face.

Faced with such terrifying Saber Intent, disciples in the Body Refining and Acquired realm felt uneasy, their minds seemingly sliced by the Saber Intent repeatedly.

However, there were benefits too. At the very least, it could temper the disciples' mental fortitude. After all, Lin Fei didn't attack anyone with his Saber Intent; he simply released it.

As for asking the Martial Arts Pavilion elder to remind Lin Fei to restrain his Saber Intent? The elder dared not.

Thus, the disciples within the Martial Arts Pavilion could only endure the "intimidation" of the Saber Intent.

Lin Fei, on the third floor, released his Saber Intent and thirty-meter-high saber energy to attract martial arts techniques, allowing them to come to him on their own accord. As the saying goes, the destined shall have the martial arts come to them!

Time passed by the minute and second. Lin Fei didn't notice anything unusual.

Suddenly, a voice resounded within Lin Fei's mind.

"Water Splitting Chop, requesting to be your martial art."

"Mountain Cleaving Slash, requesting to be your martial art."

"Water Splitting Chop and Mountain Cleaving Slash are competing to become your martial art."

"Three Abyssal Sabers defeated Water Splitting Chop and Mountain Cleaving Slash, requesting to be your martial art."

One after another, voices emerged in Lin Fei's mind. However, Lin Fei was somewhat bewildered. Hadn't he made it clear that those destined would come on their own?

Water Splitting Chop and Mountain Cleaving Slash could be considered compatible with Lin Fei's Saber Intent and Saber Qi. But what was the deal with the Three Abyssal Sabers?

Its killing intent soared to the heavens! Moreover, practicing the Three Abyssal Sabers would lead to comprehending Saber Intent on its own and the Saber Intent of the Three Abyssal Sabers would certainly differ from Lin Fei's Saber Intent. Even so, the Three Abyssal Sabers still joined the fray. What was the meaning of this? And it even defeated Water Splitting Chop and Mountain Cleaving Slash.

However, whether Lin Fei would accept the Three Abyssal Sabers as his martial art depended on his approval.

"Are there no other saber techniques that can defeat the Three Abyssal Sabers?"

Lin Fei furrowed his brow. The Three Abyssal Sabers, judging from the description, seemed to be a very powerful saber technique. However, it was unsuitable for Lin Fei's saber technique. Even if it were powerful, Lin Fei wouldn't practice it.

"Twenty-Three Sabers suddenly ambushed the Three Abyssal Sabers, heavily injuring it."

"The Three Abyssal Sabers retaliated in anger, fiercely battling with Twenty-Three Sabers."

"Twenty-Three Sabers eventually defeated the Three Abyssal Sabers and requested to become your martial art."

Just when Lin Fei thought of rejecting the Three Abyssal Sabers, another saber technique emerged.

Twenty-Three Sabers! Moreover, this saber technique was somewhat "treacherous." It had ambushed the Three Abyssal Sabers. Twenty-Three Sabers could command a saber to kill enemies. It seemed quite good as well.

However, Lin Fei already had Saber Qi. Saber Qi itself could leave his body and be controlled by Lin Fei. He could effortlessly control Saber Qi. Therefore, the saber-commanding technique of Twenty-Three Sabers was of little use to him.

Lin Fei was still contemplating whether to let Twenty-Three Sabers become his martial art. At present, Twenty-Three Sabers seemed quite good.

"Boom."

The next moment, a saber appeared in Lin Fei's mind. A magnificent saber, condensing out of thin air. The moment this saber appeared, Lin Fei's mind seemed to be illuminated. It was as if countless saber edges were slicing through the void.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei's gaze, guided by his intuition, instantly looked toward the corner of the bookshelf. There, a saber technique manual lay.

"Heavenly Saber Art!"

Lin Fei murmured softly as he saw the name of this saber technique.

"Twenty-Three Sabers, fearing the Heavenly Saber Art, voluntarily distance itself from the host."

"Heavenly Saber Art requests to become your martial art."

The moment the Heavenly Saber Art appeared, a voice resounded within Lin Fei's mind. Moreover, Twenty-Three Sabers feared the Heavenly Saber Art and withdrew from the competition voluntarily.

This surprised Lin Fei. After all, Twenty-Three Sabers was not an ordinary martial art. It had defeated the Three Abyssal Sabers. Although it was due to an ambush... Even so, strength was required.

It resisted the counterattack of the Three Abyssal Sabers and defeated it in the end. This showed that Twenty-Three Sabers was definitely a top-tier innate-level saber technique. However, even so, when the Heavenly Saber Art appeared, Twenty-Three Sabers voluntarily retreated.

Lin Fei went to the corner of the bookshelf and took down the Heavenly Saber Art manual hidden in the corner.

Flipping open the Heavenly Saber Art manual, he read:

"Heavenly Saber Art, when cultivated to perfection, can condense a Heavenly Saber. With the Heavenly Saber unleashed, it can break the void and make countless sabers bow!"

Lin Fei's eyes narrowed slightly.

"What a domineering tone. Heavenly Saber unleash, countless sabers bow. What kind of Heavenly Saber can make countless sabers bow?"

Lin Fei was somewhat skeptical that this saber technique was bound to have some exaggeration or even boasting.

Nevertheless, judging solely from the introduction of the Heavenly Saber Art and the fact that it had made Twenty-Three Sabers voluntarily withdraw from the competition, the Heavenly Saber Art seemed to be the most suitable saber technique for Lin Fei.

Lin Fei continued to study the contents of the Heavenly Saber Art.

The Heavenly Saber of the Heavenly Saber Art had to be cultivated to perfection in order to condense a Heavenly Saber. When the Heavenly Saber was unleashed, countless sabers would bow, shattering the void!

This could be described as the ultimate domineering and powerful. It was in line with the attributes of a "saber." After all, sabers were the epitome of domineering and sharpness.

The Heavenly Saber Art took the domineering and sharpness of sabers to the extreme. However, it was clear that not everyone could cultivate the Heavenly Saber Art to perfection. Therefore, the specific cultivation steps of the Heavenly Saber differed.

At the perfection realm, one could condense a Heavenly Saber. At the transcendence realm, one could condense a Tyrant Saber. At mastery or below, one could condense a Fierce Saber. But even without reaching perfection, the power of the Heavenly Saber Art was not inferior to other top-tier saber techniques.

Seeing this, Lin Fei had already made up his mind.

"Heavenly Saber Art, since you have chosen to follow me, you should know you are the Heavenly Saber, the king among sabers! As a top-tier and mature saber technique, you should disdain to remain at the beginner level. So, come on, let's reach the mastery level directly! Show off the elegance of your Heavenly Saber!"

After Lin Fei finished speaking, he silently agreed to Heavenly Saber Art's request.

"Boom."

The next moment, the Heavenly Saber in Lin Fei's mind shattered instantly. At the same time, a surge of new memories emerged in his mind.

121. No Saber Available

In Lin Fei's mind, new memories emerged, which all were memories of cultivating the Heavenly Saber Art. From beginner to proficient, and then to mastery, all appeared clearly in Lin Fei's memory.

It was as if Lin Fei had gone through a long period of time, slowly mastering the Heavenly Saber Art. At the same time, a system voice appeared in his mind.

"Your Heavenly Saber Art has a noble origin, surpassing beginner and proficient, directly reaching mastery!"

Lin Fei heard the voice in his mind. He paused for a moment.

"Really... it directly reached mastery? This Heavenly Saber Art seems to have a very proud character. With just a little stimulation, it directly reached mastery, saving a lot of time."

Lin Fei wondered if stimulating it again would directly lead to transcendence. However, he only thought about it.

It must be because the Heavenly Saber Art is very special, plus Lin Fei's provocation, made it suddenly reach mastery. Perhaps it was because the Heavenly Saber Art had exhausted all its strength to barely achieve this.

Of course, Lin Fei also had some guesses. The speed at which these martial arts could be improved actually had something to do with Lin Fei himself. It must be because Lin Fei's saber realm was extraordinary. That's why the Heavenly Saber Art could so easily be elevated to mastery.

If Lin Fei immediately went to learn sword techniques or other martial arts. No matter how much Lin Fei provoked them, their progress wouldn't suddenly improve to mastery.

With the Heavenly Saber Art reaching mastery, Lin Fei could wield it as easily as moving his arm. However, this was the Martial Arts Pavilion. He couldn't test his martial arts here.

The power of the Heavenly Saber Art was extremely terrifying. If combined with Lin Fei's Saber Qi, its destructive power would reach a terrifying level.

"The saber technique has been chosen. Now for the fist technique and lightness technique. Let's use the same method. Those who are destined, the martial arts will come naturally!"

So, Lin Fei used the same method. One fist technique after another, one lightness technique after another, all wanted to become Lin Fei's martial arts. This was because Lin Fei's strength had increased. Naturally, he was very "attractive" to martial arts. Otherwise, those martial arts wouldn't eagerly want to become Lin Fei's martial arts.

After careful consideration, Lin Fei chose a fist technique called the Immeasurable Fist.

The Immeasurable Fist was, in fact, a burst technique and martial art that unleashed innate true qi. It allowed for an instantaneous eruption of nearly ten percent of the innate true qi within the body.

This was incredibly terrifying. Moreover, as the realm advanced, the Immeasurable Fist could unleash even greater power.

In the beginner and proficient realms, the innate true qi unleashed was likely less than ten percent. At the mastery realm, it could erupt about ten percent. In the transcendence realm, it could unleash twenty percent. If it reached perfection, it would be truly horrifying. A perfected Immeasurable Fist could even release half of the innate true qi within the body.

The power of a single strike, unleashing half of the innate true qi, Its might was beyond imagination. Hence, it was named "Immeasurable."

After all, a typical martial art that could release only ten percent of the innate true qi in a single strike was already considered quite remarkable. A perfected Immeasurable Fist, on the other hand, could unleash fifty percent of the innate true qi in a single blow. This could undoubtedly be considered one of the top innate fist techniques.

Of course, its flaw might be a slight deficiency in prolonged battles. But when experts exchanged blows, who needed endurance? If a single punch couldn't solve the problem, it most likely couldn't be solved at all.

Against ordinary opponents, Lin Fei could simply use Saber Qi. There was no need for him to throw a punch.

Next was the lightness technique. This time, the winning lightness technique was called "Close Yet Distant." If Close Yet Distant were cultivated to perfection, even if it is far away, it allowed being reached in an instant. It would be challenging to capture Lin Fei's silhouette.

Moreover, the speed of Close Yet Distant was also incredibly fast. As long as there was innate true qi, Lin Fei could cover a distance of over one hundred meters in a single step. The stronger the innate true qi, the greater the distance that could be covered!

Thus, Lin Fei ultimately chose Close Yet Distant as his specialized lightness technique. With that, Lin Fei had chosen his innate level saber, fist, and lightness techniques. Or rather, these martial arts had chosen Lin Fei.

"System."

Lin Fei immediately accessed the system to check his martial arts progress.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Innate Martial Artist

Master: Early Stage

True Intention Scroll: Early Stage (31% Progress)

Saber Intent: Mastery (21% Progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (45% Progress)

Heavenly Saber Art: Mastery (0% Progress)

Immeasurable Fist: Proficient (0% Progress)

Close Yet Distant: Proficient (0% Progress)

The three martial arts Lin Fei had just chosen, Heavenly Saber Art reached mastery directly, while Immeasurable Fist and Close Yet Distant only reached proficiency.

So, Lin Fei became even more certain that the Heavenly Saber Art was somewhat special. Or, Lin Fei's accomplishments in saber techniques were deep, which allowed the Heavenly Saber Art to reach mastery in an instant.

Having chosen his martial arts, Lin Fei stood up and walked down from the third floor of the Martial Arts Pavilion. The Martial Arts Pavilion Elder was extremely respectful and didn't dare to say anything.

Then, Lin Fei left the Martial Arts Pavilion. He had just chosen the Heavenly Saber Art and it needed a suitable saber to match.

Star Saber was no longer suitable ever since Lin Fei had cultivated Saber Qi. A treasure saber that could withstand the eruption of innate true qi was necessary.

So, Lin Fei went to the Treasure Pavilion and revealed the identity token of the Grand Elder. Immediately, the Treasure Pavilion Elder became respectful.

"Grand Elder Lin, what treasure do you need?"

"A saber! After advancing to the innate realm, I lack a suitable treasure saber."

"A saber? Grand Elder Lin might not know, once you advance to the innate realm, ordinary sabers are no longer usable because even a star saber cannot withstand the eruption of innate true qi from Masters! Therefore, only treasure sabers made from special materials can be used.

This row of treasure sabers can be used by masters. They can fully withstand the eruption of innate true qi. Even Martial Grand Masters can use these treasure sabers without any issues. Grand Elder Lin, you can choose any treasure saber you like."

Lin Fei glanced at them. These treasure sabers emitted a cold light. Even from a distance, one could seemingly sense their sharp aura.

Lin Fei casually picked up a treasure saber. The weight was just right.

"Let's test it."

Lin Fei had thought and activated his Saber Qi. He swung it gently in the void.

"Slash!"

With a soft shout from Lin Fei, the Saber Qi erupted instantly, saber energy roared out and slashed into the ground. Instantly, a large pit appeared on the ground.

"Crack."

However, the treasured saber in Lin Fei's hand, which was said to withstand the eruption of a Martial Master's true qi, had shattered just like that.

"Hmm? Didn't you say it could withstand a grandmaster's true qi eruption? What's going on? Could it be that the sabers in the Treasure Pavilion are all defective?"

Lin Fei's expression turned cold.

Immediately, the Treasure Pavilion Elder's face turned pale, and he hurriedly said, "Grand Elder Lin, please calm down. The sabers in the Treasure Pavilion are definitely not defective. Perhaps it's due to being stored for too long. Grand Elder Lin, please try this one."

So, the Treasure Pavilion Elder handed Lin Fei another treasure saber. Lin Fei once again swung it casually.

"Crack."

The treasure saber shattered again.

"Next."

Lin Fei gripped the third treasure saber.

"Crack."

It was the same as before.

After swinging the saber, the treasured saber shattered on the ground.

"Uh... Grand Elder Lin, this..." The Treasure Pavilion Elder was cautious, hesitating to speak.

Lin Fei threw away the broken treasure saber in his hand. His expression was calm as he said lightly, "I see now, it's my problem."

The Treasure Pavilion Elder didn't know what to say.

Three treasure sabers were that even Martial Grand Masters could use them. Why couldn't Lin Fei use them? Could it be that Lin Fei was stronger than a Martial Grand Master? That was simply impossible!

Only Lin Fei knew that it was most likely due to his Saber Qi. Saber Qi was much stronger than Innate True Qi. Even treasure sabers that innate martial artists could use couldn't withstand the eruption of Lin Fei's Saber Qi.

"It seems I'm not suited for using sabers anymore. I can only unleash Saber Qi and use my hand as a saber."

Lin Fei felt somewhat helpless in his heart. It seemed that in the future, the scenes of him using a thirty meters high saber energy to slash people wouldn't be few...

122. Chen Lian's Shock

Lin Fei returned to his cave dwelling.

At this moment, the maid serving Lin Fei reported, "Elder, a letter just came from the inner sect addressed to inner sect disciple Lin Fei. After the inner sect elder learned about it, they forwarded the letter here."

"A letter?" Lin Fei took the letter.

Lin Fei had only been an inner sect disciple for a few months and only a small number of people in the Nine Profound Sect knew that Lin Fei was now a Grand Elder. Others didn't know his identity at all. But even in the inner sect, Lin Fei hadn't made many acquaintances. Who sent him the letter?

Lin Fei opened the letter. Upon reading the contents, he understood. It turned out that the letter was from Chen Lian. When Lin Fei first entered the inner sect and was preparing to sell his outer sect courtyard, it was Chen Lian bought it.

Moreover, Lin Fei accepted Chen Lian's invitation and became a guest elder of the Chen family. At that time, the Chen family gave Lin Fei 15,000 taels of silver, which was to be paid annually.

They had paid a year's worth of silver in advance, which showed sincerity. After all, Lin Fei had not yet become an acquired martial artist at that time.

Lin Fei did a quick calculation. He had been a guest elder of the Chen family for less than a year. That is to say, he had taken the silver and was still a guest elder of the Chen family.

Now, Chen Lian sent a letter. She mentioned that the Chen family had encountered some troubles. They hoped Lin Fei could go to the Chen family and help them resolve the issue. The Chen family had prepared a generous reward for Lin Fei's assistance: 10,000 taels of silver!

If Lin Fei were an ordinary acquired martial artist, this reward would be quite impressive. It did demonstrate considerable sincerity. However, Lin Fei was now an innate martial artist! So, how much should an innate martial artist be rewarded for their assistance?

"Never mind, I did accept the Chen family's silver after all. And indeed, I am currently a guest elder of the Chen family. Bring Chen Lian here, and I'll ask her in person what troubles the Chen family has encountered."

"Yes, Elder."

The maid left the cave dwelling. It wasn't long before the maid brought Chen Lian to the cave dwelling.

Chen Lian's face was full of confusion. She was still in the outer sect of the Nine Profound Sect. Judging by the situation, it seemed difficult for her to reach the seventh level of Body Refining before the age of twenty.

It was unlikely that she would become an inner sect disciple. Of course, this was normal. Chen Lian's talent was quite average. Being able to stay in the outer sect was already quite good. She could provide the Chen family with information about potential disciples.

It should be noted that the Chen family didn't have Lin Fei as their only guest elder.

Chen Lian looked at the cave dwelling with a mix of apprehension and confusion. She had been doing well in the outer sect. Suddenly, she was informed that the Grand Elder had summoned her. But what could a Grand Elder want with an insignificant outer sect disciple like her?

Chen Lian couldn't even enter the inner sect. When she needed to contact their guest elders in the inner sect, she could only send a message through someone. What merit or ability did she have to be invited by the Grand Elder?

"Chen, the Grand Elder is inside. Please come in."

The maid brought Chen Lian to the entrance of the main hall and stopped. Chen Lian hesitated a bit, but she quickly stepped inside.

She didn't dare to look up at the Grand Elder sitting at the top. Instead, she quickly entered the main hall and respectfully knelt down, saying, "Disciple Chen Lian pays her respects to the Grand Elder."

"Chen Lian, you're here. Lift your head and take a look at who I am."

A young voice entered Chen Lian's ears she faintly felt it was familiar. She cautiously raised her head and looked at the Grand Elder sitting at the top. However, when she saw the person clearly, her eyes widened in shock. A look of disbelief appeared on her face.

"You... you are Senior Brother Lin Fei? But... why are you in the Grand Elder's cave dwelling? Could it be that you have become a disciple of the Grand Elder?" Chen Lian immediately thought of a possibility.

"Disciple?"

Lin Fei smiled enigmatically, his gaze fixed on Chen Lian, "Some time ago, I advanced to the innate realm and became a Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect. So, I am the Grand Elder!"

Lin Fei's words exploded like a thunderbolt in Chen Lian's mind.

"What? Senior Brother Lin, you are the Grand Elder? And you have advanced to the innate realm..."

Chen Lian was a skilled socializer among the Nine Profound Sect's outer disciples. But now, her mind was completely blank and she didn't know what to say.

Lin Fei being a Grand Elder, an innate martial artist, and a martial arts master was beyond her imagination.

"Chen Lian, I don't have time to joke with you. I am still a guest elder of the Chen family, after all. I have taken the Chen family's silver, and a year has not yet passed. During this year, no matter what troubles the Chen family encounters, I can help resolve them. Chen Lian, are you sure you still want me to help resolve the troubles faced by the Chen family?"

Lin Fei's meaningful words brought Chen Lian back to her senses. She seemed to regain her usual calm demeanor.

Chen Lian immediately replied, "No, Grand Elder Lin, it's just a trivial matter for the Chen family. How could we bother the Grand Elder with it? But, may I ask the Grand Elder, can the Chen family announce the fact that you are our guest elder?"

Chen Lian asked cautiously. She was still shocked in her heart that how the acquired disciple they had originally hired suddenly become an innate master and a Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect.

This status was incredible. At the very least, if Lin Fei were associated with the Chen family, Even if it was just a little connection, it would be great news for the Chen family!

"Of course, I am indeed your guest elder."

"When the one-year period is over..." Chen Lian hesitated to ask.

"Do you still want me to be your guest elder? But can your Chen family afford to support a martial arts master?" Lin Fei said calmly.

When the one-year term expires, Lin Fei's price won't be the same. To be a guest elder? Of course, it's possible! As long as they can provide treasures that can significantly improve his True Intention Scroll or rapidly enhance his saber intent.

As long as they have those treasures, then there would be no problem supporting him as a guest elder. However, if it's just some silver, It would be of no use to Lin Fei now.

"Ah... I apologize for my thoughtlessness."

Chen Lian's expression stiffened slightly. Indeed, Lin Fei was now a martial arts grandmaster and a Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect. As soon as the one-year term with the Chen family ends, if the Chen family wanted to continue supporting him, they would have to pay the price of a martial arts master.

Could the Chen family afford to support a martial arts grandmaster? It seemed impossible.

"Grand Elder, I will take my leave now!"

Chen Lian respectfully saluted and then hurriedly left the cave dwelling. She had to hurry back and report this news to the Chen family.

The Chen family would be shocked as well. Originally, they had hired an acquired disciple as a guest elder. But in the blink of an eye, he became an innate master and even a Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect. This was like a pie falling from the sky. What a profit!

If the Chen family could make good use of their relationship with Lin Fei and announce their connection with Lin Fei, from then on, the Chen family might soar to new heights. Who would dare to provoke them?

"Guest elder..."

Lin Fei thought of the Zhang family. He was also a guest elder for the Zhang family. However, ever since the last time when Lin Fei helped the Zhang family to drive away the disciples from Autumn Haze Mountain, the Zhang family seemed to have not encountered any troubles.

"Next, I should focus on cultivation. I must at least reach the middle stage of the True Intention Scroll and make my Saber Qi more profound, only then can I fight with Saber Qi for an extended period. I also need to continue honing my Martial Dao True Intents. I should go to the Ancestral Master Peak to polish them..."

Lin Fei got up, left the cave dwelling, and headed towards the Ancestral Master Peak.

123. Once Enlightened, One Can Die Happily

Time passed quickly.

The weather gradually became colder. Especially on the Ancestral Master Peak, the cold wind was as sharp as a saber, chilling to the bone.

"Whoosh."

Zhao Kongming's figure appeared on the Ancestral Master Peak. He didn't speak immediately but gazed into the distance at the figure beneath the stone stele.

Lin Fei sat quietly beneath the stele, eyes closed. He sat there, letting the cold wind hit his face, like an old monk in meditation.

However, as Zhao Kongming was about to approach,

"Hmm?"

a fierce saber edge burst out from Lin Fei's body.

At the same time, the stele also emitted a similarly fierce aura. It was Martial Dao True Intent, or rather, saber intent.

One saber intent was extremely domineering. The other saber intent was incredibly sharp. The two intents clashed with each other. However, the slightly domineering True Intent seemed to be losing strength. That was the saber intent left by the Nine Profound Sect's Ancestral Master in the stone stele.

After such a long time of consumption, it gradually diminished. Naturally, it was losing strength. Meanwhile, the incredibly sharp saber intent seemed to have endless power. That was Lin Fei's saber intent.

"Lin Fei."

At this moment, Zhao Kongming finally spoke.

"Swish."

Lin Fei opened his eyes. The saber intent around him immediately retracted. The entire Ancestral Master Peak was restored to its previous tranquility.

"Lin Fei, you've been cultivating beneath the stele every day for so long. It's too dull and monotonous. Sometimes, haste makes waste. Too much effort and desire for improvement would lead to inferior results."

Zhao Kongming couldn't help but advise. He was satisfied with Lin Fei in every aspect. But sometimes, Lin Fei was too diligent and worked too hard. He had stayed on the Ancestral Master Peak for ten days or half a month, regardless of cloudy days or rain. He spent almost every day beneath the stele. This was akin to being an ascetic cultivator. Zhao Kongming admitted that he couldn't be as diligent as Lin Fei.

"Master, I understand."

Lin Fei smiled faintly. Zhao Kongming felt somewhat helpless. Every time he reminded Lin Fei, Lin Fei would respond with the same words. Then, he would continue cultivating hard in his own way.

In fact, Lin Fei also wanted to balance relaxation and diligence. The feeling of spending every day under the stele was not pleasant. However, his saber intent had a standard "ascetic" personality, only by cultivating hard beneath the stele every day could his saber intent improve slightly.

Otherwise, there would be no improvement at all. This was different from his fist intent. No matter how Lin Fei tried to hone his fist intent under the stele, there was little improvement.

Different martial arts personalities required different treatments.

During this period, Lin Fei mainly focused on cultivating the True Intention Scroll and his saber intent. Therefore, naturally, he had to "cultivate hard" according to the saber intent's way.

"By the way, Master, what do you want to tell me by coming to the Ancestral Master Peak?" Lin Fei asked. He knew that Zhao Kongming was not so idle. He must have something important if he came to find him specifically.

Zhao Kongming nodded and said, "Indeed, there is something. The once-in-a-decade Martial Alliance Exchange Conference is about to begin. Our Nine Profound Sect has already received the invitation. In the past, every Martial Alliance Exchange Conference was led by a Grand Elder from our Nine Profound Sect with some outstanding inner disciples participating in the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference.

This time, I was supposed to lead the team. But seeing you cultivate hard on the Ancestral Master Peak every day, I think you should go out and take a break. Therefore, I'll give you this opportunity to let you, the newly promoted Grand Elder, lead some disciples from the sect to gain some worldly experience. On the path of martial arts, the exchange and discussions between martial artists are also very important."

Lin Fei pondered for a while, then nodded and said, "Master is right, it's good to go out and take a break. When do we set off?"

"In three days."

"Is this Martial Alliance Exchange Conference just a simple exchange between disciples of various sects?" Lin Fei asked again. He wanted to ask clearly. So he could be prepared.

"Actually, the main purpose of the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference is for the various sects to meet. The Martial Alliance was initially established to counter the Immortal and Daoist sects.

However, as you know, the various sects are constantly scheming against each other and have many concerns. How could they possibly be united? So, over time, the Martial Alliance has become a loose organization.

But even if it's loose, on the surface, the Martial Alliance is still the strongest martial force in Great Chang. Exchanges and discussions among fellow martial artists can promote one's martial arts.

Moreover, it allows sharing of recent situations and even the movements of the Immortal and Daoist sects. After all, the world has not been peaceful recently. Those Immortal and Daoist sects have begun to stir again.

Lin Fei, when you go, just feel the attitudes of the various sects and train the disciples along the way. As for the rest, the sect master and other Grand Elders will discuss."

Lin Fei understood. This Martial Alliance Exchange Conference, in fact, was not a very important event. It was barely considered a martial arts gathering in the world of martial arts,

"One last question, Master, are there any Martial Saints in the Martial Alliance?" Lin Fei asked solemnly.

"Martial Saints..."

Zhao Kongming's expression became serious, and his eyes gradually sharpened. Then, He spoke slowly, word by word, "In the past three hundred years, no Martial Saint has been born! As for whether there are hidden Martial Saint ancestors in the various martial sects, it is unclear.

Once one becomes a Martial Saint and establishes the foundation of martial arts, one can live for more than three hundred years. Some Foundation Establishment martial artists can even live up to five hundred years!

The last publicly known Martial Saint was the Sword Saint Bai of the Hidden Sword Sect. He passed away three hundred years ago when his time came.

Since then, there has been no Martial Saint in Great Chang! Even, over the past three hundred years, the various martial sects have begun to believe. Perhaps, the path of the Martial Saint has been severed..."

Lin Fei fell silent. In the past three hundred years, no Martial Saint had been born in the entire Great Chang's martial sects. This was almost like a fault. This was not the same as those Immortal and Daoist sects.

The Foundation Establishment cultivators of the Immortal and Daoist sects have never been severed. Every ten years, or several decades, a Foundation Establishment cultivator would be born. Over the course of nine hundred years in Great Chang, the accumulated number of Foundation Establishment cultivators was quite considerable.

This was also the reason why martial sects were always suppressed by the Immortal and Daoist sects. It was too difficult for martial arts to produce a Martial Saint, almost as hard as ascending to heaven.

But the Immortal and Daoist sects could steadily give birth to Foundation Establishment cultivators with such gains and losses, it was clear who was stronger and who was weaker.

"The path of Martial Saints will not be severed!"

Suddenly, Lin Fei raised his head, his eyes determined.

"Hahaha, my disciple, I was initially somewhat shaken. In three hundred years, no Martial Saint has been born. Is it true that the path of Martial Saints has been severed? But since you appeared, I firmly believe. The path of Martial Saints must not be severed. Where there are martial arts, there are Martial Saints. No one can sever this path!"

Zhao Kongming spoke passionately. He even couldn't help but draw the long sword from behind him.

"Whoosh."

A sword light flew out in an instant. It slashed at the empty ground of the Ancestral Master Peak.

"Hum."

A vast sword intent suddenly burst out from the stone tablet. It instantly enveloped Zhao Kongming's body, Gradually, an incredibly sharp aura began to rise. Even the long sword in Zhao Kongming's hand was emitting bursts of soft humming sounds.

"Boom."

Finally, above Zhao Kongming's head, a long sword seemed to be faintly forming! Seeing this scene, Lin Fei immediately understood what was happening.

"Congratulations, Master, on comprehending sword intent!"

At this moment, Zhao Kongming actually comprehended the sword intent!

"Hahaha, I have practiced the sword for eighty years, and now I have finally comprehended the sword intent! My heart's wish is fulfilled! The path of martial arts is long, but even if I die tonight, I will have no regrets!"

Zhao Kongming laughed loudly, his sword intent on soaring into the sky.

124. Slaying immortals, Who Needs A Saber?

The fierce wind howled. It was still snowing on the Ancestral Master Peak.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei opened his eyes.

"It's been three days. It's time to lead the disciples to the Martial Alliance and participate in the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference."

Lin Fei murmured softly. Ever since three days ago, when Lin Fei's master Zhao Kongming accidentally comprehended the sword intent, he returned to his cave and closed himself off.

Zhao Kongming's unexpected comprehension of sword intent. Nine Profound Sect had one more Grand Elder with sword intent. For the Nine Profound Sect, this was naturally a good thing.

"System."

Lin Fei brought up the system panel. He had been on the Ancestral Master Peak for almost twenty days. Every day, he honed his saber intent. He hadn't carefully examined the changes in his martial arts.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Innate Martial Artist

Master: Mid-stage

True Intention Scroll: Mid-stage (2% Progress)

Saber Intent: Mastery (61% Progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (51% Progress)

Heavenly Saber Art: Mastery (40% Progress)

Immeasurable Fist: Proficient (40% Progress)

Close Yet Distant: Proficient (40% Progress)

Lin Fei's True Intention Scroll had reached the mid-stage. That is to say, Lin Fei is now in the mid-stage of the Innate realm.

The Saber Qi in his body had increased fivefold. It was very difficult for an innate martial artist to improve. However, even if it was just advancing a small realm, the gap was enormous and the strength would be greatly improved.

However, after reaching the mid-stage of the Innate realm, Lin Fei found that even if there was abundant Spiritual Qi on the Ancestral Master Peak, the cultivation progress of the True Intention Scroll was still slow. It could only advance about 1% per day.

Moreover, Lin Fei had a feeling. Once he reached the late stage, without external help, the cultivation progress of the True Intention Scroll might not be able to advance.

This was not because the True Intention Scroll wasn't working hard. In fact, the saber intent was pushing the True Intention Scroll every day, striving to cultivate. It's just that the cultivation speed of the True Intention Scroll was so slow.

After all, the True Intention Scroll had an extra step of integrating Martial Dao True Intent compared to ordinary martial arts, the speed would naturally slow down.

As for saber intent and fist intent, saber intent had improved a lot, while fist intent had only improved a little bit. This showed that saber intent could still be improved through honing. It's just that it was still very slow. Then there were Heavenly Saber Art, Immeasurable Fist, and Close Yet Distant. Their cultivation speed was about 2% per day.

It should not be a problem for these three martial arts to reach transcendence. As for achieving perfection, it is necessary to find the "character" of the three martial arts. Or, the three martial arts might also need a bit of luck.

"Innate mid-stage, with thick Saber Qi. It's time to go out and explore the world..."

Lin Fei stood up. Then, he took a step forward.

"Whoosh."

Lin Fei covered a distance of thirty meters in one step. Step by step, he walked towards the main hall.

...

Nine Profound Sect main hall.

More than a dozen inner disciples had arrived at the main hall and were on standby. They had already received the news that today Grand Elder "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei would lead the team to participate in the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference.

The Martial Alliance Exchange Conference was held once every ten years. It was a grand event in the martial arts world! However, compared to the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference, these disciples were actually more interested in "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei.

News about Lin Fei gradually spread within the Nine Profound Sect. After all, the Nine Profound Sect did not intentionally block the news. Moreover, throughout Great Chang, the feats of "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei became more and more widespread. These outstanding inner disciples of the Nine Profound Sect naturally received the news as well.

"I heard that this time it's 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Grand Elder Lin Fei leading the team personally. Grand Elder Lin Fei has recently become a legendary figure in the martial arts world of Great Chang. His battle achievements are simply too fierce.

What's more important is that his saber can cut down those haughty Qi Condensation cultivators. Even when Grand Elder Lin was in the Acquired realm, he was able to slay a sixth-level Qi Condensation disciple from the He Mountain Dao. It's truly incredible. I wonder what kind of style 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Grand Elder Lin has?"

These inner disciples were all looking forward to it in their hearts. Martial artists worship the strong. Besides, the fame of "Immortal Slayer Saber" has spread far and wide. He can be regarded as the most prominent martial artist in the entire Great Chang right now. How could they not look forward to it?

The sect master looked at these disciples below. Although his expression was solemn, he was very pleased. Nowadays, the Nine Profound Sect, because of Lin Fei's "Immortal Slayer Saber" widespread reputation, everyone was practicing martial arts more diligently. Especially the confidence in martial arts. This was something the Nine Profound Sect never had before. The belief in martial arts is intangible and untouchable.

For martial artists, it is very important. Even the sect master believed that, given time, the strength and cultivation of the entire Nine Profound Sect's disciples would greatly improve.

This was all thanks to Lin Fei, the "Immortal-Slayer Saber," and the changes he brought to the Nine Profound Sect. Even though Lin Fei, as a Grand Elder, rarely made appearances, it didn't affect his prestige in the hearts of the numerous Nine Profound Sect disciples.

"Hm? He's arrived!"

The sect master suddenly looked up and saw a faint shadow approaching in the distance outside the main hall. The shadow quickly closed the distance, arriving in the main hall within a few leaps.

"Whoosh."

Everyone's gaze turned toward the figure that had just entered the hall.

"Grand Elder Lin, these disciples have been eagerly awaiting you!" The sect master said with a smile. The eyes of a dozen inner sect disciples simultaneously focused on Lin Fei.

"We greet the Grand Elder!" These inner sect disciples spoke in unison, saluting Lin Fei. Lin Fei nodded slightly in acknowledgment, having grown accustomed to his Grand Elder identity.

"Sect master, can we depart now?" Lin Fei asked.

"Grand Elder Lin, I entrust these disciples to you," The sect master saluted Lin Fei.

These disciples were the elite of the Nine Profound Sect and represented its future. There could be no room for failure. Thus, for each Martial Alliance Exchange, an innate martial artist would lead the team to ensure the safety of the disciples to the greatest extent.

"Alright, let's set off."

Lin Fei led the group of disciples out of the grand hall and arrived at the mountain gate. At this moment, at the mountain gate, more than a dozen swift horses had already been prepared for the long journey to the Martial Alliance. The dozen inner sect disciples had been carefully observing Lin Fei, but he remained silent, leaving them hesitant to overstep their bounds.

Finally, one disciple, carrying a large saber and presumably skilled in saber techniques, couldn't help but ask, "Grand Elder Lin, it's widely rumored that you are the 'Immortal-Slayer Saber,' possessing divine saber skills that can slay Qi Condensation cultivators from the Immortal Sect.

However, we notice that you don't have a saber on you. Without a saber, how can you be the 'Immortal-Slayer Saber'? Pardon our boldness, but may we ask, Grand Elder Lin, have you forgotten to bring your saber?"

This disciple, carrying the large saber, displayed some courage, voicing the greatest doubt in all the disciples' minds.

As a result, all the disciples' gazes were now fixed on Lin Fei. They had searched but couldn't find Lin Fei's saber. But without a saber, how could he be the "Immortal-Slayer Saber"?

With a calm expression, Lin Fei glanced at the disciples and noticed the confusion on their faces. He slowly spoke, "Watch closely, all of you! Slaying immortals, who needs a saber?"

The next moment, Lin Fei extended his hand. Instantly, the Saber Qi within his body burst forth.

"Boom."

The saber energy on Lin Fei's hand surged and rapidly condensed into a thirty meters tall saber in mid-air.

"Buzz."

Some disciples carrying sabers were astonished, their faces filled with horror. Their sabers, seemingly beyond their control, began to tremble and hum as if wanting to break free from their sheaths. Simultaneously, Lin Fei fiercely swung his hand down toward the empty ground outside the mountain gate.

"Rumble."

The thirty-meter-tall saber energy viciously slashed the ground, causing the earth to shake violently as if a dragon was turning beneath it. Where Lin Fei's Saber Qi passed, a massive fissure was cleaved into the ground.

From a distance, it seemed as though the empty land outside the mountain gate had been split in two. All the disciples stood with their mouths agape, staring in amazement at the seemingly miraculous fissure on the ground, unable to speak for a long time.

"Let's go!"

Lin Fei didn't linger. He mounted a swift horse and sped away, leaving a trail of dust behind him.

125. Lin Fei Takes His Seat, Stunning The Audience

The Martial Alliance Headquarters was situated on Mount Cang City. The reason for choosing this location was quite simple. There was no powerful martial arts sect here.

When the Martial Alliance was first established, its purpose was to jointly resist the pressure of the immortal sects. However, martial arts sects were also wary of each other. They feared that a major sect would control the Martial Alliance Headquarters, thereby threatening other sects. Thus, Mount Cang City, a place without a powerful martial arts sect, was chosen.

Nowadays, the Martial Alliance had declined and had become a mere shell of its former self. Usually, there were only a few disciples in charge of cleaning and guarding the place, without even a single acquired martial artist. This showed the desolation of the Martial Alliance Headquarters.

However, recently, the headquarters had been receiving a steady stream of visitors from the martial arts world. Consequently, the town at the foot of Mount Cang City gradually became lively.

Lin Fei, along with the members of the Nine Profound Sect, arrived at Mount Cang City. Seeing the endless stream of martial artists, many inner sect disciples were excited.

"Are those people from the Blood Refining Sect? I heard that the Blood Refining Sect values body refining the most. Their body-refining techniques are extremely terrifying.

"If one's body refining doesn't meet the Blood Refining Sect's requirements, they might even be expelled from the sect. And those white-clad swordsmen, they must be disciples of the Hidden Sword Sect, right?"

"The Hidden Sword Sect excels in swordsmanship. Each generation of their disciples must venture into the world to inherit the title of 'The Number One Sword Under Heaven.'"

"Yes, the Hidden Sword Sect is really arrogant. Each generation's top swordsman must use actual combat to seize the title of 'The Number One Sword Under Heaven.'"

"That's why the 'Number One Sword Under Heaven' in Great Chang almost always comes from the Hidden Sword Sect."

The Nine Profound Sect disciples were abuzz with chatter. For a moment, Lin Fei realized that these disciples knew more about martial arts sects than he did.

"The Hidden Sword Sect, huh?"

Lin Fei instantly spotted the Hidden Sword Sect disciples. They all carried long swords on their backs.

Lin Fei's deep impression of the Hidden Sword Sect was for two reasons. One was the Sword Saint Bai from three hundred years ago, who was considered the last Martial Saint of Great Chang. Secondly, each generation of the Hidden Sword Sect produced the most outstanding swordsmen.

Moreover, without exception, those who inherited the title of "The Number One Sword Under Heaven" would definitely comprehend Sword Intent! In the entire Great Chang, martial artists who could comprehend Martial Dao True Intent were scarce, even countable on one's fingers. But the Hidden Sword Sect always occupied one or several spots on that list.

Each generation saw the birth of a Sword Intent expert from the Hidden Sword Sect! In this aspect, the Hidden Sword Sect was much stronger than the Nine Profound Sect.

Of course, while the Nine Profound Sect disciples discussed other sects, those from other sects also talked about the Nine Profound Sect.

The Nine Profound Sect was not a sect without a foundation. The Nine Profound Sect had produced such a remarkable figure as the Nine Profound Sect's founder.

Back then, he had been invincible, seeking a worthy opponent but failing to find one. Even Foundation Establishment Realms praised him as an unparalleled genius, rarely seen in the world!

And now?

Although the Nine Profound Sect was no longer as strong as it used to be, the Nine Profound Sect produced an extraordinary individual. He was the most renowned figure in the entire Great Chang recently.

Immortal Slayer Saber!

The Nine Profound Sect had given birth to the "Immortal Slayer Saber." He had slain two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators from He Mountain Dao.

This news had already shaken the entire Great Chang martial arts world. All martial artists felt exhilarated. After all, martial artists had been suppressed by Qi cultivators for too long.

The appearance of the "Immortal Slayer Saber" undoubtedly restored some dignity to martial artists. However, as for who the "Immortal Slayer Saber" was? What did he look like? Most people were not clear about it.

Therefore, many martial artists, although they saw the people from the Nine Profound Sect, they did not know which one was the Immortal Slayer Saber. Lin Fei also traveled with the inner sect disciples. He was equally young. No one could tell he was the Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect.

Soon, the Nine Profound Sect's group arrived at the Martial Alliance Headquarters. Disciples were already there to greet them.

"We are disciples of the Nine Profound Sect."

A disciple handed over the invitation letter from the Martial Alliance.

"Senior brothers and senior sisters of the Nine Profound Sect, the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference is about to begin. Please follow me."

The reception disciple led the Nine Profound Sect members directly to the venue of the exchange conference.

Lin Fei took a glance. There were not many martial artists left at the foot of the mountain. Many sects' disciples had arrived at Mount Cang City yesterday or even the day before. They just stayed in the town at the foot of Mount Cang City for one night. As for the Nine Profound Sect's group, they had just arrived at Mount Cang City, looking travel-worn. Soon, Lin Fei and the others saw the venue of the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference in the distance.

It was a huge open space. Weapon racks were placed all around and various weapons were displayed on them. Each sect occupied a section, forming a large circle.

Inside the circle, there were many temporary arenas. These were for the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference, used for disciples of various sects to "exchange" ideas.

At the top of the arenas, thirteen chairs were arranged. They represented the thirteen sects of the Martial Alliance. Only the representatives of the thirteen sects could sit on those chairs.

According to past conventions, the martial artists representing the thirteen sects were generally innate martial artists. In other words, these thirteen chairs represented thirteen martial arts masters.

At this moment, twelve masters had already taken their seats on the thirteen chairs. Only one chair was left unoccupied. Moreover, there was still an empty space on the ground. That was the position for the Nine Profound Sect.

"The people from the Nine Profound Sect haven't arrived yet."

"The Nine Profound Sect is quite far from Mount Cang City. They should be here soon. Let's wait a bit longer."

"I wonder which master from the Nine Profound Sect will lead the team this time? Could it be the famous 'Immortal Slayer Saber'?"

"Immortal Slayer Saber? It's unlikely. Although the Immortal Slayer Saber has been in the spotlight lately, He Mountain Dao hates him to the core. How could Immortal Slayer Saber dare to leave the Nine Profound Sect at this time?"

"Hehe, didn't you know? He Mountain Dao has temporarily closed their mountain for some reason."

"Closed the mountain? He Mountain Dao is a prestigious immortal sect. How could they just close their mountain like that?"

"Perhaps it's because of the 'Immortal Slayer Saber.' I heard that the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' has a deep connection with the royal family."

"Anyway, I really want to see the 'Immortal Slayer Saber.' What kind of demeanor does someone who can slay immortals with a saber have?"

Many disciples and martial artists were staring at the empty chair. Their eyes were filled with anticipation, hoping that the master leading the Nine Profound Sect would be the Immortal Slayer Saber. In this way, they could witness the demeanor of the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' with their own eyes.

"They're here."

"The people from the Nine Profound Sect have arrived."

"Who is the master leading the Nine Profound Sect?"

"Did the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' come?"

As the Nine Profound Sect's group arrived, the entire Martial Alliance Exchange Conference became lively. Countless martial artists craned their necks in anticipation. Their eyes were fixed on the Nine Profound Sect's group.

For a moment, the disciples of the Nine Profound Sect felt extremely proud. Even though they were travel-worn and had just arrived at Mount Cang City, they all held their heads high, looking spirited. However, among the disciples of Autumn Haze Mountain, one person was not as excited.

Liu Hao!

After being defeated by Lin Fei, he took it as a great shame. So, he practiced martial arts like crazy for several months. He actually soared from the acquired third level to the acquired sixth level! Of course, Liu Hao's family also contributed a lot. But this was also due to Liu Hao's outstanding talent and his extreme efforts.

Liu Hao also came to the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference with Autumn Haze Mountain this time. He wanted to see if Lin Fei was among the Nine Profound Sect disciples. This time, he wanted to avenge his previous disgrace!

"Lin Fei, your talent is quite impressive. You will most likely come to this Martial Alliance Exchange Conference. For this day, I have trained hard for months, which is equivalent to years of practice! We martial artists know shame and then become courageous. The grudge of that day's saber, if we meet today, I will return it twice!" Liu Hao murmured quietly.

He had been waiting for this day for a long time. As for the recent popular Immortal Slayer Saber from the Nine Profound Sect, Liu Hao didn't pay any attention at all.

Moreover, everyone was talking about the Immortal Slayer Saber. But who exactly was the Immortal Slayer Saber? What was his real name? Many people didn't know. Liu Hao didn't care either.

How could he, a mere disciple, have any contact with such a lofty and influential figure? He was very clear that his biggest dream in this life was to achieve innate and become a martial arts master.

However, even if he became a master, he would definitely not be able to compare with top experts like the "Immortal Slayer Saber" who could stir up the world's situation. Liu Hao still had this self-awareness.

"The people from the Nine Profound Sect are here!"

Liu Hao fixed his gaze, searching among the Nine Profound Sect group.

Liu Hao's eyes narrowed slightly. He locked onto a figure, Lin Fei! The Lin Fei, who had made Liu Hao flee in panic like a lost dog at the Zhang family that day, had indeed come!

"Lin Fei, you really came. It seems that I'm still lucky. Today, I have the opportunity to avenge my past disgrace!"

Liu Hao was very excited. He had been practicing hard for months for this day! After that, Liu Hao watched as Lin Fei and his group came to the seats reserved for the Nine Profound Sect at the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference.

Then, Liu Hao saw Lin Fei stand up. Surprisingly, he walked towards the thirteen chairs reserved for the masters.

What was Lin Fei doing? Those thirteen chairs were reserved for martial arts masters. Lin Fei was an acquired disciple, what was he doing there?

However, Lin Fei didn't stop. Instead, under Liu Hao's astonished gaze, step by step, he came to the empty chair. Then, Lin Fei directly sat down.

"Boom."

Suddenly, Liu Hao's mind went blank.

"Could it be..."

Liu Hao's face turned pale. At this moment, not only was Liu Hao shocked, everyone at the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference was stunned.

Lin Fei was so young, yet he sat in the chair reserved for masters.

"Nine Profound Sect Grand Elder, 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei, takes his seat!"

A disciple from the Martial Alliance announced loudly. Each martial arts master would be announced by a Martial Alliance disciple. This was a sign of respect for the martial arts masters.

126. Having No Saber IS Better Than Having A Saber

"He is the Immortal Slayer Saber?"

Liu Hao's face turned pale. He widened his eyes, seemingly unable to believe the scene before him.

However, the fact was right there. Lin Fei had already sat down in the chair and even the Martial Alliance disciple announced that the Immortal Slayer Saber was Lin Fei!

At this moment, Liu Hao felt as if all the strength had left his body. His body was even trembling. He had practiced hard for months just waiting for the day when he could meet Lin Fei and avenge his past disgrace.

But what about now?

Lin Fei was the Immortal Slayer Saber! That was a top expert who could slay high-level Qi cultivators from He Mountain Dao with his saber! He was a martial arts master, the Grand Elder of the Nine Profound Sect.

How could he avenge his past disgrace?

"How can a firefly compete with the bright moon?"

Liu Hao's face showed a bitter expression. Then, he closed his eyes and stopped talking.

At this moment, when Lin Fei took his seat, the Martial Alliance announced it, instantly setting off a commotion throughout the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference.

Almost all martial artists' gazes were focused on Lin Fei. Among them, there were some eager gazes, filled with a touch of reverence. It was at this time that Lin Fei began to faintly understand how famous he was now in the martial arts world.

"Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei, in just a few months, had slain several Qi cultivators from He Mountain Dao. His fame then spread rapidly. Throughout the entire Great Chang, he had already surpassed the reputation of countless veteran masters. His popularity was at its peak."

"I didn't expect the famous 'Immortal Slayer Saber' to be so young."

"Just now, when 'Immortal Slayer Saber' was among the Nine Profound Sect group, I thought he was an ordinary disciple. I didn't expect him to be a martial arts master!"

"This 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei is really low-key. He looks just like the other disciples of the Nine Profound Sect. Who would have thought that he is the famous 'Immortal Slayer Saber'?"

"But why doesn't the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei carry a saber?"

For a while, many people were discussing. Of course, many people also noticed that Lin Fei didn't have a saber on him.

One has to know that Lin Fei was the "Immortal Slayer Saber." He had slain several Qi cultivators with his saber. Lin Fei's saber was incredibly sharp that could not only cut down high-level Qi cultivators but also innate martial artists.

However, there was no trace of a saber on Lin Fei. Could it be that Lin Fei practiced a type of martial arts that involved concealing a saber?

In the martial arts world, there were some peculiar martial arts. For example, the Hidden Saber Technique. It involves hiding a saber in the most concealed places on one's body, making it difficult for others to detect. But once in combat, the saber is drawn silently, making it hard for the opponent to defend against.

However, the hidden saber technique was ultimately a "peculiar martial art." The emphasis was on "peculiar." If it was seen through by others, it would lose its power.

As for Qi cultivators, especially high-level Qi cultivators, they had magical artifacts to protect themselves, so they wouldn't care about martial artists' peculiar skills.

There was only one way. That was to use overwhelming power, crush everything in its path, and defeat them head-on.

Although curious about where Lin Fei's saber was hidden, no one asked him. At this time, the focus was on the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference.

"The Martial Alliance Exchange Conference begins now!" A Martial Alliance disciple announced loudly.

In previous Martial Alliance Exchange Conferences, disciples from various sects would go on stage to exchange and compete with each other. There was a familiar process. Of course, there were rewards for the disciples' competitions. The rewards were provided by the various sects together. As for what the rewards were, Lin Fei didn't ask.

On both sides of Lin Fei were two martial arts masters. On his left was a middle-aged man dressed in white. Judging from his attire, he should be the Grand Elder of the Hidden Sword Sect. He looked to be in his early forties, quite young.

After all, many martial artists only broke through to the innate realm and became martial arts masters in their fifties or even sixties. At forty years old, he naturally appeared young.

However, he couldn't compare to Lin Fei, who was not even twenty years old. His youthfulness was somewhat excessive.

On Lin Fei's right was an old man with white hair. He appeared old and frail, with a face full of wrinkles. But his spirit was still strong. As for which sect he belonged to, Lin Fei was not sure. After all, Lin Fei only knew a few sects.

Lin Fei was new to the martial arts world. He hadn't spent much time in the martial arts world and hadn't made many acquaintances.

Among the thirteen martial arts masters, Lin Fei didn't recognize any of them. Therefore, Lin Fei didn't engage in conversation. Instead, he looked at the stage below.

The Martial Alliance Exchange Conference had begun. Disciples from various sects went on stage.

They demonstrated their skills and began to exchange and compete.

This was Lin Fei's first time watching disciples' competitions as a Grand Elder and a martial arts master. After all, Lin Fei used to be on the stage, not in the role of a judge. This made him feel a little novel.

However, after watching for a while, Lin Fei found it somewhat dull.

These acquired realm disciples displayed various martial arts, studying martial arts techniques and moves. It seemed lively. But in reality, they were quite vulnerable.

The essence of martial arts lies in oneself, inner power, body, martial arts beliefs, and so on. These were the most important aspects.

Lin Fei didn't practice that many martial arts in the past. Because he had long understood the essence of martial arts, practicing too many fighting martial arts and studying techniques was meaningless.

At this moment, a white-clothed and heroic-looking female disciple from the Hidden Sword Sect took the stage. With a single sword stroke, she basically ended the battle.

As soon as the sword was drawn, a flash of white light followed. Her opponent was defeated. Her sword technique was similar to Lin Fei's saber method. Just one word, fast!

Moreover, Lin Fei also noticed that this female disciple was not only fast, but her inner power was also very profound. Otherwise, speed alone would not be enough to defeat her opponent with a single sword strike.

This female disciple had already grasped some of the fundamentals of martial arts, and her future was promising.

"Brother Lin, what do you think of my Hidden Sword Sect disciple's swordsmanship?"

Suddenly, Lin Fei heard a voice in his ear.

Lin Fei turned his head. He found that the person speaking was the innate martial artist from the Hidden Sword Sect beside him, the forty-something martial arts master.

"What's your name, sir?" Lin Fei asked. He really didn't know this master.

"Hidden Sword Sect, Lu Zongyi."

"So, it's Brother Lu. Your disciple's swordsmanship is as fast as lightning and very accurate, truly extraordinary. And with exquisite inner power, her future is boundless."

Lin Fei didn't hesitate to praise. This female disciple of the Hidden Sword Sect was indeed very remarkable. She could be considered the disciple with the greatest potential Lin Fei had discovered in this Martial Alliance Exchange Conference. Her future attainment of the innate realm was hopeful.

"I heard that Brother Lin practiced Saber-drawing Technique in the acquired realm. In my Hidden Sword Sect, we also have a Sword-drawing Technique, similar to Saber-drawing Technique. I wonder which is superior, the sword-drawing technique or Saber-drawing Technique?"

Lin Fei shook his head and said, "There may not be much difference. What really determines a martial artist's strength is not the martial arts moves or even which martial art they practice. It's the martial arts foundation and martial arts beliefs! This is the essence of martial arts!"

Lu Zongyi's eyes lit up, and he continued, "That's right. The essence of martial arts is not about martial arts techniques or moves, but about martial arts beliefs and the foundation laid down earlier. My Hidden Sword Sect disciples practice swordsmanship for ten years like a single day.

Every day, they practice and spar with swords, always accompanied by their swords. Every moment, the sword is never far from them, and they cherish their swords as they cherish their lives, only in this way can they achieve something in swordsmanship!

But I haven't seen a saber on Brother Lin. I know a thing or two about whether Brother Lin has a saber or not. Since Brother Lin is the Immortal Slayer Saber, how can he slay immortals without a saber? Could it be that Brother Lin has already given up using the saber?"

Lu Zongyi expressed doubt in his heart. How could the Immortal Slayer Saber slay immortals without a saber?

As a swordsman, Lu Zongyi could naturally sense whether Lin Fei had a saber. So he knew that Lin Fei hadn't practiced any hidden saber techniques. Lin Fei simply didn't carry a saber!

At this point, Lu Zongyi was puzzled. For a swordsman, it is common knowledge to always have their sword with them. The same should apply to saber wielders. How could he not carry a saber? Especially when he was the famous Immortal Slayer Saber?

Lin Fei had a smile on his face, his expression calm. In fact, Lin Fei also wanted to carry a saber. However, no treasured saber could withstand his Saber Qi.

So naturally, Lin Fei couldn't carry a saber. Instead, he used Saber Qi to condense and replaced the saber with his hand.

However, these were Lin Fei's secrets. They couldn't be easily revealed.

Not to mention explaining it to Lu Zongyi, so Lin Fei closed his eyes, and spoke calmly and slowly, "In my hand, there is no saber, but in my heart, there is a saber! My saber is in my heart! Having no saber is better than having a saber!"

Upon hearing this, Lu Zongyi's body shook as if a thunderbolt exploded in his mind and kept rumbling in his mind. The look in his eyes as he stared at Lin Fei was filled with extreme astonishment!

127. The Battle Between Saber Intent and Sword Intent

Lu Zongyi felt as if he had received enlightenment in his mind. It was as if he had grasped a ray of inspiration.

"What a concept! Having no saber is better than having a saber. No saber in hand, but a saber in the heart. No wonder you are the Immortal Slayer Saber, even though you have just reached the innate level, but in terms of the saber realm, you have already reached the peak..."

Lu Zongyi's emotions surged. For a long time, his sword realm had not made any progress. And now, Lin Fei's few words seemed to have suddenly enlightened Lu Zongyi. Flashes of inspiration kept appearing in his mind.

"Brother Lin, please accept my salute!"

Lu Zongyi was obviously a genuine gentleman, or perhaps, a sword fanatic. He was devoted to the sword all his life, which led him to his current level. Lin Fei's words were worth ten years of hard work!

Lu Zongyi's actions were noticed by others. Especially the martial arts masters nearby. They all looked at Lu Zongyi and Lin Fei with a hint of shock. They didn't know what had gotten into Lu Zongyi, who was actually saluting Lin Fei.

"Whoosh."

The next moment, Lu Zongyi jumped onto one of the empty arenas. Then, he shouted to Lin Fei: "Hidden Sword Sect's Lu Zongyi, specially seeks advice from 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei. I hope Brother Lin can come on stage and exchange pointers with me!"

Lu Zongyi's words left everyone somewhat dumbfounded. It was well known that the arena was for the disciples of various sects to exchange ideas. Why did Lu Zongyi take the stage?

After all, Lu Zongyi was the Grand Elder of the Hidden Sword Sect. He was also a young martial arts master and his swordsmanship was very profound. An innate expert was actually going on stage himself! And most importantly, the one Lu Zongyi was challenging was the "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei. For a moment, this naturally caused a sensation.

"What is Lu Zongyi doing?"

"How can a respectable innate expert, martial arts master, and the Grand Elder of the Hidden Sword Sect act so recklessly?"

"Although the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference does not forbid martial artists from exchanging ideas, isn't a martial arts master being too impatient?"

"The disciples haven't even finished their matches, what's the hurry for Lu Zongyi?"

"However, I'm looking forward to the battle between Lu Zongyi and Lin Fei."

"Let's see whose swordsmanship is more powerful, Lu Zongyi's or the 'Immortal Slayer Saber's saber techniques?"

The other martial arts masters were somewhat dissatisfied, but the disciples' eyes were shining. Their emotions were extremely exciting. A battle between two innate experts! Moreover, it was a contest between a swordsman and a saber wielder.

There is no first in literature, no second in martial arts. It is the same in the martial arts world. Conflicts between saber and sword often occur. Which is more powerful, the saber or the sword? This has been a long-standing debate in the martial arts world. And now, they could witness such an intense and exciting battle. How could these acquired martial artists not be excited and thrilled?

"Challenge me?"

Lin Fei's eyes narrowed slightly. He saw the fighting spirit of Lu Zongyi. However, he did not immediately agree. Even if Lu Zongyi was an innate martial artist and a martial arts master, so what? Not everyone was qualified to challenge Lin Fei. Otherwise, wouldn't Lin Fei be troubled by challenges wherever he went? Therefore, Lin Fei remained silent.

Lu Zongyi seemed to guess Lin Fei's thoughts. He took a deep breath. Then, a terrifying aura suddenly erupted from his body.

"Boom."

This aura condensed into a huge sword phantom above Lu Zongyi's head that only innate martial artists could "see" it.

At the same time. around the arena, disciples of various sects and some wandering martial artists, anyone holding a sword in their hand, these swords were trembling slightly. Faintly, it seemed that there was a light humming sound.

"What's going on?"

"Is my sword moving?"

"Sword intent! Lu Zongyi has comprehended sword intent!"

"Is this sword intent? I thought only one master in the Hidden Sword Sect had comprehended sword intent?"

"Hidden Sword Sect has always been mysterious. Letting Lu Zongyi lead the team this time may be to showcase the strength of the Hidden Sword Sect."

"That's right, although the Hidden Sword Sect is named 'Hidden Sword', in fact, the sword should not be hidden. The sword should be exposed, and it should be displayed openly!"

"Hidden Sword Sect, worthy of being a deep-rooted martial arts sect, once gave birth to a Martial Saint. Even though the Sword Saint Bai passed away three hundred years ago, the Hidden Sword Sect still has outstanding talents. Now another master who has comprehended sword intent has emerged!"

"No wonder Lu Zongyi has the confidence to challenge 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei, it turns out he has comprehended sword intent. Lu Zongyi truly has the qualification to fight Lin Fei."

"What kind of sparks will the collision of sword intent and saber intent create? How exciting would it be?"

For a moment, countless people's gazes were on Lin Fei. Now, Lu Zongyi had already challenged Lin Fei. Moreover, he had even displayed his sword intent. Would 'Immortal Slayer Saber' Lin Fei accept or decline?

"Sword intent..."

A glint of light flashed in Lin Fei's eyes as well. Ever since Lin Fei had comprehended Martial Dao True Intent, he had not encountered a second martial artist who had comprehended Martial Dao True Intent except for his master Zhao Kongming.

But since Zhao Kongming had comprehended sword intent, Lin Fei had never exchanged pointers with him. Therefore, Lin Fei was indeed very interested in other martial artists with sword intent. Martial artists were meant to battle against heaven and earth. Fighting was the instinct of martial artists.

So, Lin Fei spoke, "The Martial Alliance Exchange Conference is for martial artists to exchange ideas with each other. Since Master Lu Zongyi wants to exchange pointers, I will gladly accompany him!"

Lin Fei slowly stood up. However, Lin Fei did not quickly come to the arena. Instead, he took one step at a time. With a very slow and steady pace, he walked over slowly.

With every step Lin Fei took, the momentum on his body became stronger. After arriving at the arena, Lin Fei's momentum finally reached its peak.

"Boom."

Saber intent!

Lin Fei's saber intent erupted completely. Moreover, Lin Fei had honed his saber intent on Ancestral Master Peak. Although it hadn't reached transcendence, the saber intent had indeed become stronger. Therefore, when the saber intent fully erupted, it instantly enveloped the entire exchange meeting in the sky.

"Buzz, buzz, buzz."

As Lin Fei's saber intent erupted, the sabers in those saber-wielding martial artists' hands also began to vibrate intensely. Moreover, the vibrations were very intense. As a result, a strange scene appeared among the many martial artists.

The sounds of swords and sabers hummed one after another. Many martial artists were astonished. In the void, it seemed as if there were two invisible forces constantly clashing with each other.

"Shh, crack."

Many people seemed to feel that Lin Fei's saber intent and Lu Zongyi's sword intent were constantly entwining and colliding. It was as if even the void would be torn apart.

Of course, this was an illusion. Both Lin Fei and Lu Zongyi's saber and sword intent had not yet reached the level of being able to tear apart space. That was simply impossible. But in the perception of many innate powerhouses, the collision of Lin Fei and Lu Zongyi's Martial Dao True Intent made these innate experts feel a strong sense of threat.

Martial Dao True Intent was not only effective against Qi condensing cultivators, but it was also a part of martial arts strength. Whether or not an innate martial artist had Martial Dao True Intent made a huge difference.

"How terrifying saber intent and sword intent. Both Lin Fei and Lu Zongyi are extremely young. I didn't expect them to have comprehended saber intent and sword intent to such an extent."

"'Immortal Slayer Saber' is truly extraordinary. His saber intent is clearly stronger than Lu Zongyi's sword intent."

"Saber intent is indeed stronger for Lin Fei. However, in a martial artist's battle, as long as Martial Dao True Intent is not crushed, the outcome still depends on their martial arts."

"The swordsmanship of the Hidden Sword Sect is unparalleled in the world. It's hard to predict who will win and who will lose in this battle."

"Although Lin Fei is known as the 'Immortal Slayer Saber', he only faced high-level Qi condensing cultivators, who were suppressed by his saber intent. In terms of real strength, Lu Zongyi is not inferior to Lin Fei, and may even be stronger!"

These martial arts masters' eyes were sharp and experienced. They all knew that the current situation between Lin Fei and Lu Zongyi was just a competition between Martial Dao True Intent.

For martial artists, as long as Martial Dao True Intent doesn't collapse, it still depends on their own martial arts in the end. Both Lin Fei and Lu Zongyi were motionless as if they were looking for each other's flaws. They didn't make a move, but once they did, they would decide the outcome.

At the level of Lin Fei and Lu Zongyi, martial arts, lightness techniques, and Martial Dao True Intent were all top-notch. To decide the outcome, one move was enough!

128. Sudden Change, Qi Cultivators Arrive

Just as the momentum of the two reached its peak, preparing to decide the victory with one move, a crane's cry suddenly came from the distance. At the same time, Lin Fei and Lu Zongyi both felt something. They immediately looked towards the distant sky.

In the sky, more than ten immortal cranes flew over the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference. On the cranes, there were more than ten Qi cultivators wearing Daoist robes!

Yes, Qi cultivators.

At a glance, innate martial artists could sense the spiritual power fluctuations of the Qi cultivators. Among them, an old man with white hair and proud eyes glanced at the many martial artists below. Then he shouted loudly, "I am Yuan Gangzi from Guardian Primordial Mountain! I am tracking a demonic cultivator who stole our Guardian Primordial Mountain's cultivation technique, and he deserves death for his crime!

This demonic cultivator has blended into the crowd and may be among the Martial Alliance. So, I have no choice but to offend you all, and I must find this demonic cultivator today! Before the demonic cultivator is found, no one is allowed to leave the mountain. Set up the formation!"

As Yuan Gangzi gave the order, more than ten Qi cultivators behind him who were sitting on immortal cranes, jumped off the cranes directly. Formation flags in their hands were placed in all directions in an instant.

"Buzz."

The next moment, the entire Martial Alliance headquarter was separated by a layer of light. This was a formation that completely sealed the inside and outside. Once someone tried to leave, Yuan Gangzi would be alerted. No one could escape!

"Yuan Gangzi, what do you want? Today is our Martial Alliance's grand event, quickly withdraw your formation to save face."

"That's right, Yuan Gangzi, let's talk about whatever matter you have after the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference is over."

For a moment, many older martial arts masters from various sects stood up, angry at Yuan Gangzi. Although their tone was severe, there seemed to be a hint of apprehension.

"Guardian Primordial Mountain?"

Lin Fei's eyebrows furrowed slightly. He had never heard of Guardian Primordial Mountain. At this time, Lu Zongyi, who was opposite Lin Fei, had already withdrawn his sword intent.

His face was pale, and he said in a deep voice, "Guardian Primordial Mountain is the only immortal sect near Cang City Mountian. Like He Mountain Dao, it is a major sect in the immortal Daoist school. There are many top Qi cultivators in the sect.

More importantly, Guardian Primordial Mountain has a Qi Condensation Perfection cultivator. It is said that within a short period of time, no more than a year, he will definitely succeed in forming his foundation. So, Guardian Primordial Mountain has been acting quite unscrupulously recently."

Lin Fei understood. He looked at Yuan Gangzi who was still sitting on the back of the immortal crane, looking down at all the martial artists below from a high position.

As for those Guardian Primordial Mountain's Qi cultivators, their eyes were indifferent. They didn't care about the curses from the martial artists below. More importantly, there was no fear in their eyes.

Perhaps, in the eyes of the Qi cultivators of Guardian Primordial Mountain, the Martial Alliance is nothing at all. Cang City Mountain, rather than being the territory of the Martial Alliance, it is more like the sphere of influence of Guardian Primordial Mountain.

"Too much bullying!"

"This is the headquarters of the Martial Alliance, not the gate of your Guardian Primordial Mountain."

"Talking about sealing off just like that, what do you Guardian Primordial Mountain think of us?"

The Martial Alliance's thirteen sects were established initially to counter the immortal sects.

But what about now?

Although they were angrily cursing one by one, not a single one dared to take action. Even the mighty innate martial artists and martial arts masters, facing the Qi cultivators of Guardian Primordial Mountain, didn't even dare to make a move.

"Martial Alliance..."

Lin Fei glanced at the martial arts masters of the Martial Alliance's thirteen sects. He was very disappointed.

These martial arts masters, innate experts, were unattainable powerhouses in the eyes of ordinary disciples.

But what about now?

Facing the Qi cultivators of Guardian Primordial Mountain, they didn't even dare to make a move.

Yuan Gangzi had already set up a formation directly. It was equivalent to sealing off all the martial artists here.

This is a disgrace! The disgrace of martial artists!

"Brother Lin, are you very disappointed?"

At this moment, Lu Zongyi suddenly spoke up. His eyes were sharp as a sword.

"This is the Martial Alliance. Or rather, this is the martial artist of today. For hundreds of years, they have been suppressed by the Qi cultivators. Facing the Qi cultivators, martial artists have long lost their bravery.

Moreover, do you know why those innate martial artists don't dare to make a move at all? Because Yuan Gangzi is at the eleventh level of Qi condensation. That is, a top Qi condensation cultivator! Other than martial arts Grand Masters, no one among martial artists can fight against top Qi Condensation cultivators."

Lin Fei understood. No wonder Yuan Gangzi was so fearless. Even in the face of hundreds of martial artists and thirteen martial arts masters, he remained unflustered. Even standing proudly on the back of the immortal crane, looking down at the crowd. That's because Yuan Gangzi had enough confidence!

The eleventh level of Qi condensation was a truly top Qi Condensation cultivator.

Qi condensation also had twelve levels. And those above the tenth level could be called top Qi cultivators. Unless martial arts grandmasters, no one could compete with top Qi cultivators. Of course, except for some rare and exceptional talents.

However, the current martial arts world was in decline. Where were those rare and exceptional talents? Even martial arts grandmasters are few and far between.

On the back of the immortal crane, Yuan Gangzi stood with his hands behind his back. With an indifferent gaze, he looked at the martial artists below and said coldly, "All of you cooperate well with the search by my Guardian Primordial Mountain disciples. Otherwise, you will be killed without mercy!"

Domineering!

This is Yuan Gangzi.

This is Guardian Primordial Mountain.

This is the Immortal Sect!

Some acquired martial artists clenched their teeth, obviously furious to the extreme. Guardian Primordial Mountain's Qi-condensing disciples were about to begin their search.

"Fuck your search!"

"Die!"

Martial artists never lack bravery. Some acquired martial artists or hot-tempered wanderers couldn't hold back the anger in their hearts. They attacked the Qi condensing disciples who came to search.

However, the next moment, these acquired martial artists couldn't even break through the defensive spells of these disciples. They were killed by the magical artifacts activated by the Qi-condensing disciples, their heads severed, or their hearts pierced.

A strong smell of blood filled the air. Many martial artists were extremely angry, but they dared not speak. They were acquired martial artists and they couldn't even break the defensive spells of the Qi cultivators. What could they do to resist?

Only innate martial artists could use Innate True Qi to break through the spells and magical artifacts of the Qi cultivators, to compete with them.

However, out of the thirteen innate martial artists, who would dare to take action?

"Buzz."

Many martial artists' swords suddenly began to hum. Sword Intent! It was Lu Zongyi who had unleashed his Sword Intent.

"Yuan Gangzi, martial artists are not to be insulted!"

Lu Zongyi's eyes were as sharp as a sword. At this moment, his eyes were filled with killing intent!

"Whoosh."

Lu Zongyi drew his sword! He pulled out the sword from behind him. Even just now, when Lu Zongyi challenged Lin Fei, he didn't draw his long sword. But now, he unsheathed his sword.

"Sword Control Slash!"

Lu Zongyi's voice was loud and resounding, echoing in everyone's ears. At the same time, his sword actually flew out directly, carrying a meter of sword energy and soaring Sword Intent, slashed fiercely at Yuan Gangzi!

"Boom."

Everyone looked at Yuan Gangzi in the void. Sword Intent plus a meter of sword energy, none of the martial arts masters present, except Lin Fei, dared to guarantee that they could withstand Lu Zongyi's sword. This was also Lu Zongyi's strongest sword.

However, this sword stopped. It stopped three meters in front of Yuan Gangzi. Yuan Gangzi didn't even move his body. He just stared coldly at Lu Zongyi below. Even his eyes were filled with a hint of pity and mockery.

"Sword Intent is indeed not bad. You martial artists always think that with Sword Intent, you can slash us Qi cultivators? How ignorant! And the recently popular 'Immortal Slayer Saber', killing two useless He Mountain Dao disciples, was exaggerated by you as an immortal slayer?

Today, even if I stand here, the 'Immortal Slayer Saber' won't hurt a hair on my body! As for you, the innate martial artist of Hidden Sword Sect, go to hell!"

Yuan Gangzi stretched out his hand, pointed at Lu Zongyi, and flicked his finger lightly.

"Whoosh."

A silver flash appeared and disappeared in an instant.

Flying sword! This is a real flying sword!

In the blink of an eye, it arrived in front of Lu Zongyi.

The flying sword didn't reveal any earth-shattering aura, only the ultimate sharpness!

Lu Zongyi could only slash out with his sword again. A massive amount of Innate True Qi erupted instantly.

However, the flying sword seemed unaffected. Its speed increased dramatically. It pierced through Lu Zongyi's protective True Qi in an instant.

Lu Zongyi knew he couldn't block Yuan Gangzi's flying sword. So, he closed his eyes in despair.

"Snap."

The next moment, a fair hand reached out in front of Lu Zongyi. It gently grabbed the sharp flying sword that was aimed at him.

129. This Is My Saber

Silence!

The entire Martial Alliance Exchange Conference suddenly became quiet that even the sound of people's breathing could be heard. One could hear a pin drop!

Lu Zongyi felt something was off. It seemed like he hadn't died?

Lu Zongyi slowly opened his eyes. The first thing he saw was a fair hand in front of him. Following the direction of the hand, he saw that in this fair palm, there was actually a delicate, exquisite-looking flying sword.

The flying sword had no handle and was faintly silver-white in color. An endless sharp aura emanated from the flying sword. This was the flying sword that had just pierced through Lu Zongyi's protective True Qi.

In the hands of a Qi Condensation cultivator, a small flying sword could kill invisibly. Even a martial arts master like Lu Zongyi, who possessed Sword Intent, couldn't block it.

But at this moment, this terrifying flying sword was being held by a fair hand. Even though the flying sword was struggling violently, it was to no avail.

"Brother Lin?"

Lu Zongyi's eyes suddenly focused. It was Lin Fei!

Moreover, Lin Fei had actually caught the flying sword with his flesh and blood hand. How was this possible? This was a flying sword!

The flying swords refined by Qi cultivators were made of special materials. The material was better than any treasure saber. Very hard, almost indestructible, and extremely sharp.

Lu Zongyi had never heard of anyone being able to directly catch a flying sword with their bare hands. But now, the fact was right before his eyes.

Although the flying sword was constantly struggling and the sharp aura of the flying sword continuously cut Lin Fei's palm, trying to escape from Lin Fei's hand, the jade-like palm seemed harder than refined steel. No matter how the flying sword struggled, it was futile.

This scene shocked everyone. Even those innate experts and martial arts masters, were dumbfounded, with waves of astonishment surging in their hearts.

"Is it true that a mere flesh and blood hand can grasp the flying sword of a top-notch Qi Condensation cultivator?"

"Everyone says that 'Immortal Slayer Saber' has an incredibly sharp saber technique. But his body is so strong too. Is he even a martial artist?"

"Something's not right. There seems to be some power in Lin Fei's hand. Is it Innate True Qi?"

"Innate True Qi can suppress a flying sword and even prevent its struggle?"

Innate experts were shocked by this scene. Not to mention the acquired martial artists. They were beyond words with shock. Catching a flying sword with bare hands, was this still the martial artist they knew?

"Who are you?"

At this moment, Yuan Gangzi spoke. His expression was a mix of shock and anger. Knowing that his flying sword was caught by someone with their bare hands, he knew it was serious.

He was very familiar with his own flying sword. How could someone catch a flying sword with their bare hands? But the reality was right in front of him, and he had no choice but to believe it.

"Who am I?"

Lin Fei smiled. He looked down at the flying sword in his palm. Then, he gently applied force.

"Crack."

The flying sword shattered! Not only did Lin Fei catch the flying sword with his bare hands, he even crushed the flying sword with his bare hands.

"Puff."

Yuan Gangzi spat out a mouthful of blood. The flying sword and the Qi cultivator were connected in life. Especially this flying sword, which had been refined by Yuan Gangzi for decades. Now that the flying sword was suddenly destroyed, Yuan Gangzi naturally suffered some backlash.

"How dare you destroy my flying sword?"

There was still blood at the corner of Yuan Gangzi's mouth and his expression became distorted with anger.

"Who are you?"

There was a cold killing intent in Yuan Gangzi's voice.

"Didn't you just say that if you stand still and let me attack, you won't be harmed in the slightest? Now you're asking me who I am?"

Lin Fei's words made Yuan Gangzi's eyes suddenly focus.

"Immortal Slayer Saber!"

Yuan Gangzi finally understood. The martial artist in front of him was none other than the Immortal Slayer Saber, whose recent exploits had caused a sensation throughout Great Chang.

Before, Yuan Gangzi thought that the two Qi cultivators from He Mountain Dao were just too incompetent. They were killed by a mere martial artist. Even if it was an innate martial artist, what of it? As long as it wasn't a Grandmaster, killing any innate martial artist wasn't a problem for Yuan Gangzi.

However, now that he faced the real "Immortal Slayer Saber," he suddenly realized. Maybe it wasn't that the two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators from He Mountain Dao were too incompetent, "Immortal Slayer Saber" Lin Fei might be truly extraordinary. At least, Yuan Gangzi had never heard of any martial artist who dared to catch a flying sword bare-handed, and without any harm to themselves.

Lin Fei released his hand. He casually threw the fragments of the flying sword to the ground. In fact, Lin Fei was able to catch the flying sword with his bare hands because of Saber Qi!

Lin Fei's Saber Qi had long been spread all over his palm. The Saber Qi far surpassed Innate True Qi that even a flying sword couldn't penetrate it.

No matter how the flying sword struggled, Lin Fei's Saber Qi firmly trapped the flying sword. Even more, Lin Fei unleashed his Saber Qi, easily crushing it.

Lin Fei looked at Lu Zongyi and said calmly, "Brother Lu, didn't you want to see my saber? Now, I'll show you my saber!"

The next moment, Lin Fei extended his fair hand.

"Boom."

Lin Fei's Saber Qi within his body erupted instantly. At the same time, the Saber Qi that burst from Lin Fei's palm was immense. In the void, saber energy as tall as thirty meters was directly condensed.

The terrifying sharpness radiated from it. Even a glance from afar would make the eyes feel stinging pain. Saber Qi was formed by the fusion of saber intent and a large amount of Innate True Qi. Every strand of Saber Qi contained saber intent!

The Saber Qi as tall as thirty meters suddenly spanned across the void. Even Lu Zongyi, a well-versed martial arts master, couldn't help but widen his eyes.

Shocking!

An unparalleled shock!

A typical innate martial artist, having a three meters saber energy was already extraordinary.

And now?

Lin Fei had a thirty-meters saber energy and it was ten or even a hundred times stronger than the saber light!

At the same time, the thirty-meter saber energy faintly gave people the feeling that it was like a peerless fierce blade. A "killing aura" emanated from the ten-meter Saber Qi.

"Watch closely, this is my saber! Heavenly Saber Art, slash!"

Lin Fei's eyes were cold. He directly waved his hand and slashed fiercely toward Yuan Gangzi in the distance.

"Boom."

The terrifying saber energy was surging and overwhelming. Yuan Gangzi wanted to avoid it at first moment. However, he suddenly discovered that a killing aura locked him in. It seemed that no matter how he dodged, he couldn't escape.

This was the Heavenly Saber Art! Below mastery, it condensed a Fierce Saber. It could emit a killing aura, locking onto the opponent's breath, leaving the opponent with no escape.

It was Lin Fei's first time using the Heavenly Saber Art to condense a Fierce Saber against an enemy, but it wasn't his first time using Saber Qi. Therefore, this time using Saber Qi was incredibly satisfying for Lin Fei!

"As long as I want, the saber is there! Victory without a saber. The saber is in the heart, and only then can this saber be unleashed!"

Lin Fei's words echoed in everyone's ears. Like the sound of a giant bell, it made all martial artists feel enlightened.

To what extent had his saber realm reached?

"This youngster, his saber technique can reach divine levels!"

After a long time, a white-haired martial arts master, staring at the thirty-meter saber energy in the void and said.

130. Who in the world would dare to take on Lin Fei's saber?

Compared to the shock of others, Yuan Gangzi, who was locked by the thirty-meter saber energy, felt like a lost soul. He seemed to have already sensed the threat of death.

"I am at the 11th level of Qi Condensation. I have high hopes for building my foundation in the future. How can I be afraid of a mere martial artist? These saber energy must be superficially strong but weak inside. It's impossible to break through my spells. Also, my magical artifact, the Four Divine Umbrella, block it!"

Yuan Gangzi slapped his forehead. Suddenly, an umbrella-shaped magical artifact flew out of his body. The magical artifact instantly opened, enveloping Yuan Gangzi inside.

At the same time, Yuan Gangzi grabbed a large handful of talismans from his bosom. No matter what kind of talismans, his spiritual power crazily flowed, pouring into the talismans. He threw them directly at the terrifying thirty-meter Saber Qi in the void.

"Rumbling."

Countless talismans, dozens, even hundreds of them, instantly unleashed their spells. However, these spells were varied. The real defensive spells were few and far between. Under the immense saber energy, they were completely crushed and cut, instantly turned into dust.

At the same time, the thirty-meter saber energy finally fell, and the void seemed to emit a muffled sound.

Yuan Gangzi was originally standing on a crane. But now, he was pressed down by Lin Fei's thirty-meter Saber Qi. Both the person and the crane fell to the ground. The terrifying power acted on the crane's body.

"Splatter."

The crane let out a mournful cry. Then, the force of the saber energy slashed directly and crushed the crane into a pool of blood.

Yuan Gangzi's face was full of horror. The defensive spells he had cast, and even several layers of them, turned out to be as fragile as paper, easily cut open by the saber energy.

The terrifying Saber Qi even directly landed on his Four Divine Umbrella.

The Four Divine Umbrella was a half-finished magical treasure personally refined by a Foundation Establishment cultivator. All the materials used were suitable for magical treasure. It was just that the refining process failed in the end. So it didn't become a magical treasure.

It was considered a semi-finished product, an inferior one. But when used by Yuan Gangzi, who was at the 11th level of Qi Condensation, its defensive ability had reached a very terrifying peak. Yuan Gangzi's hope was all in these Four Divine Umbrella.

The thirty-meter saber energy was like a mountain pressing down on him. With unstoppable momentum, it fiercely slashed on the Four Divine Umbrella.

The sharpness of the saber energy and the terrifying saber intent it contained made Yuan Gangzi extremely nervous.

The protective barrier of the Four Divine Umbrella was brutally flattened by the saber energy.

"Block it, you must block it!"

Yuan Gangzi's eyes turned bloodshot, full of blood vessels. However, the Four Divine Umbrella ultimately couldn't withstand Lin Fei's thirty-meter saber energy.

"Crack."

The Four Divine Umbrella shattered. Its spiritual light dimmed, no longer having any effect. Yuan Gangzi could only watch helplessly as the terrifying saber energy effortlessly cut through his protective spiritual power like cutting through tofu.

"Bang."

Yuan Gangzi's figure was engulfed in the thirty-meter saber energy. In an instant, he was shredded into a mist of blood by the saber energy. The terrifying saber energy even had remaining power, landing on the ground, slashed a huge crack.

Silence!

Very quiet!

The Martial Alliance Exchange event, with hundreds or even thousands of people, was originally lively. The crowd was noisy.

But now, it seemed to be silent. All the martial artists just stared blankly at the huge crack in the ground.

Was that the crack created by Lin Fei's saber energy? Even, it incidentally killed a top-level Qi Condensation cultivator!

That was an 11th-level Qi Condensation cultivator, a core elder of Guardian Primordial Mountain!

And now? Dead!

Yuan Gangzi died just like that under Lin Fei's saber energy, in one move!

Yuan Gangzi couldn't even withstand a single move. Just like the two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators from He Mountain Dao in the rumors, they were killed by Lin Fei with a single slash.

Yuan Gangzi was a top-level Qi Condensation cultivator. It seemed that he wasn't much stronger than the Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao. The outcome was the same.

"Immortal Slayer Saber, this is the real Immortal Slayer Saber!"

"Another Qi Condensation cultivator has died. This time, it's a top-level one!"

"How many Qi cultivators have died at the hands of the Immortal Slayer Saber?"

"Sure enough, there are only wrong names in the martial world, but no wrong titles. The 'Immortal Slayer Saber' truly lives up to its name, with the saber out, it slays immortals!"

"Is this 'Immortal Slayer Saber' really martial arts? The power of this saber is probably not inferior to that of a grandmaster, right?"

"Even in some aspects, a grandmaster might not be able to slash out such a terrifying saber!"

Some martial artists couldn't help but think of martial arts grandmasters. It seemed that the grandmasters in the rumors were nothing more than this!

Of course, martial arts grandmasters also varied in strength. The difference was very significant. For example, the grandmaster like the founder of the Nine Profound Sect, who was invincible below Foundation Establishment! Even if it was a Qi Condensation cultivator at the peak of perfection, when facing the Nine Profound Sect founder, it would only take a single slash.

Otherwise, how could they be called invincible?

The title of "invincible" isn't so easy to obtain. It's based on real achievements. Dominating the world, invincible in all directions!

At this moment, Lin Fei seemed no different from being invincible in the eyes of some martial artists. They had just witnessed Lin Fei unleash a thirty-meter-tall saber energy.

How terrifying was that?

They didn't know what kind of person or power could withstand such a thirty-meter saber energy.

"This saber technique..."

Lu Zongyi's gaze was complicated as he looked at Lin Fei, unable to speak for a long time. Such a saber technique was beyond his ability to describe. He even felt that his decades of practicing the sword paled in comparison to Lin Fei's single saber strike. Even if he practiced his sword for another hundred years, it would be no match for Lin Fei's saber.

Lin Fei stood with his hands behind his back, looking at Lu Zongyi, and calmly asked, "Brother Lu, do you still wish to continue the exchange?"

Upon hearing this, Lu Zongyi couldn't help but shake his head, sighing, "Master Lin's saber technique is divine! I admit my inferiority, consider this exchange a joke on my part."

Lu Zongyi admitted defeat, wholeheartedly accepting it. Clearly, he had been thoroughly convinced by Lin Fei's saber strike just now.

At this point, the Qi Condensation cultivators Guardian Primordial Mountain finally came to their senses. How could they continue to blockade the Martial Alliance? They quickly collected their flags, jumped onto the back of their immortal cranes, and fled in panic.

In the blink of an eye, they vanished without a trace. Gone was their arrogance from before. This allowed many martial artists to witness the weak side of the Qi cultivators for the first time. Immortal Sect's Qi Condensation cultivators were nothing more than that!

"Master Lin, let's end this Martial Alliance Exchange Conference here. After this incident, it would be best for Master Lin to leave Cang City Mountain quickly. Guardian Primordial Mountain has not only top Qi Condensation cultivators but also powerful cultivators close to Foundation Establishment.

Moreover, the Martial Alliance isn't far from Guardian Primordial Mountain. If the Guardian Primordial Mountain sect leader becomes furious and brings the mountain-protecting treasure, it'll be troublesome.

Guardian Primordial Mountain's mountain-protecting treasure is a genuine magical treasure! If set up in a grand formation, even an ordinary Foundation Establishment cultivator can't break through."

Some masters of the Martial Alliance's thirteen factions urged Lin Fei to leave quickly.

"A mountain-protecting treasure that even Foundation Establishment cultivators can't break?"

A hint of curiosity flashed in Lin Fei's eyes. These immortal sects had a heritage spanning over a thousand years. Even the Great Chang's founding emperor, the mighty Martial Saint, could only suppress but not completely annihilate these immortal sects. It seemed that it was because of these sects' mountain-protecting treasures.

"Well, this Martial Alliance Exchange Conference has come to an end, and it's time to leave."

Lin Fei nodded in agreement. He had killed Yuan Gangzi simply because Yuan Gangzi had provoked him. Unless it was absolutely necessary, no one would choose to confront an immortal sect with a thousand-year heritage.

Lin Fei was no exception. As long as he returned to the Nine Profound Sect, Guardian Primordial Mountain would have no way to deal with him.

"Brother Lin, once everything settles down, please do visit our Hidden Sword Sect. Our Hidden Sword Sect has produced a Martial Saint. As for sword intent perfectionists, there have been several throughout history. We won't disappoint you."

Lu Zongyi enthusiastically invited Lin Fei to be a guest at the Hidden Sword Sect. Lin Fei's eyes lit up upon hearing this.

Sword intent perfection! Martial Saints! Both had appeared in the Hidden Sword Sect's history. In terms of foundation, it was much stronger than the Nine Profound Sect.

"If I have the time, I will definitely visit the Hidden Sword Sect!"

After saying this, Lin Fei led the Nine Profound Sect disciples and quickly left the Martial Alliance.

Thus, the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference came to a hasty end. Many martial artists left Cang City Mountain one after another.

However, even though there were some unexpected incidents during the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference, making it an incomplete event, the martial artists who attended this exchange felt that their trip was worthwhile!

Not only did they witness sword intent and saber intent, but they also saw the unparalleled prowess of the "Immortal Slayer Saber." Lin Fei slayed immortals once again. Moreover, with a single saber strike, a thirty-meter saber energy! Who in the world would dare to take on Lin Fei's saber?

131. Master and Disciple Sparring

"Finally back."

Lin Fei looked at the Nine Profound Sect and breathed a sigh of relief. After the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference had ended, he had not stopped at all. He led his disciples day and night, and they finally returned to the Nine Profound Sect.

If it were only Lin Fei, he wouldn't fear Guardian Primordial Mountain. However, there were many Nine Profound Sect disciples following him. So, Lin Fei had some concerns.

"Alright, you all go back to the inner sect and rest."

"Yes, Grand Elder."

These disciples had all witnessed Lin Fei's display of power at the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference. With a single saber strike, he killed Yuan Gangzi, Guardian Primordial Mountain's top Qi Condensation cultivator. The thirty-meter-tall saber energy and the terrifying saber intent deeply impressed these disciples. In their eyes, Lin Fei had become the spiritual symbol of the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei didn't mind the fanaticism in the disciples' eyes. Titles and fame were like passing clouds in his eyes. Strength was the foundation! He sought immortality!

"Killing Yuan Gangzi this time didn't increase my saber intent. This means Yuan Gangzi wasn't strong enough in the eyes of saber intent. It seems I need to go to the Ancestral Master Peak to improve my saber intent."

Lin Fei furrowed his brows. His saber intent was aloof. The only way to improve it was to defeat powerful opponents or hone it. Of course, there was also sudden enlightenment, but it was something one could encounter but not seek.

"Going to Ancestral Master Peak."

Lin Fei wanted his saber intent to reach transcendence as soon as possible. Being only at Mastery, Lin Fei felt it was no longer enough. Its power was far inferior to Saber Qi. After all, Lin Fei's opponents were either top Qi Condensation cultivators or those at Qi Condensation perfection. His opponents would only grow stronger.

At the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference, Lin Fei realized that though his saber intent was strong, only slightly surpassed Lu Zongyi's sword intent. His saber intent was not that impressive among martial artists who had comprehended Martial Dao True Intent.

If it could reach transcendence, it would be a different story. Transcendence saber intent would at least increase tenfold or even dozens of times! Moreover, Lin Fei had another consideration. His progress in cultivating the True Intention Scroll was slow. But the True Intention Scroll was closely related to his saber intent.

If his saber intent could improve, even reaching transcendence, the True Intention Scroll would undoubtedly advance rapidly. This would be killing two birds with one stone! So, upon returning to the Nine Profound Sect, Lin Fei had no intention of resting at all.

With a step forward, his figure appeared thirty meters away. Step by step, he headed towards Ancestral Master Peak.

At Ancestral Master Peak, in front of a stone tablet, an old man sat cross-legged. His eyes were closed, and his face was calm.

Lin Fei approached the Ancestral Master Peak step by step. Seeing the old man in front of the stone tablet, he was slightly surprised.

"Master!"

Lin Fei called out. The old man in front of the stone tablet was none other than Lin Fei's master, "Empty Abyss Sword" Zhao Kongming.

"Buzz."

Suddenly, a vast and mighty sword intent erupted from the stone tablet! It was as if the sky was about to be torn apart by the sword intent. At the same time, Zhao Kongming's body also erupted with terrifying sword intent.

Above Zhao Kongming's head, a vague sword shadow appeared. It was confronting the sword intent within the stone tablet. Zhao Kongming was also learning from Lin Fei, using the sword intent left by the ancestor of the Nine Profound Sect within the stone tablet to hone his own sword intent.

"Swish."

Zhao Kongming opened his eyes. In his eyes, there seemed to be a hint of sharp sword intent. His edge was exposed! This was Zhao Kongming now.

Ever since he comprehended sword intent, Zhao Kongming felt rejuvenated. His swordsmanship realm advanced rapidly, making astonishing progress!

"Hahaha, disciple, you're finally back. The founder's sword intent is truly extraordinary. Even after hundreds of years, the founder's sword intent is still like a blazing sun, making it difficult for me to resist.

However, using the founder's sword intent to hone my own sword intent has been quite effective. In just a few days, I feel that my sword intent has gradually become more stable, and even my swordsmanship realm has advanced rapidly.

No wonder you always like to stay in front of this stone tablet and cultivate diligently. Is this cultivation? This is enjoying!"

Zhao Kongming seemed to have seen through Lin Fei's "secret." Previously, Zhao Kongming thought that Lin Fei had been cultivating diligently at Ancestral Master Peak. He thought Lin Fei was very hardworking.

But now, he had also comprehended sword intent. After honing his sword intent at Ancestral Master Peak, he finally understood. Lin Fei was not cultivating, It was just enjoying!

Visibly improving sword intent and swordsmanship realm at an incredible speed. What a great opportunity! So, since Lin Fei left the Nine Profound Sect, Zhao Kongming had been staying at Ancestral Master Peak every day.

"Congratulations, Master, for making great progress in your swordsmanship!"

Lin Fei also congratulated Zhao Kongming. Zhao Kongming was full of pride. Seeing Lin Fei, he couldn't help but laugh and say, "Disciple, currently within the Nine Profound Sect, only you and I, master and disciple, have comprehended Martial Dao True Intent.

The path of martial arts is too difficult and requires other martial artists to accompany us. Why not have a friendly spar between you and me? You use your saber technique, and I'll use my sword technique. Let's verify our martial arts and see if there are any shortcomings?"

"Spar?"

Lin Fei's heart warmed up as well. He had always had some regrets during the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference. He was originally going to spar with Lu Zongyi, but it was ruined by Yuan Gangzi.

Lu Zongyi was a martial arts master who had comprehended sword intent. Lin Fei also wanted to try and see what the differences were between him and other innate martial artists who had comprehended Martial Dao True Intent.

Perhaps, as his master Zhao Kongming said, under the mutual verification of a friendly spar, both of them could gain something. However, Lin Fei knew that his strength was now too strong. Especially his Saber Qi, its power was terrifying. Zhao Kongming might not be able to withstand it.

So, Lin Fei tactfully suggested, "Master, why don't we just compare our saber intent and sword intent directly? As for the actual swordsmanship and saber techniques, since sabers and swords have no eyes, it's better not to try."

Hearing this, Zhao Kongming's expression became serious, "Martial arts were originally created for fighting. We martial artists fight against the heavens and the earth, how can we be afraid of battle?

Besides, it's just a friendly spar. How can we find out our flaws without using saber techniques and sword techniques? You and I are both martial arts masters, so there won't be any danger. Just fight freely."

Zhao Kongming's expression was solemn and serious. His eyes were also full of confidence. After all, he had been in the martial arts world for decades and was known as the "Empty Abyss Sword."

In Zhao Kongming's opinion, his swordsmanship was the best in the Nine Profound Sect. Even if he wanted to find an opponent in swordsmanship, he was afraid that only those sword fanatics from the Hidden Sword Sect could match him.

"Alright, we'll stop when we touch."

Lin Fei nodded. Thinking about it, Zhao Kongming was also a martial arts master and now he had comprehended sword intent. How could he be underestimated? Lin Fei would never underestimate the martial artists of the world.

"Come, my swordsmanship focuses on killing with a single strike."

Zhao Kongming's hand was already on the hilt of his sword. Once he drew his sword, it would undoubtedly be earth-shattering! Lin Fei took a deep breath and didn't hesitate any longer.

"Boom."

Suddenly, Lin Fei unleashed all of his Saber Qi.

"Heavenly Saber Art!"

More than thirty-meter saber energy stretched across the void. Moreover, Lin Fei displayed the Heavenly Saber Art, condensed a Fierce Saber, which was filled with monstrous, sinister energy. This sinister energy directly locked onto Zhao Kongming.

Suddenly, Zhao Kongming felt as if he would be instantly turned into dust with just a slight movement! Even his hand gripping the sword hilt was trembling slightly, Zhao Kongming had seen Lin Fei display the thirty-meter-tall saber energy before.

At that time, he had only felt shocked. Moreover, it was not aimed at him. As a bystander, his feelings were not too real. But now, when Lin Fei's Saber Qi locked onto Zhao Kongming. Zhao Kongming finally felt how terrifying this thirty-meter-tall saber energy really was.

"Master, why haven't you drawn your sword yet? Do you want your disciple to make the first move?"

Lin Fei was a bit puzzled. Zhao Kongming's hand gripping the sword hilt showed no signs of movement. It seemed like he was letting Lin Fei make the first move. Thinking of this, Lin Fei didn't hesitate any longer, he prepared to slash down his Saber Qi.

"Stop!" Zhao Kongming immediately shouted, "Disciple, you're right, sabers and swords have no eyes. Besides, at our level, having comprehended Martial Dao True Intent, no need to wield sabers and swords. Why don't we just compare our sword intent and saber intent directly, and stop when we touch? What do you think, disciple?"

Zhao Kongming gradually loosened his grip on the sword hilt. It seemed that he was really not planning to draw his sword.

132. Yuan Gangzi deserved to die

"Compare saber intent and sword intent?"

Lin Fei's eyes flickered slightly. Looking at Zhao Kongming's tense expression, Lin Fei seemed to faintly understand something. So, Lin Fei directly waved his hand. The thirty-meter-tall saber energy instantly collapsed and disappeared without a trace.

"Master is right, sabers and swords have no eyes. We martial artists who have comprehended Martial Dao True Intent can compare Martial Dao True Intent. There's no need to wield sabers and swords. However, does Master really want to compare saber intent with his disciple?"

"Of course, come on, let me see how far your saber intent has progressed."

Zhao Kongming saw Lin Fei withdraw his saber energy. After the terrifying thirty-meter saber energy completely collapsed and disappeared, his heart finally relaxed a bit.

That thirty-meter-tall saber energy was really frightening just looking at it. He actually wanted to have a friendly spar with Lin Fei using saber techniques and sword techniques just now? Thinking about it now, it was scary!

Zhao Kongming knew how "fierce" his disciple was. He had killed He Mountain Dao's Qi Condensation cultivators with a single saber strike. It would be better to compare saber intent and sword intent. It's not as dangerous.

"Master, this is my saber intent, please give me your guidance!"

The next moment, Lin Fei's saber intent burst forth from within his body.

"Boom."

The terrifying saber intent soared into the sky. The sharp aura filled the air above the Ancestral Master Peak. It was as if countless sharp great sabers were suspended above Zhao Kongming's head, ready to fall at any time, putting immense pressure on Zhao Kongming.

Zhao Kongming's face stiffened slightly. At that moment Lin Fei unleashed his saber intent. He already knew his sword intent was far inferior to Lin Fei's. Even the gap was huge!

Lin Fei had no expression on his face. However, he knew his saber intent had reached Mastery. His master Zhao Kongming had only just begun to comprehend sword intent. There was still a long way to go to reach Mastery.

Martial Dao True Intent, a difference of one realm was a world of difference. There was no comparison at all. Even Lu Zongyi, who had comprehended sword intent for many years, was suppressed by Lin Fei's saber intent. Not to mention Zhao Kongming.

For a moment, Zhao Kongming fell silent.

"Forget it, there's no need to compare saber intent and sword intent. You and I are master and disciple, and the sharpness of our saber intent and sword intent can cause harm to the opponent's Martial Dao True Intent if we're not careful. It's better not to compare."

Zhao Kongming's expression was resolute. He refused to unleash his sword intent.

"Master, it's true that saber intent and sword intent are sharp and dangerous, but I also have fist intent. I don't know if Master would be willing to..."

Lin Fei hesitated for a moment before saying. Fist intent didn't seem as dangerous. It might be worth comparing.

Zhao Kongming resolutely refused: "Disciple, you've just come back, you should rest more. If you really want to spar, let's do it another day. I want to ask you about this trip to the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference. How did you come back so soon?"

Zhao Kongming immediately changed the subject. It seemed that he had just realized Lin Fei's return seemed a bit too fast. He had also led a team to participate in the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference in the past. From the time they left to the time they returned, it should have taken at least ten days to half a month.

After all, after the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference was over. Many martial artists would often stay behind to continue exchanging and networking for a while.

But Lin Fei? It hadn't even been ten days since he left the Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei also withdrew his saber intent. He then explained, "Master, the trip to the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference went smoothly. However, after it began, suddenly a Qi Condensation cultivator from Guardian Primordial Mountain, Yuan Gangzi, wanted to seal off the Martial Alliance and prevent anyone from leaving.

Yuan Gangzi's reason was to capture a demonic cultivator who had stolen Guardian Primordial Mountain's techniques. That demonic cultivator was hiding in the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference. Moreover, those Qi Condensation cultivators from Guardian Primordial Mountain even attacked other martial artists. Those who dared to resist were killed without mercy!

Left with no choice, I had to draw my saber and kill Yuan Gangzi. So, the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference ended early. I brought those inner disciples back to the Nine Profound Sect."

Lin Fei briefly explained his experience during the Martial Alliance Exchange Conference.

"Wait, you killed Yuan Gangzi? The top Qi Condensation cultivator of Guardian Primordial Mountain, who had reached the eleventh level of Qi Condensation?"

Zhao Kongming suddenly asked with a serious expression.

"Yes, it was him. However, he didn't seem to be much different from the two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao. I ended them all with a single saber strike."

Lin Fei calmly said. He didn't think it was a big deal. Whether it was the eleventh level of Qi Condensation or the ninth level, for Lin Fei, it was all the same. He killed them all with just one saber strike, never needing a second one.

Zhao Kongming fell silent again. He didn't know how many times he had fallen silent. At this moment, he felt somewhat speechless.

What did it mean that there was no significant difference between the top Qi Condensation cultivators and high-level Qi Condensation cultivators? What did it mean to end them all with a single saber strike?

Top Qi Condensation cultivators were usually only dealt with by grandmaster-level martial artists. Those below the grandmaster level would face great danger when encountering a top Qi Condensation cultivator. Throughout the entire Great Chang, when a top Qi Condensation cultivator appeared, the martial artists had almost no way to deal with them.

Especially Yuan Gangzi, who wasn't an ordinary top Qi Condensation cultivator. He had reached the eleventh level of Qi Condensation. He was only one step away from Qi Condensation perfection!

Such a top Qi Condensation cultivator could be considered one of the strongest in the entire Great Chang. And yet, he was slain by Lin Fei with a single saber strike. Judging from Lin Fei's demeanor, it seemed that he didn't exert much effort.

Now, Zhao Kongming thought about it, he had previously wanted to spar with Lin Fei. It was really too dangerous. Maybe Lin Fei would accidentally unleash his Saber Qi and with a single saber strike, Zhao Kongming would be slain. That would be a great joke.

After a long time, Zhao Kongming slowly sighed and said, "Disciple, you've caused trouble again. It seems that every time you go down the mountain, you stir up trouble. Last time, it was He Mountain Dao. This time, it's Guardian Primordial Mountain. From high-level Qi Condensation cultivators to top Qi Condensation cultivators. Your master is starting to suspect that the next time you go down the mountain, you'll provoke a Foundation Establishment cultivator..."

Zhao Kongming looked at Lin Fei with a complicated expression. His disciple was good in every aspect. Except that he caused too much trouble. And not just small trouble, but big trouble every time.

He Mountain Dao was already bad enough. They were now forced to seal off their mountain. Although Lin Fei didn't cause He Mountain Dao to seal off the mountain, their decision to do so had a direct connection with Lin Fei.

Now it was Guardian Primordial Mountain. A prominent eleventh-level Qi Condensation core elder, a top Qi Condensation cultivator, was slain by Lin Fei with a single saber strike.

"By the way, did you find the demonic cultivator Yuan Gangzi mentioned?" Zhao Kongming suddenly asked.

"Demonic cultivator?"

Lin Fei thought carefully. He had completely forgotten. None of the innate masters from the Thirteen Sects of the Martial Alliance had thought of it. It was likely that even if there was a demonic cultivator, they had already blended into the crowd and escaped.

Lin Fei took a deep breath, his eyes as sharp as a saber, and said in a low voice, "Master, is the presence of a demonic cultivator important? Yuan Gangzi represented Guardian Primordial Mountain and the Qi Condensation cultivators. The Martial Alliance represents the martial arts sects and the martial artists of the world.

Yuan Gangzi trampled on the dignity of martial artists! If the founder of our Nine Profound Sect were still alive, would Yuan Gangzi dare to do this? Even if the Great Chang founder were still here, during the peak of Great Chang's martial arts, would Yuan Gangzi dare to do this?

Yuan Gangzi was searching for a demonic cultivator, yet he trampled on the dignity of all the martial artists in Great Chang! If I don't kill Yuan Gangzi, I will never be at peace!"

Zhao Kongming looked at Lin Fei's resolute expression. His heart was slightly shaken. He had thought that Lin Fei was just prone to causing trouble, causing a big incident every time.

However, it seemed now Lin Fei's decision to kill Yuan Gangzi was well thought out. Yuan Gangzi trampled on the dignity of martial artists all over the world.

As a martial artist, if he didn't kill Yuan Gangzi, his heart would never be at ease! When his faith in martial arts was gone, from then on, his martial arts would never progress!

Yuan Gangzi deserved to die!

133. Stone Tablet Shattered

"Disciple, you are right, Yuan Gangzi deserved his death. Since Yuan Gangzi is dead, let it be. Guardian Primordial Mountain is indeed stronger than He Mountain Dao. However, with the imperial family suppressing the world, at least in recent years, they dare not do anything," Zhao Kongming said coldly.

Lin Fei raised his head, looked at Zhao Kongming, and calmly asked, "Master, there is something I don't understand, and I would like to ask for your guidance."

"Speak."

"Those immortal sects seem to be getting more and more unscrupulous. But they haven't caused any large-scale incidents. It's as if they are waiting for something. What exactly are they waiting for?"

Lin Fei had always been puzzled. Logically speaking, the Great Chang dynasty suppressed the world. Now that the world was unstable, the imperial family was weak and unable to control the local areas. It should be the time for these immortal sects to "be active". But although they were somewhat unscrupulous, they were also somewhat restrained. This seems contradictory.

Zhao Kongming's eyes were deep, and he sneered, "They are waiting for the imperial family's Supreme Elder to pass away! The world's instability is indeed due to the imperial family's poor governance and the corruption and degeneration of the court. However, the key point is that the imperial family's Supreme Elder is not far from his life limit.

Although the Supreme Elder is not as powerful as the Great Chang founder who could suppress the world, be invincible, and dominate everywhere, he is still an extraordinary cultivator, a top-tier Foundation Establishment expert.

It is precisely because of this imperial Supreme Elder that the Great Chang dynasty was able to revive. Otherwise, the Great Chang dynasty would have disintegrated long ago. Those immortal sects are now so active, yet they remain polite. They are actually fearing that imperial Supreme Elder.

Once the imperial's Supreme Elder passes away, it will probably be the time for chaos in the world and the disintegration of the Great Chang dynasty..."

Zhao Kongming, as an elderly martial artist, could see the situation very clearly. The current Great Chang seemed calm, but in fact, it had long been filled with undercurrents.

Once the imperial Supreme Elder passed away, the world would undoubtedly fall into chaos. Now those immortal sects were actually withholding. This time they probably won't mobilize a large force.

Even if Lin Fei just killed Yuan Gangzi, Guardian Primordial Mountain wouldn't be furious and they won't come to Nine Profound Sect to capture people. Because they are focused on the "big picture" and waiting for the imperial Supreme Elder to pass away.

Once the imperial Supreme Elder passes away, whether it's He Mountain Dao or Guardian Primordial Mountain, it probably won't be so easy to deal with. At that time, the immortal sects would surely rise. Perhaps, Nine Profound Sect would be in trouble!

Lin Fei's expression became serious. He understood everything. That is to say, even if He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain really gave birth to Foundation Establishment experts, they most likely won't do anything to the Nine Profound Sect.

The imperial Supreme Elder was like the anchor for the entire Great Chang. As long as the Supreme Elder didn't encounter any accidents, no matter how turbulent the world was, it would always remain an undercurrent.

But once the Supreme Elder dies, those immortal sects will raise their banners and return to the world, completely controlling the secular power of the world.

Such things have happened before. Before the establishment of the Great Chang, it was like this. Immortal sects controlled the entire world. Various forces fought, and the people suffered. Finally, the Great Chang founder emerged, with the supreme power of a Martial Saint, sweeping across the world, establishing the Great Chang dynasty, only then could the world enjoy 900 years of peace.

"However, disciple, you don't need to worry. If you can reach innate perfection and become a grandmaster, even if you can't compare to the founder, you won't be far behind. By then, even if the world is in chaos, you can still protect the Nine Profound Sect."

Zhao Kongming looked deeply at Lin Fei. The reason why the Nine Profound Sect values Lin Fei so much, even giving him everything he wanted and fully supporting him, even if it meant offending some immortal sects, was because they saw the hope of Lin Fei becoming a grandmaster.

At that time, if they want to protect the sect in the chaos of the world. There must be a grandmaster to sit in the town. And Lin Fei is almost the only hope of the Nine Profound Sect.

"Master, rest assured, I will definitely practice hard, strive to become a grandmaster as soon as possible, and live up to the expectations of the sect!" Lin Fei said solemnly.

"Good, I naturally believe in you. You continue to practice here at the Ancestral Master Peak. My sword intent is almost stable."

Zhao Kongming voluntarily gave up his position and left the Ancestral Master Peak.

Lin Fei didn't stand on ceremony. He immediately sat cross-legged under the stone tablet. Now that he knew that the entire world might fall into chaos in the next few years. He had to seize every opportunity to enhance his strength.

"A grandmaster of martial arts can protect the sect? However, my goal is not just to become a master or a grandmaster. What I want is longevity. To enter the Dao through martial arts and step onto the path of longevity..." Lin Fei murmured softly. Then, he closed his eyes.

Time flew by, and two months passed. Every day, Lin Fei practiced on the Ancestral Master Peak, using the saber intent left by the Nine Profound Sect's founder to sharpen his own saber intent.

On this day, Lin Fei was still doing the same thing as usual. He stimulated his own saber intent, hoping to trigger the saber intent on the stone tablet so that he could continue to sharpen his saber intent. However, an unexpected change occurred.

"Crack."

A soft sound. The stone tablet cracked!

Lin Fei opened his eyes. His gaze instantly fell on the stone tablet in front of him.

A crack had appeared on the tablet. Although the crack was small and subtle. If he didn't look closely, Lin Fei wouldn't even notice it. But, a crack is still a crack. This meant that there was a problem with the stone tablet.

But this stone tablet had been exposed to wind and rain on the Ancestral Master Peak for 900 years. There were no cracks before and it had only been slightly weathered but not seriously. How did it suddenly crack?

Lin Fei looked at the stone tablet in front of him. He sensed Martial Dao True Intent within the tablet. Suddenly, Lin Fei understood.

"It's Martial Dao True Intent! The Martial Dao True Intent left by the founder is in the perfection realm. Three strands of Martial Dao True Intent, for a full 900 years, had already merged with the stone tablet. But as I constantly stimulated the Martial Dao True Intent within the stone tablet to sharpen my own Martial Dao True Intent.

Over time, the Martial Dao True Intent within the tablet would naturally be consumed. And now, with excessive consumption, the Martial Dao True Intent is about to disappear. Once the Martial Dao True Intent disappears, this stone tablet will quickly become an ordinary tablet, rapidly weathering and cracking, eventually collapsing."

Lin Fei fell silent. He knew he couldn't continue. After all, this stone tablet was left behind by the founder and it still contained Martial Dao True Intent. He couldn't destroy it completely.

"System."

Lin Fei summoned the system to check his martial arts progress.

Host: Lin Fei

Martial Arts Realm: Innate Martial Artist

Master: Mid-stage

True Intention Scroll: Mid-stage (92% Progress)

Saber Intent: Mastery (96% Progress)

Fist Intent: Mastery (51% Progress)

Heavenly Saber Art: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Immeasurable Fist: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Close Yet Distant: Transcendence (0% Progress)

Lin Fei's True Intention Scroll had reached 92% progress. This was actually quite good. After reaching the mid-stage of Master, the cultivation speed of the True Intention Scroll had drastically reduced. Reaching 92% was thanks to the improvement of saber intent.

The progress of saber intent had reached 96%. The growth was not huge. But it was already close to breaking through. Once it broke through, it would be saber intent transcendence and Lin Fei's strength could increase by several times or even more than ten times. Heavenly Saber Art had also reached transcendence, and the Tyrant Saber could be condensed.

The Tyrant Saber was much more powerful than the Fierce Saber. Once the Tyrant Saber was released, its terrifying aura would not only affect saber wielders, even martial artists and Qi cultivators would be suppressed by the Tyrant Saber.

Immeasurable Fist and Close Yet Distant had both reached transcendence. However, after these three martial arts reached transcendence, there was no more progress. It seemed that reaching perfection still required some opportunities.

Lin Fei knew that the higher the martial arts and the more profound they were, the more difficult it was to cultivate them to perfection. This had nothing to do with the martial artist's efforts. To achieve perfection, one must rely on some opportunities.

"The Martial Dao True Intent on the Ancestral Master Peak can no longer be used. I must find a place to sharpen my saber intent and strive to make it reach transcendence. Where in the world can I find a place to sharpen my saber intent?"

A name flashed through Lin Fei's mind.

134. Down The Mountain Again

"Hidden Sword Sect!" Lin Fei murmured softly.

When it came to sharpening saber intent, the name "Hidden Sword Sect" appeared in his mind. After all, Hidden Sword Sect had Lu Zongyi. Moreover, it had once given birth to a Martial Saint. An innate martial artist with perfect sword intent was born there!

For Lin Fei to sharpen his saber intent, Hidden Sword Sect was undoubtedly the best choice. What's more, Lin Fei had also established a good relationship with Hidden Sword Sect. He had saved Lu Zongyi's life and Lu Zongyi had sincerely invited Lin Fei to visit Hidden Sword Sect.

"It seems that I need to pay a visit to Hidden Sword Sect."

Lin Fei stood up and prepared to leave the mountain. Under normal circumstances, he would quietly leave the mountain alone.

However, his identity was different now. Nine Profound Sect Grand Elder! Every move he made represented the Nine Profound Sect. Therefore, Lin Fei had to inform the Nine Profound Sect's sect master.

Moreover, he could also learn about the situation of He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain from the sect master. After all, if there were forces that wanted Lin Fei dead and had enough power to kill him, it would be these two.

Lin Fei had to pay more attention to the situation of these two forces when he left the mountain. So, Lin Fei went directly to the main hall of the Nine Profound Sect.

The sect master was also in the main hall. It seemed that he was listening to a disciple's report.

"Greetings to the Grand Elder."

Upon seeing Lin Fei, the disciple immediately saluted. Lin Fei's prestige in the entire Nine Profound Sect was higher than anyone else's. He had even become the symbol of the current Nine Profound Sect.

Lin Fei nodded. The disciple hurriedly left the main hall.

"Sect Master. I plan to leave the mountain soon and visit Hidden Sword Sect. So I came to inform Sect Master."

Upon hearing Lin Fei's words, the sect master's face changed drastically.

"Elder Lin, you... you're leaving the mountain again?"

The sect master was somewhat scared. Although he was always calm and steady, he couldn't help but feel an ominous premonition when he heard that Lin Fei was leaving the mountain again.

The previous times Lin Fei left the mountain, he always caused trouble. Moreover, the troubles he caused grew larger and larger.

When he was still in the Acquired Realm, he killed an ordinary Qi Condensation disciple of He Mountain Dao during a trip down the mountain. Then, he went to Chang City and killed a sixth-level Qi Condensation disciple of He Mountain Dao.

Even on the way back to the mountain, he successively killed two high-level Qi Condensation cultivators of He Mountain Dao. But that was not the end.

The last time he left the mountain, Lin Fei led a team to participate in the Martial Alliance Exchange. This should have been relatively safe.

Many Grand Elders had led teams to participate in the Martial Alliance Exchange in the past. Almost no problems occurred.

And Lin Fei?

He led a team to the Martial Alliance Exchange and ended up killing Guardian Primordial Mountain's Yuan Gangzi with a single saber strike. That was a peak Qi Condensation cultivator at the eleventh level and he was a core elder of Guardian Primordial Mountain!

When the sect master first heard this news, it was like a bolt from the blue.

He was somewhat dazed.

"How come? Can't I leave the mountain?" Lin Fei frowned.

The sect master smiled bitterly, "Elder Lin, you are the Grand Elder of our Nine Profound Sect, how could you not be allowed to leave the mountain? It's just that, for this trip to visit Hidden Sword Sect, I have a small request."

"Sect Master, just say it."

"I just hope that Elder Lin, during this trip down the mountain, won't provoke any powerful enemies. Elder Lin has already provoked a peak Qi Condensation cultivator at the eleventh level last time.

According to Elder Lin's pattern of leaving the mountain. This time, you may provoke Qi Condensation perfection or even Foundation Establishment cultivators. Our Nine Profound Sect can't withstand the wrath of Foundation Establishment cultivators now..."

Lin Fei raised an eyebrow, "So Sect Master is worried about this. Sect Master, rest assured, I can't defeat Foundation Establishment cultivators now, so I definitely won't provoke them. So, Foundation Establishment cultivators won't come to the Nine Profound Sect.

Moreover, I am going to visit Hidden Sword Sect to see if I can sharpen my saber intent there so that my saber intent can reach transcendence. For the matter of saber intent transcendence, I must leave the mountain!"

The sect master breathed a slight sigh of relief. As long as he didn't provoke Foundation Establishment cultivators, that would be fine.

But Lin Fei didn't say he wouldn't provoke Qi Condensation perfection? The sect master thought for a moment and finally didn't say anything. It was already good not to provoke Foundation Establishment cultivators.

As for Qi Condensation perfection? Almost all Qi Condensation perfection cultivators were desperately trying to refine Foundation Establishment pills. Therefore, there were very few Qi Condensation perfection cultivators roaming outside. There was no need to worry too much.

"By the way, have there been any recent movements from He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain?" Lin Fei asked again.

Hearing Lin Fei mention this, the sect master's eyes flashed with a trace of solemnity.

"Elder Lin, regarding He Mountain Dao and Guardian Primordial Mountain, we have been keeping an eye on them. Currently, He Mountain Dao is still sealed off.

As for Guardian Primordial Mountain, it's a bit strange. It's as if they're acting like Yuan Gangzi never died. They have no reaction to his death, which is really strange."

"No reaction?" A glint flashed in Lin Fei's eyes, "No reaction is the biggest reaction. That means Guardian Primordial Mountain is harboring resentment. Once the Imperial Supreme Elder dies and the person they fear disappears, they will definitely make a move against our Nine Profound Sect! Guardian Primordial Mountain is even more dangerous than He Mountain Dao!"

The Sect Master's face gradually darkened. He clearly considered the possibility as well.

"Rest assured, Sect Master. Once I become a Grand Master, or my saber intent reaches perfection. If Guardian Primordial Mountain dares to come, I will ensure they never return."

After speaking, Lin Fei turned and left the hall.

This time, Lin Fei didn't ride a horse. His movement technique, Close Yet Distant, had reached transcendence. Moreover, Lin Fei's Saber Qi was incredibly profound, using Close Yet Distant to travel was much faster than riding a horse.

A day later, Lin Fei had already arrived at the foot of the mountain where the Hidden Sword Sect was located.

The Hidden Sword Sect was situated on a continuous range of mountain peaks. At the foot of the mountain, there was a town named Sword City.

The people here, influenced by the Hidden Sword Sect, had some mastery in swordsmanship, almost everyone carried a long sword with them. Moreover, they were extremely hostile towards those carrying other weapons.

Lin Fei even saw a saber-wielding guest constantly provoked by the people of the city. The saber-wielding guest dared not fight. Once a real battle took place, and if he won, the trouble would be even greater. An endless stream of swordsmen would come to challenge, utterly annoying.

Lin Fei didn't bring a saber. Ever since he possessed Saber Qi, he had stopped carrying a saber. Otherwise, coming to Sword City rashly would indeed be troublesome.

Hidden Sword Sect was located on a mountain peak a few miles outside of Sword City. The peaks here soared into the clouds. Moreover, there was only one path for entering and exiting. That was a flight of steps. A total of one thousand and eight steps.

Hidden Sword Sect's gates were wide open. They didn't refuse anyone seeking to become a disciple. But the prerequisite was to walk to the top of the mountain on their own.

These steps were extremely narrow. One slight misstep, a slip of the foot, and falling would result in being shattered to pieces. Even some Hidden Sword Sect disciples had died, falling off the stone steps when entering or exiting the sect. But the Hidden Sword Sect showed no intention of improving the road conditions.

The Hidden Sword Sect's creed was only those who could climb the one thousand and eight steps were considered to have passed the test of will and courage and qualified to become a swordsman. Otherwise, they would be sent back to where they came from.

As for the danger? A swordsman's life was filled with life-and-death experiences. How could one become a swordsman without being tempered in life and death?

Lin Fei had learned a bit about the Hidden Sword Sect. At the moment, he had only one thought in his mind.

Ruthless! The Hidden Sword Sect was truly ruthless! Whether they were ruthless to others, Lin Fei didn't know. But the Hidden Sword Sect was indeed ruthless towards its own people!

However, perhaps it was such extreme and harsh conditions allowed the Hidden Sword Sect to endure for thousands of years.

Among all the martial arts sects in Great Chang, it was the only one with a heritage surpassing a thousand years, that could stand alongside those immortal and Daoist sects!

Lin Fei arrived at the foot of the mountain and saw many people gathered together. He made his way through the crowd. It turned out there were three unrecognizable corpses on the ground. All were young individuals. It seemed they had fallen from the tall stone steps.

"Another three dead."

"Five died this morning."

"More and more people are coming to join Hidden Sword Sect lately, and more are unafraid of death."

"Heh, these are all refugees. With the recent chaos, some think that joining the Hidden Sword Sect will at least provide food and clothing. And the result? People who can't even feed themselves think they can easily enter the Hidden Sword Sect?"

"Reaching the peak is nearly impossible for an ordinary person. Even martial artists with years of Body Refining and excellent physical strength often fall to their deaths."

Lin Fei gazed at the corpses on the ground. It seemed that the one thousand and eight stone steps of Hidden Sword Sect were not easily surmountable.

Lin Fei turned and stood at the base of the mountain. He prepared to step onto the first stone stair. However, he noticed a young man and a little girl standing before the steps.

The boy appeared to be sixteen or seventeen, while the girl was only seven or eight. Both were dressed in rags and reeked. They likely hadn't bathed in days and were probably refugees as well.

The number of refugees in Great Chang was increasing. This foreshadowed potential unrest.

"Brother, don't climb the stone steps. So many people just fell to their deaths. If you climb, you will certainly die too."

Tears streamed down the girl's face. The youth was thin and sallow, but resilient. He clenched his teeth, gazing at the towering peak, and whispered, "Sister, if I don't reach the top and become a disciple of the Hidden Sword Sect, we'll both starve to death. Father and mother are gone.

I swore I would raise you. Only by joining the Hidden Sword Sect and becoming a disciple can I support you. Perhaps I could even become a powerful swordsman, slaying our enemies and avenging our parents!"

The youth took a deep breath and he then prepared to step onto the first stone stair.

"This Hidden Sword Sect is interesting. They have people climb the stone steps to forge their willpower. Would carrying you to the top count as passing the Hidden Sword Sect's test?"

Suddenly, a calm voice sounded behind the youth.